<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="plate"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="plates"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="silver"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             silver plate
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             An octagonal silver plate decorated with archaic, ornamental symbols. Columns of strange symbols are carved on it. A sense of horror tingles your skin upon watching the plate. You realize something is really wrong.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             An archaic silver plate with strange symbols carved on it. A sense of horror tingles your skin upon watching the plate. Something clearly tells you a closer look might be dangerous.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             $[Call(${Ironclaw:Props:Plot:ChapelDesecration:Plate}, "curse")]
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="blood" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="blood"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="blood"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the blood on the silver plate
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A few drops of dried blood apparently smeared on one of the symbols.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A few drops of dried blood.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="oil" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="oil"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="oils"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             spot of oil on the silver plate
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A spot of oil on the ornamental symbols. <propcheck skill="alteration:gardening"> This is most likely oil of the mandragora plant.</propcheck>
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A spot of oil on the ornamental symbols.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="symbols" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="symbol"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="symbols"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="archaic"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ornamental"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="strange"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the symbols on the silver plate
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A strange symbol, most likely a letter from a long forgotten alphabet. You wonder if this does have some meaning to it or not. You notice a set of brown spots on it.<br/>
$[Call(${Ironclaw:Props:Plot:ChapelDesecration:Plate}, "curse")]
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A strange symbol, possibly a letter from a long forgotten alphabet.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             $[Call(${Ironclaw:Props:Plot:ChapelDesecration:Plate}, "curse")]
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:curse">
         X[M] /* return what they see when reading the symbols */
string output;

\$religion = Int(\$actor."skill:career:priest") + Int(\$actor."skill:academics:religion") + Int(\$actor."career:academics:religion");
\$history = Int(\$actor."skill:academics:history") + Int(\$actor."career:academics:history");
\$magic = Int(\$actor."skill:academics:magic") + Int(\$actor."career:academics:magic");
\$curselevel = 25 - \$magic - Int(\$actor."trait:mind");

if(\$religion \>= 7) \{
  output = "Archaic scrolls describe plates of pure silver used to alter the behavior of the spirits, both of the white and black nature. Legend says the earliest plate of this nature was given by S'allumer to his most loyal priest. Soon enough, masters of black magic learnt how to tain the plates and use them for evil deeds. The most adept at this were members of a long-ago vanished swamp tribe, who specialized in blood rituals. It has been 300 years since the last item from that tribe was seen. A white or black mage may know how to use the symbols on this plate to help with casting spells.";
\} else if(\$religion \>= 5) \{
  output = "Archaic scrolls describe plates of pure silver used to alter the behavior of the spirits, both of the white and black nature. Legend says the earliest plate of this nature was given by S'allumer to his most loyal priest, and later corrupted by the black mages. A white or black mage may know how to make use of the plate.";
\} else if(\$religion \>= 3) \{
  output = "You recall some legend from a book you once read about S'allumer giving an octagonal silver plate to his most loyal priest as a gift. The reason and the details of the legend escape you.";
\} else if(\$religion \>= 1) \{
  output = "You cannot really make out any difference between the ornamentals and the symbols. You notice some repetitions in the lines. When you try to differentiate them you touch a symbol that feels surprisingly warm.";
\} else \{
  output = "The plate is clearly not meant for mundane eyes. Even those aware of archaic and ancient will need time to understand the meaning of the symbols. The symbols feel surprisingly warm to your touch.";
\}


if(\$history \>= 7) \{
  output += "\\nIn Vahraden's sixth book there is a passage dedicated to a long gone swamp tribe and their ritual plates. According to the knowledgeable scholar this tribe was specialized in necromancy pointedly the blood rituals thereof. But 300 years passed since the last items were found of them. They somehow manipulated the symbols in order to bend the spirits to their own will, she simply described it as a remote control panel for spirits.";
\} else if(\$history \>= 5) \{
  output += "\\nThe famous scholar Vahreden called these silver plates remote control panels for spirits. She said swamp tribes of old used these to manipulate black spirits.";
\} else if(\$history \>= 3) \{
  output += "\\nThe diary of a scholar refers to these plates as remote control panels for spirits. They were used in the rituals of a long gone swamp tribe.";
\} else if(\$history \>= 1) \{
  output += "\\nYou recall some notes about these plates that connect them to a tribe that no longer exists, but once conducted special rituals.";
\}


if(\$curselevel \>=9) \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you wonder if any of the symbols might be dangerous to read.";
  Call(this, "givecurse");
\} else if(\$curselevel \>=7) \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you know you should skip past any magical symbols which could be dangerous, but how could you know which are dangerous until you've looked at them?";
  Call(this, "givecurse");
\} else if(\$curselevel \>=5) \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you attempt skip past any magical symbols which could be dangerous, although you're really not sure which bits are dangerous.";
  Call(this, "givecurse");
\} else if(\$curselevel \>=3) \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you attempt skip past any magical symbols which could be dangerous. You probably read over a few in passing, though.";
  Call(this, "givecurse");
\} else if(\$curselevel \>=1) \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you are careful to allow your eyes to skip past any magical symbols which could be dangerous. You may have briefly glanced at one or two, but only in passing.";
  Call(this, "givecurse");
\} else \{
  output += "\\n\\nWhile reading "+Describe(\$target, nil, nil, STYLE_NONPOSS)+" you are careful to allow your eyes to skip past any magical symbols which could be dangerous.";
\}

return output;

/*

Other: with italics you have the punishment for meddling into dark magic without knowing what you do. Tisk, tisk. Don%u2019t read plates which make you fear just like that. (max a day or two, then they feel relieved and it is gone)

Unskilled: The plate is clearly not meant for mundane eyes. Even those aware of archaic and ancient will need time to understand the meaning of the symbols. The symbols feel surprisingly warm to your touch. (growing of extra horn / wart /lizard tail: some emote with them so people who were not present and don%u2019t do a look see it too.)

Priest 1/magic 3: You can not really make any difference between the ornamentals and the symbols. You notice some repetitions in the lines. When you try to differentiate them you touch a symbol feeling surprisingly warm. (periodical leap into the air, lewd whistling)

Priest 3/ magic 5: You recall some legend in a book you put your hands one about S%u2019Allumner giving an octagonal silver plate to his most loyal priest as a gift. The reason and the details of the legend escape you. (involuntary singing of: We are the champions at random occasions / sudden unstoppable laughs attacks until the cheeks start to hurt. Then abrupt stop there of. )

Priest 5/magic 7: Archaic scrolls describe plates of pure silver used to alter the behavior of the spirits, both of the white and black nature. Legend says earliest plate was given by S%u2019Allumner and later corrupted by the black mages. A white or black mage might know how to make use of the plate. (You only notice you touched a part of the ornamentals which unleash a curse upon you when it is too late. You sense a strange emptiness in your stomach, a hunger you never experienced before, and the knowledge you simply must eat cherries/apples/strawberry cakes. %u2013 A day later the hunger ceases and they no longer will carve cherries.)

Priest 7/magic 9: Archaic scrolls describe plates of pure silver used to alter the behavior of the spirits, both of the white and black nature. Legend says the earliest plate was given to his most loyal priest by S%u2019Allumner himself. Soon enough masters of black magic learned how to taint the plates and use it for their own deeds. The most adept in this were members of a long gone swap tribe, who specialized in blood rituals, but 300 years are past since the last item were seen from them. A white or a black mage might know how to use the symbols in order to help them with casting spells. (You skillfully avoid a part of the ornamentals you know would release a curse upon you.)


Scholar 1/history 3: You recall some notes about these plates that connect them to a tribe no longer existing for their special rituals. A disgusting stench emerges from the plates as you touch the symbols. (and add a stench to them. Make them stink. Mwahaaahaaaa %u2013 Scent myself, you smell of the sick transpirations of swamp).

Scholar 3/history 5: The diary of a scholar refers to these plates as remote control panels for spirits. They were used in the rituals of a long gone swamp tribe. You suddenly sneeze. (Your nose tickles terribly.)

Scholar 5/history 7: The famous scholar Vahreden called these silver plates remote control panels for spirits. She said swamp tribes of old used these to manipulate black spirits. You accidentally touch a symbol Vahreden warned you about. (Suddenly pack of flies attack you. %u2013 imaginary flies regularly appearing to buzz in the ear of the cursed victim)

Scholar 7/history 9: In Vahraden%u2019s sixth book there is a passage dedicated to a long gone swamp tribe and their ritual plates. According to the knowledgeable scholar this tribe was specialized in necromancy pointedly the blood rituals thereof. But 300 years passed since the last items were found of them. They somehow manipulated the symbols in order to bend the spirits to their own will, she simply described it as a remote control panel for spirits. (You skillfully avoid a part of the ornamentals they obviously used to concealed the symbol of curse.)


Observation 5: You notice some spots of dried blood on the 13th symbol of the 1st column.

Observation 8: At the bottom of the silver plate you see a slight spot of oil.

Details of the silver plate: Symbol, blood, oil, spirits?

*/
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:givecurse">
         X[M] /* give a curse to the player */

if(\$actor.cursed) return TRUE;
\$actor.cursed = TRUE;

\$delay(5, TRUE, "8d58");

if(\$curselevel \>= 7) \{
  /* hiccups and vomit and convusions */
  \$actor.cursed = time() + 60*60*\$curselevel*3;
  while(\$actor.cursed \&\& time() \< \$actor.cursed) \{
    \$tmp = random(70);
    \$tmp = 60;
    if(\$tmp \< 1) \{
      Social(\$actor, "spin", "unnaturally", nil, nil, NewNRef(\$actor, "head"));
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 5) \{
      Social(\$actor, "vomit", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "messily"), nil, "on", \$actor);
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 20) \{
      Social(\$actor, "convulse", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "suddenly"));
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 35) \{
      Social(\$actor, "hiccup", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally"));
    \} else \{
      EmitTo(\$actor, TAG(oneof(
"You wonder why the people who anger you are still alive.",
"You find yourself pondering the benefits of pain.",
"You wonder why the church of S'allumer is so popular, considering what hypocrites they are.",
"You find yourself craving the taste of flesh.",
"You realize that nothing in the rules of S'allumer say you have to be nice.",
"You begin to think that undead may make better companions than the living.",
"You think that you should probably be wearing only black.",
"You decide to decorate your room in black.",
"You know, the next person who insults you should probably get a fist in their face.",
"You know, people talk too much!\\nThe next person who talks to you should probably get a fist in their face.",
"Why have you been wasting your life, when the dark arts are such a quick path to power, wealth, and glory?",
"It seems so pointless, when there's always more people with weapons than there are healers. Why not just let injured people suffer?"
), "IMP"));
    \}
    \$delay(random(60*10), TRUE, "2046");
  \}
\} else if(\$curselevel \>= 5) \{
  /* hiccups and vomit and convusions */
  \$actor.cursed = time() + 60*60*24;
  while(\$actor.cursed \&\& time() \< \$actor.cursed) \{
    \$tmp = random(35);
    if(\$tmp \< 1) \{
      Social(\$actor, "spin", "unnaturally", nil, nil, NewNRef(\$actor, "head"));
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 5) \{
      Social(\$actor, "vomit", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "messily"), nil, "on", \$actor);
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 20) \{
      Social(\$actor, "convulse", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "suddenly"));
    \} else \{
      Social(\$actor, "hiccup", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally"));
    \}
    \$delay(random(60*10), TRUE, "25ad");
  \}
\} else if(\$curselevel \>= 3) \{
  /* hiccups and vomit */
  \$actor.cursed = time() + 60*60*20;
  while(\$actor.cursed \&\& time() \< \$actor.cursed) \{
    \$tmp = random(20);
    if(\$tmp \< 1) \{
      Social(\$actor, "spin", "unnaturally", nil, nil, NewNRef(\$actor, "head"));
    \} else if(\$tmp \< 5) \{
      Social(\$actor, "vomit", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "messily"), nil, "on", \$actor);
    \} else \{
      Social(\$actor, "hiccup", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally"));
    \}
    \$delay(random(60*10), TRUE, "0113");
  \}
\} else if(\$curselevel \> 1) \{
  /* hiccups and vomit */
  \$actor.cursed = time() + 60*60*15;
  while(\$actor.cursed \&\& time() \< \$actor.cursed) \{
    if(!random(5)) \{
      Social(\$actor, "vomit", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally", "messily"), nil, "on", \$actor);
    \} else \{
      Social(\$actor, "hiccup", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally"));
    \}
    \$delay(random(60*10), TRUE, "d8a9");
  \}
\} else \{
  /* hiccups */
  \$actor.cursed = time() + 60*60*5;
  while(\$actor.cursed \&\& time() \< \$actor.cursed) \{
    Social(\$actor, "hiccup", oneof("violently", "convulsively", "spontaneously", "uncontrollably", "unnaturally"));
    \$delay(random(60*10), TRUE, "41b2");
  \}
\}

\$actor.cursed = nil;

return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:react-post:wash-dob">
         X[M] /* allow the plate to be cleansed via washing with holy water */
/* are they using holy water? */
if(!\$iob \|\| !contains(dump_value(\$iob), "IronClaw:Props:Special:Sallumer:FlaskofHolyWater"))
  return TRUE;

/* cleanse the plate */
this.cleansed = TRUE;
this."base:immobile" = nil;

return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052085, "-", "SYNC", 1194771917, "tonyd", "E", 1194771938, "tonyd", "E", 1194771975, "tonyd", "E", 1194772002, "tonyd", "E", 1194772026, "tonyd", "E", 1194772214, "tonyd", "E", 1194772302, "tonyd", "E", 1194772377, "tonyd", "E", 1194772449, "tonyd", "E", 1194772464, "tonyd", "E", 1194772489, "tonyd", "E", 1194772534, "tonyd", "E", 1194772583, "tonyd", "E", 1194772937, "tonyd", "P", 1194773007, "tonyd", "E", 1194773057, "tonyd", "P", 1194773885, "tonyd", "P", 1194773893, "tonyd", "P", 1194773934, "tonyd", "P", 1194774352, "tonyd", "P", 1194774995, "tonyd", "E", 1194776048, "tonyd", "E", 1194776070, "tonyd", "E", 1194777218, "tonyd", "E", 1195964763, "tonyd", "P", 1195964851, "tonyd", "P", 1195964890, "tonyd", "P", 1195964978, "tonyd", "P", 1195968746, "tonyd", "E", 1195968760, "tonyd", "E", 1195968791, "tonyd", "P", 1195968825, "tonyd", "P", 1195969118, "tonyd", "P", 1195969324, "tonyd", "P", 1195969806, "tonyd", "P", 1195969908, "tonyd", "P", 1195969925, "tonyd", "P", 1195970047, "tonyd", "P", 1195970096, "tonyd", "P", 1195970116, "tonyd", "P", 1195970198, "tonyd", "P", 1195970227, "tonyd", "P", 1195970454, "tonyd", "P", 1195970504, "tonyd", "P", 1195970529, "tonyd", "P", 1195970595, "tonyd", "P", 1195970615, "tonyd", "P", 1195970674, "tonyd", "P", 1195970864, "tonyd", "P", 1195970931, "tonyd", "P", 1195971020, "tonyd", "P", 1195971407, "tonyd", "P", 1195971652, "tonyd", "P", 1195972014, "tonyd", "P", 1195972053, "tonyd", "P", 1195972456, "tonyd", "P", 1195972483, "tonyd", "P", 1195972535, "tonyd", "P", 1195972621, "tonyd", "P", 1196133198, "tonyd", "P", 1196133234, "tonyd", "P", 1196133352, "tonyd", "P", 1196133404, "tonyd", "P", 1196133461, "tonyd", "P", 1196133517, "tonyd", "P", 1196133545, "tonyd", "P" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
