<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="annemairi">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0" verb2="are carrying" verb3="is carrying"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="lying" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="objskin" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="contract"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="contracts"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="contract"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="looking"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="official"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             official looking contract
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             An official looking contract. A formal or legally binding document comprised of several pages. $[Call(${Allegory:Props:VPs:Selene:Contract}, "display")]
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             An official looking contract.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             $[Call(${Allegory:Props:VPs:Selene:Contract}, "display")]
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:solo:refresh:0100">
         "set writable 1"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:html:display">
         X[S] \<html\>
\<head\>
\<title\>The Contract\</title\>
\<style\>
    html \\\{
        width: 90%;
        margin: auto;
    \\\}
    .header \\\{
        border-top: 1px solid black;
        padding-top: 20px;
        padding-bottom: 15px;
        font-size: 20px;
        font-weight: bolder;
    \\\}
    .title \\\{
        font-weight: bolder;
    \\\}
    .description \\\{
        font-style: italic;
        padding-top: 5px;
        padding-bottom: 20px;
    \\\}
\</style\>
\</head\>\<br/\>
\<center\>\<h1\>The Contract\</h1\>\</center\>
\<center\>\<div class="header"\>Dominant Submissive Agreement\</div\>\</center\>
\<div class="title"\>This Dominant Submissive Agreement is made as of the \<b\>23rd\</b\> day of \<b\>September\</b\>, \<b\>1603\</b\>
between \<b\>Sumner Oberon Lightheart\</b\> (hereinafter referred to as "Dominant") and \<b\>Nereza Selene Cosenza Lightheart\</b\> (hereinafter referred to as "submissive") with reference to the recitals below.\</div\>
\<center\>\<div class="description"\>Initial to confirm above date: 23 Sept 1603 Dominant \<i\>SOL\</i\> submissive \<i\>NSCL\</i\>\</div\>\</center\>
\<center\>\<div class="header"\>Recitals\</div\>\</center\>
\<div class="description"\>A. The fundamental purpose of this contract is to allow the Submissive to explore their sensuality and their limits safely, with due respect and regard for their needs, their limits, and their
wellbeing.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>B. The Dominant and the Submissive each warrant that they suffer from no sexual, serious,
infectious or life-threatening illnesses. If during the Term (as defined below) or any extended term of this contract either party should be diagnosed with or become aware of any such illness they undertake to inform the other
immediately and in any event prior to any form of physical contact between the parties.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>C. The Dominant and the Submissive agree and acknowledge that all that occurs under the terms of this contract will be consensual, confidential, and subject to the agreed limits and safety
procedures set out in this contract. Additional limits and safety procedures may be agreed in
writing. \</div\>
\<center\>\<div class="title"\>Roles\</div\>\</center\>
\<div class="description"\>1. The Dominant shall take responsibility for the wellbeing and the proper training, guidance, and discipline of the Submissive. He shall decide the nature of such training, guidance, and
discipline and the time and place of its administration, subject to the agreed terms, limitations
and safety procedures set out in this contract or agreed additionally under clause C above.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>If at any time the Dominant should fail to keep to the agreed terms, limitations and safety
procedures set out in this contract or agreed additionally under clause C above the Submissive is
entitled to terminate this contract forthwith and to leave the service of the Dominant without
notice.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>2. The Submissive is to serve and obey the Dominant in all things. Subject to the agreed terms, limitations and safety procedures set out in this contract or agreed additionally under clause C above they shall without query or hesitation offer the Dominant such pleasure as he may require and they shall accept without query or
hesitation his training, guidance and discipline in whatever form it may take. \</div\>
\<center\>\<div class="title"\>Agreement\</div\>\</center\>
\<div class="description"\>Now, therefore, in considerations of the above Recitals, the mutual covenants and provisions contained within this Agreement, and other good and valuable consideration, the receipt of which is hereby acknowledged, the parties of this Agreement agree as follows:\</div\>
\<div class="title"\>\<u\>DOMINANT\</u\>\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>1. The Dominant shall make the Submissive’s health and safety a priority at all times. The Dominant shall not at any time require, request, allow or demand the Submissive to participate at the hands of the Dominant in the activities detailed in Exhibit "B" or in any act that either party deems to be unsafe. The Dominant will not undertake or permit to be undertaken any action which could cause serious injury or any risk to the submissive’s life.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>The Dominant accepts the Submissive as theirs, to own, control, dominate and discipline during the Term. The Dominant may use the Submissive’s body at any time during the Allotted Times or any agreed additional times in any manner they deem fit, sexually or otherwise. \</div\>
\<div class="description"\>2. The Dominant shall provide the Submissive with all necessary training and guidance in how to properly serve the Dominant.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>3. The Dominant shall maintain a stable and safe environment in which the Submissive may perform their duties in service of the Dominant.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>4. The Dominant may discipline the Submissive as necessary to ensure the Submissive fully appreciates their role of subservience to the Dominant and to discourage unacceptable conduct. The Dominant may flog, spank, whip or corporally punish the Submissive as they see fit, for purposes of discipline, for their own personal enjoyment, or for any other reason, which they are not obliged to provide.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>5. In training and in the administration of discipline the Dominant shall ensure that no
permanent marks are made upon the Submissive’s body nor any injuries incurred that may
require medical attention.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>6. In case of illness or injury the Dominant shall care for the Submissive, seeing to their
health and safety, encouraging and when necessary ordering medical attention when it is judged
necessary by the Dominant.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>7. The Dominant shall maintain their own good health and seek medical attention when
necessary in order to maintain a risk-free environment.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>8. The Dominant may restrain, handcuff, or bind the Submissive at any time during the
Allotted Times or any agreed additional times for any reason and for extended periods of time,
giving due regard to the health and safety of the Submissive.\</div\>
\<div class="title"\>\<u\>SUBMISSIVE\</u\>\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>1. The Submissive accepts the Dominant as their master, with the understanding that they are now the property of the Dominant, to be dealt with as the Dominant pleases during the Term
generally but specifically during the Allotted Times and any additional agreed allotted times. \</div\>
\<div class="description"\>2. The Submissive shall obey the rules (“the Rules”) set out in Exhibit "A" to this agreement.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>3. The Submissive shall serve the Dominant in any way the Dominant sees fit and shall
endeavor to please the Dominant at all times to the best of their ability.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>4. The Submissive shall take all measures necessary to maintain their good health and shall request or seek medical attention whenever it is needed, keeping the Dominant informed at all
times of any health issues that may arise.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>5. The Submissive will ensure that if pregnancy is suspected/confirmed, they will seek medical attention promptly and inform the Dominant immediately for the wellbeing of the Submissive and the child.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>6. The Submissive shall accept whippings, floggings, spankings, caning, paddling or any
other discipline the Dominant should decide to administer, without hesitation, enquiry or complaint.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>\<b\>(a)\</b\> \<u\>Discipline.\</u\> All Services performed by submissive shall be considered binding obligations while directed during the effective period of this Agreement. As such, and under Dominant's exclusive discretion, provisions for the punishment of submissive for refusal to perform , or when submissive becomes lax in their diligence, may be presented on an "as needed" basis and as required to provide direction and training to submissive. Any punishment deemed necessary for the direction or training of submissive may be performed immediately, regardless of location, time of day or personal discomfort, or scheduled for a later time or location depending entirely on the circumstances of the offence and the desires of Dominant.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>\<b\>\<u\>Safe Words\</u\> \</b\>The Dominant and the Submissive recognize that the Dominant may make demands of the Submissive that cannot be met without incurring physical, mental, emotional, spiritual, or other harm at the time the demands are made to the Submissive. In such circumstances related to this,
the Submissive may make use of a safeword (“The Safeword (s)”). Two Safewords will be invoked depending on the severity of the demands.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\> The Safeword “Yellow” will be used to bring to the attention of the Dominant that the Submissive is close to their limit of endurance.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\> The Safeword “Red” will be used to bring to the attention of the Dominant that the Submissive cannot tolerate any further demands. When this word is said the Dominant’s action will cease completely with immediate effect.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>\<b\>\<u\>Term\</u\>\</b\> The term of this Agreement shall be revisited in three months on the date in which the contract started provided in the first paragraph of this Agreement.  The term may be extended for additional periods of time as agreed to by mutual written consent of the Dominant and submissive.\</div\>
\<div class="header"\>IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties to this Agreement, having fully read and understand all provisions herein,
have executed this DOMINANT SUBMISSIVE AGREEMENT as of the date written in the first paragraph above.\</div\>
\<div class="title"\>\<b\>"DOMINANT":\</b\>PRINT: \<u\>SUMNER OBERON LIGHTHEART\</u\>   SIGN: \<i\>\<u\>Sumner Oberon Lightheart\</u\>\</i\>  \</div\>
\<div class="title"\>\<b\>"SUBMISSIVE":\</b\>PRINT: \<u\>NEREZA SELENE COSENZA LIGHTHEART\</u\>   SIGN: \<i\>\<u\>Nereza Selene Cosenza Lightheart\</u\>\</i\>\</div\>
\<div class="header"\>\<center\>EXHIBIT "A"\</center\>\</div\>
\<center\>\<div class="title"\>Rules\</div\>\</center\>
\<div class="description"\>1. The Submissive will obey any instructions given by the Dominant immediately without hesitation or reservation and in an expeditious manner. The Submissive will agree to any sexual activity deemed fit and pleasurable by the Dominant excepting those activities which are outlined in hard limits (Exhibit "B"). They will do so eagerly and without hesitation.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>2. The Submissive will eat healthy and regularly to maintain their health and wellbeing as well as learn to cook meals that are both healthy and pleasing to the Dominant and the household of the Dominant and submissive.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>3. You must refer to me; by a name of respect (e.g. My name or other endearment) when we are in the presence of those we are familiar with in the "vanilla" World (Outside of the Dom/sub lifestyle); as "Sir" when we are in public where others could hear; and "Master" or "My Master" all other times. *To accommodate the unique circumstance of romantic + Dom/sub relationship, the Submissive does request that the Dominant refer to the Submissive as "Nera" to \<b\>initiate\</b\> Dom/sub time.*\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>4.The Submissive will not enter into any sexual relations with anyone other than the Dominant. The Submissive will conduct themself in a respectful and modest manner at all times. They must recognize that their behavior is a direct reflection on the Dominant. They shall be held accountable for their actions and punshied as the Dominant sees fit. In turn, the Dominant will not enter into any sexual relations with anyone other than the Submissive.\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>5. As the Submissive you will dress yourself in generally feminine clothing when not in uniform. The Submissive is to dress in a way that is pleasing to show off and look at and is to apply at least one cosmetic daily.\</div\>
\<div class="header"\>Exhibit "B"\</div\>
\<div class="title"\>Hard Limits (Non-Negotiable)\</div\>
\<div class="description"\> No acts including the following; fire play, needles, knives, piercing, permanent marks on the skin.\</div\>
\<div class="header"\>Exhibit "C"\</div\>
\<div class="title"\>Soft Limits (Negotiable)\</div\>
\<div class="description"\>To be discussed and agreed between both parties (place an "x" by agreed upon activities):\</div\>
\<div class="description"\> Masturbation (individual;together)__x__ Vaginal intercourse__x__ Anal intercourse__x__ Finger penetration (vaginal/anal)__x__  Oral sex (both parties) __x__ Bondage(hands in front/behind back, elbows, ankles, rope, handcuffs, blindfolds, tied to furniture/objects)__x__ Pain (paddles, canes, spanking, pinching, biting, whipping (riding crop), slapping)__x__ Choking (light, no marks, submissive is never to fully lose consciousness)__x__  - Specifications: No striking the face \</div\>
\<div class="title"\> Aftercare \</div\>
\<div class="description"\> Aftercare is attention given to the Submissive by the Dominant after a session. These are techniques that can comfort the Submissive after intense experiences may leave them in a vulnerable state. The Submissive prefers; verbal reassurance/affirmation from her Dominant (specifically that she is a very good girl); cuddling with her Dominant; her Dominant cleaning her up; a blanket; checking in with her the next day; etc.\</div\>
\</html\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:isascroll">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:objecttype">
         "scroll"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:display">
         X[M] Popup(\$actor, \$this, "display");
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:getleader">
         X[M] \$guild = Obj("Allegory:Guilds:" + \$guild);

if(!\$guild.leader) return "";

\$leader = \$guild.leader;

return Str(\$leader."trait:title") + " " + capitalize(\$leader."skotos:charname") + " " + Str(\$leader."trait:lastname");
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1585778737, "jominey", "E", 1585778751, "jominey", "K", 1585779509, "jominey", "E", 1585779817, "jominey", "E", 1585779899, "jominey", "E", 1585780864, "jominey", "E", 1585780945, "jominey", "E", 1585780958, "jominey", "E", 1585780978, "jominey", "E", 1585781028, "jominey", "E", 1585781070, "jominey", "E", 1585781132, "jominey", "E", 1585781222, "jominey", "E", 1585781267, "jominey", "E", 1585781294, "jominey", "E", 1585781321, "jominey", "E", 1585781338, "jominey", "E", 1585781732, "jominey", "E", 1585781870, "jominey", "E", 1585781951, "jominey", "E", 1585781970, "jominey", "E", 1585782004, "jominey", "E", 1585782029, "jominey", "E", 1585782058, "jominey", "E", 1586268567, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1605489313, "ezralee", "E", 1605489550, "ezralee", "E", 1638155713, "ezralee", "E", 1648600534, "ezralee", "E", 1694392603, "ezralee", "E", 1695218964, "annemairi", "K", 1695221627, "annemairi", "E", 1695221826, "annemairi", "K", 1695222178, "annemairi", "E", 1695222234, "annemairi", "E", 1695222345, "annemairi", "E", 1695222385, "annemairi", "E", 1695222990, "annemairi", "E", 1695223102, "annemairi", "R", 1695223638, "annemairi", "E", 1695224319, "annemairi", "E", 1695224417, "annemairi", "E", 1695224608, "annemairi", "E", 1695224664, "annemairi", "E", 1695224811, "annemairi", "E", 1695224851, "annemairi", "E", 1695226812, "annemairi", "E", 1695227472, "annemairi", "E", 1695228150, "annemairi", "E", 1695229080, "annemairi", "E", 1695229139, "annemairi", "E", 1695230153, "annemairi", "E", 1695230191, "annemairi", "E", 1695230281, "annemairi", "E", 1695230409, "annemairi", "E", 1695230444, "annemairi", "E", 1695231713, "annemairi", "K", 1695231721, "annemairi", "K", 1695231975, "annemairi", "E", 1695232010, "annemairi", "E", 1695232130, "annemairi", "E", 1695232165, "annemairi", "E", 1695232204, "annemairi", "K", 1695232453, "annemairi", "E", 1695233381, "annemairi", "K", 1695233518, "annemairi", "E", 1695233643, "annemairi", "E", 1695233669, "annemairi", "E", 1695233744, "annemairi", "E", 1695233900, "annemairi", "E", 1695233918, "annemairi", "E", 1695251787, "annemairi", "E", 1695251985, "annemairi", "E", 1695252879, "annemairi", "E", 1695253825, "annemairi", "E", 1695256537, "annemairi", "E", 1695257141, "annemairi", "E", 1695257267, "annemairi", "E", 1695257375, "annemairi", "E", 1695257439, "annemairi", "E", 1695257604, "annemairi", "E", 1695258364, "annemairi", "E", 1695276339, "annemairi", "E", 1695276830, "annemairi", "E", 1695436124, "annemairi", "E", 1695436162, "annemairi", "E", 1695436195, "annemairi", "E", 1695438100, "annemairi", "E", 1695439165, "annemairi", "E", 1695517465, "annemairi", "E", 1695519064, "annemairi", "E", 1695519874, "annemairi", "E", 1695525486, "annemairi", "E", 1695525576, "annemairi", "E", 1695526172, "annemairi", "E", 1695526421, "annemairi", "E", 1695526542, "annemairi", "E", 1695526748, "annemairi", "E", 1702536637, "ezralee", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:objecttype">
         "scroll"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="writable">"1"</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
