<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="/*to do*/">
         X[M] /*

TO BE ADDED...

Aconite
Used by ancient Chinese as arrow tip poison \& in medieval times to poison wolves. Never to be taken internally. Aconite preparations are applied externally as pain killers and sedatives to treat sciatica, neuralgia \& rheumatic pain.

Ajuga
Once called the ‘Carpenter’s herb’ for it’s use in staunching bleeding. Nicholas Culpeper in 1652 praised the herb when taken as a decoction of leaves \& flowers as an internal wound healer. Mrs. Grieve, a herbalist in 1931 said it lowered the pulse rate \& equalised the circulation.


AQUILEGIA ‘Columbine’
Used as an antiseptic, astringent \& weak sedative. The root is used in homoeopathy to treat nervous conditions \& externally for the treatment of ulcers. Seeds are POISONOUS (similar effect to Monkshood ‘Aconitum’)

ARMERIA ‘Thrift or Sea Pink’
Once used in the treatment of obesity. Used to treat certain nervous disorders \& urinary infections. Antibiotic properties, but not to be used as an antiseptic poultice as it may cause dermatitis.

Arum
All parts of the fresh plant are POISONOUS, although the well baked tubers are edible, nutritious \& harmless. The bruised fresh leaves were once applied externally to relieve rheumatism.

Asparagus
Cultivated over 4,000 years ago by the Egyptians. It has long been known as a diuretic, useful in treatment of rheumatic conditions as it hastens the flushing of waste products accumulated in the joints out of the body in the urine. Greek physician Dioscorides recommended decoction of asparagus root to improve urine flow \& to treat kidney problems. He also recommended holding the chewed root against aching teeth. Asparagus is also a mild laxative \& sedative.

Barberry
Cultivated in medieval times near monasteries \& churches. It’s sour berries were used in jam, jellies \& candied sweets. It is a host plant of wheat rust \& long ago was recognised by farmers as a plant that ‘blighted’ wheat. The bark yields a yellow dye useful for wool, linen \& leather. Ancient Egyptians crushed the berries along with fennel seeds to make a drink to relieve fevers. Strongly antibacterial \& thought to have cancer inhibiting properties. Barberry has similar properties to ‘Oregon Grape’ so is useful in treating eczema. Useful in treating amoebic dysentery, cholera \& similar gastro-intestinal infections. Do not take during pregnancy.

Celery
Cultivated for over 3,000 years. Italian gardeners developed the celery we know today. Used to treat rheumatic conditions \& gout. Seeds are useful in arthritis, helping to detoxify the body \& improve circulation of blood to the muscles \& joints. Celery seeds are also beneficial for asthma \& bronchitis \& in combination with other herbs reduce blood pressure. The seeds are an effective treatment for cystitis helping to disinfect the bladder \& urinary tubules.

Chickweed
Long used as a bird feed \& in winter provides one of the few fresh sources for them. Also popular as a tasty \& nutritious vegetable, can be used in salads or cooked with a knob of butter. Chickweed is chiefly employed medicinally to treat eczema. The juice ribbed onto the itchy skin will bring relief.

Clematis
In the Middle Ages travellers used the caustic sap to raise mock wounds, encouraging the donation of alms. The leaves irritate the skin causing it to redden \& blister, but they are also strongly analgesic. Applied to arthritic joints they help relieve pain \& encourage the removal of waste products. The plant is diuretic \& in the past was taken internally to counter urinary problems - however the mature plant is toxic \& should not be digested. In the past the juice was reputed to relieve headaches \& migraine if sniffed, but as this might destroy the mucous linings of the nose it is not advised to do so.

Dittany
Dittany exudes such large amounts of volatile oil that in hot, dry conditions a match held close will cause the whole plant to burst into flames - yet will not damage the plant! The plant has been used to flavour liqueurs \& in Siberia it is brewed as a tea. In European folk medicine Dittany was believed to be a remedy for venomous bites. Dittany has a similar action to that of Rue, it strongly stimulates the muscles of the uterus, inducing menstruation. Dittany relaxes the gut \& acts as a mild tonic for the stomach. CAUTION: Do not take during pregnancy.

Larkspur
Formally used internally as a violent purgative. A strong tincture of fresh seeds may be applied externally to head \& pubic hair to destroy human parasites. Blue ink may be prepared from the fresh petals.  POISONOUS.

Mugwort
An ancient magical plant used to repel demons. Used to flavour drinks especially beer, name derived from Old Saxon muggia wort meaning ‘midge plant’ after it’s ability to repel insects. Leaves may be used in tobacco. Romans placed it in their sandals believing it beneficial to the soles of their feet. Known in ancient times as bringing about the on set of labour, in the 13th century the Welsh Herbal recommended binding a sprig of mug wort to a woman’s left thigh to induce child birth but removing it immediately the child is born lest the mother should haemorrhage.

Onion
In cultivation since Egyptian times. Antibiotic, reduces blood pressure \& blood sugar levels. Used to treat acne. Warmed juice can be dropped into the ear for ear ache. Useful in preventing oral infections \& tooth decay. Baked onions used as a poultice to drain pus from sores. Long standing reputation as an aphrodisiac \& used cosmetically to promote hair growth.

Tarragon
Essential component in French cuisine. Latin name means ‘little dragon’ after coiled serpent like root \& belief that it’s use cures snake bite. While Tarragon stimulates digestion, it is a mild sedative \& aids sleep. With it’s mild menstruation inducing properties it is taken if periods are delayed. Do not take during pregnancy! The root has traditionally been applied to relieve toothache.

Thornapple
The Delphic Oracle in ancient Greece \& the Inca’s in South America used it as an aid to making prophecies - It has hallucinogenic properties. Interestingly, even though it is hallucinogenic, thornapple has traditionally been used to treat insanity. May be applied externally as a poultice to reduce local pain, muscle spasm \& the symptoms of Parkinsonism. Applied externally it gives relief to rheumatic pains \& neuralgia. Toxic in high doses, poisoning can occur if taken without medical supervision.

*/
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="acanthus">
         ([ "level":9, "notes":"A plaster of the roots wrapped around dislocated joints relaxes \& tightens \& encourages the joint back into place. Crushed leaves to treat burns. The plants emollient properties treat irritated mucous membranes within the digestive \& urinary tracts. Once used to relieve wind." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="agrimony">
         ([ "level":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ajowan">
         ([ "level":13, "notes":"Trachyspermum ammi, commonly known as ajowan,[1] bishop's weed,[1] ajowan caraway, carom seeds, or thymol seeds, is a plant of India, Pakistan and the Near East whose seeds are used as a spice.[3] Trachyspermum ammi originated in the Middle East, possibly in Egypt, and the Indian subcontinent, but also in Iran and Afghanistan. It is sometimes used as an ingredient in berbere, a spice mixture favored in Eritrea and Ethiopia. The raw fruit pod of Trachyspermum ammi smells almost exactly like thyme because it also contains thymol, but is more aromatic and less subtle in taste, as well as slightly bitter and pungent. Even a small amount of raw fruit pods of Trachyspermum ammi tend to dominate the flavour of a dish." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="allspice">
         ([ "level":8, "notes":"Allspice is the dried fruit of the Pimenta dioica plant. The fruit are picked when green and unripe and, traditionally, dried in the sun. When dry, the fruit are brown and resemble large brown peppercorns. The whole fruit have a longer shelf life than the powdered product and produce a more aromatic product when freshly ground before use. Fresh leaves are used where available. They are similar in texture to bay leaves and are thus infused during cooking and then removed before serving. Unlike bay leaves, they lose much flavour when dried and stored, so do not figure in commerce. The leaves and wood are often used for smoking meats where allspice is a local crop. Allspice can also be found in essential oil form." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="aloe">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"Of the 500+ species, only a few were used traditionally as a herbal medicine, aloe vera again being the most commonly used species. Also included are A. perryi and A. ferox. The Ancient Greeks and Romans used aloe vera to treat wounds. In the Middle Ages, the yellowish liquid found inside the leaves was favored as a purgative.[citation needed] Unprocessed aloe that contains aloin is generally used as a laxative, whereas processed aloe vera juice does not usually contain significant aloin." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="amchur">
         ([ "level":20, "notes":"mango" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="angelfishorchid">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"variation of the orchid" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="angelica">
         ([ "level":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="anise">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"a licorice scented ferny annual. The seeds were used to treat gas and to induce sweating, as well as in sweets and candies." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="annattoo">
         ([ "level":22, "notes":" It was probably not initially used as a food additive, but for other reasons, such as body painting, treatment for heartburn and stomach distress, sunscreen, repelling insects, and to ward off evil." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="anthurium">
         ([ "level":11 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="apple">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"yummy fruit, seeds are poisonous" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="applered">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"yummy fruit, seeds are poisonous" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="arnica">
         ([ "level":19, "notes":"Arnica montana has been used medicinally for centuries, however there are no scientific studies that prove the medical effectiveness.[1] The roots contain derivatives of thymol,[3] which are used as fungicides and preservatives. Arnica is currently used in liniment and ointment preparations used for strains, sprains, and bruises. Commercial Arnica preparations are frequently used by professional athletes.[4] Arnica contains the toxin helenalin, which can be poisonous if large amounts of the plant are eaten, and contact with the plant can also cause skin irritation.[6][7] If enough of the material is ingested, the toxin helenalin produces severe gastroenteritis, and internal bleeding of the digestive tract.[8] Homeopathic preparations of Arnica 24X dilution or more are not toxic as negligible amounts of Arnica remains.[9][10][11]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="asafoetida">
         ([ "level":15, "notes":"This spice is used as a digestive aid, in food as a condiment, and in pickles. Helps colds. Scent bait (fishing). Repels spirits." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="asphodel">
         ([ "level":11, "notes":"The leaves are used to wrap burrata, an Italian cheese. The leaves and the cheese last about the same time, three or four days, and thus fresh leaves are a sign of a fresh cheese, while dried out leaves indicate that the cheese is past its prime. In Greek legend the asphodel is one of the most famous of the plants connected with the dead and the underworld. Homer describes it as covering the great meadow (ἀσφόδελος λειμών), the haunt of the dead. It was planted on graves, and is often connected with Persephone, who appears crowned with a garland of asphodels. Its general connection with death is due no doubt to the greyish colour of its leaves and its yellowish flowers, which suggest the gloom of the underworld and the pallor of death. The roots were eaten by the poorer Greeks; hence such food was thought good enough for the shades. The asphodel was also supposed to be a remedy for poisonous snake-bites and a specific against sorcery; it was fatal to mice, but preserved pigs from disease. The Libyan nomads made their huts of asphodel stalks." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="assam">
         ([ "notes":"assam tea" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bambooorchid">
         ([ "level":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="basil">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"a fleshy-leaved perennial. Used in cooking-- for potage or boiled greens, in green pickles." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bayleaf">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"cooking spice" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bean">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"food" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="blackberry">
         ([ "level":12, "notes":"yummy fruit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="blackroot">
         ([ "level":21, "notes":"nada" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="blueberry">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"yummy fruit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bluejavabanana">
         ([ "level":19, "notes":"yummy fruit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="borage">
         ([ "level":22, "notes":"Historical descriptions of Borage all refer to the herb’s abilities to bring happiness \& drive away melancholia. It was once widely used in a variety of alcoholic drinks. Candied flowers used for cake decorations. Fresh leaves \& flowers can be added to salads, the roots are used to flavour wine. Borage seed oil is used to treat premenstrual complaints, rheumatic problems \& eczema." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bougainvillea">
         ([ "level":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bryony">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"Grows in grassy and woodland areas. Most of this plant, with the exception of the edible seeds, is toxic. Topical application of the juice from the root causes inflammation, rashes, and ulcers. Symptoms of ingestion include nausea/vomiting and diarrhea, though ingestion of larger amounts can result in paralysis or death. The best antidote for bryony poisoning through ingestion is to induce vomiting as soon as possible and to give the patient demulcent herbs. (Bryonia dioica)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bulrush">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"edible cattail" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cacao">
         ([ "level":24, "notes":"chocolate bean" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="callalily">
         ([ "level":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="caraway">
         ([ "level":16, "notes":"The fruits, usually used whole, have a pungent, anise-like flavor and aroma that comes from essential oils, mostly carvone and limonene.[citation needed] They are used as a spice in breads, especially rye bread. Caraway is also used in desserts, liquors, casseroles, curry and other foods. It is more commonly found in European cuisine. For example, it is commonly used in British caraway seed cake and is also added to sauerkraut. [6][7][8][9][10] It is also used to add flavor to cheeses such as bondost, pultost, nøkkelost and havarti. Akvavit and several liqueurs are made with caraway. In Middle Eastern cuisine, caraway pudding is a popular dessert during Ramadan.[11] The roots may be cooked as a root vegetable like parsnips or carrots." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cardamom">
         ([ "level":8, "notes":"Green cardamom is broadly used in South Asia to treat infections in teeth and gums, to prevent and treat throat troubles, congestion of the lungs and pulmonary tuberculosis, inflammation of eyelids and also digestive disorders. It also is used to break up kidney stones and gall stones, and was reportedly used as an antidote for both snake and scorpion venom. Both forms of cardamom are used as flavorings in both food and drink, as cooking spices and as a medicine. E. cardamomum (the usual type of cardamom) is used as a spice, a masticatory, and in medicine; it is also smoked sometimes." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="carnation">
         ([ "level":3, "notes":"pretty, calming flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="carrot">
         ([ "level":9 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cassia">
         ([ "level":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="catnip">
         ([ "level":14, "notes":"cured evils a  man has about his throat" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cattail">
         ([ "level":6, "notes":"see bulrush" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cedar">
         ([ "level":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ceylon">
         ([ "level":0, "tea":([ "leaf":\<Ironclaw:Props:Gardening:Tea:Black:C:Ceylon\> ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cherry">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"Yummy fruit with poisonous pits. If you consume a cherry pit, when you chew it up you are releasing a chemical in your body called cyanide. Cyanide is a compound that disables the ability of the blood in the body to transport oxygen around. Large doses of cyanide in oneâs body can result to them unfortunately passing away due to asphyxiation. Some of the symptoms of cyanide poisoning include: confusion, excessive sleepiness, seizure, general weakness and even strange behavior." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cherryblossom">
         ([ "level":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chive">
         ([ "level":4, "notes":"food, medicinal properties similar (but weaker) to that of garlic", "tea":([ "tea-part":\<Ironclaw:Props:Gardening:Tea:Herbal:C:Chive\> ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chrysanthemum">
         ([ "level":18, "notes":"pretty flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cinnamon">
         ([ "level":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="clove">
         ([ "level":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cloverpatch">
         ([ "level":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="coffea">
         ([ "level":23 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="coral">
         ([ "level":16, "notes":"pretty flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="coriander">
         ([ "level":5, "notes":"a fringy annual. The seeds were used for cooking and to deter fevers. Cultivated for over 3,000 years it is mentioned by Egyptian, Greek \& Sanskrit authors. Chewing the seed stimulates secretion of gastric juices. Bruised seed is applied externally as a poultice to relieve painful joints in rheumatism. The fresh leaf is the most widely used flavouring herb in the world. The root can be cooked \& eaten as a vegetable. The seed is employed in baking, as a spice or condiment, in liqueur, \& in confectionary. Chewing Coriander freshens the breath after eating garlic \& settles the stomach." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cowbane">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"This plant grows in wet areas. Symptoms of ingestion include nausea, vomiting, and abdominal pain. More severe symptoms include tremors, seizures, and death. Onset of symptoms typically takes about an hour. The stems and the roots are both toxic, the roots being the most toxic part of the plant. There is no antidote to cowbane poisoning, but inducing vomiting early may help if ingestion is suspected. Symptoms normally taper off within a day or two if the patient survives. During this time, the only option is to treat the patient's symptoms as they arise. (Cicuta virosa)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cranberry">
         ([ "level":20, "notes":"fruit, tastes good (allegedy)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cubeb">
         ([ "level":4, "notes":"In Europe, cubeb was one of the valuable spices during the Middle Ages. It was ground as a seasoning for meat or used in sauces. A medieval recipe includes cubeb in making sauce sarcenes, which consists of almond milk and several spices.[17] As an aromatic confectionery, cubeb was often candied and eaten whole.[18] Ocet Kubebowy, a vinegar infused with cubeb, cumin and garlic, was used for meat marinades in Poland during the 14th century.[19] Cubeb can still be used to enhance the flavor of savory soups. In India, Sanskrit texts included cubeb in various remedies. Charaka and Sushruta prescribed a cubeb paste as a mouthwash, and the use of dried cubebs internally for oral and dental diseases, loss of voice, halitosis, fevers, and cough." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cumin">
         ([ "level":3, "notes":"the seed of an annual plant. Used in cooking and to treat gas." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cypress">
         ([ "level":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="daffodil">
         ([ "level":4, "notes":"flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="daisy">
         ([ "level":4, "notes":"flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dill">
         ([ "level":7, "notes":"Egyptians used dill as an ingredient in a pain killing mixture. Ancient Greeks covered their eyes in Dill fronds to induce sleep. Used as a charm in Middle Ages against witchcraft when it was burned to ward off thunder clouds. Chewing seeds improves bad breath. Used in Gripe water to settle the stomach. Dill increases milk production \& when taken regularly by nursing mothers helps prevent colic in their babies." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="echinacea-coneflower">
         ([ "level":24, "notes":"Echinacea is one of the world’s most important herbs. It has the ability to raise the body’s resistance to bacterial \& viral infections by stimulating the immune system. The Comanche used Echinacea as a remedy for toothache \& sore throats. The Sioux took it for rabis, snake bite \& septic conditions. It is a good antibiotic \& is useful to relive allergies \& to clear skin infections." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="elderberry">
         ([ "level":24, "notes":"Elder has almost more folklore attached than any other plant. Inhabited by nature spirits it is essential to ask permission of them before taking any part of the plant. The wood of the branches is traditionally  used by witches for wands. Elder is a valuable remedy for flu, colds \& chesty conditions. It flowers in spring \& an infusion of the flowering tops and peppermint is a useful treatment for colds, it also produces a mild perspiration that helps reduce fever. The autumn berries are rich in vitamin C, mixed with honey \& rum they are effective in relieving sore throats." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ergot">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"Ergot is a highly toxic fungus that grows on cereal crops. Symptoms of ingestion include convulsions, hallucinations, and restriction of the blood supply, which can create burning pain in the extremities and lead to gangrene if left untreated. There is no antidote for ergot poisoning; only option is supportive care of symptoms. (Claviceps purpurea)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="eucalyptus">
         ([ "level":17, "notes":"Eucalyptus oil is used in aromatherapy \& is also an excellent disinfectant \& antiseptic. It is useful for the treatment of skin infections \& as a decongestant. The vapour can be inhaled to relieve symptoms of colds. The leaves are useful in pot-pourris." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fennel">
         ([ "level":6, "notes":"food but known to cause hallucinations, breathing problems, convulsions, and heart arrhythmia if eaten in large quantities" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fenugreek">
         ([ "level":4, "notes":"Fenugreek has three culinary uses: as an herb (dried or fresh leaves), as a spice (seeds), and as a vegetable (fresh leaves, sprouts, and microgreens)." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="feverfew">
         ([ "level":23, "notes":"Used widely in the past to treat fever by lowering the temperature \& cooling the body. Useful in treating migraine when taken on a regular basis. Used since Roman times to induce menstruation \& given during childbirth to expel the placenta. Useful as a non-toxic insecticide for control of mosquito, cockroach, domestic fly \& other pests." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fir">
         ([ "level":9, "notes":"used for decorative/artsy purposes" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="foxglove">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"Foxglove enables the heart to beat more strongly, slowly \& regularly without requiring more oxygen. It’s benefits on the heart became wide spread in the 1700’s when William Withering, while visiting Shropshire, discovered a herbalist prescribing Foxglove tea for dropsy. May be used externally as a poultice to aid the healing of wounds. POISONOUS." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="garlic">
         ([ "level":9, "notes":"food, spice, draws out infection from wounds. Egyptian slaves building Cheops pyramid ate garlic daily to sustain strength, as did Roman soldiers. Antibacterial, weak fungicide. Gives some protection against common cold, amoeboid dysentery, typhoid \& other infectious diseases. Prevents circulatory problems \& strokes by keeping the blood thin. Garlic lowers cholesterol levels \& blood pressure." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="garmflowerblue">
         ([ "level":22, "notes":"ICO flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="garmflowerpurple">
         ([ "level":24, "notes":"ICO flower used to make unholy babies" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="garmflowerred">
         ([ "level":23, "notes":"ICO flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ginger">
         ([ "level":7, "notes":"an Indian root plant. Used in food, including gingerbread, cakes, meats and sidedishes. Its warmth was used medicinally to treat stomach problems, and as a remedy for the plague." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="grapered">
         ([ "level":17, "notes":"yummy fruit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="grapewhite">
         ([ "level":18, "notes":"yummy fruit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="heliconia">
         ([ "level":17, "notes":"ornamental plant" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="henna">
         ([ "level":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hibiscus">
         ([ "level":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="holly">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"helps with hysteria and epilepsy, but berries are high toxic and deadly" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ivymagnolia">
         ([ "level":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="juniper">
         ([ "level":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="kokum">
         ([ "level":14, "notes":"The outer cover of fruit is dried in the sun to get aamsul or kokam. It is used as a slightly sour spice in recipes from Maharashtra. Kokum yields a peculiar flavour and blackish red colour. It is a preferred substitute for tamarind in curries and other dishes from the Konkan region. It is also used in cuisine from Gujarat, where it is frequently used to add flavor and tartness to dal (lentil soup) for flavor balance, and parts of South India. Used in preparation of medicines." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ladyfern">
         ([ "level":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="larch">
         ([ "level":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="laurel">
         ([ "level":5, "notes":"The plant is the source of several popular spices used in a wide variety of recipes, particularly among Mediterranean cuisines.[2] Most commonly, the aromatic leaves are added whole to Italian pasta sauces. However, even when cooked, whole bay leaves can be sharp and abrasive enough to damage internal organs, so they are typically removed from dishes before serving, unless used as a simple garnish.[ Italian spice. Aqueous extracts of bay laurel can also be used as astringents and even as a reasonable salve for open wounds. In massage therapy, the essential oil of bay laurel is reputed to alleviate arthritis and rheumatism, while in aromatherapy, it is used to treat earaches and high blood pressure.[5][unreliable source?] A traditional folk remedy for rashes caused by poison ivy, poison oak, and stinging nettle is a poultice soaked in boiled bay leaves." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lavender">
         ([ "level":5, "notes":"the dried flowers of, were used in food, and in refreshing washes for headaches; a cap with lavender flowers quilted in it kept headaches at bay. Used extensively in baths, as a personal scent and as a moth repellent." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lemon">
         ([ "level":12, "notes":"yummy, helps with sleepy time" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lemongrass">
         ([ "level":5, "notes":"food/tea flavoring, soothes sore throat" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="licorice">
         ([ "level":7, "notes":"yummy, soothes sore throat" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lily">
         ([ "level":7, "notes":"Pretty flower. Native Peoples used wood lily roots to make medicinal teas that were taken to treat stomach disorders, coughs, tuberculosis, fevers, and help women in labour deliver the afterbirth. The same teas were also used as a wash for swellings, bruises, wounds and sores. A concoction of this plant combined with sweet viburnum roots was used to treat irregular menstruation. Furthermore, lily roots in combination with blackberry roots, raspberries, and staghorn sumac were used to treat coughs, fevers, and consumption." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lilyofthevalley">
         ([ "level":16, "notes":"Super pretty. All parts of the plant are highly poisonous, including the red berries which may be attractive to children.[19][20] If ingested—even in small amounts—the plant can cause abdominal pain, vomiting, and a reduced heart rate." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lotus">
         ([ "level":11, "notes":"Pretty flower.  Medicinal Properties: Astringent; Cancer; Cardiotonic; Febrifuge; Hypotensive; Miscellany; Resolvent; Stomachic; Styptic; Tonic; Vasodilator." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="marigold">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"A very useful herb, it yields a yellow dye \& can be used for culinary \& cosmetic purposes as well as medicinal. Useful to treat inflamed lymphatic nodes, duodenal ulcers \& some inflammatory skin lesions. Used externally for treatment of leg ulcers \& in conjunctivitis as an eye lotion. Petals are substitutes for Saffron \& may be added to salads \& omelettes or used to colour cheese \& butter. Young leaves can be added to salads, petals can be added to tea which can be drunk or used as a hair rinse. The yellow dye is obtained by boiling the flowers." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meleguetapepper">
         ([ "level":19, "notes":"food, spice" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mint">
         ([ "level":6, "notes":"of all kinds were used in food and medicine. Mint vinegar was used as a mouthwash; mint sauce restored the appetite. Used for all stomach ailments and in treating venom and wounds." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mistletoe-oak">
         ([ "level":0 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mullein">
         ([ "level":18, "notes":"Pretty. The plant has a long history of use as a herbal remedy,[3] and is an effective treatment for asthma and respiratory disorders.[dubious – discuss] Extracts made from the plant's flowers are a very effective treatment for ear infections.[citation needed] Although this plant is a recent arrival to North America, Native Americans used the ground seeds of this plant as a paralytic fish poison due to their high levels of rotenone.[citation needed] One species, Verbascum thapsus (Great mullein), is used as a herbal remedy for sore throat, cough, and lung diseases." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mustard">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"a huge annual with tiny yellow or black seeds. Used to make sauces." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="nasturtium">
         ([ "level":21 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="nettle">
         ([ "level":16, "notes":"helps slow blood flow and cure for the poops" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="nigella">
         ([ "level":11, "notes":"seeds are called black cumin and used as a spice. In the Unani Tibb system of medicine, black cumin is regarded as a valuable remedy for a number of diseases. Sayings of Islamic Prophet Muhammad underline the significance of black cumin. According to a hadith narrated by Abu Hurairah, he says, 'I have heard the Messenger of Allah, peace be upon him, saying that the black granules (kalonji) is the remedy for all diseases except death.'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="nutmeg">
         ([ "level":9, "notes":"the nuts of an Asian tree. Ground and eaten to improve digestion; set in silver and carried as scented jewelry. Common in medieval cookery" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="orchid">
         ([ "level":6, "notes":"pretty flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="paprika">
         ([ "level":9, "notes":"food, spice" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="peach">
         ([ "level":5, "notes":"super yummy fruit with poisonous pits" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pine">([ "level":7 ])</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="plum">
         ([ "level":17, "notes":"yummy fruit, helps the poop come out" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="poinsettia">
         ([ "level":15, "notes":"Pretty floer. While the sap and latex of many plants of the spurge genus are indeed toxic,[15] the poinsettia's toxicity is relatively mild. Its latex can cause an allergic reaction in sensitive individuals.[16] It is also mildly irritating to the skin or stomach[5] and may sometimes cause diarrhea and vomiting if eaten.[17] Sap introduced into the human eye may cause temporary blindness." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="poppy">
         ([ "level":15, "notes":"Most species of poppies are attractive and are cultivated as ornamental plants. A few species have other uses, principally as sources of drugs and foods. The opium poppy (Papaver somniferum) is so widely used, for both drugs and food, that its worldwide production is monitored by international agencies. It yields opium and opiates, poppy seeds for use in cooking and baking, and poppyseed oil for culinary and other uses, and is also cultivated as an ornamental plant. Ancient Egyptian doctors would have their patients eat seeds from a poppy to relieve pain. Poppy seeds contain both morphine and codeine, which are pain-relieving drugs that are still used today." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="potmarigold">
         ([ "level":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pricklypearcactus">
         ([ "level":15, "notes":"Fruits are edible. In Mexican folk medicine, its pulp and juice have been used to treat numerous maladies, such as wounds and inflammations of the digestive and urinary tracts" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="redcurrant">
         ([ "level":0 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="reed">
         ([ "level":1, "notes":"used for thatching and is edible apparently" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1418281907, "jominey", "E", 1418346866, "jominey", "E", 1418348951, "jominey", "E", 1418352826, "jominey", "E", 1418352922, "jominey", "E", 1418356653, "jominey", "E", 1418356696, "jominey", "E", 1418356793, "jominey", "E", 1418356811, "jominey", "E", 1418356933, "jominey", "E", 1418356965, "jominey", "E", 1418357009, "jominey", "E", 1418357040, "jominey", "E", 1418357142, "jominey", "E", 1418357205, "jominey", "E", 1418357354, "jominey", "E", 1418357432, "jominey", "E", 1418357501, "jominey", "E", 1418357577, "jominey", "E", 1418357621, "jominey", "E", 1418357662, "jominey", "E", 1418357704, "jominey", "E", 1418357770, "jominey", "E", 1418357827, "jominey", "E", 1418357876, "jominey", "E", 1418357901, "jominey", "E", 1418357923, "jominey", "E", 1418357987, "jominey", "E", 1418358662, "jominey", "E", 1418358705, "jominey", "E", 1418358729, "jominey", "E", 1418358756, "jominey", "E", 1418358789, "jominey", "E", 1418358840, "jominey", "E", 1418358876, "jominey", "E", 1418358898, "jominey", "E", 1418358918, "jominey", "E", 1418358955, "jominey", "E", 1418358979, "jominey", "E", 1418359016, "jominey", "E", 1418359040, "jominey", "E", 1418526656, "jominey", "E", 1418526680, "jominey", "E", 1418526698, "jominey", "E", 1418526764, "jominey", "E", 1418526788, "jominey", "E", 1418526808, "jominey", "E", 1418531274, "jominey", "E", 1418535272, "jominey", "E", 1418543415, "jominey", "E", 1419136055, "jominey", "E", 1419136152, "jominey", "E", 1419136185, "jominey", "E", 1419136202, "jominey", "E", 1419136222, "jominey", "E", 1419136251, "jominey", "E", 1419136284, "jominey", "E", 1419136317, "jominey", "E", 1419136722, "jominey", "E", 1419136750, "jominey", "E", 1419136763, "jominey", "E", 1419136780, "jominey", "E", 1419136793, "jominey", "E", 1419136800, "jominey", "E", 1419136813, "jominey", "E", 1419136835, "jominey", "E", 1419136865, "jominey", "E", 1419136878, "jominey", "E", 1419136892, "jominey", "E", 1419136907, "jominey", "E", 1419136948, "jominey", "E", 1419137037, "jominey", "E", 1431056855, "jominey", "E", 1567566715, "jominey", "E", 1567566733, "jominey", "E", 1567566760, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rose">
         ([ "level":13, "notes":"pretty flower, smells good" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rosebay">
         ([ "level":13, "notes":"The young shoots were often collected in the spring by Native American people and mixed with other greens. As the plant matures the leaves become tough and somewhat bitter. The southeast Native Americans use the stems in the stage. They are peeled and eaten raw. When properly prepared soon after picking they are a good source of vitamin C and pro-vitamin A. The Dena'ina add fireweed to their dogs' food. Fireweed is also a medicine of the Upper Inlet Dena'ina, who treat pus-filled boils or cuts by placing a piece of the raw stem on the afflicted area. This is said to draw the pus out of the cut or boil and prevents a cut with pus in it from healing over too quickly." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="saffron">
         ([ "level":3, "notes":"the inner parts of a kind of crocus flower. Used in cooking, especially soups and grains, and to dye yellow; also used to treat infections." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sage">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"a green woody perennial, symbolic of age and wisdom. The leaves were used in salads and green sauces and as a spring tonic. 'A man shall live for aye who eats sage in May.' 'Cleans out' the system.", "tea":([ "tea-part":\<Ironclaw:Props:Gardening:Tea:Herbal:S:Sage\> ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sassafras">
         ([ "level":7, "notes":"smells good" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sassafrasleaf">
         ([ "level":"delete" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sem">([ "level":13 ])</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sesame">
         ([ "level":6, "notes":"foodstuff" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="shaggymane">
         ([ "level":24, "notes":"yummy food" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="strawberry">
         ([ "level":13, "notes":"Known to Dioscorides \& early Arabian physicians, but never widely employed. Used to treat diarrhoea \& biliousness. A decoction provides an excellent antiseptic wash. Fruit can be used in alcoholic drinks or preserves such as marmalade. The bark was once used in leather tanning. The wood provides good quality charcoal, \& is suitable for turning \& marquetry." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sumac">
         ([ "level":19, "notes":"Sumac was used as a treatment for half a dozen different ailments in medieval medicine, primarily in Islamic countries (where sumac was more readily available than in Europe). An 11th-century shipwreck off the coast of Rhodes, excavated by archeologists in the 1970s, contained commercial quantities of sumac drupes. These could have been intended for use as medicine, or as a culinary spice, or as a dye. Some species, such as Poison ivy (Rhus toxicodendron, syn.Toxicodendron radicans), Poison oak (Rhus diversiloba, syn. Toxicodendron diversilobum) and Poison sumac (Rhus vernix, syn. Toxicodendron vernix), have the allergen urushiol and can cause severe allergic reactions. Poison sumac may be identified by its white drupes." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sweetpea">
         ([ "level":8, "notes":"Flowering plant. Unlike the edible pea, there is evidence that seeds of members of the genus Lathyrus are toxic if ingested in quantity. A related species, Lathyrus sativus, is grown for human consumption but when it forms a major part of the diet it causes symptoms of toxicity called lathyrism." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tamarind">
         ([ "level":15, "notes":"The ripened fruit is considered the more palatable, as it becomes sweeter and less sour (acidic) as it matures. It is used in desserts as a jam, blended into juices or sweetened drinks, sorbets, ice creams and all manner of snacks. In northern Nigeria, fresh stem bark and fresh leaves are used as decoction mixed with potash for the treatment of stomach disorders, general body pain, jaundice, and yellow fever, and as blood tonic and skin cleanser. In Indonesia, Malaysia and the Philippines and Javanese traditional medicine, asem leaves are used as a herbal infusion for malarial fever, the fruit juice as an antiseptic, and for scurvy and even cough cure. Throughout Southeast Asia, fruit of the tamarind is used a poultice applied to foreheads of fever sufferers." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="thyme">
         ([ "level":2, "notes":"a low, creeping perennial with tiny leaves, symbolic of courage. Used in cooking, and in baths and as an astringent. Burned as to fumigate against infection and to scent sacrifices." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tigerlily">
         ([ "level":12, "notes":"pretty stuff" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tobacco">
         ([ "level":12, "notes":"roll it, smoke it" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tomato">
         ([ "level":12, "notes":"it's yum" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tulip">
         ([ "level":8, "notes":"pretty stuff" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="turmeric">
         ([ "level":8, "notes":"Although usually used in its dried, powdered form, turmeric is also used fresh, much like ginger. It has numerous uses in Far Eastern recipes, such as fresh turmeric pickle, which contains large chunks of soft turmeric. In combination with annatto (E160b), turmeric has been used to color cheeses, yogurt, dry mixes, salad dressings, winter butter and margarine. Turmeric is also used to give a yellow color to some prepared mustards, canned chicken broths and other foods (often as a much cheaper replacement for saffron). In Goa and Dakshina Kannada (Karnataka state, India), turmeric plant leaf is used to prepare special sweet dishes, patoleo, by layering rice flour and coconut-jaggery mixture on the leaf, and then closing and steaming it in a special copper steamer (goa). In Tamil Nadu, an Indian State, it is called 'Manjal', which is extensively used for its aroma, color and as a disinfectant. Turmeric, with its antibacterial action, prevents bacterial infections on wounds." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="vanilla">
         ([ "level":10, "notes":"yummy yummy flavoring" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="waterhemlock">
         ([ "level":23, "notes":"Water hemlock is considered one of North America's most toxic plants being highly poisonous to humans.[1] Three members of the genus contain a toxin named cicutoxin which causes central nervous system stimulatory effects including seizures following ingestion. Medical treatment of poisoning may include the use of activated charcoal to decrease gastrointestinal absorption of the toxic principle along with supportive care including anticonvulsant drugs such as a benzodiazepine. High doses of anticonvulsant medicine are often required to halt seizure activity and further medical care including intubation and mechanical ventilation may be required. Upon consumption, both in humans and other species, the symptoms of poisoning are mainly characterized by generalized seizures.[1] The onset of symptoms following ingestion may be as soon as 15 minutes post ingestion. Initial symptoms reported may include nausea, vomiting, abdominal pain, tremors, confusion, weakness, dizziness, and drowsiness;[16][28] although the rapid onset of seizure activity may be the first sign presenting following poisoning. Seizures are usually described as clonic or tonic–clonic.[1] Additional neurological symptoms may include hallucinations, delirium, tingling, pricking, or numbness of a person's skin, dilated pupils, and coma.[1][16] Cardiovascular symptoms include alternating slow or fast heart rate[31] and alternating low and high blood pressure.[32] Other cardiac effects may include ECG abnormalities such as widening of the PR interval, supraventricular tachycardia, and ventricular fibrillation.[1][17][33] Symptoms of excess salivation, wheezing, respiratory distress, and absence of breathing have also been reported. Water hemlock poisoning is usually diagnosed following a history of plant ingestion and symptoms of abrupt onset of seizures." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="watermint">
         ([ "level":18, "notes":"Often found in shallow areas of larger bodies of water, watermint is often crossed with spearmint to aid in the creation of new peppermint plants. In the kitchen, dried watermint leaves can be used to brew an excellent, aromatic tea, or mixed in with other teas to create tasty combinations. The oil derived from the watermint plant can also be used to add flavor to oil and vinegar based dressings, which can be used for green salads or to give raw fruits and vegetables a little extra taste. The mint also can be added to cake batter, providing an unexpected burst of flavor to chocolate and lemon cakes.From a medicinal perspective, watermint is also understood to be an excellent choice when it comes to cleaning surface wounds, removing excess oil from the face, calming ulcers, and helping to relieve indigestion." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="weeping fountain">
         ([ "level":21 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="whiteviolet">
         ([ "level":19, "notes":"congestion, coughing, sore throat" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wildcarrot">
         ([ "level":11, "notes":"food, I reckon" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wisteria">
         ([ "level":14, "notes":"pretty decorative flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wormwood">
         ([ "level":22 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wysteria">
         ([ "level":14, "notes":"pretty decorative flower" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="yarrow">
         ([ "level":21 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="zedoary">
         ([ "level":18, "notes":"The edible root of zedoary has a white interior and a fragrance reminiscent of mango; however, its flavour is more similar to ginger, except with a very bitter aftertaste. In Indonesia, it is ground to a powder and added to curry pastes, whereas in India, it tends to be used fresh or in pickling. In Thai cuisine it is used raw and cut in thin strips in certain Thai salads. It can also be served cut in to thin slices together with other herbs and vegetables with certain types of nam phrik (Thai chilli pastes). The essential oil produced from the dried roots of Curcuma zedoaria is used in perfumery and soap fabrication, as well as an ingredient in bitter tonics." ])
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
