<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="jominey">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="anchor">
         ([ "design":"An anchor comprised of deeply embossed lines adorns the surface. In maritime lore, this symbol represents the success of a seaman upon the ocean. It is said to guarantee stability and security in the physical world, and, by extension, also steadfastness, hope, and trust", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="apple blossom">
         ([ "design":"Elegantly embossed apple blossoms delicately display their many petals, with each flower spaced strategically throughout the surface.", "skill":9 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="arabesque">
         ([ "design":"Elegant embossings subtly accents the surface in an arabesque design.", "skill":22 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="autumn leaf">
         ([ "design":"Dancing embossed autumn leaves scatter along the surface playfully.", "skill":9 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bud">
         ([ "design":"Elaborately-embossed vines adorned with freshly-sprouted buds decorate the surface.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="butterfly">
         ([ "design":"Complex embossings forms an elaborate butterfly across the surface.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="celestial">
         ([ "design":"Artfully embossed lines depict an elaborate celestial design across the surface.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="circle">
         ([ "design":"Complicated and delicately carved celtic circles curve along the surface before tracing back on each other to form seemingly endless mazes.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="claw">
         ([ "design":"An embossed scene of sharp claws ripping through the surface is depicted.", "skill":23 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cloud">
         ([ "design":"Meandering embossed lines forms a swirling cloud design across the surface.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cloudy mountain">
         ([ "design":"A majestic mountain seemingly rises from the surface, circled overhead by a halo of billowing clouds.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="constabulary crest">
         ([ "design":"The surface bears three seashells on a shield, with two spears crossed behind.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="criss-cross">
         ([ "design":"Criss-cross patterns etch a curious design along the surface.", "skill":2 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dahlia">
         ([ "design":"The surface is etched with a delicate swirling pattern of dahlias.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="daisy">
         ([ "design":"Elaborately embossed ivy twists and turns gracefully from one end to another, creating an elegant background for a splattering of five-petaled daisies.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dot">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with liens of miniature dots.", "skill":2 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dragon">
         ([ "design":"An embossed dragon poses dramatically with wings expanded as if in flight, and mouth wide open spraying curls of fire.", "skill":21 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dragonfly">
         ([ "design":"Crisp dragonflies are carefully embossed across the surface.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="firefly">
         ([ "design":"A graceful series of embossed fireflies are scattered about the surface.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fish">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with lines of miniature fish.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fist">
         ([ "design":"The surface has been embossed with a strong fist.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flame">
         ([ "design":"embossed flames dance across the surface with the heart of each flame emboldened by deeply carved lines.", "skill":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fleur-de-lis">
         ([ "design":"Elaborately embossed lines devour the surface in a fleur-de-lis design.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flower">
         ([ "design":"The material has been embossed to depict a myriad of clusters and single, detailed flowers.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="foray">
         ([ "design":"Thinly embossed lines depict a cluster of butterflies and bees in a foray of pollen gathering.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="geometric">
         ([ "design":"Simplistic embossings covers the surface in a geometric design.", "skill":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ghost">
         ([ "design":"Gossamer-like etchings depict spooky ghosts floating along the surface of piece.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="gorath">
         ([ "design":"Miniature embossed goraths in various stages of carrying, collecting, and consuming berries are situated upon the surface.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="heart">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature hearts.", "skill":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hummingbird">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature hummingbirds.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="idol">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature Lutaran idols.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="jack o' lantern">
         ([ "design":"The surface has been embossed with miniature jack o' lanterns.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="knot">
         ([ "design":"Embossed knots and crosses spatter the surface.", "skill":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="knotwork">
         ([ "design":"Delicate embossings form a celtic knotwork across the surface.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="labyrinth">
         ([ "design":"Subtle embossings decorate the surface in an understated labyrinth design.", "skill":24 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="leaf">
         ([ "design":"Richly-embossed leaves are scattered liberally across the surface.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lily">
         ([ "design":"Three elaborately embossed blooms of lilies dangle down along the surface while delicate stems and leaves weave gracefully around the flowers.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mountain">
         ([ "design":"Mountains of all shapes and sizes decorate the surface with elaborately embossed lines.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="orchid">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a delicate swirling pattern of orchids.", "skill":19 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="owl">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature owls.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="petal">
         ([ "design":"The embossed petals of an early morning bloom have been splayed openly upon the surface.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="poppy">
         ([ "design":"Large embossed poppy flowers are scattered liberally across the surface.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pumpkin">
         ([ "design":"Deeply embossed lines portray creepily carved pumpkin faces upon the surface of the piece.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rapier">
         ([ "design":"embossed rapiers cross to make an X on the middle of the surface. Each blade is well detailed from the hilt to the tip.", "skill":11 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1539806321, "jominey", "E", 1539808300, "jominey", "E", 1562787928, "jominey", "X", 1562796692, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1570295063, "jominey", "R", 1573606622, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606629, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606633, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606640, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606651, "sendnoodlez", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rose">
         ([ "design":"embossed rose buds add a splash of decoration to this surface.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="shield">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature shields.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ship">
         ([ "design":"A ship and anchor have been elaborately embossed on the surface of the piece.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skink">
         ([ "design":"Artfully embossed lines depict a lone skink as it crouches upon the surface.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skull">
         ([ "design":"An accurately detailed skull is displayed with finely embossed lines upon the surface of the piece.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skull and crossbone">
         ([ "design":"embossed here are the crossbones and skull favoured by dishonorable types.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="smoke">
         ([ "design":"Delicately embossed wisps of smoke radiate over the surface in circular patterns.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="snake">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature snakes.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spider">
         ([ "design":"The surface boasts a crouching spider depicted with deeply etched lines.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spooky mansion">
         ([ "design":"Super-thin embossed lines fuse together in elaborate depictions of dilapidated mansions, complete with miniature apparitions and otherworldly details.", "skill":22 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="star">
         ([ "design":"Tiny etched stars add a touch of elegance to this piece.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="starburst">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature starbursts.", "skill":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="strawberry">
         ([ "design":"Heart-shaped embossed evergreen leaves travel around this piece to eventually cushion plump strawberries.", "skill":11 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sun-and-moon">
         ([ "design":"Fancily embossed lines form a sun-and-moon motif across the surface of the piece.", "skill":19 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sword">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature swords.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="thorn">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature thorned vines.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="turtle dove">
         ([ "design":"A pair of embossed turtle doves face each other while resting peacefully on a decorative branch.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wave">
         ([ "design":"Richly-embossed waves dominate the surface of the piece.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wheel">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature eight spoked wheels.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="x">
         ([ "design":"The surface is embossed with a line of miniature X's.", "skill":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
