<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="abstract smoking pipe">
         ([ "skill":20, "symbol":"a slender, feminine hand lightly shaded in muted grey and black ink lines. The fingers curl gently inward to grip a stylish black smoking pipe with an almost feather-shaped mouthpiece that lazily trickles a trail of swirling maroon smoke into the background. The bowl of the piece cradles a pale red heart comprised entirely of delicate rose petals that have gradually begun to overflow. A trio of these in various stages of openness and life hang suspended in mid-air, captured in their descent of the body. Overhead, a centrally positioned hazy red sun has been strung with flowing cursive letters that follow its circular border and read 'The Ones Who Got Away'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="anchor">
         ([ "skill":10, "symbol":"an anchor comprised of light blue ink and edged in red. In maritime lore, this symbol represents the success of a seaman upon the ocean. It is said to guarantee stability and security in the physical world, and, by extension, also steadfastness, hope, and trust" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="anchor-special">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"an anchor and bat wings. A rusty brass anchor perches atop the backbone, framed by a myriad of little bat wings" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="asclepius">
         ([ "skill":8, "symbol":"an asclepius wand, a symbol of the medical profession. This serpent-twined staff represents physical healing" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="avoirdupois prayer">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"an ornate bastard sword with tip pointing down bearing an aged maple rosary wrapped around the cross-guard which forms an infinity symbol. Super imposed on either side of the blade are two rearing destriers, one white and the other black. In a circle around the whole thing this prayer is written, 'Oh, great radiant Light that shines upon us, may you illuminate my path and ensure that my sword rings true against the enemies of your divine plan'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="avoirdupois toile">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"complex toile that cascades downward to seamlessly flow into a rearing blue destrier at the center" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="awen">
         ([ "skill":9, "symbol":"the Awen, or rays. It is a glyph of three vertical lines of light converging at the top, and represents spiritual illumination and harmonious balance" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="barb wire">
         ([ "skill":7, "symbol":"a long, twisting section of barbed wire, criss-crossing occasionally" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="barbed heart">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"a heart surrounded in barbed wire, with a depiction of S'Allumer in the center. It is a symbol of religious protection and faith" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bear claw">
         ([ "skill":4, "symbol":"a bear claw. This is a symbol of power, both literal and spiritual, and is a portrayal of the strength of an animal itself and it's ability to draw energy from supernatural realms" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bisclavret">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"a majestic windmill symbolizing the Bisclavret insignia" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bisclavret family">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a single hammock floating on the wind between two massive oak trees. Just before the hammock a pond has a few lily pads floating on the inked surface. A ghost image done in grey overlaps the rest of the picture; the ghostly vision is two wolves in profile with their muzzles tipped up as if howling at a moon" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="black wolf head">
         ([ "skill":8, "symbol":"a black wolf head portrayed howling toward a distant, full moon. Beneath are tattooed the words UNTO ONE KIN, UNTO ALL" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="butterfly">
         ([ "skill":3, "symbol":"a butterfly with outstretched wings. It symbolizes transformation, rebirth, and the beauty of life" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="butterfly in flight">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a medium-sized blue and white variegated butterfly suspended in mid-flight. A thin, gossamer-like trail of silver dust has been intricately inked to flow whimsically behind it. This tattoo symbolizes transformation, rebirth, and the beauty of life" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="button rainbow">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a rainbow comprised entirely of multi-colored buttons in various sizes whimsically strung together. The ends have been capped in white inked clouds heavily striated to give a textured appearance, not unlike that of cloth" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="celestial zodiac">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"white specked dots on a blackened sky. On top of the simple night sky a gold and purple circle surrounds a crescent moon inside a sun. The spikes of the sun point to twelve small zodiacs; a bow, a fish, a sword, a destrier, a chalice, a flying feathered lizard, a coffer, a spider, a scepter, a serpent, a scythe, and a comhach" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="celtic knotwork">
         ([ "skill":10, "symbol":"a series of interlaced patterns with unbroken lines colliding together to form a band of celtic knotwork" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cherry blossoms">
         ([ "skill":2, "symbol":"a string of cherry blossoms. The fragility of the cherry blossom represents the fragility of existence, a brief period of life and implacable movement toward death. It is a symbol of individual and perfect beauty" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="child silhouette">
         ([ "skill":23, "symbol":"a trio of child-sized silhouettes forming a haphazard pillar against the gentle glow of a starlit night sky like some ephemeral tapestry. The youngest figure balances on top of the obscure living ladder while futilely reaching for the brightest star at the center of a densely speckled wayward nebulae. Shining eyes glow with unspoken hope as fingers curl inwards, willing the ardent star into his open palm. The other two accomplices rest on hands and knees with the largest of the group on bottom, both reach out with splayed fingers, fingertips nearly touching the nearby twinkling stars that evasively dance from capture. For those who can connect the dots easily, the tranquil lilliputian stars in the dark velvety sky discreetly read, 'Never Stop Believing'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="concentric target">
         ([ "skill":1, "symbol":"a small target made from a series of concentric rings surrounding the number one" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crescent moon">
         ([ "skill":1, "symbol":"a crescent moon" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crossed swords">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a pair of decorative, diagonally-crossed swords with spiraling silver hilts and ornate hooked guards" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cutlass">
         ([ "skill":10, "symbol":"a vicious-looking pirate cutlass. It is a short, slightly curved blade, with a knucklebow hilt" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dagger-heart">
         ([ "skill":8, "symbol":"a vivid red heart pierced with a dagger. This tattoo essentially represents the heart in great pain, perhaps due to mortal wounding, love betrayed, or even a sacrifice made" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="daisy">
         ([ "skill":1, "symbol":"a simple daisy with elongated pale petals shooting forth from a patterned yellow center" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="decrepit oak">
         ([ "skill":22, "symbol":"a decrepit oak tree rendered starkly with high-contrast shading, its black furrowed bark stretches skyward into stiff, gnarled branches bereft of leaves. From the lower branches hang four weather-beaten dreamcatchers that are composed of pliant willow hoops decorated with intricate spiral webs of beaded thread, wrapped in buff suede strips and adorned with white-banded bronze feathers. The background is immersed in an otherworldly indigo haze out of which ethereal wisps of spectral tendrils burst through via negative space and swirl about the tree before creeping their way between the branches, as if drawn to the mystique of the dream catchers. A flock of ravens circle just above the tree and lend an ominous air to the scene" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="doloreaux filigree">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"stylized vine filigree that cascades downward to seamlessly flow into a large green tower at the center" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="doloreaux prayer">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"two battle axes crossed at the hilt with vines dangling down from the blades. The vines come together under the blades to connect to a large lotus flower in full bloom. In the center of the flower a simple prayer is written, 'As above so below. As within, so without. As the universe, so the soul'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dove">
         ([ "skill":7, "symbol":"a dove with delicate grey plumage. It is a symbol of love, tenderness, peace and tranquility" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dragon">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a large dragon, rearing up on its back legs, wings spread and neck extended high" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="eagle and snake">
         ([ "skill":18, "symbol":"a battle royale. This is a classic design that represents opposing forces locked in combat. An eagle in mid-air with wings fanned out clutches a hissing snake firmly. These two together represent the forces of creation and fertility and the forces of nature which are ever in opposition but always in balance" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="elemental koi fish">
         ([ "skill":18, "symbol":"four koi fish swimming in a swirling pool of sparkling blue water. The first koi fish is bright red with a ball of fire surrounding it. Next is a dark blue koi fish with light blue swirls dancing around it. The third fish is white with black spots and is sitting in a fluff of clouds. The fourth fish is green with jagged boulders floating around it. The fish curve around each other to represent the balance of the elements" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="everchanging tree">
         ([ "skill":21, "symbol":"a center piece of a large, colorful tree. This tree represents the changing of the seasons via its shifting plumage of foliage. The left side of the tree is vibrantly alive and all green, obviously the leaves of summer. These leaves gradually change into bright shades of red and orange. The leaves of autumn are the most colorful, right as they fall into piles at the bottom of the tree. As more leaves fall the branches of the tree are left barren to represent the hibernation of winter. Soon enough bright pink blossoms start to dot the empty branches and eventually turn into a plumage of pink spring flowers" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flame dragon">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a large black dragon, rearing up on its back legs with wings spread and neck extended high. Gouts of orange flames spout from its maw in harmony with its red eyes" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fleshy corset">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a fleshy corset via ink. The back has been morphed into a life-like depiction of the garment. The seam of the corset runs down the spine with the strings of the corset loosened at the top as if coming off" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="floral sun">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a floral sun design. This tattoo uses a scrolled vine as a backdrop, framing and contrasting with the central sun image. The sun itself is also given a floral treatment, it's petals or rays, blown in the wind and turning over to show the yellow color of their underside" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flying bat trio">
         ([ "skill":6, "symbol":"three bats flying in succession through a breeze represented in shaded, wavy lines" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="forearm-sea-serpent">
         ([ "skill":19, "symbol":"a sea serpent winding about a length of flesh decorated in tatters and tears as if it has been through hell and back again. The creature's head rests just under the elbow on the inside of the arm, while the body is possessively coiled around the forearm and a centrally inked, sinisterly-styled claymore. It boasts a long, gleaming silver blade with menacing serrations upon the last quarter and a cross-bar guard that is comprised of sharpened metal ends. The sword is as deadly looking as the beast, and it is kept like a trophy with the head of the animal resting just under the guard, its cold green eyes staring outward in a challenging manner" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="four leaf clover">
         ([ "skill":3, "symbol":"a pair of four-leaf clovers with interlaced stems. Traditionally a symbol of good luck, each leaf represents one of four concepts: Love, Faith, Hope, and Luck" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="full-rigged ship">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"a full-rigged ship. This piece of artistry represents the dangerous accomplishment of sailing upon the sea. The port ship light is red, and the starboard light is green to show the orientation of colors at night by which a sailor can tell if a vessel is moving toward them or sailing away" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="gladiator">
         ([ "skill":20, "symbol":"an extensively muscled and oversized grizzly bear with razor-sharp teeth parted in a roar. His face has been tattooed to depict an ornate death mask and is scrunched with ferocity allowing the majority of his scars to stay hidden from sight. He's clad in a black textured loincloth secured in place by a matching trophy belt adorned with a skull overflowing with crimson blood. His claws are blood-stained, and his rust colored fur has been methodically highlighted with blood-colored ink lines. An intricate series of tribal symbols and swirls radiate outward from the sides of his body" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="gliding eagle">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"an elaborate gliding eagle. Detailed wings are outspread and heavily striated with contrasting black and white ink to suspend the creature in mid-flight. Its regal head and beak are upturned with wise, golden eyes focused skyward in an air of meditation or prayer. The talons are extensively shaded and loosely curled beneath the body of the creature to symbolize self contentment and spiritual protection" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hammer and rod">
         ([ "skill":4, "symbol":"a set hammer striking an orange-hot iron rod on an anvil" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hamsa">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"hamsa, also known as the Hand of Fatima. In dark red ink a hand-shaped symbol with the evil eye on the palm is featured. The hamsa is used to ward off the evil eye and has lotus flowers, koi fish, and celtic knots drawn inside the hand to ensure protection" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="heart locket">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a heavily filigreed heart locket shaded in black and grey ink. The chain of the locket drapes upward in a delicate curl of links, while the center of the heart boasts a single skeleton keyhole" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="heart lyrics">
         ([ "skill":16, "symbol":"an oversized heart in mid-beat with a trail of staffs, brackets, and braces decorated in a myriad of clefs radiating from the center outward in a diagonal fashion. A wavy banner adorns the bottom of the heart ending in ribboned tails with the words 'Bumpbump da bump' inked along the length" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hexagram">
         ([ "skill":7, "symbol":"a hexagram, or six-pointed star. The number six represents balance and beauty, while the upright triangle represents fire, and the upside-down triangle is the symbol for water. Together these markings symbolize the unity of opposites" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="kilana-ribcage-spiderweb">
         ([ "skill":20, "symbol":"an intricate design adorning the ribcage just beneath the breasts. A long, sharp sword points upwardly between the breasts, sitting atop an elaborate flare of spiderweb, with a detailed, realistic black widow spider resting on the pommel. The complex spiderweb fans out from the center of the sword's sharpened blade to curve widely around each breast while the malicious spider dances carefully along its silk. Small dew drops sparsely decorate the span of the spiderweb, glistening in imaginary light." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="kraken">
         ([ "skill":23, "symbol":"a massive hybrid creature. Half skeleton, and half octopus, it stares menacingly into the unknown through large, round orbs which have been darkly shaded in rings along the outer rim and then wind inward into an almost luminescent white. Sizable oblong ears set with gridded holes grace each side of the head, allowing the creature to hear passing ships and other water disturbances. The skull itself is comprised of two sets of six bones situated horizontally against one another, and decorated on the right and left by glowing balls of light. Eight bubbled and bony tentacles lash outward from the beast in a three-dimensional manner, sinking into the skin in random places and almost seeming to disconnect before emerging from a nearby piece of flesh mere inches away and continuing downward into the tips" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="labyrinth">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a labyrinth. An ancient symbol that relates to wholeness, it combines the imagery of squares and lines into a meandering but purposeful path. It represents a journey to our own center and back again, out into the world" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="light protection prayer">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a pair of aged hands holding aloft a white steel longsword with a semi liquefied black smoke dripping off the tip. The smoke morphs into the following protection prayer, 'Light watch over your servant, temper my will in iron and endow me with the mettle to stand against all adversity, for it is my blade that cleaves through the clinging dark in the hearts of men'" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lily">
         ([ "skill":2, "symbol":"a large-leafed lily, spreading petals wide open" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="maul smashing skull">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a maul smashing a skull. Bone fragments have been inked tearing away to fly in all directions" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mining picks">
         ([ "skill":4, "symbol":"two mining picks, crossed" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="nautical skull">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a blackened skull bearing a beard of tentacles. The top half of the skull is aged and cracked with a few barnacles attached to its cragged surface while the bottom half has a thick beard of tapering curled tentacles. Surrounding the skull is an antiqued compass rose complete with cardinal directions" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="octogram">
         ([ "skill":9, "symbol":"an octogram, or eight-pointed star. The number eight represents completeness and the regenerative cycle" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="old salty">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"an aged bear outlined boldly in black ink with two matching eyepatches, hooked hands and peg legs. The name 'Ole Salty' has been scribed in large, blocky letters underneath." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="peace dagger">
         ([ "skill":10, "symbol":"an olive branch tightly wound around the handle of a simple dagger. The olive leaves face the sky while the dagger angles down. This represents the duality of their nature, if you want peace you must be ready for war" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="peacock feather">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"a colorful and vibrant peacock plume. A large, deep blue eye bordered by a crimson 'eyebrow' has been inked in the center of the piece and is framed by feathery and fringed fingers in a slew of rainbow colors. They taper decoratively downward before ending in a gently curved point. It symbolizes creativity, spiritual evaluation, and rebirth" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pentagram">
         ([ "skill":9, "symbol":"a pentagram, or five-pointed star surrounded by a circle. The number five represents the Earth, and the points stand for the four elements and our spirit" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="phelan swirl">
         ([ "skill":7, "symbol":"a rolling, swirling pattern. The Phelan believe that this pattern represents the wild motions of life and the hunt" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="plow">
         ([ "skill":6, "symbol":"a metallic gold plow. This metallic gold plow is shown in profile while being slightly tilted up as if in use" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pomegranate">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"a pomegranate. A vivid red, smooth fruit attached to a small sprig of leaves. It is generally believed to represent righteousness and prosperity" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="religious hand">
         ([ "skill":8, "symbol":"a hand with three fingers raised. It serves as an ancient talismanic way of averting the evil eye and providing protection" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="repense zodiac">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"a downward pointing sword, symbolic of the Repense Zodiac" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1402085897, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402085932, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402085971, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086004, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086054, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086117, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086176, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086216, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086271, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086308, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086333, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086358, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086375, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086384, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086404, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086444, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086456, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086494, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086535, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086570, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086582, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086593, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086666, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086721, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086802, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086845, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086888, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086933, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402086974, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087010, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087047, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087419, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087511, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087557, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087573, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087585, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087595, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087603, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087616, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087626, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087635, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087644, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087654, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087660, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1402087667, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1405353818, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1405356352, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1405356368, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1405356374, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1410284748, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1410284896, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425407575, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425407642, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425407901, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425407965, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408023, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408156, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408210, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408336, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408743, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425408821, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409348, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409408, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409462, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409513, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409651, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409671, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409684, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425409694, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425481192, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425481241, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1425882152, "jominey", "E", 1425882163, "jominey", "E", 1425882194, "jominey", "E", 1425882201, "jominey", "E", 1425882220, "jominey", "E", 1425882278, "jominey", "E", 1425882285, "jominey", "E", 1425882298, "jominey", "E", 1425882357, "jominey", "E", 1425882376, "jominey", "E", 1425882382, "jominey", "E", 1425882395, "jominey", "E", 1425882401, "jominey", "E", 1425882417, "jominey", "E", 1428809021, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1428809077, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1430453905, "jominey", "E", 1444791243, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1445113126, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1445113253, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1445116237, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1445116323, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1445116382, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1445374686, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1445830664, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1445830694, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1446172441, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1446172473, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1446350047, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1446485643, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1446485662, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1448330986, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1451863274, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1451863314, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1451863396, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1459444291, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459444318, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459444387, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445133, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445213, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445273, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445367, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445433, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459445997, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459539069, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459540856, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459541376, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459840757, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459840905, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459840932, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459840944, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459841098, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459841104, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459841119, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459843319, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459843729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459843737, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1459843750, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1460420307, "jominey", "E", 1460420330, "jominey", "E", 1460420350, "jominey", "E", 1460988114, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1460988131, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1460988214, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598787, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598822, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598831, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598846, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598852, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598864, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598917, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461598989, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461599010, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1461600905, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1466476311, "ezralee", "E", 1477607574, "jominey", "E", 1477724896, "pp74", "E", 1501202759, "jominey", "E", 1501263179, "jominey", "E", 1501263265, "jominey", "E", 1501263470, "jominey", "E", 1501263522, "jominey", "E", 1561503779, "sendnoodlez", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rinaldi arabesque">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"a fancy arabesque design that cascades downward to seamlessly flow into three purple scallop shells at the center" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rinaldi garden">
         ([ "skill":9, "symbol":"a simple labyrinthine garden ornately decorated with filigreed patterns. The garden itself consists of four boxes close together to make a bigger box. In the center of the garden is a frog on a seashell holding three smaller shells in its hand" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rosary">
         ([ "skill":16, "symbol":"a rosary, or chaplet. It is a string of beads grouped in five sets of ten, or decades, with a large bead separating each set. The beads culminate in a small medallion with Saint Helloise's picture and then a small string of one bead, three beads and one bead, at the end of which is suspended a small octagram of creation" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rose">
         ([ "skill":10, "symbol":"a rose head, decorated with a cluster of petals, framed by a leaf" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sad panda">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"a sad panda. It has been depicted with a smoothly shaded white face, teardrop-filled dark eyes framed by rich black pools of fur, and faintly drooping round ears" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="scattered stars">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"a smattering of scattered silver stars in various sizes, simplistically whimsical in design" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="scrollwork">
         ([ "skill":9, "symbol":"elaborate scrollwork cascades over and along the body part" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="scrollwork-bisclavret">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"elaborate scrollwork cascades downward to seamlessly flow into a large red windmill at the center" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sea serpent">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a stylized sea serpent. The sinewy creature coils its body in the shape of an S, with barbed points protruding from its snake-like form. Mariners often claim to have sighted such a creature" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="seahorse">
         ([ "skill":17, "symbol":"a golden seahorse. The seahorse is tattooed in profile with shades of gold, pale and dark, giving shimmering depth to the ridges along its body. A symbol of bounty, it stands hauriant, spines emerging from its head and back like a mane. Its tail curls and wraps around the body, anchoring it" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="semper">
         ([ "skill":1, "symbol":"the word 'Semper', meaning forever in Matriloquendi" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="semper vester">
         ([ "skill":3, "symbol":"the words 'Semper Vester', meaning forever yours in Matriloquendi" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="shattered glass">
         ([ "skill":23, "symbol":"a pale blue and silvery white hourglass. The columns of the object have been created in golden textured ink with serpentine bodies wrapped about the length. They climb and descend into a halo and base respectively where they join with heavily detailed dragon heads. The maws of the beasts are parted wide, exhaling curly tendril designs over the entirety of each circular formation to surround it in exotic beauty. The bottom portion of the glass has been noticeably broken and sports jagged edges through which fine golden sand seeps out into small piles. A luxurious golden castle unevenly built upon and from the spilled sand rests to the side, littered with small chunks of blood-stained glass fragments, as if in decoration" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skink">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"a black skink posed in an S-shape on four legs" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skull and crossbone">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"the skull and crossbones. The bones crossed underneath the skull appear to be femurs" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sleeping dragon">
         ([ "skill":20, "symbol":"a long, elegant dragon sleeping upon a background of curling foliage. The dragon has pointed scales running down its lengthy body while its wings are spread outward in a protective blanket around it. The foliage has many curls and twists that end in simple leafs." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="solar sun">
         ([ "skill":12, "symbol":"a solar sun. Composed of an equal armed cross within a circle, it represents the solar calendar and the movements of the sun, marked by the solstices" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spiked vine heart">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"an angled tip which slowly curls into a curvy heart. From the heart expands a black vine with leaves and spikes twisting about" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="symbolic bracelet">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a symbolic bracelet bearing a pattern of curling flames, rolling waves, swirling lines, and a small flower encircled by moss" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tree of life">
         ([ "skill":15, "symbol":"the Tree of Life. It is depicted as a tall pillar of entwined branches, and represents man, the cosmos, and the roots of the underworld" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="triquetra">
         ([ "skill":16, "symbol":"a triquetra. It is a tripartate symbol composed of three interlocked vesica pisces, marking the intersection of three circles" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tuatara">
         ([ "skill":8, "symbol":"a shaded tuatara. This lizard-like creature boasts patterned scales, a long, thick tail, and a spine laced lengthwise with sharp points" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="tulip">
         ([ "skill":5, "symbol":"a full-bodied tulip, its petals beautifully formed" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="uxio-serpent-axe">
         ([ "skill":21, "symbol":"a detailed serpent entwined around the handle of a single-bladed axe. The features of the serpent give the reptile a hungry expression, complemented by the bared fangs" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="vines">
         ([ "skill":11, "symbol":"entwining vines, twisting around each other in an intricate pattern" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="winged key">
         ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a delicate wrought iron key attached to two floofy, heavily-detailed wings" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="winged rapier">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a silver rapier with white wings attached and folded in the front" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wysteria vine">
         ([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a heavy, twining, and decorative vine featuring large elaborate clusters of purple pea-like blossoms which hang downturned in an air of sadness. It serves as a warning of clinging too heavily with the heart, and understanding that love is the fruit, but our obsession with it can be as choking as the vine" ])
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="1425882201" state="Open" user="jominey">
           symbolic bracelet - ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a symbolic bracelet bearing a pattern of curling flames, rolling waves, swirling lines, and a small flower encircled by moss" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1425882285" state="Open" user="jominey">
           sword and rose - ([ "skill":13, "symbol":"a sword and rose. The stylized rose is elegantly formed by delicate petals, and framed with five lush leaves behind. A sword horizontally underlines the vibrant flower" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1425882357" state="Open" user="jominey">
           weddingringadon-custom - ([ "skill":24, "symbol":"a pale silver band bordered in feral brambles strewn with wildflowers. The body itself has been circularly wrapped in the words 'A love that is more than love', emboldened in black outlines, and then streaked with pure white ink for visual enhancement" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1425882401" state="Open" user="jominey">
           weddingringshahir-custom - ([ "skill":24, "symbol":"a simple, fluid white dragon with silver wings outstretched and wrapping about the flesh in a band-like manner. In its great, curved talons a heart dangles downward with the word 'Endless' inked centrally in delicate handwriting" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1459840905" state="Open" user="slurpeeslurp">
           chestfalcon-virendra
([ "skill":14, "symbol":"a dark purple falcon perches nobly here. It faces the left profile with a fiercely stoic expression. The falcon is highly detailed, especially the feathers as they look stunningly life-like. The talons of this lethal predator appear to dig into the flesh and muscle as if holding onto Virendra. Dangling from the beak are gossamer white strands of spider web, torn asunder and fluttering in the wind. " ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1459841104" state="Open" user="slurpeeslurp">
           sab-backdragon
([ "skill":24, "symbol":"a draconic beast. The massive body of the creature is strong and lean, strung with elaborately popping vein details, a ripped abdomen, and a serpentine tail topped with spikes and capped with a sharp, fleshy tip. Thick, bluish spittle drips lazily in globs from its razored teeth, clinging in miniature rivulets to the bottom of its gaping maw. A pair of angry golden eyes stare menacingly forward framed in a series of dangerously spined facial protrusions. Larger horns grace the top of its head to spiral backward above the shoulders and form a noticeably agitated expression while its talon-like feet seemingly press into the flesh and are tautly poised as if ready to spring forward for attack. A sizable pile of glinting gold run through with an elegantly barbed shortsword is snugly coiled within the grasp of the lizards empennage, secured eternally in a protective embrace" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1459843737" state="Open" user="slurpeeslurp">
           drea-antoniasymbol
([ "skill":24, "symbol":"a heavily shaded, iron-like collar with an inked depiction of a noble falcon, wings outstretched, perched atop a trifecta of delicate lavender seashells" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1460420330" state="Open" user="jominey">
           raven-in-flight
([ "skill":21, "symbol":"the silhouette of a raven in flight. The body and initial wing span have been inked in a cut-out snowflake fashion to depict inlaid images of columned arcs, floral crosses and five petaled blooms which radiate outward into white-highlighted feathery pinions. In the background, pallid hues stream vibrantly through a circular, ebon framework to create seraphic rays which shine down luminously upon the creature" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1461598787" state="Open" user="slurpeeslurp">
           dorcas-skull - ([ "skill":24, "symbol":"a large, well-defined nautical skull starting at the center of the throat, and extending from the chin down to the breast bone. The skull has been done in hues of various greys, the cracked and broken surface of the skull giving way to an expanding compass that dominates the upper-half of the throat. The empty sockets of the eyes and missing nose slant down the skin to reveal a rictus grin of a mouth, with sharp fangs that overlay the lower jaw slightly. The bottom of the skull has been decorated with a flowing beard of onyx-black tentacles that seem to be caught in mid writhe as they extend downward over the collarbones and into the top of the chest like mindless, searching fingers" ])
        </Notes:Note>
        <Notes:Note ix="1461598852" state="Open" user="slurpeeslurp">
           dorcas-hands - ([ "skill":24, "symbol":"the dark red hands of fate resting on each side of the neck, above the collarbone and extending upward toward the jaw. The red ink is lined with dark, ebony highlights to show the weathered and aged look of the palm and fingers. Inside each palm is a golden colored eye, the pupils are slit like a feline as they gaze out in blank malevolence. Along the lower portion of the palms is a bright orange and black koi fish, curled around a celtic knotting of stark black lotus flowers with bright gold centers" ])
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
