<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:Books:FabricBook)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1.6"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames/>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="default"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="dyer"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="none"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tailor"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="waterlogged"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             book on 'Sailing for Profit'
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="#traits[0]">"3"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="#traits[1]">"binding"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="#traits[2]">"color"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="#traits[3]">"symbol"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:auto:start:0310">
         "set this.trait:editor to \$brief(actor) [\$date] :: set this.zval to \$obj(this.clone).trait:mastermark :: if \$prop(this.zval) \<\> nil then set this.trait:mastermark to \$prop(this.zval)"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:auto:start:0320">
         "rem GENERAL EXIT"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:auto:start:0330">
         "if this.isplain \<\> nil then set this.ztemp to \$sam(\<add-adj adjective=\\"plain\\" obj=\\"\$this\\" detail=\\"default\\"/\>)"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:auto:start:0340">
         "call bilbo:react:descsub"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:auto:start:0350">
         "set this.isplain to nil :: set this.clone to nil :: set this.ztrait to nil :: set this.zval to nil :: set this.trait:codeobject to nil :: set this.trait:dataobject to nil :: set this.zcode to nil :: set this.zdata to nil :: set this.zcnt to nil :: set this.zmax to nil :: set this.ztemp to nil :: call this.bilbo:react:exitsub"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:+clone">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:adorn">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:alter">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:altersub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:bind">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:bookgotsub">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:build">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:burn">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:carve">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:cobble">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:descsub">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:dye">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:embellish">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:emboss">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:embroider">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:engrave">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:erase">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:exitsub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:forge">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:gotsub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:howsub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:inscribe">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:inscribesub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:kiss">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:listsub">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:ornament">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:point">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:read">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:recite">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:reset">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:stain">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:tailor">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:teachsub">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:react:write">
         \<Generic:DB:UrBookDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bilbo:inherit:solo:renamed">
         \<Generic:DB:CodeDB\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "waterlogged book"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:examine">
         "A waterlogged book of 11 pages."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:look">
         "A waterlogged book."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:material">
         "waterlogged"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         "Sailing for Profit: A Privateer’s Guide\\n\\nBy Captain Gideon F."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         "Dedication:\\nTo my crew, thank you for never mutinying, you scurvy bunch of miscreants, with out you all I would never have sailed anywhere as I can’t raise the anchor alone.\\n\\nTo the many women I have shared my bed with, your thanks was always given to me at the time, now I am thanking you on behalf of my gender for giving me the will to live\\n\\nTo my best friend, Josh, for supporting me and, more importantly, keeping me out of jail."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         "Chapters\\nForeword by K. Hall, First Mate \\nIntroduction\\n1. The Code\\n2. Dress for success\\n3. Gaining and keeping Employment\\n4. The Lingo\\n5. A note on Letters of Marque\\n6. Dealing with Landlubbers\\n7. Superstition. \\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         "Foreword by K. Hall, First Mate \\n\\n\\nIf you're reading this book, you're either interested in becoming a pirate, or you're a lawman with a pirate in custody. If it's the former, then you've taken a step in the right direction, as I've never read a more comprehensive guide to beginners pirating. If it's the latter, remember that S’allumer preached forgiveness, and no one needs that more than a pirate.\\n\\nWith the sailors’ guilds increasingly taking more of a cut of profits and wallowing in incestuous bureaucracy, the path of the pirate is becoming more attractive to an entirely new audience. No longer the violent savages that used to ravage the seas, the modern pirate is one who is simply tired of having to fill in endless forms merely to revisit his deep blue mistress. Such was the life I lived before meeting the author of this book.\\nThough he claims to hate the romanticisation of our chosen profession (though he's never so indignant as to not benefit from the image if there are ladies about), I believe he is one of the reasons for it. A great captain, who knows the life and is not too modest to admit it, he has chosen now to bequeath his years of knowledge into one exciting and somewhat comprehensive title. If you find it useful, encourage your shipmates to purchase their own copy, as each copy sold makes my purse just that little bit heavier.\\n\\nClear skies, and merry sailing.\\n\\nK Hall.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         "Introduction\\n\\nIf you have salt water in your veins, and feel the pull of the ocean, you CAN, with this book, be a successful and wealthy sailor.\\n\\nThis book is most definitely not about life in the navy.  It is about a career for men who have thrown off the shackles of traditional lawful and ethical pursuits for a form of profiteering with its own code of ethics and its own laws.  This is a dangerous book to write in this day and age.  There was a time when our profession was respected and feared, but now it seems to be either reviled and mocked, or worse, romanticised.  In reference to the latter, I have even attended a wedding that had a lovely “pirate theme”, complete with paper pirate hats.  This book is dangerous as it attempts to explain the reality of a profitable sea career, but in all likelihood the City Guard will attempt to remove it from sale and have all copies of it destroyed. As an author, my identity must remain unknown to save me from the hangman’s noose.  But know that my information is accurate and based on real life experiences and not the fanciful imaginations of some ridiculous writer- type.  I feel compelled to share these experiences with you all, in order to educate Triskellian about the truth of piracy.  \\n\\nPirates are not cute.  Pirates are not cuddly.  Discard your overly romanticised notions of slightly dangerous men with stylish hats.  While it is natural that women will flock to you if you pursue this career, you must understand that your career is not noble or romantic.  It is hard, bloody, and ruthless as well as highly profitable.\\n\\nNeither, however, are pirates evil.  We have a very bad name in some places of the world, but we do not deserve all of this bad press.  We have been vilely misrepresented in an attempt by naval merchants and navy officers to label us the enemy and themselves the “good guys”.  We are simply sailors who seek to make a living to support our loving families and bring discounted goods to you, the consumer.  We steal, yes, and stealing is wrong unless you steal from the rich merchants and nobles who treat you common folk as their slaves. Also, we give to the poor, especially if that poor is the ladies of the night, and people who can only afford goods that have fallen off the stern of the merchant ship.\\n\\nAs a Captain, I have oft been asked for advice for those considering this life of crime on the high seas.  So, below is a summary of my wisdom to you on this matter:\\n\\nFirstly, start young.  No sensible captain wants some old landlubber who gets seasick just being on the dock.  Unless you have exceptional skills in fighting and think you can overcome the barrier of your age I suggest this: find ye a wife with wide, child bearing hips and have at least one son and send him to sea when he is under twelve, eight is best.\\n\\nNo women.  Women are bad luck on boats unless they have red hair.  Please see Chapter Seven.\\n\\nFinally, follow the code.  There must be honour amongst the thieves of the sea, and any who behave dishonourably towards his fellow pirate will be dealt with severely.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         "Chapter one – The Code\\nThe Code is a set of Articles generally accepted between pirates, although different captains will make various cha`nges.  Just do what he says.\\n\\nDon’t mutiny, please!\\n Bagsies : If there already appears to be a ship engaged with your intended target, it's considered bad form to try to steal their booty, unless they have finished and you think can now take *their* ship with minimum casualties to your own\\nAny man caught disguising a woman and bringing her on board will be maimed in such a way that it is unlikely to happen again, and the lady in question will be placed under the boatswains \\\\\\"care\\\\\\" to stop the rest fighting over her, which usually just means he gets the lion’s share of \\\\\\"booty\\\\\\"\\nTrade-marked: Don't go copying another captain's jolly roger. Sure, it might get you some easy surrenders (if its say, mine), but it'll also get you on the fast track to the impersonated captain’s cannon’s sights. \\nWho ever falls behind stays behind - At least if we're sailing at a decent speed, ships can't reverse easily, and unless it’s the captain who happens to fall over-board.\\nObey all orders from anyone who outranks you even if they are silly\\nNo bunny jokes - The sea god’s corporeal form is a rabbit, so no bunny jokes if you value your life\\nNo one trusts a teetotaler.\\nNo prey, no pay.  All to be paid a share of loot according to his position.\\nUnguarded flames are only the friends of pirates when they are being used to light cannons. Keep your tobacco covered, else lung cancer won’t be what kills ye.\\n\\n[insert here is a picture of a pig smoking and blowing up the whole ship]\\n\\nDiscipline is your superior’s prerogative, and no man may question that whether at shore or sea (so shut up you bunch of namby pamby peace loving hippies). If another should take issue with the nature of the discipline, he will have the punishment enacted on his own person in place of the guilty party.\\nNo women, gambling or fighting while at sea - but when ashore, do all these to excess\\nLosing a limb in battle is a valid excuse for compensation. Taking your own limb is a valid excuse for marooning."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         "Chapter Two – Dress for Success\\nBandanas are to be worn around the head, and only around the head. Anyone found wearing their bandanas around their necks will likely be cast adrift for being a 'lad'\\nSimilarly, any man found wearing a hat above his station will be dealt with. Protection from the bright rays of the sun is a privilege granted to few, not a right.\\n\\na shirt with horizontal stripes, \\n\\nMost clothing on board a ship is considered optional, and going without a shirt is a excellent way to get a nice blonde coat (which I can assure you, the ladies will love). Pants are the exception, and must always be worn when any other man can see. Cabin quarters are tight enough, lets not make them more uncomfortable.\\n\\nAny pirate worth his salt will tell you shoes are a waste of money. If you go overboard, they'll weigh you down. If you're in the rigging, they slow you down. If the deck is wet, they'll slip. Plus, my topsmen swear that going barefoot is like having an extra pair of hands. But what can you expect from monkeys?\\n\\nHolding your knife in your teeth while attacking another ship is a good way to achieve a flip top head\\n\\nEye patch  If one has been unfortunate enough to loose an eye, please wear a patch, its disgusting not to. A patch is an inexpensive and fashionable alternative to a glass eye, for when the financial compensation for losing one’s eye can be better spent elsewhere (eg, alehouses, whorehouses, gaming houses...)\\\\\\".  \\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         "Chapter 3 – Gaining and Keeping employment\\nIt is important to start young in this profession.  The youngest pirate I have seen was not quite five years of age upon commencement of his piratical career.  The young adapt well to change and have minds like great sea sponges capable of storing all the new knowledge that they require.  I have, however met and even trained men far older than myself and they have gone on to be very successful as well.  It is simply less statistically likely that this will occur.\\n\\nIt is a good idea to be of able mind and body upon commencement of this career, although we are more accepting and inclusive than, for example, the elitist Navy.  As you are likely to loose an eye, an arm, or a leg at some point in your career (at minimum), and one gains significant financial compensation for this loss, then it is best to start with all of these parts in order to gain the most compensation.  Pirates are also more accepting of mental eccentricity as long as it does not involve disobedience towards one’s superiors.  Many a pirate has been known to have some odd rituals that would have you discharged from the Navy lickety-split, such as; biting every and any coin that you see, an inability to say every-day words such as ‘yes’ and ‘no’ (these are most often replaced with “aye-aye’ and ‘nay’, the latter always in the singular, most embarrassing to make that mistake, trust me) the compulsion to say other words such as “Arghhh” a lot (I mean really, what does it even mean?) and replacing one’s missing appendages with spikes and other such impractical objects.\\n\\nWhen approaching a captain to seek employment, it is best to have previously identified the attributes you possess that are most helpful towards the area you wish to work in as a pirate.  For example, if you wish to work as a purser, then telling the captain about your keen eyes is not very smart.  Better to highlight your ability to calculate numbers that always appear to make your Captain-to-be richer.  This ability in a look-out is likely to confuse and worry him.  Never ever tell him you want to be a captain.  That is like saying “Hello, do you sleep deeply? And would you prefer I cut your throat or stab you in the back?”\\n\\nAlso note that it is generally accepted and well known that Boars are terrible people, and therefore no Captain will ever hire you if you are a Boar unless you explain that you will try to be as un-boorish as possible, and accept that you will be at the butt end of a lot of japes.  \\n\\nIn order to keep employment I suggest the following:\\n·\\tDo what the Captain says\\n·\\tDo what any one who out ranks you says\\n·\\tPitch in with the other lads and buy the Captain a girl on his birthday\\n·\\tDon’t mutiny, talk of mutiny, or even think of mutiny\\n·\\tDo not fall in love with a wench, especially if she is a pro.  You will never be able to go to sea with a free heart again, nor will you be happy to stay at home as the dutiful husband.  The call of the ocean will always be there, beckoning you.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page08">
         "Chapter 4 – The Lingo\\nImportant pirate words:\\n\\nBlower - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nBooze - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nBottle, the - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nBroad - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nBroth - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nCall girl  - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nCat - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nChain lightning - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nConcubine - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nCourtesan - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nElixir - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nFallen woman - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nFirewater - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nFloozy - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nFluid - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nGrog – the liquid that brings meaning to a life at sea\\n\\nHarbour – into which one dips his anchor, please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nHard stuff - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nHarlot - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nHooker - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nHostess - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nHustler - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nIntoxicant - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nJoy juice - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nLady (or alternative: Lady of the Night) - please see entry for ‘prostitute’, Note: when used as a title such as Lady Persia, please note that the transaction has already occurred and there may, but not necessarily, be a vast increase in the price one is expected to pay, and if you offer too little when suggesting such an exchange, you may find yourself in the gallows.\\n\\nLoose woman - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nMoonshine - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nPainted woman - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nPickup - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nPoison - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nPro - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nProstitute - One who solicits and accepts payment for sex acts\\n\\nSauce - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nScarlet woman - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nSlut - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nSpirits - please see entry for ‘grog’\\n\\nStreetwalker - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nStrumpet - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nTart - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nTramp - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nTrollop - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nVice – please see entry for ‘prostitute’ and also  ‘grog’\\n\\nWhore - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n\\nWorking girl - please see entry for ‘prostitute’\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page09">
         "Chapter 5 - A note on Letters of Marque \\nMany of you may have heard of a privateer, but may not be aware that he is simply a special breed of pirate.  This title is a wonderful invention of government to make a profit from our labour.  A privateer is a sailor whose ship attacks and plunders other ships and ports.  However, the difference is that the privateer has the Don’s blessing in the form of a piece of paper known as a “Letter of Marque”.  This is a very expensive piece of paper that says that the once pirate, after gaining this piece of paper can attack any ship not of his allegiance, and he avoids any legal repercussions of his actions at home.  There are many obvious advantages to this.  Sadly, no longer reviled and hated now that they live under the title “Privateer”, many sailors forget their humble beginnings as “Pirates” and encourage our mistreatment.\\n\\nThis aside, one can always use this handy little point of law to one’s own advantage.  If you have been captured by the law, claim that your captain has a letter of marque from the city that you are captured in, e.g.\\n\\nCaptured pirate “Release me at once, by order of the Don!”\\nGuard “oh ok, sorry mister you sound important, sorry to have arrested you, Sir.”\\nThe Captain of the Guard, wondering why he employed such a ninny “Shut up stupid.” And to you “ What do you mean by order of the Don?”\\nPirate “you have arrested me whilst I was carrying out the Don’s business, as my Captain works for the Don.  He has a letter of marque.\\nGuard “What’s that then?”\\nYou explain the nature of the document.\\nCaptain of the Guard “Well, we have to see this document.”\\nPirate “Sorry, not possible, and it would be best you release me immediately before you anger the Don.  If I am not on my ship shortly, the task the Don has charged us with will be tardy, and that would not make for a happy Don.  That is if I am right in assuming that your income, job and very lives depend on the whim of the Don, right?”\\nCaptain “Well, then, we had best release you immediately, with our apologies.  Can I escourt you to the dock to meet your ship?\\nPirate “No, but an aureal for paying for the hire of a mount would be appreciated”\\nCaptain “Of course, Sir Privateer.”\\n\\nNaturally, the law is likely to ask to see this letter, but naturally your captain has it secreted somewhere.  After all, the cost for one is extraordinary, as the Don only wants highly successful pirates working for him.  A captain worth his salt is not going to leave his letter lying about in his cabin or on his person for any one to steal (he is surrounded by the thieves of the sea, remember).  This will most likely at least delay your execution and may well prevent it occurring.  Use it well, and do not abuse it.  Best just to not get caught at all.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page10">
         "Chapter 6 - Dealing with Landlubbers\\n\\nEvery pirate needs to dock now and again, and after a few months at sea you're liable to forget what dry ground feels like, let alone what people who live on it are like. Don't be alarmed, dissociating yourself from these former friends is a natural process, and one which helps when pillaging supply ships that are their livelihood. \\nNevertheless, a land-locked pirate is likely to need the services of at least one of the following individuals:\\n\\nProstitutes - After a few months at sea, even the cheapest starts to look pretty attractive. Last time I checked, they held more pirate gold than all the pirates in creation.\\nBar men - Hallowed bringers of the grog, and usually good for a story or two. But be warned, they are quick to anger, and will usually have a weapon of some sort within easy reach. Also usually on good terms with guards, because who needs to drink more than they.\\nBar wenches - Like barmen, only better. Keep it friendly and they'll return the favour, if you know what I mean. Just don't take it too far, their brother's the one behind the bar with an axe.\\nLawmen - If you've encountered one of these, you're in trouble. Don't let him see this book, or you're in more trouble. If you've not been branded as a pirate, then you're an honest sailor down on his luck. If you've been branded, keep out of their way.\\n\\nPriests - for visiting after the prostitutes.\\n\\nNow, the landlubbers ways are not like ours, and as such you may have trouble understanding their strange parlance. So we've put together a glossary of things you might have trouble with.\\nYes - Aye. They agree with you.\\nNo - Ye've not paid me enough yet, ye scallywag. Landlubbers are notoriously greedy, and will often say no (the literal equivalent being \\\\\\"Nay\\\\\\") when in fact what they mean is the price isn't right yet.\\nBoat - Anything that floats, don't take offence when they demean your proud 3-master.\\nWait - Avast. In the case of Lawmen, feel free to ignore this request.\\nParley - I surrender, please don't hurt me.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page11">
         "Chapter 7 - Superstition. \\nDon't be a baby, the sea is simple. All the same, don't let women on your ship unless they have red hair.  Actually, there are a series of rules that one should follow in order to avoid bad luck at sea:\\n·\\tNo women on the ship unless in port, and even then they should only be red haired.  The sea is a jealous mistress\\n·\\tit is lucky to use stolen timbers for the construction of a ship\\n·\\tduring the caulking of a wooden ship a shipwright can claim a ‘caulking kiss’ from any passing girl.  If she refuses him, she has to pay a denar\\n\\nInsert picture of a rabbit shipwright building a ship. There is a queue of girls waiting to kiss him and also a hat full of coins \\n\\n·\\tIt is unlucky to have a dead body aboard ship.  A corpse should be buried at sea as soon after death as possible, but never parallel to the line joining the bow and stern of the ship.  If it is necessary to bring a dead body ashore, it must always be taken off the ship before anyone else disembarks.  \\n·\\tthe naked body of a woman is always a luck-bringer, unless this contradicts with point One\\n·\\tSneezing to the left side while boarding a ship incorrectly - with the left foot first - is bad luck.\\n\\nFollowing these rules you should have a highly successful career as a pirate.\\n\\nAvast ye reading now for tis’ the end.\\n"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:pagecnt">
         "11"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="generic">"true"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "StoryHost Azrael"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1167911764
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167911923, "tonyd", "S", 1167911952, "tonyd", "S", 1169176899, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1169177081, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1169645561, "tonyd", "E", 1172077486, "tunk_bodin", "E", 1306552608, "tonyd", "R", 1457134953, "slurpeeslurp", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spawn:creator">
         (\{ "tonyd", 1167911326 \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:binding">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:binding:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:binding:expert">
         "Bookbinder"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:color">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:color:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:color:expert">
         "Dyer"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:default-skill">
         "Bookbinder"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:default-skillverb">
         "bind"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:desc-version">
         "1"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:design">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:design:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:design:expert">
         "Jeweler"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         "nobody"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:fit">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:fit:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:fit:expert">
         "Tailor"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:inscription">
         "none"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:isare">"is"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:material:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:material:expert">
         "Tailor"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:metal">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:metal:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:metal:expert">
         "Jeweler"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:pagecnt">11</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:shape">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:shape:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:shape:expert">
         "Jeweler"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1169176740
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:stone">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:stone:detail">
         "default"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:stone:expert">
         "Jeweler"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:superbrief">
         "book"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:symbol">"none"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:symbol:detail">
         "pattern"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:symbol:expert">
         "Embosser"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:symboladj">
         "embossed"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:symboltype">
         "embossing"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:textloc">"this"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="writable">"true"</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
