<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="1599)"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="1"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="1599"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="nov"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="november"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="review"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="vol"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] BREAKING NEWS: \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Assassins Attack Queen Mirielle and Others at Feast of Nations! \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 1 \\\& 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Season of Goodwill Announcement \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Grand Processional with Archduke Alonzo \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Guild \\\& Crafter Advertisements \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 6 \\\& 7)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - vol. 1 (Nov, 1599)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] Assassins Attack Queen Mirielle and Others at Feast of Nations!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 17, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Six people were struck by arrows during the Feast of Nations at the Grand Palace, including Queen Mirielle of the Royal Family. The others shot were Duke Willieam, Duke Wilhelm, Emmaline, Arafel, and Ysandra. Ysandra died of her wounds and the others were in critical condition at the time of this publication.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The evening began normally enough, when Archduke Alonzo Fortini welcomed the guests to the Royal Palace, "We have arranged a grand feast for everyone to enjoy this evening! Our most revered guests from afar are awaiting us inside and His Highness and His Queen will arrive shortly." Upon entering the Great Hall, guests were welcomed to seven counters filled with foods. Each counter was set with vanilla apple brandy cake, red cabernet sauvignon, white sauvignon blanc, and braised pheasant. A group of minstrels breaks out into raucous cheering before returning to their upbeat and melodious song.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;After some food and drink were consumed, Archduke Alonzo announced the entrance of the Royal Family. When King Dominic addressed the crowd, he said "I invite you all to remember this evening, for it is a testament to what can be achieved as a whole!" Queen Mirielle also greeted the Great Hall, "It does my heart well to have you all here with us today. Please do have a wonderful evening." \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(continued on next page)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Breaking News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] (continued from page one)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Shortly thereafter, Prince Jacoba joined the feast and handed out six blood red poppies to the Queen, Duke Wilhelm, Duke Willieam, Emmaline, Arafel and Ysandra. Moments later, arrows rained down from the upper balcony on those who had received the poppies. Chaos ensued, with some diving behind tables, some fleeing the palace, and others rushing into the balcony to search for the shooters.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Royal Family were rushed into the antechamber of the Throne Room where they were protected by the Royal Guardsmen, north of the Great Hall. Queen Mirielle was treated for her wound by a medic, while the Royal Guardsmen made sense of the attack with the King and Prince.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Prince said a man in a mask visited the previously two nights, then gave him sweets and the poppies. Prince Jacoba said “He said they would love me. And.. and... I would be a good... king... if they love me." When asked how he decided who to give the poppies to, the Prince said this masked person ordered him to give them to Duke Wilhelm and Duke Willieam, as well as “the pretty lady from Spain” who may have been Ysandra or Duchess Yasmin; then Prince Jacoba was told to choose the other recipients himself. Prince Jacoba said the person promised to show him the secret tunnels of the palace.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Upon inspection, the arrows used for the assassinations had the engraving of a dove with a sprig in its beak. The words ‘Watch Out’ were also engraved on the arrows.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Breaking News (continued)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] Announcing the Season of Goodwill\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 3, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Mikhael Cordyn, on behalf of the Royal Office, heralded the following announcement on the public announcements:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“His most Royal Majesty, King Dominic Ricchezza, hereby declares that the Season of Good Will is upon us!  Beginning on the forthcoming Friday and lasting for approximately one weeks time, King Dominic will so very graciously host a number of events to celebrate this season and foster good will between Nations and people alike.”  Dates and locations were added for The Grand Processional, The Feast of the Nations, and open hours for each consulate’s Royal Advisors.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Grand Processional with Archduke Alonzodas\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 10, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo hosted a Grand Processional, including a tour of Rinascita’s landmarks and concluding with a social gathering at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain. The Archduke was joined by Duke Archibald, Duke Wilhelm, Duchess Yasmin and six of the Roaming Minstrels. Many cityfolk joined in the processional, enjoying song, dance, food and drink along the way. Archduke Alonzo discussed over two centuries of history, and his tour highlighted the most significant locations in Rinascita. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The processional ended at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain, with minstrels singing to the crowd. Cookies, hot chocolate, and lots of other more powerful drinks were enjoyed by those assembled. Duchess Yasmin departed early in the evening, Duke Archibald and Duke Wilhelm left together to discuss something privately, and Archduke Alonzo remained with the crowd. Before concluding the event, Archduke Alonzo mentioned that King Domenic and his wife plan to attend the Feast of Nations in the Royal Palace, later in the week.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Patriarch Mattissimo Performs a Blessing Upon the People\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 16, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Patriarch Mattissimo Lopresti, on behalf of Pope Fontaine Fortini, of the Holy Roman Catholic Church performed a Blessing Upon The People, followed by an audience hour and chance to give confession at the Abbey. The blessing began with a reading and a prayer in Latin, before addressing the congregation. Afterwards, the sacrament of confession was administered for all who were interested. Donations were offered to the Holy Roman Catholic Church by some of the participants.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] Duke Willieam Spars Sir Matteo by Piazza Vecchia Fountain\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 12, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There was a sparring match held at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain to determine the strongest amongst Sir Matteo and Duke Willieam. Sir Matteo fought with a polished steel rapier in his main hand and a shiny steel dagger in his off hand. Duke Willieam fought with a massive darkened steel executioner's axe in his main hand. Although both combatants landed blows, Sir Matteo was quickly knocked out of combat by the Duke. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Following the spar, Duke Willieam suggested a glass of whiskey and Sir Matteo said he should have worn armor. Sir Matteo later commented, "His Grace, Duke Willieam is not only a highly trained and sizable opponent. His power is nearly unmatched and that is saying something with the number of fighters I have ever faced. He is faster than he looks, and a fierce competitor. I hope to continue my training and one day defeat him."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Martial Events
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] November 11, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Wilhem von Karlstadt held general audience hours at the Consulate of the German Kingdom, and attended a consulate dinner. According to Ambassador Trevyn, “There was rahm kohlrabi, cobblers, strudels, snitzels...and plenty of drink."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 12, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Royal Advisor Archduke Pierot du Mensonge discussed matters pertaining to the nation of France at the French Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 13, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Willieam Hughes, Royal Advisor to the Queen Regent of Scotland, discussed matters at the Scottish Consulate. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 14, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duchess Yasmin Flores met with the Spanish Consulate and further discussed issues pertaining to the nation of Spain. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo Fortini, the King’s Own Royal Advisor, was available for discussions pertaining to the Kingdom of Italy.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Archibald Hughes, Royal Advisor to the Queen of England, was available for a meeting and audience hours at the English Consulate. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Advertising with the Rinascita Review can attract new customers and employees to your business. Contact Salvatore Costello to purchase advertising space in next month's paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Daelys is new to town, but she’s eager and ready to weave our hearts as beautifully as her fabrics. Crafters, collectors and fans can all contact Daelys for one of her woven products today. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Guild Advertisements 1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising with the Rinascita Review can attract new customers and employees to your business. Contact Salvatore Costello to purchase advertising space in next month's paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;"Knock knock, whose hair? Your hair that's whose! Book your appointment or drop into the salon today and show it some love with the Haar twins Ava and Arlo! We promise your new hair will be a better advertisement for our business than this one!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Guild Advertisements 2
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Salvatore"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1574109552
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1575383794, "sendnoodlez", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spawn:creator">
         (\{ "jominey", 1573349483 \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] BREAKING NEWS: \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Assassins Attack Queen Mirielle and Others at Feast of Nations! \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 1 \\\& 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Season of Goodwill Announcement \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Grand Processional with Archduke Alonzo \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Guild \\\& Crafter Advertisements \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(p. 6 \\\& 7)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - vol. 1 (Nov, 1599)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] Assassins Attack Queen Mirielle and Others at Feast of Nations!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 17, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Six people were struck by arrows during the Feast of Nations at the Grand Palace, including Queen Mirielle of the Royal Family. The others shot were Duke Willieam, Duke Wilhelm, Emmaline, Arafel, and Ysandra. Ysandra died of her wounds and the others were in critical condition at the time of this publication.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The evening began normally enough, when Archduke Alonzo Fortini welcomed the guests to the Royal Palace, "We have arranged a grand feast for everyone to enjoy this evening! Our most revered guests from afar are awaiting us inside and His Highness and His Queen will arrive shortly." Upon entering the Great Hall, guests were welcomed to seven counters filled with foods. Each counter was set with vanilla apple brandy cake, red cabernet sauvignon, white sauvignon blanc, and braised pheasant. A group of minstrels breaks out into raucous cheering before returning to their upbeat and melodious song.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;After some food and drink were consumed, Archduke Alonzo announced the entrance of the Royal Family. When King Dominic addressed the crowd, he said "I invite you all to remember this evening, for it is a testament to what can be achieved as a whole!" Queen Mirielle also greeted the Great Hall, "It does my heart well to have you all here with us today. Please do have a wonderful evening." \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;(continued on next page)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Breaking News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] (continued from page one)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Shortly thereafter, Prince Jacoba joined the feast and handed out six blood red poppies to the Queen, Duke Wilhelm, Duke Willieam, Emmaline, Arafel and Ysandra. Moments later, arrows rained down from the upper balcony on those who had received the poppies. Chaos ensued, with some diving behind tables, some fleeing the palace, and others rushing into the balcony to search for the shooters.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Royal Family were rushed into the antechamber of the Throne Room where they were protected by the Royal Guardsmen, north of the Great Hall. Queen Mirielle was treated for her wound by a medic, while the Royal Guardsmen made sense of the attack with the King and Prince.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Prince said a man in a mask visited the previously two nights, then gave him sweets and the poppies. Prince Jacoba said “He said they would love me. And.. and... I would be a good... king... if they love me." When asked how he decided who to give the poppies to, the Prince said this masked person ordered him to give them to Duke Wilhelm and Duke Willieam, as well as “the pretty lady from Spain” who may have been Ysandra or Duchess Yasmin; then Prince Jacoba was told to choose the other recipients himself. Prince Jacoba said the person promised to show him the secret tunnels of the palace.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Upon inspection, the arrows used for the assassinations had the engraving of a dove with a sprig in its beak. The words ‘Watch Out’ were also engraved on the arrows.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Breaking News (continued)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] Announcing the Season of Goodwill\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 3, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Mikhael Cordyn, on behalf of the Royal Office, heralded the following announcement on the public announcements:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“His most Royal Majesty, King Dominic Ricchezza, hereby declares that the Season of Good Will is upon us!  Beginning on the forthcoming Friday and lasting for approximately one weeks time, King Dominic will so very graciously host a number of events to celebrate this season and foster good will between Nations and people alike.”  Dates and locations were added for The Grand Processional, The Feast of the Nations, and open hours for each consulate’s Royal Advisors.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Grand Processional with Archduke Alonzodas\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 10, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo hosted a Grand Processional, including a tour of Rinascita’s landmarks and concluding with a social gathering at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain. The Archduke was joined by Duke Archibald, Duke Wilhelm, Duchess Yasmin and six of the Roaming Minstrels. Many cityfolk joined in the processional, enjoying song, dance, food and drink along the way. Archduke Alonzo discussed over two centuries of history, and his tour highlighted the most significant locations in Rinascita. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The processional ended at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain, with minstrels singing to the crowd. Cookies, hot chocolate, and lots of other more powerful drinks were enjoyed by those assembled. Duchess Yasmin departed early in the evening, Duke Archibald and Duke Wilhelm left together to discuss something privately, and Archduke Alonzo remained with the crowd. Before concluding the event, Archduke Alonzo mentioned that King Domenic and his wife plan to attend the Feast of Nations in the Royal Palace, later in the week.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Patriarch Mattissimo Performs a Blessing Upon the People\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 16, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Patriarch Mattissimo Lopresti, on behalf of Pope Fontaine Fortini, of the Holy Roman Catholic Church performed a Blessing Upon The People, followed by an audience hour and chance to give confession at the Abbey. The blessing began with a reading and a prayer in Latin, before addressing the congregation. Afterwards, the sacrament of confession was administered for all who were interested. Donations were offered to the Holy Roman Catholic Church by some of the participants.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] Duke Willieam Spars Sir Matteo by Piazza Vecchia Fountain\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 12, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There was a sparring match held at the Piazza Vecchia Fountain to determine the strongest amongst Sir Matteo and Duke Willieam. Sir Matteo fought with a polished steel rapier in his main hand and a shiny steel dagger in his off hand. Duke Willieam fought with a massive darkened steel executioner's axe in his main hand. Although both combatants landed blows, Sir Matteo was quickly knocked out of combat by the Duke. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Following the spar, Duke Willieam suggested a glass of whiskey and Sir Matteo said he should have worn armor. Sir Matteo later commented, "His Grace, Duke Willieam is not only a highly trained and sizable opponent. His power is nearly unmatched and that is saying something with the number of fighters I have ever faced. He is faster than he looks, and a fierce competitor. I hope to continue my training and one day defeat him."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Martial Events
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] November 11, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Wilhem von Karlstadt held general audience hours at the Consulate of the German Kingdom, and attended a consulate dinner. According to Ambassador Trevyn, “There was rahm kohlrabi, cobblers, strudels, snitzels...and plenty of drink."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 12, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Royal Advisor Archduke Pierot du Mensonge discussed matters pertaining to the nation of France at the French Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 13, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Willieam Hughes, Royal Advisor to the Queen Regent of Scotland, discussed matters at the Scottish Consulate. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 14, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duchess Yasmin Flores met with the Spanish Consulate and further discussed issues pertaining to the nation of Spain. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo Fortini, the King’s Own Royal Advisor, was available for discussions pertaining to the Kingdom of Italy.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke Archibald Hughes, Royal Advisor to the Queen of England, was available for a meeting and audience hours at the English Consulate. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Advertising with the Rinascita Review can attract new customers and employees to your business. Contact Salvatore Costello to purchase advertising space in next month's paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Daelys is new to town, but she’s eager and ready to weave our hearts as beautifully as her fabrics. Crafters, collectors and fans can all contact Daelys for one of her woven products today. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Guild Advertisements 1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising with the Rinascita Review can attract new customers and employees to your business. Contact Salvatore Costello to purchase advertising space in next month's paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;"Knock knock, whose hair? Your hair that's whose! Book your appointment or drop into the salon today and show it some love with the Haar twins Ava and Arlo! We promise your new hair will be a better advertisement for our business than this one!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Guild Advertisements 2
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page08">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page08:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1574109618
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1574078562
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
