<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(IronClaw:Staff:Angelo:Urs:PageBook)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="0.01" density="0.01"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0.2" maxweight="1" verb2="contain" verb3="contains"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="lying" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="tome"/>
            <Base:SName sname="book"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="tomes"/>
            <Base:PName pname="books"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="amethyst"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="healing"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="book:page:count">
             7
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             amethyst leather book on Everything Healing
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             An amethyst leather book on "Everything Healing: A guide book for healers of all kinds". The spine has been embossed with decorative gold filigree framing a golden rose.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             An amethyst leather book on "Everything Healing: A guide book for healers of all kinds."
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="tome:page:count">
             7
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             An amethyst leather book. On the middle portion of the cover is the title of 'Everything Healing: A guide book for healers of all kinds' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Dr. Hush Rose esq'.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="cover" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="cover"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="covers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tome"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             amethyst leather cover
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             An amethyst leather cover. On the middle portion of the cover there is writing.  'Everything Healing: A  guide book for healers of all kinds' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Dr. Hush Rose esq.'
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A amethyst leather cover
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             'Everything Healing: A guide book for healers of all kinds' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Dr. Hush Rose esq.'
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page01" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="two"/>
            <Base:SName sname="content"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="opening"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="table"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Table of Content
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is a table of content that explains what page has what on it.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Page 1: Table of Content<br/><br/> Page 2: Basic healing<br/><br/> Advanced Healing <br/><br/> Ethics <br/><br/> Humourology <br/><br/> Herbal Medicine <br/><br/> Equipment <br/><br/> OOC Help
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page02" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="one"/>
            <Base:SName sname="basic"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="basics"/>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="beginning"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="opening"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Basic healing and first aid
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page will deal with what beginners should know and first-aid techniques.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The very first thing all healers should be able to do is identify injury and disease. The way we do this is two fold, first by assessing the patient by asking questions. Example of assessing the patient is asking questions such as: How bad the pain is on a scale of 1-10. The second way to identify the injury or disease is by the senses. You should smell for blood or unusual odors.  You should listen for labored breathing, wheezing, or oral complaints such as moaning and crying. You should look for bruising, abrasion, irritations, or open wounds. You should feel on and around the wound for further damage. After you have all available information you can make a diagnosis. <br/><br/>   When in stressful situations it is critical to stay calm and to keep others around you calm. It is also important to make sure yourself, the patient, and bystanders are safe.  A good way to accomplish this is to have bystanders 'help' you by having them do small errands for you. The sense of accomplishment will ease the worry of those close to the patient. <br/><br/>   Important first-aid techniques:  <br/><br/> Have a good supply of bandages on you at all times.  This will ensure you are not scrambling to make them in critical situations.  When wrapping a bandage around a body part make sure it is tight enough to stay on but not tight enough to cut off blood flow. A good way to ensure this is to stick two fingers between the bandage and the skin. Your fingers should fit easily. Stopping lose of blood is important, it should be one of the first things you tend to other then breathing and heart beat. Firm pressure on the wound will do the trick.  When  dealing with burns, water is the good solution. Wet bandages on burns will ensure quick healing. It is important to keep the bandage wet so treating it with ointment is the best solution.  If someone has stopped breathing, firm pats on the back or head might help if they are choking.  If someone's heart has stopped the patient is dead.  <br/><br/>   A small painting is shown on this page. It is a collage of pictures surrounding a prone man. The pictures are: a detailed eye, a fuzzy muzzle, a pointy ear, and a outreached hand.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page03" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="two"/>
            <Base:SName sname="surgery"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="surgeries"/>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Advanced healing and surgery
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page will deal with advanced healing and surgery procedures.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Advanced healing has to do with more serious injuries. The kinds of unseen injury include: broken bones, internal bleeding, organ failure, and blood on the brain. To treat broken bones, first you must identify the kind of break: simple fracture, compound fracture, displaced fractures, non-displaced fracture. A simple fracture is a slight crack but does not completely break bone. A compound break is where the bone breaks and pokes through the skin. A displaced fracture is where the bone splits into many parts, and a non-displaced fracture is where the bone completely breaks but doesn't move.  For non-displaced and simple the treatment is support of bone and direct pressure (direct pressure is on the bone itself, vertical pressure is not advised). For compound and displaced fractures surgery is needed to correct the bone placement. Make sure to get splinters and chips out of the wound before correction. <br/><br/> To check for internal bleeding the best way is to feel and look for bloating and discomfort and vomiting blood. Treatment is surgery. <br/><br/> Organ failure and blood on the brain are for surgeons only.  Organ failure is detected by humour testing and assessments, you should look for serious signs before surgery such as septic blood and severe illness. Blood on the brain causes headaches, blurred vision, and personality changes. Only treatment is drilling the skull to relieve pressure. <br/><br/>  Surgery procedures: First sedate patient and numb area. It may be needed to explain what you are going to do if patient is awake. Next plan exactly what you are going to do and follow through accordingly. Lastly, close up any incisions made and bandage. <br/><br/>  A small painting is depicted on this page. Shown is a leg with the bones clearly painted. On the top portion, a simple fracture is display and is labeled according. Lower on the bone is a compound fracture with the bone obviously poking through the skin, it is labeled as such. Lower still a line is painted through the bone and is labeled non-displaced fracture. The lowest part of the bone is merely pieces of what should be one, it is labeled displaced fracture.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page04" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="three"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ethic"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="ethics"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">Ethics</Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This section will explain about ethics of medicine and the Hippocratic oath.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             It is important to realize that as a healer you literally have life in your palms. It is ok to make mistakes but with such an important subject as life, mistakes are lethal.  First point of ethics is to never lie to a patient. It is a fine line to walk, if a patient is critically injured and asks "How am I.", the truth could trigger panic or shock so it is best to be vague. Notice I say vague not lie. Another good point in lying to patients is if dealing with stubborn or difficult people. It may seem easier to just lie when diagnosing or medicating but it can lead to harmful situations, the biggest being lost of trust. If people don't trust you to heal them what good are you as a healer? The last bit I want to discuss about ethics is code of conduct and privacy.  You as a healer can turn no one down nor force people to get healed. The big issue here is even if you hate somebody it is your duty as a healer to see that they are healthy. The only exception is if someone is blacklisted from the infirmary (usually for violence towards healers) then you can refuse to treat them in the infirmary. <br/><br/> Following is the Hippocratic oath: <br/><br/> I swear to fulfill, to the best of my ability and judgment, this covenant: I will respect the hard-won scientific gains of those physicians in whose steps I walk, and gladly share such knowledge as is mine with those who are to follow. I will apply, for the benefit of the sick, all measures [that] are required, avoiding those twin traps of over treatment and therapeutic nihilism. I will remember that there is art to medicine as well as science, and that warmth, sympathy, and understanding may outweigh the surgeon's knife or the chemist's drug. I will not be ashamed to say "I know not", nor will I fail to call in my colleagues when the skills of another are needed for a patient's recovery. I will respect the privacy of my patients, for their problems are not disclosed to me that the world may know. Most especially must I tread with care in matters of life and death. If it is given to me to save a life, all thanks. But it may also be within my power to take a life; this awesome responsibility must be faced with great humbleness and awareness of my own frailty. Above all, I must not play at God. I will remember that I do not treat a fever chart, a cancerous growth, but a sick person, whose illness may affect the their family and economic stability. My responsibility includes these related problems, if I am to care adequately for the sick. I will prevent disease whenever I can, for prevention is preferable to cure. I will remember that I remain a member of society with special obligations to all my fellow people, those sound of mind and body as well as the infirm. If I do not violate this oath, may I enjoy life and art, be respected while I live and remembered with affection thereafter. May I always act so as to preserve the finest traditions of my calling and may I long experience the joy of healing those who seek my help.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page05" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="four"/>
            <Base:SName sname="humour"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="humours"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pages"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Humorology
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This section will deal with all things humorology. Including: definition, testing, and diagnosis.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Humourology is the the study of humours. Humours are the bodily fluids that keep a person healthy and balance. These humours are split into four categories and associate with elements. Blood(air), yellow bile (fire), black bile (earth) , and phlegm (water).  If one is unbalanced, either with excess or depletion, one will be ill or diseased. <br/><br/> The testing of one's humour should be done indoors with these tools: water, rock, and a candle.  In essence you need to test the humor with the element associated with it. To test blood you have the patient hold a candle and watch the smoke.  To test the yellow bile have the patient hold a candle and watch the flame. To test the black bile have the patient hold a rock. To test the phlegm pour water on the patient and watch the way the water falls. <br/><br/>  To diagnose the patient simply apply your finding from the testing. (ooc for testing I suggest having the patient @roll four times, unless you know what is wrong with the patient and want to apply a humour to it. If they roll 1-4 they are low in that humour, 5-8 they are normal in that humour, and 9-12 they are high in the humour).   <br/><br/>  Blood- If the smoke from the candle was invisible then the patient has depleted their blood humour. Oppositely if the smoke from the candle is heavy and swirls around the patient their blood humour is excessive. To treat a low balanced blood humour, have the patient eat red meat, fruity drinks, or have them smoke a cigar at dawn while facing the sun. If the blood humour is excessive have the patient bled. <br/><br/> Yellow bile- If the the flame from the candle is barely seen and doesn't move the yellow bile is depleted. If the flame is huge and dances wildly, the patient has excessive  yellow bile. To treat a low balanced yellow bile have the patient drink a cup of ale, eat a piece of bread, or sleep on their stomach for a week. If the yellow bile is excessive then have the patient drink water, fast for three days, or kneel on grass at dawn facing away from the sun. <br/><br/> Black bile-  If the rock is cold to the touch after five minutes of holding the black bile is low. If the rock is hotter then the skin of the patient after five minutes of holding it the black bile is high.  To treat low black bile have the patient eat a vegetable, drink a cup of saffron tea, or hold dirt in their palm every day at noon for thirty minutes. To treat high black bile have the patient eat a bug, drink mint tea, or sleep on their back for a week. <br/><br/>  Phlegm- If the water travels in a straight line their phlegm is depleted. If the water splits into two rivulets the phlegm is excessive. To treat depleted phlegm have the patient drink three cups of water, sleep an extra hour, or float in the bay every morning for ten minutes. If the phlegm is excessive have the patient smoke a cigar, sleep by the fire, or drink a cup of cinnamon tea. <br/><br/> A miniature painting is depicted in the lower corner.  A square diamond is segmented into four elemental regions: the northern yellow square represents fire and yellow bile, the eastern black square represents earth and black bile, the southern blue square represents water and phlegm, and the western red square represents air and blood. The walls of the square are labelled according to seasonal temperature: the northeast facing wall represents dry, the southeast facing wall represents cold, the southwest facing wall represents wet, and the northwest facing wall represents hot. OOC: http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2b/4_body_fluids.PNG
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page06" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="five"/>
            <Base:SName sname="medicine"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="medicines"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Herbal medicine
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Following is a list of herbs and what they treat.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Essential oils (sold by the herb garden clerk):<br/><br/> ~Bergamot - Abscess, acne, anxiety, boils, bronchitis, carbuncles, cold sores, colds, colic, cystitis, depression, eczema, fevers, flatulence, halitosis, herpes, insect bites, intestinal parasites, nervous tension, oily complexion, psoriasis, respiratory tract infections, sore throat, varicose veins. Add bergamot to a massage blend for indigestion; remember to rub the abdomen in a clockwise direction.<br/><br/> ~Carrot Seed - Accumulation of toxins, amenorrhea, anemia, arthritis, colic, dermatitis, dysmenorrhea, eczema, indigestion, mature skin, psoriasis, rashes, skin irritation. In perfumery carrot can be added to a blend to round out the aroma.<br/><br/> ~Cedarwood - Acne, air purifier, anxiety, arthritis, bronchitis, cellulite, coughs, dandruff, dry skin, fungal infections, immune stimulant, insect repellent, nervous tension, rashes, rheumatism, ulcers. Cedarwood is a good addition to a hair tonic, and gives the aroma a long lasting undertone.<br/><br/> ~Chamomile - Acne, arthritis, boils, burns, chilblains, colic, cuts, dermatitis, dysmenorrhea, earache, eczema, fevers, hair care, headache, indigestion, inflammations, insect bites, insomnia, menopause, migraine, muscular pain, nausea, nervous tension, neuralgia, rheumatism, sprains, stress related complaints, teething pain, toothache, wounds. Chamomile may give a blend for muscle pain a warm fruity note.<br/><br/> ~Cinnamon - Candida, colds, cough, diarrhea, flatulence, infection, insect bites, nervous exhaustion, rheumatism, slow circulation, stomach cramps, stress, toothache. Cinnamon is a good addition to a blend for disinfecting the air.<br/><br/> ~Clary Sage - Acne, amenorrhea, boils, constipation, convulsions, cramps, dandruff, depression, dysmenorrhoea, dyspepsia, excessive perspiration, flatulence, infection, inflamed skin, leucorrhoea, migraine, muscular aches and pains, nervous fatigue, oily skin and hair. Clary sage is a good addition to a bath for many reasons. The antispasmodic actions may help with headaches and migraines. This action along with the emmenagogue property support the reproductive system and may relieve painful menstruation, and the nervine and sedative actions will help you relax after a busy day.<br/><br/> ~Clove - Asthma, chest infections, colic, diarrhea, exhaustion, flu, flatulence, indigestion, insect repellent, muscle pain, nausea, ringworm, scabies, sprains, stale breath, toothache, ulcers, wounds. Clove oil contains analgesic properties which makes it useful for toothaches. The anti-inflammatory action of this oil helps with insect bites and reduces the swelling.<br/><br/> ~Eucalyptus Blue Gum - Asthma, blisters, bronchitis, bruises, burns, candida, catarrh, chills, colds, cough, cystitis, fever, headache, influenza, insect bites, lack of concentration, measles, mental exhaustion, muscular aches and pains, neuralgia, respiratory infection, rheumatism, sinusitis, skin infections, skin ulcers, slow circulation, sore throats, sprains, throat infections, viral infections, wounds. Eucalyptus is often added to inhalations, oils, and ointments for respiratory infections and congestion. The properties that help with these ailments include antispasmodic, expectorant, decongestant, and antiviral.<br/><br/> ~Eucalyptus Lemon - Asthma, athlete's foot, candida, colds, cuts, infections, insect repellent, sore throat, sores, wounds. The fungicidal and antiviral actions of this oil make it effective against infections. It also contains properties that repel insects.<br/><br/> ~Geranium - Acne, anxiety, bruises, burns, cuts, cystitis, depression, dermatitis, diabetes, diarrhea, eczema, fluid retention, hemorrhoids, herpes, insect bites, menopause, neuralgia, ringworm, shingles, sore throats, stabilize emotions, tonsillitis, ulcers, wounds. The antidepressant and emotional stabilizing effects of this oil can be used in many ways. For example, you can add the oil to a bath.<br/><br/> ~Ginger - Arthritis, bronchitis, bruises, chills, colds, colic, congestion, constipation, coughs, cramps, diarrhea, fatigue, fever, flatulence, flu, hangover, headaches, indigestion, loss of appetite, muscular aches and pains, nausea, nervous exhaustion, poor circulation, rheumatism, sinusitis, sore throat, sprains, toothache, travel sickness, varicose veins, vomiting. The stimulant action of this oil makes it useful for fatigue and exhaustion. It may be rubbed on the earlobes, temples, or base of the neck.<br/><br/> ~Grapefruit - Acne, anxiety, cellulite, chills, colds, depression, exhaustion, fatigue, gall bladder, hangovers, headaches, muscle fatigue, nervous exhaustion, obesity, oily hair and skin, poor circulation, stiffness, stress, tones the skin and tissues, water retention. To help with fatigue, stress, or exhaustion this oil may be added to a salve which can be applied to the temples and nape of the neck.<br/><br/> ~Lavender - Acne, allergies, amenorrhea, asthma, athlete's foot, bruises, burns, colic, conjunctivitis, cystitis, dandruff, depression, dermatitis, earache, eczema, flatulence, halitosis, headache, hypertension, indigestion, infection, inflammations, insect bites and stings, insomnia, laryngitis, leucorrhea, migraine, nausea, nervous tension, neuralgia, psoriasis, rashes, rheumatism, scars, slow digestion, sore muscles, sprains, stress, sunburn, teething, toothache, ulcers, wound. Lavender oil is a good addition to most skin care products. For bug bites and burns the oil is generally safe to apply neat to the affected area.<br/><br/> ~Lemongrass - Acne, athletes foot, cellulite, colitis, digestion, excessive sweat, fevers, headaches, infectious disease, insect repellent, muscular pain, nervous exhaustion, poor circulation, scabies, stress.<br/><br/> ~Patchouli - Acne, allergies, burns, constipation, dandruff, depression, dermatitis, dry skin, eczema, edema, indigestion, infections, insect repellent and bites, nervous exhaustion and stress related conditions, oily hair and skin, open pores, uterine tonic, wounds, wrinkles. Patchouli may be added to skin and hair care products.<br/><br/> ~Peppermint - Acne, asthma, bronchitis, cholera, colds, cough, cramps, dermatitis, diarrhea, exhaustion, fainting, fever, flatulence, flu, gaseous indigestion and irritated colon, halitosis, headache, hysteria, indigestion, insect bites, kidney stones and gallstones, mental fatigue, migraine, motion sickness, mouth or gum infections, muscular pain, nausea, nerve pain, nervous disorders, neuralgia, palpitations, poor circulation, sinusitis, toothache, travel sickness, vertigo, vomiting.<br/><br/> ~Rosemary - Acne, amenorrhea, arthritis, asthma, bronchitis, colds, colitis, constipation, coughs, dandruff, dermatitis, diarrhea, dysmenorrhea, eczema, fainting, flatulence, flu, fluid retention, greasy hair, hangovers, headache, hysteria, insect repellent, jaundice, leucorrhea, lice, memory loss, mental fatigue, migraine, muscle aches and pains, nervous disorders, neuralgia, rheumatism, scabies, sinus problems, slow circulation, sore muscles, tonic, varicose veins, whooping cough, wounds. Rosemary oil has many applications. Using the oil in a massage oil may help with nasal congestion and sore muscles.<br/><br/> ~Rosewood - Acne, burns, colds, coughs, damaged skin, depression, fatigue, frigidity, headaches, immune stimulant, impotence, insect bites, lethargy, memory loss, minor cuts and abrasions, muscles and joint pain, nausea, nervous tension, neuralgia, poor circulation, stress, toothaches, vomiting, wrinkles. The mild spicy, floral and sweet smell of this oil can serve as an ideal natural deodorant.<br/><br/> ~Spearmint - Acne, asthma, bronchitis, colds, colic, congested skin, dermatitis, dyspepsia, fatigue, fevers, flatulence, flu, headache, migraine, nausea, nervous strain, sinusitis, stress, vomiting. Spearmint can be used in similar ways as peppermint. When blended together they create a mild slightly sweet mint aroma.<br/><br/> ~Sweet Orange - Asthma, colds, cough, depression, flatulence, hypertension, indigestion, infections, insomnia, muscle aches and pains, slow circulation, stress, tension, wounds. To use this oil for its uplifting properties it may be added to a bath.<br/><br/> ~Tangerine - Acne, congested and oily skin, constipation, dyspepsia, fluid retention, coughs, indigestion, insomnia, intestinal problems, nervous tension, obesity, restlessness, scars, stretch marks.<br/><br/>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page07" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="six"/>
            <Base:SName sname="equipment"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="equipments"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Equipment
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This lists the equipment used and it's function.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Bandage- used for keeping open wounds dry and dirt free.<br/><br/>   scissors- used to cut cloth into bandages and to cut surgical thread.<br/><br/>   sewing needle -used to sew fabric or to pop blisters. <br/><br/>   Stitching needle- used to sew flesh only. <br/><br/>   scalpel-used to make incisions in flesh. <br/><br/>   tweezers- used to pinch small objects. <br/><br/> surgical thread - used to keep wounds closed for faster healing.<br/><br/>  surgical kit- used to hold supplies and equipment.<br/><br/>   tray- used to hold equipment in a safe spot. <br/><br/>   bowl- used to hold discards such as dead flesh ect.<br/><br/>   towel- used for cleansing purposes. <br/><br/>   soap- used for cleansing purposes.<br/><br/>   water- used for cleansing purposes. <br/><br/>   mortar and pestle- used for grinding raw herbs into medicine.<br/><br/>   candle- used for cauterizing. <br/><br/>   dagger- used for cauterizing. <br/><br/>   bonesaw- used for amputation. <br/><br/>   blunt hook- used for probes for dissection and for raising blood vessels <br/><br/>   sharp hook- used to hold and lift small pieces of tissue so that they could be extracted, and to retract the edges of wounds.<br/><br/>   bone forceps- used to extract bone pieces that can't be grasped with fingers. The edges are serrated to help clamp down. <br/><br/>   bone lever- used to move bones and secure them in place. <br/><br/>   spatula probe- used to mix and apply various ointments to patients.<br/><br/>   surgical scissors- used to hold wounds open or blood veins closed. Can also cut through tough tissue.<br/><br/>   trephine- used to drill holes into thick bone such as skulls.<br/><br/> A painting of a a surgical kit filled with each tool is clearly depicted.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seven"/>
            <Base:SName sname="help"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="helps"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">OOC help</Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             OOC commands and tips for healers of all kinds
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             tailor my fabric into bandage (must have fabric, scissors, and needle in hand)= make bandage<br/><br/>examine person's injury = get a list of all injuried body parts.<br/><br/> examine person's body part = examine the wound description <br/><br/> apply my bandage to person's body part= bandage a person's body part <br/><br/> unbandage person(will take off all bandages on person)/unbandage person's body part(will only remove that bandage)=removes the bandages<br/><br/> rub my ointment on person's body part = rub numbing ointment on person.<br/><br/> dip my needle in my ointment jar= cover you needle in numbing ointment. <br/><br/> press my aloe leaf= make aloe gel.<br/><br/> wrap my fruit/herb= make tea bag <br/><br/> harvest/pick plant = to pick a fruit<br/><br/> grind my fruit/herb with my mortar (must have mortar and herb/fruit in hand)= make pastes.<br/><br/> roll my tobacco leaf = make cigar <br/><br/> add my paste to my leaf= make flavored tabaccoo leaf for flavored cigars <br/><br/>twist my cap's jar (must have strange jar in hand of person it is to affect. This will remove all cstat damage but the wounds remain)=use the strange jar<br/><br/>cut person's body part with my scalpel=to make the person bleed <br/><br/> collect blood in my vial =to get a vial full of blood <br/><br/>melt candle into oil (must have candle and oil in hand)= make paraffin
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="spine" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="spine"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="spines"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the spine of a book
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The spine of a book.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:react:sigh-iob">
         X[M] \$delay(2, TRUE, "030f");              
EmitTo( \$actor, "Left this here so the book can react to the actor if the coder chooses it to. In this place write the script you want the actor to see and maybe change the verb it reacts to.");
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1098379422, "tunk_bodin", "E", 1098379475, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1099024133, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1099367282, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1136914169, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1139783619, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1339175826, "meandmine", "K", 1339175920, "meandmine", "E", 1339177407, "meandmine", "K", 1339203487, "meandmine", "K", 1339991862, "meandmine", "K", 1339992004, "meandmine", "E", 1339992058, "meandmine", "K", 1339992065, "meandmine", "E", 1339992066, "meandmine", "E", 1339992067, "meandmine", "E", 1339992067, "meandmine", "E", 1339992068, "meandmine", "E", 1339992076, "meandmine", "E", 1339992194, "meandmine", "K", 1339992294, "meandmine", "E", 1339992317, "meandmine", "E", 1339993544, "meandmine", "K", 1339997635, "meandmine", "K", 1339997693, "meandmine", "K", 1339997729, "meandmine", "K", 1339998907, "meandmine", "K", 1339998913, "meandmine", "E", 1339998941, "meandmine", "K", 1339999010, "meandmine", "K", 1339999144, "meandmine", "K", 1339999167, "meandmine", "E", 1339999184, "meandmine", "K", 1340006676, "meandmine", "K", 1340008780, "meandmine", "K", 1340055892, "meandmine", "K", 1340058087, "meandmine", "K", 1340058258, "meandmine", "K", 1340061126, "meandmine", "K", 1340313445, "meandmine", "K", 1340314032, "rastalabor", "X", 1340314060, "rastalabor", "X", 1340314088, "rastalabor", "X", 1340314325, "meandmine", "K", 1340413256, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
