<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="ezralee">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Effects:UrEffect)"/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-actor">
         X[S] The pit of you stomach drops as a sharp pain throbs in your abdomen.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-audience">
         X[S] \$(person) appears to be in abdominal pain.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:degrees">
         (\{ 0, "cured", 1, "minor", 2, "moderate", 4, "severe", 6, "grave" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:extension">
         \<Effects:Extensions:NonLethalDescribed\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:history">
         (\{ "StoryHost Roo, Wed Sep  4 21:57:14 2019", "StoryHost Roo, Wed Sep  4 22:01:55 2019", "StoryHostess Topsy, Wed Sep  4 22:02:07 2019", "StoryHost Roo, Sun Sep  8 16:09:56 2019", "StoryPuppet Kata, Sun Sep  8 16:12:26 2019", "StoryHostess Topsy, Sun Sep  8 23:25:29 2019", "StoryPuppet Kata, Wed Sep 18 14:14:10 2019", "StoryCoder Roo, Thu Apr 23 11:27:30 2020", "StoryBuilder Kjell, Thu Apr 23 11:31:04 2020", "StoryCoder Roo, Thu Apr 23 14:19:55 2020", "StoryCoder Roo, Thu Apr 23 16:56:31 2020", "StoryCoder Roo, Thu Apr 30 17:26:49 2020", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon May  4 22:27:43 2020", "StoryCoder Roo, Fri May  8 17:10:56 2020", "Diego, Tue Jun  2 23:04:17 2020", "Margrat, Tue Jun  2 23:23:55 2020", "Aldur, Sat Jun  6 14:13:55 2020", "Isabelle, Thu Jun 18 20:27:48 2020", "StoryBuilder Kjell, Wed Jul 22 21:35:55 2020", "Maena, Sun Aug  9 05:50:18 2020", "Lord Trevyn, Sun Aug  9 13:58:53 2020", "Emmaline, Fri Aug 21 23:55:15 2020", "Leliana, Wed Aug 26 14:17:40 2020", "Doctor Beth, Mon Sep  7 13:48:07 2020", "Toddia, Mon Sep 21 00:37:53 2020", "Valeria, Sat Oct 10 08:25:08 2020", "Percival, Tue Jan 19 11:03:38 2021", "Locklan, Wed Mar  3 18:36:01 2021", "Poe, Wed Apr 28 23:38:47 2021", "Toddia, Tue Jun  8 12:51:31 2021", "Elspeth, Wed Jun  9 23:38:34 2021", "Steve, Wed Jun 23 16:06:47 2021", "Richard, Wed Dec 22 15:58:20 2021", "Isabelle, Sun Apr  3 00:17:43 2022", "Ethan, Sun Apr  3 19:21:49 2022", "Isabelle, Sun Apr 10 17:50:38 2022", "Santiago, Thu Dec 15 17:21:07 2022", "Marcellio, Tue Oct 10 02:01:04 2023", "Farmer Sumner, Thu Nov  2 17:55:34 2023", "Giovanni, Fri Nov  3 02:55:46 2023", "Farmer Sumner, Fri Nov  3 19:29:05 2023", "Farmer Sumner, Tue Nov 14 14:23:00 2023", "Dahlia, Mon Nov 20 18:39:56 2023", "Lady Emmaline, Wed Nov 22 21:06:55 2023", "Selene, Sun Dec 17 00:08:18 2023", "Valentin, Mon Dec 25 22:03:51 2023" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:name">
         "diarrhea"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:base">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:severity_effect">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:severity_increase">
         -1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:severity_cap">
         8
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-grave">
         X[S] \{ With a cold shiver and overwhelming terror, you lose the battle against the intense stomach pain as well as your control over your bowels. \| With a sharp and intensely painful rolling sensation in your stomach, you lose control over your bowels. \| Without warning, you are no longer able to maintain control over your bowels. \| With a pained groan, you are left breathless by another wave of intense abdominal pain that results in you losing control of your bowels. \| Unable to fight against it, another wave of intense and painful stomach cramps causes you to lose control of your bowels. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-minor">
         X[S] \{ A pain jabs through your stomach, sending chills down your spine. \| Pain and discomfort rolls through your stomach like a tidal wave. \| A rolling sensation in your stomach overwhelms your senses for a moment. \| Sending a shiver down your spine, abdominal pain sweeps through you before subsiding. \| Sudden abdominal discomfort sweeps through your body before settling once more. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-moderate">
         X[S] \{ An intense wave of stomach pain and discomfort washes through your body, sending icy cold shivers down your spine. \| A rapid and intense rolling in your gut momentarily takes your breath away. \| You find it hard to talk as another wave of stomach pain tears through your body. \| The pit of your stomach feels like it drops as you struggle through another wave of stomach pain and discomfort. \| The intense rolling waves of pain and discomfort tear through your midsection, causing your face to grow pale. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-severe">
         X[S] \{ You double-over in pain as you struggle with the feeling that you might lose control of your bowels. \| A searing pain strikes your abdomen as you feel like you might lose control of your bowels. \| You struggle with a wave of pain and discomfort that feels like it might threaten your control over your bowels. \| With a groaning sound, you clutch your gut and worry that you might need to find a chamber pot very, very soon. \| Your stomach clenches in pain, overwhelming your senses with the feeling that you might lose control of your bowels. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-grave">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ looks dangerously pale and somewhat horrified as they lose control of their bowels. \| grimaces in pain and horror before finally losing control over their bowels. \| gasps in a mix of terror and pain as they lose the fight to control their bowels. \| groans with a pained and panicked sound as their bowels unleash against their will. \| is unable to control their bowels any longer, resulting in an unfortunate turn of events. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-minor">
         X[S] \$(person) \{grows pale for a moment. \|appears to be suffer abdominal pain. \|shivers while growing pale in the face. \|makes a facial expression of discomfort. \|pauses for a moment with a pained expression before regaining composure once more. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-moderate">
         X[S] \$(person) \{grows deathly pale as they struggle with abdominal pain and discomfort. \| shivers and pauses with a look of discomfort on the face. \| pauses and seems to struggle with abdominal pain. \| gasps softly while making a pained, uncomfortable facial expression. \| struggles with a pained look of discomfort upon the face. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-severe">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ clutches their stomach in pain with a slightly panicked expression. \|doubles-over in pain with a groan. \| struggles with a fearful and tense expression as they clutch their stomach in pain. \| groans in pain and appears pale and panicked. \| appears to struggle with a pained and uncomfortable expression. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1589066414, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
