<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="pamphlet"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pamphlets"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ivory"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="vellum"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ivory vellum pamphlet
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             This ivory vellum pamphlet contains five pages of useful information for beginning players. Use the 'read' command to peruse the pages inside ('read pamphlet's first page').
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             An ivory vellum pamphlet full of useful information.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a first page
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             MOVEMENT \& NAVIGATION <sbr/><sbr/> Use directional commands to navigate the game world (north, northeast, east, southeast, south, southwest, west, northwest, up, and down) <sbr/><sbr/> You can also use shorthand versions of these commands for simplicity (n, ne, e, se, s, sw, w, nw, u, and d). <sbr/><sbr/> Use the @map command to navigate Triskellian. <sbr/><sbr/> The @world command will show a map of Calabria.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is writing upon the first page of the pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a second page
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             COMMUNICATION BASICS (IC) <sbr/><sbr/> In-Character (IC) communication consists of actions your character makes to portray thoughts or feelings of that character (not the player behind the character). In Ironclaw Online, there are hundreds of verb and adverb combinations at your fingertips that you can use to express your character. <sbr/><sbr/> Basic Syntax: [verb] [adverb] [preposition] [target] "Evoke."<sbr/> * Verb - Required. A word used to describe an action (ie. speak, smile, wave). A full list of verbs can be found here: http://wp.skotos.net/ironclaw/knowledge-base/verbs/.<sbr/> * Adverb - Option. A word used to modify a verb to show manner, place, or time (ie. happily, sadly, excited). A full list of adverbs can be found here: http://wp.skotos.net/ironclaw/knowledge-base/adverbs/.<sbr/> * Preposition - Optional. Can be one of the follow prepositions: to, at, toward, towards, under, before, over, from, around, by, for. Note that not all prepositions work with all verbs.<sbr/> * Target - Optional. Can be a person (including yourself), a thing, or a detail of a person or a thing. <sbr/><sbr/> Examples<sbr/> * huff angrily<sbr/> * laugh amusedly at bob<sbr/> * rub my faced stressedly "I will never get this job done in time."<sbr/> * clasp bob's hand with my hand "Nice to meet you!" <sbr/><sbr/> Remember that Ironclaw Online is considered a PG-13 game so keep this in mind when interacting with others. <sbr/><sbr/>
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is writing upon the second page of the pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a third page
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             COMMUNICATION BASICS (OOC) <sbr/><sbr/> Sometimes it is necessary to use out-of-character (OOC) communication using out-of-character commands. <sbr/><sbr/> * @ooc - this command is visible to everyone in the room and should only be used as needed (such as setting up a scene).<sbr/> * @msg [person] - this command is only visible to the person you are targeting. Again, this command should be used sparingly as it can be disruptive to roleplay.<sbr/> * @chat - this is a global command visible to all players who have the @chat chatline enabled. <sbr/><sbr/> You should never, under any circumstance, share in-character information via out-of-character channels.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is writing upon the third page of the pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a fourth page
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             OBJECT INTERACTION \& MANIPULATION <sbr/><sbr/> All objects, people, details can be targeted and interacted with in some form. You can use the "look" and "examine" commands to get descriptions of objects and these descriptions will also give you an idea of what details you can also interact with. <sbr/><sbr/> Example:<sbr/> \> examine Melanee<sbr/> You examine a brochure vendor named Melanee.<sbr/> This brochure vendor is a short waifish cat, with short, wild patchwork fur, and long thick reddish-blonde hair, worn crimped. Innocent soft blue eyes are set above a dainty nose and roseate lips. Short slightly dirty nails, on slender hands, and bony feet are also visible. You also note her multi-colored ears. She has a varietal stash of brochures in her bag. She is wearing a pair of pale brown tweed pants, a royal blue cotton blouse, a royal blue cotton sack and a pair of pale brown tweed slippers. <sbr/><sbr/> \> examine Melanee's hands<sbr/> You examine a brochure vendor named Melanee's slender hands.<sbr/> A pair of slender hands. <sbr/><sbr/> While most people and objects can be interacted with, you may have to request proximity depending on what you are trying to do (in other words, will require you to be CLOSE TO that person or object). When performing an action that requires you to be in proximity to a person, they will need to CONSENT to the action. The consent system exists to protect players against unwanted in-character actions. <sbr/><sbr/> Consent Commands:<sbr/> * @consent allow [person] - this will allow [person] to move in your proximity any time they want<sbr/> * @consent deny [person] - this will deny [person] to move in your proximity any time they want<sbr/> * @consent allow all - this will allow EVERYONE to move in your proximity any time they want<sbr/> * @consent deny all - this will deny EVERYONE to move in your proximity any time they want<sbr/> * @allow [person] - this will allow [person] to move in your proximity THIS TIME ONLY<sbr/> * @deny [person] - this will deny [person] to move in your proximity THIS TIME ONLY<sbr/> * @consent list - will display all consent rules you have defined so far<sbr/> * @consent - command help files <sbr/><sbr/> Inanimate objects will not require consent to move in proximity with them. Examples include benches, rocks, walls. Sometimes there will be multiple of the same object and you will need to specify which one you wish to interact with (ie. sit on 3rd chair). To interact with an object in your inventory, you can use the MY keyword (ie. read my 4th scroll). <sbr/><sbr/> You can consume food and drinks using verbs such as eat, drink, nibble, sip, gobble, and guzzle. Smell and taste will also give you more information about consumables. <sbr/><sbr/> Some objects can be picked up, put down, or given to someone else. Examples of these commands include:<sbr/> * take [object] - object will appear in your inventory. Other verbs that move an object to your inventory include catch, retrieve, snatch.<sbr/> * drop [object] - object will be moved from your inventory into your environment. Other verbs that move an object from your inventory into your environment include put, toss, throw, discard.<sbr/> * take [object] from [container] - take an object from a container. The container must be in your inventory or in your environment to work (in other words, you cannot take an item from someone else's bag).<sbr/> * drop [object] into [container] - put an object in a container. There are no restrictions when placing things in containers meaning you can drop an object in someone else's bag as long as you have consent from that person.<sbr/> * give [object] to [person] - offer and object to someone. They will need to ACCEPT the object from you.<sbr/> * accept [person] - accept the thing that [person] is offering you. <sbr/><sbr/> Looking/examining a container will show the contents of that container. Most containers can be opened and closed (a closed container will hide the contents of what is inside). Additionally, some containers can be locked which require a key to open. <sbr/><sbr/> * close [container] - close the container<sbr/> * open [container] - open the container<sbr/> * lock [container] with my key - lock the container. The key has to be in your inventory.<sbr/> * unlock [container] with my key - unlock the container. The key has to be in your inventory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is writing upon the fourth page of the pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a fifth page
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             NPCs <sbr/><sbr/> There are many NPCs (non-player characters) in Ironclaw Online, most of which are merchants who sell goods. <sbr/><sbr/> * ask [npc] - get a list of items the npc sells.<sbr/> * ask [npc] for [item] - buy an item from the npc.<sbr/> * ask [npc] for [X] [item] - buy X number of item from npc. <sbr/><sbr/> Merchant characters play an important role in Triskellian as they can obtain better quality goods from merchants for discounted prices. This is especially important for crafter characters as the quality of their wares is based on the types of materials that they use. <sbr/><sbr/> Other NPCs include guards, beggars, couriers, and skinks.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is writing upon the fifth page of the pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:react-pre:read-what">
         X[M] \$page = NRefDetail(\$what[0]);

if(\$page == "default") \{
    EmitTo(\$actor, "[OOC: You would have better luck reading one of the pages. Try \\"read my pamphlet's first page\\"]");
    return FALSE;
\}

EmitTo(\$actor, UnSAM(Get(\$this."base:urparent", "details:" + \$page + ":description:examine")));

return FALSE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1537229581, "jominey", "E", 1537229584, "jominey", "E", 1537229684, "jominey", "E", 1537229735, "jominey", "E", 1537229753, "jominey", "E", 1537229789, "jominey", "E", 1537229846, "jominey", "E", 1537229864, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
