<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="anchor">
         ([ "design":"An anchor comprised of COLOR threading adorns the surface. In maritime lore, this symbol represents the success of a seaman upon the ocean. It is said to guarantee stability and security in the physical world, and, by extension, also steadfastness, hope, and trust", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="apple blossom">
         ([ "design":"Apple blossoms delicately strung in COLOR display their many petals, with each flower spaced strategically throughout the garment.", "skill":9 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="arabesque">
         ([ "design":"Elegant COLOR threading subtly accents the front of the garment in an arabesque design.", "skill":22 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="autumn leaf">
         ([ "design":"Dancing COLOR autumn leaves scatter along the seams of the garment playfully.", "skill":9 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="bud">
         ([ "design":"Elaborately-stitched vines adorned with freshly-sprouted COLOR buds decorate the hem of this garment.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="butterfly">
         ([ "design":"Complex COLOR needlework forms an elaborate butterfly across the back of the garment.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="celestial">
         ([ "design":"Sparkling COLOR threads depict an elaborate celestial design across the back of the garment.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="circle">
         ([ "design":"Complicated and delicate COLOR celtic circles curve along the seams of the garment before tracing back on each other to form seemingly endless mazes.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="claw">
         ([ "design":"A sewn scene of sharp COLOR claws ripping through the fabric is depicted.", "skill":23 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cloud">
         ([ "design":"Meandering COLOR threads forms a swirling cloud design across the side of the garment.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cloudy mountain">
         ([ "design":"A majestic COLOR mountain seemingly rises from the front of the fabric, circled overhead by a halo of billowing clouds.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="constabulary crest">
         ([ "design":"The left side of this garment bears three seashells on a COLOR shield, with two spears crossed behind.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="criss-cross">
         ([ "design":"Criss-cross COLOR patterns etch a curious design along the length of the garment.", "skill":2 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dahlia">
         ([ "design":"The front of this garment is embroidered with a delicate swirling pattern of COLOR dahlias.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="daisy">
         ([ "design":"Elaborate ivy twists and turns gracefully from one end to anoother, creating an elegant background for a splattering of five-petaled COLOR daisies.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dot">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR dots.", "skill":2 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dragon">
         ([ "design":"A COLOR dragon poses dramatically with wings expanded as if in flight, and mouth wide open spraying red and orange curls of fire.", "skill":21 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="dragonfly">
         ([ "design":"Crisp COLOR dragonflies are carefully embroidered across the front of the garment.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="firefly">
         ([ "design":"A graceful series of COLOR fireflies are scattered about the garment.", "skill":18 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fish">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR fish.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fist">
         ([ "design":"The fabric has been embroidered in COLOR thread with a strong fist.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flame">
         ([ "design":"Embroidered COLOR flames dance across the seams of the garment with the heart of each flame emboldened by rich yellow stitching.", "skill":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="fleur-de-lis">
         ([ "design":"Elaborate COLOR threading devours the garment in a fleur-de-lis design.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="flower">
         ([ "design":"The material has been embroidered in COLOR thread to depict a myriad of clusters and single, detailed flowers.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="foray">
         ([ "design":"Some COLOR embroidery depicts a cluster of butterflies and bees in a foray of pollen gathering.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="geometric">
         ([ "design":"Simplistic COLOR threading covers the front of the garment in a geometric design.", "skill":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ghost">
         ([ "design":"Gossamer-like COLOR threads depict spooky ghosts floating along the surface of the fabric.", "skill":17 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="gorath">
         ([ "design":"Miniature goraths in various stages of carrying, collecting, and consuming COLOR berries are situated upon the body of the garment.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="heart">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR hearts.", "skill":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="hummingbird">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR hummingbirds.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="idol">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR Lutaran idols.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="jack o' lantern">
         ([ "design":"The fabric has been embroidered in COLOR thread with miniature jack o' lanterns.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="knot">
         ([ "design":"Knots and crosses spatter the material in COLOR thread.", "skill":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="knotwork">
         ([ "design":"Delicate COLOR needlework forms a celtic knotwork across the side of the garment.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="labyrinth">
         ([ "design":"Subtle COLOR needlework decorates the body of this garment in an understated labyrinth design.", "skill":24 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="leaf">
         ([ "design":"Richly-embroidered COLOR leaves are scattered liberally across the back of this garment.", "skill":13 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lily">
         ([ "design":"Three elaborate blooms of COLOR lilies dangle down the fabric while delicate stems and leaves weave gracefully around the flowers.", "skill":16 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="mountain">
         ([ "design":"Mountains of all shapes and sizes decorate the surface of this garment in elaborate COLOR threading.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="orchid">
         ([ "design":"The front of this garment is embroidered with a delicate swirling pattern of COLOR orchids.", "skill":19 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="owl">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR owls.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="petal">
         ([ "design":"The petals of an early morning COLOR bloom have been splayed openly upon the fabric.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="poppy">
         ([ "design":"Large COLOR poppy flowers are scattered liberally across the garment.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="pumpkin">
         ([ "design":"Shimmering COLOR thread portrays creepily carved pumpkin faces upon the surface of the fabric.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rapier">
         ([ "design":"Glinting COLOR rapiers cross to make an X on the middle of the garment.  Each blade is well detailed from the hilt to the tip.", "skill":11 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1539806321, "jominey", "E", 1570294550, "jominey", "R", 1573606950, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606955, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606959, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606964, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1573606972, "sendnoodlez", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="rose">
         ([ "design":"Ribbon worked COLOR rose buds add a splash of decoration to this garment.", "skill":12 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="shield">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR shields.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="ship">
         ([ "design":"A ship and anchor have been elaborately embroidered in COLOR thread on the material.", "skill":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skink">
         ([ "design":"A lone COLOR skink crouches upon the backside of the garment.", "skill":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skull">
         ([ "design":"An accurately detailed skull is displayed in COLOR thread on the backside of the garment.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skull and crossbone">
         ([ "design":"Embroidered here in COLOR threads are the crossbones and skull favoured by dishonorable types.", "skill":15 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="smoke">
         ([ "design":"Delicate wisps of threaded COLOR smoke radiate over the garment in circular patterns.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="snake">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR snakes.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spider">
         ([ "design":"The fabric boasts a crouching spider depicted in COLOR thread.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spooky mansion">
         ([ "design":"Super-thin COLOR threads fuse together in elaborate depictions of dilapidated mansions, complete with miniature apparitions and otherworldly details.", "skill":22 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="star">
         ([ "design":"Tiny ribbon-worked COLOR stars add a touch of elegance to this garment.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="starburst">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR starbursts.", "skill":20 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="strawberry">
         ([ "design":"Heart-shaped evergreen leaves travel around this garment to eventually cushion plump, COLOR strawberries.", "skill":11 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sun-and-moon">
         ([ "design":"Fancy COLOR threads form a sun-and-moon motif across the back of the garment.", "skill":19 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sword">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR swords.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="thorn">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR thorned vines.", "skill":14 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="turtle dove">
         ([ "design":"A pair of COLOR turtle doves face each other while resting peacefully on a decorative branch.", "skill":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wave">
         ([ "design":"Ribbon worked COLOR waves dominate the body of the garment.", "skill":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="wheel">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR eight spoked wheels.", "skill":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="x">
         ([ "design":"The seams of this garment are lined with miniature COLOR X's.", "skill":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
