<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:abc:how-to">
         X[M] /*
 * Similar to a State Lottery
 *
 * OBJECTS required:
 * An NPC to sell and take Tickets (Ironclaw:NPCs:Lottery:Vendor),
 * Tickets to be sold (Ironclaw:Props:Systems:Lottery:Ticket),
 * Chalkboard announcing winners (Ironclaw:Props:Systems:Lottery:Chalkboard).
 *
 * About NPC:
 * NPC will offer Tickets for 1 denar each,
 * NPC will take winning tickets which results in a deposit to the character's bank account,
 * NPC will explain the rules of the game, if asked (due to length, this will be done via whisper if possible),
 * NPC will only be available during daylight hours (Offices of Prime, Tierce, Sext, \& None),
 * NPC will not be present on Dimache (Holy Day).
 *
 * About TICKETS:
 * Tickets are sold for 1 denar each,
 * Multiple tickets can be purchased by any character,
 * Tickets will be spawned with random numbers,
 * There will be 3 numbers per ticket (future results may dictate a change),
 * Numbers will range from 01-25 without duplications on same ticket (future results may dictate a change),
 * Tickets will be valid for the next drawing only,
 * Tickets will decay (be auto-slain) 1 month after related drawing,
 * Tickets must be turned in for the prize within 30 days of drawing.
 * 
 * About CHALKBOARD:
 * Chalkboard will be BB'd as guarded by Ticket NPC to prevent tampering,
 * Chalkboard will display winners by name for the last 5 drawings,
 * Players automatically agree to their name being shown by participating (they cannot opt-out),
 * Chalkboard will show the current Prize value at the top; updated every change of Office (3 hours?),
 * Chalkboard will be similar to an A-frame sign,
 * Chalkboard will only be available during daylight hours (Offices of Prime, Tierce, Sext, \& None),
 * Chalkboard will not be present on Dimache (Holy Day),
 * Chalkboard display will have a clear \& concise output such as:
 * +-----------------------------+
 * \|  PRIZE: 1,000 denar!        \|
 * \|_____________________________\|
 * \|                             \|
 * \| PAST 5 WEEKS WINNERS:       \|
 * \|(tie) Death    - 150 denari  \|
 * \|(tie) Spot     - 150 denari  \|
 * \|      Sirazad  - 1000 denari \|
 * \|      Azrael   - 500 denari  \|
 * \|      Nyx      - 850 denari  \|
 * \|      Roo      - 50 denari   \|
 * \|                             \|
 * +-----------------------------+
 *
 * About PRIZE/WINNING:
 * Drawing is held every week on Samedi during the Office of Lucernarim,
 * Winners need not be present at time of drawing to win,
 * Winners do need to present ticket to NPC to receive prize,
 * Just as in RL, lost tickets are lost money (no exceptions sans system bugs),
 * Multiple winners will split prize and all names will be shown on winner's list,
 * Prize is equal to 90% of all denari spent on tickets,
 * 10% of all denari spent on tickets will go the Rinaldi House kitty (tokens?) as IG sponsors of Lottery (doesn't -have- to happen),
 * Any week where the prize is not won, it rolls over to the following week,
 * Prize never to exceed 2,500 denari,
 * If prize exceeds 2,500 denari, excess money will go to Rinaldi House kitty (tokens?),
 * Drawing winner(s) will be announced across the city via Town Crier emit immediately following drawing,
 * Optional: A message will be displayed to winner (or next time they log in).
 *
 * RELIGIOUS CONCESSIONS:
 * NPC, chalkboard \& game will not be run during Dimache (Holy Day),
 * Whether this is seen as Gambling and/or a sin, will be up to the Church.
 *
 * SCRIPTS:
 *
 * In Tickets:
 * merry:act:start which sets the appropriate random numbers,
 * look/examine descriptions which show the chosen numbers,
 * writing description that shows the numbers and the rules of the game,
 *
 * In NPC:
 * ability to sell tickets for 1 denar,
 * ability to respond appropriately if asked about lottery, rules, etc,
 * ability to accept tickets, determine if it is a winner, and place denari in player's account,
 * script to travel to-and-fro (teleport) public places to backstage area based on daylight hours.
 *
 *
 * In Chalkboard:
 * The chalkboard will run the actual game,
 * ability to move (teleport) from public area to backstage based on daylight hours,
 * timed script to determine winners every Samedi during the Office of Lucernarim,
 * timed script to update prize amount (90% of total denari not to exceed 2500),
 * writing description that can find the prize amount and past winners for 5 weeks
 * timed script to transfer excess denari and 10% of total to Rinaldi House kitty (tokens?),
 * ability to send Town Crier emit throughout city,
 * ability to send a message directly to current winner(s).
 * 
 */
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1309054259, "tunk_bodin", "P", 1309054329, "tunk_bodin", "P", 1309055863, "tunk_bodin", "P" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
