<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="tunk_bodin">
  <Help:Node title="Clothing">
    <Log:Description>
       <br/>Title: Clothing<br/> Important Commands: remove, wear, wield<br/> Syntax: "wear tunic", "wear shoes", "remove cap"<br/><br/> {? equal | $(theatre.id) | IC | When you arrive in Triskellian (IronClaw Online's starting city) you will find yourself clothed in basic attire.|When you begin playing in a Skotos Theatre or game you will find yourself dressed in standard clothes for the period.} However, much more grand attire is possible.<br/> {? equal | $(theatre.id) | IC | To get better clothing you will want to seek out the tailors or seamstress. Seamstress and tailor characters can usually be found who will dye and tailor garments. | In many of Skotos' games and Theatres tailors and seamstresses will be available to help you improve your clothing. Wander around and ask other characters if these CNPCs are present.}<br/> Clothing is worn in layers, just as it is in the real world. A gown goes over under garments. A cloak goes over a gown. You wear and remove clothing according to this logic. Clothing covers specific parts of the body, and, therefore, it is impossible to see any body part or clothing that is covered with another garment.<br/> Weapons can also be found in many games. They are equipped with the $(udat.chatchar)WIELD command.<br/><br/> See Also: <helplink to="containers"/>, <helplink to="manipulation"/>, <helplink to="seamstress"/>, <helplink to="tailor"/><br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="clothes"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="clothing"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365935, "-", "SYNC", 1136676373, "rhenn", "E", 1137619428, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1137619724, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1137630571, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1295119541, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1312328232, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1509728163, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
