<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="balkaar">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Effects:UrEffect)"/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-actor">
         X[S] You carefully work on the carving of the pumpkin, getting closer and closer to the realisation of the imagined picture. A deeper cut causes the juices of the fresh pumpkin to freckle your skin with a light spray of sugary water.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:debug">0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:default_dosage">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:degrees">
         (\{ 6, "bats", 10, "figures", 15, "vampires" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:extension">
         \<Effects:Extensions:NonLethalDescribed\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:history">
         (\{ "StoryPlotter Sirazad, Thu Oct 29 06:12:05 2009", "StoryPlotter Sirazad, Thu Oct 29 11:05:18 2009", "StoryPlotter Sirazad, Thu Oct 29 11:25:24 2009" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:name">
         "halloween"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:base">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:severity_effect">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:severity_cap">
         15
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-bats">
         X[S] \{A friendly bat quietly hangs from the ceiling. \| Taking a peek upward your gaze stumbles into a thick group of bats hanging from any place they can. For a brief moment you wonder if they are gazing at you too.\| A bat parts from a group of bats that occupy the upper regions and makes a sudden dash at you. It alters its path in the last second. \|Did something just cling to your hair?\| Wherever you turn glowing red eyes stare at you from shadowy corners.\| A \{friendly\|curious viscous\|bloodthirsty\|nosy\|lost\} bat \{energetically\|desperately\|hastily\|calculating\|narrowly\|rapidly\} flutters its wings. \| \{Glowing\|Vibrant\|Opalescent\|Fluorescent\|Malicious\} eyes stare at you from the depth of the shadows that surround you.\| Shadows get thicker around you, slowly making their ways through your nostrils and your mouth, lingering with their sticky heaviness in your lungs.\| Something \{rigid and cold\|slimy\|icy\|moist\|cool\|frozen\|scorching and dry\|metallic and rugged\} \{darts against\|touches\|brushes\|kisses\} \{your cheek\|the backs of your hands\|your nape\|your temple\}. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-chance">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-figures">
         X[S] \{You catch a glimpse of a figure moving in the shadows, but by the time you glance there the darkness is silent and lifeless.\|A \{ghostly\|skeletal\|misty\|fog-shrouded\|shapeless\} figure walks past your peripheral vision.\|An echo of soft laughter drops on the ground, its \{tuneful\|distant\|musical\|titillating\|feminine\|soft\|taunting\|teasing\|coquetting\|unearthly\|fearful\|nervous\} ripples die away leaving room for a moment of \{eerie\|uneasy\|tension-filled\|tense\|anticipating\|longing\|empty\|haunted\|ghastly\} silence.\|Whispering voices surround you, dragging you within themselves into their careless, swirling dance. Despite their taunting, you find no mouth that utters them.\|Suddenly you face a pale face staring right at you. Pupil-less eyes blankly return your fixated attention, while thin, cruel lips curl into a translucent smile. You blink once and the image is gone.\|A \{harsh\|hard to describe\|pain-filled\|haunted\|tortured\|heavy\|shrill\|false\|playful\|broken\|frightened\|horrified\} scream invades your mind clinging tö your thoughts before fading into but a memory.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-vampires">
         X[S] \{A woman of classical beauty emerges from the dark corners, she idly smiles at you.\|A dark-clad woman walks past you, accidentally touching her shoulder against you. She mouths an apology with a subtle smile barely revealing the tips of her sharp fangs.\|You catch a sniff of distinguished perfume, sweet and laden with memories with a distant undertone of blood.\|\{A quiet, titillating\|A deep, sated\| A soft, yet hungry\|A swooning, feminine\} \{chuckle\|laughter\} \{sneaks\|crawls\|emerges\|elevates\} from the ground to demand your attention.\|Are you imagining things, or did that woman's attention not leave your neck for a single moment? Where is she again?\|For \{an uneasy\|an anxious\|a breathless\|a tense\|a terrifying\} moment you feel a piercing sensation on your jugular. Touching the place you find but the lingering memory of pain, but nothing else.\|Someone is standing right behind you. How very rude! Swiftly you turn to face breathy air and melting shadows.\| Who is eating garlics here and why? This think stinks.\|You found yourself eavesdropping on a conversation, though you can't see who is talking. What catches your attention is your name being mentioned along with a fine dinner that sates all imaginable hunger.\|A cool breeze sneaks through your hair tingling your nostrils with a waft of feminine scents.\|The air gets heavy, shadows lay their burden upon your breath stealing your energies. The moment passes, but the memory of oppression leaves its bitter flavour upon your tongue.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1256777460, "balkaar", "E", 1256810849, "balkaar", "E", 1256827493, "balkaar", "E", 1256827535, "balkaar", "E", 1256827546, "balkaar", "E", 1256828314, "balkaar", "E", 1256828704, "balkaar", "E", 1256829548, "balkaar", "E", 1256829785, "balkaar", "E", 1256829822, "balkaar", "E", 1256829832, "balkaar", "E", 1256830240, "balkaar", "E", 1256830388, "balkaar", "E", 1256830461, "balkaar", "E", 1256830590, "balkaar", "E", 1256830831, "balkaar", "E", 1256831113, "balkaar", "E", 1256831270, "balkaar", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="1256829822" state="Open" user="balkaar">
           This causes hallucinations To add this effect on an object, add the Call() line below to the appropriate Merry reaction(s):
$["";/* 
  Call(${Ironclaw:Staff:Sirazad:LC}, "apply", $who: $actor, $severity: 2 + random(2)); 
*/]
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
