<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Lib:Controls:General)"/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="command:angry">
         (\{ "THIS writhes and flails POSSESSIVE limbs, POSSESSIVE face twisted into an angry expression as NOMINATIVE occasionally wails.", "THIS grows red in the face as NOMINATIVE wails and thrashes POSSESSIVE limbs." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:cry">
         (\{ "THIS hiccups once and begins to cry with a wavering sound.", "THIS breaks into a series of small, breathy cries in between tiny little gasps." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:doze">
         (\{ "THIS fights against the heaviness of POSSESSIVE eyelids, losing the battle with each consequent blink.", "THIS blinks over and over, POSSESSIVE eyes slower to open each time NOMINATIVE does." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:frown">
         (\{ "THIS twists POSSESSIVE lips into a small frown of displeasure.", "THIS contorts POSSESSIVE face into a shadow of a frown." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:giggle">
         (\{ "THIS giggles quietly, POSSESSIVE face plastered with a small smile.", "THIS wriggles to and fro while giggling with a soft, breathy sound." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:happy">
         (\{ "THIS relaxes, observing the surroundings with a contented expression on POSSESSIVE face.", "THIS makes soft cooing sounds as NOMINATIVE serenely observes the surrounding area." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:laugh">
         (\{ "THIS bursts into full-blown belly laughs, POSSESSIVE eyes scrunched tight with uncontrollable laughter.", "THIS gasps for air in between fits of uncontrollable laughter that twist POSSESSIVE face into an ear-to-ear smile." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:sad">
         (\{ "THIS fusses and fidgets, whimpering softly with a discontented expression on POSSESSIVE face.", "THIS begins to fuss and wiggle while making small sounds of discontent." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:scream">
         (\{ "THIS begins to screech, POSSESSIVE wails becoming louder and more insistent with each inhalation.", "THIS begins to scream, POSSESSIVE cries desperate and punctuated by deep gasps for air." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:serious">
         (\{ "THIS stares with a somber expression and intensely curious eyes.", "THIS appears to be soaking in every detail as NOMINATIVE stares with a serious expression on POSSESSIVE face." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:sleep">
         (\{ "THIS breathes soft and slow, POSSESSIVE expression peaceful and relaxed as NOMINATIVE succumbs to slumber.", "THIS falls deep into sleep, POSSESSIVE face serene and POSSESSIVE body relaxed." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:smile">
         (\{ "THIS curves POSSESSIVE lips into a small shadow of a smile.", "THIS scrunches POSSESSIVE eyes as a smile curves POSSESSIVE lips." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:tears">
         (\{ "THIS sniffles once as tears moisten POSSESSIVE eyelashes.", "THIS sniffles softly as POSSESSIVE eyes glisten with burgeoning tears." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:thumb">
         (\{ "THIS closes POSSESSIVE eyes partway, softly sucking on POSSESSIVE thumb as NOMINATIVE does so.", "THIS heaves a sigh of contentment as NOMINATIVE sucks on POSSESSIVE thumb, POSSESSIVE expression serene and relaxed." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:tickle">
         (\{ "THIS writhes to and fro amid peels of laughter, POSSESSIVE expression twisted into a smile as NOMINATIVE does so.", "THIS flails POSSESSIVE limbs wildly amid deep belly laughs." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:toes">
         (\{ "THIS pulls POSSESSIVE feet up, staring in wonder and amazement as NOMINATIVE plays with POSSESSIVE toes.", "THIS stares in wide-eyed wonder as NOMINATIVE grabs hold of POSSESSIVE feet and begins playing with POSSESSIVE toes." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:wail">
         (\{ "THIS takes a deep breath in between each wailing cry, POSSESSIVE face twisted as NOMINATIVE writhes and flails.", "THIS wails louder and louder, POSSESSIVE face growing red with the intensity of POSSESSIVE cries." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:whimper">
         (\{ "THIS makes soft whimpering sounds while quivering POSSESSIVE lower lip.", "THIS sniffles softly while making tiny whimpering sounds of discontent." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:wiggle">
         (\{ "THIS wriggles and writhes, POSSESSIVE limbs moving every which way as NOMINATIVE does.", "THIS wiggles back and forth, POSSESSIVE arms and legs flailing." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="command:yawn">
         (\{ "THIS scrunches POSSESSIVE eyes closed as POSSESSIVE mouth opens wide with a hearty yawn.", "THIS stretches POSSESSIVE arms and legs outward as NOMINATIVE yawns with eyes shut tight." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1593893266, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
