<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="tunk_bodin">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(IronClaw:Staff:Angelo:Urs:PageBook)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="0.01" density="0.01"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="pamphlet"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="stuff"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pamphlets"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="everything"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="blue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="leather"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="mounted"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pale"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="book:page:count">
             4
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             pamphlet on mounted combat
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A pale blue leather pamphlet on mounted combat. It is a bit thick and the cover carries the title and authors name.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A pamphlet on mounted combat.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The title of the pale blue leather pamphlet, "Being a Concise History of the Practice of Chivalry and a Definition of the Proper Rules of Engagement" writ in embossed gold with a small notation beneath in plain black print, "A collaberation of Triskellians finest researchers".
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="cover" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="cover"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="covers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="blue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="leather"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pale"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pamphlet"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             pamphlet cover
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A pamphlet cover inscribed with the title.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The title of the pamphlet, "Being a Concise History of the Practice of Chivalry and a Definition of the Proper Rules of Engagement" writ in embossed gold with a small notation beneath in plain black print, "A collaberation of Triskellians finest researchers".
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="one"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="beginning"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="opening"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Introduction to Mounted Combat
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             "Knights should take coursers to joust and to go to tourneys, to hold an open table, to hunt for wild beasts, for in doing these things, the knights exercise their arms.... For to maintain the order of knighthood, the knight must at all times pursue the virtues of justice, wisdom, charity, loyalty, verity, humility, strength, hope, swiftness, and all other virtues that are semblance to the noble franchise of knighthood.... For honor is worth more than gold or silver, without any comparison." --Attributed to Don Constantin de Rinaldi in ON THE DISCIPLINE OF CHIVALRY. There is more writing to be READ for the those willing.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             "Knights should take coursers to joust and to go to tourneys, to hold an open table, to hunt for wild beasts, for in doing these things, the knights exercise their arms.... For to maintain the order of knighthood, the knight must at all times pursue the virtues of justice, wisdom, charity, loyalty, verity, humility, strength, hope, swiftness, and all other virtues that are semblance to the noble franchise of knighthood.... For honor is worth more than gold or silver, without any comparison." --Attributed to Don Constantin de Rinaldi in ON THE DISCIPLINE OF CHIVALRY.          The care and maintenance of riding animals is no trivial task. It takes years of training, often starting in early adulthood, for someone to become a skilled cavalier. A KNIGHT undertakes an apprentice of sorts, called a SQUIRE, who is usually only 6 or 7 years old at the start of their career. The squire performs menial chores and endures lots of hard practice. They develop thick skins from falling off their mounts over and over again and from the buffets from wooden practice-weapons that they fail to parry.          It also takes a fair amount of money to support a knight and squire. The knight is supported by a social structure known as FEUDALISM. Knights own the land; their subordinates, the VASSALS, till the land and are permitted to live upon it, in return for paying taxes and for serving the knight in time of war. The knight was also the owner of such social institutions as the mill, the baker's oven, and the kiln, since these were expensive stone buildings that had to be built on the land the knight owned. Social mobility is nearly impossible: the vassals make goods that can't be exported or require unusual skills, so they are only of value to their lord.          To prepare for the inevitable times of war, the knight was trained from youth in the difficult art of fighting while mounted. With the most expensive equipment and a lifetime of combat training, knights command heavy respect on the battlefield, especially when the bulk of many forces are made up of untrained peasants.          The Rinaldi having been wealthy for hundreds of years, developed a strong culture around the knight and the idea of CHIVALRY, that knights should not just be trained in combat but also in personal character. Chivalry was just a general idea in Triskellian, the sort of display one expects from the nobility, and its principles differed from locale to locale. It wasn't until after Don Constantin fought the Avoirdupois that a formal definition was laid down in writing, and later passed into law by royal decree. Apparently, Constantin was highly impressed with the co-ordination and discipline of the Avoirdupois ranks. He attributed this discipline to the Avoirdupois notion of FRANCHISE, that nobles derived their right to rule from theor lord and at all times must strive to be true in virtue and deed. Although the book ON THE DISCIPLINE OF CHIVALRY bears Constantin's name as author, many scholars agree that the content is largely lifted from Avoirdupois texts.          The other major houses follow similiar definitions. The Bisclavret, being eager modernists, can often recite passages from CHIVALRY by rote, although they claim to be using Bisclavret sources for theirs. The Doloreaux also have their own order of knighthood, although they concentrate less on the combative strength and swiftness, and more on charity and loyalty. The other, lesser houses are larger indifferent. The Chevernaise care little for the ways of outsiders, and the Phelan have a very different social order.          CHIVALRY is over 20,000 words in length in its complete edition, but its major principles can be summed up in a few points: -- A KNIGHT is JUST. A knight always honors surrender. When called upon to mete out justice, a knight follows the law first and the facts second, and is unmoved by personal concerns. Knights always keep their word. -- A KNIGHT is LOYAL. Knights swear by their superiors, and they follow their tasks willingly and with discernment. It is better to die by duty than to live by disobedience. -- A KNIGHT is HUMBLE. Knights do not lie or play anyone falsely. They do not "insist" upon their subordinates' loyalty, and they heed the counsel of others.          Many knights would like to think of themselves as the top of the social order. Unfortunately, Triskellian has been maintaining its own armed forces for several years. Inside the city walls, guilds and trade organizations have established their rules, protocols, offices, and heirarchy. Ironically, the strength of the denar, the coin that brought Rinaldi to power, is now being used by the common folk to further their own interests. The technology of gunpowder and the dissemination of magic have weakened the effectiveness of the mounted warrior in full plate. The sun is setting on the knight.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="two"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Riding Combat Techniques
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Fighting while seated on a mount is a difficult undertaking. To use most weapons effectively, one needs good footwork and balance; the saddle is less than ideal. The constant motion of the mount provides an unsteady platform, and sometimes the mount itself is in the way of a good swing! There is more to READ for the those willing to try.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Fighting while seated on a mount is a difficult undertaking. To use most weapons effectively, one needs good footwork and balance; the saddle is less than ideal. The constant motion of the mount provides an unsteady platform, and sometimes the mount itself is in the way of a good swing! The major advantage a riding combatant has is speed.    A knight must learn to mount and dismount but can also learn to vault onto his steed. Another useful technique is learning to use the mount to trample a target. The word TILT refers to a thrust with a lance by a rider. To gain full advantage of a thrusting weapon, such as a lance, the mount must achieve a fair amount of speed. Fighting while mounted is tricky business. Whenever your mount is moving at a gallop, it becomes difficult to hold weapons steady.          Mounts can wear armor just like any other combatants. One problem with putting armor on a mount is the issue of construction. Mounts can't talk, and aren't that bright in the first place; an armorer has to be very careful when fitting to make sure the parts won't chafe or scrape, which can cause lasting injury to the beast. The other problem with putting armor on a mount is that all mounts are massive.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="three"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Information on Riding Animals
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is broken into sections titled Destrier, Jennet, Palfrey, Rouncy, Courser and Dray.  There is more writing to be READ for the those willing.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             This page is broken into sections titled Destrier, Jennet, Palfrey, Rouncy, Courser and Dray.          DESTRIERS     In their heyday, the Rinaldi were famous for their highly trained war-mounts, the destriers. This type of mount is very rare and very expensive, the product of selective breeding and extensive training. A destrier is combat-trained and won't spook at the sound of gunfire or magic. It can also be coaxed into attacking and trampling foes. Unfortunately, destriers are known to be irritable, and skilled handlers are required for their upkeep. They are also omnivorous, requiring a high-protein diet to keep up their muscle tone, in other words, a fair amount of meat, which makes their upkeep far costlier than most mounts. Many are temperamental and can't be kept in a stable with other mounts, even other destriers, as they will bite and kick. The process of breaking a destrier in and learning to ride one is not for the faint of heart or thin of skin. A destrier is 64 stones.          JENNET     The mount preferred by the Avoirdupois, the jennet is long of leg and swift in stride. They can be combat-trained, but they would still prefer to run than to stand and fight. They are an excellent choice for outriders or skirmishers, as they are smart enough to learn formation-fighting. Their speed makes them a good choice for lancers, as well. They are herbivores and will eat most any scrub or plant matter, but better-quality food keeps them in their best shape. A jennet is 48 stones.          PALFREY     A generic term for a "higher-class" breed, the palfrey is the mount owned by those who are of distinction but not necessarily of a fighting nature, such as clergy or noble-women. While omnivorous like the destriers, palfreys are smaller and leaner and have less demanding dietary preferences. Palfreys can be trained to tolerate magic and gunfire and can be urged to strike out at footmen, but they lack the ferocity of their destrier cousins. A palfrey is 44 stones.          ROUNCY     For those mounts of no particular breeding or training, the term rouncy is used as a catch-all. Rouncies won't fight or trample, and they will spook at loud noises such as gunfire and the more brutal magics. But they will take their riders from one point to another, they will work in teams, and they are far more tractable than other, nastier mounts. Rouncies are 48 stones.          COURSER     For those who can't afford destriers and would prefer a creature of more substance than the jennet, the courser is the name applied to many breeds of war-mount found on Calabria. While they can't be trained as well as other, more "refined" breeds, they also don't cost as much. They are herbivores and have good long-range stamina, for those in need of practical transportation. Breeds vary considerably. A courser is 48 stones.          DRAY     Squat, foul-smelling, and generally unpleasant, the dray is a beast-of-burden good for heavy labor, such as wagon-hauling or field-plowing, provided one isn't in any hurry. Drays will eat most any vegetative matter, and they vary in personality from docile to downright ornery. Few will attempt to ride one; in fact, many will balk at first-time riders and shy away from saddles and the like, but they can be driven at a slow and ponderous pace for hours. A dray is 64 stones.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="four"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Specials Items and Equipment
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is a list of special items and equipment, including the lance, the polearm, the billhook, mount furniture and the mastiff.  There is more writing to be READ for the those willing.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             This is a list of special items and equipment, including the lance, the polearm, the billhook, mount furniture and the mastiff.          THE LANCE     The lance is a long weapon, consisting of a long shaft or handle and a steel blade or head. A lance weighs three quarter stone and is a one-handed weapon. It is used while tilting or jousting. Lances are not to parry.          POLEARM     To take down cavaliers, you need a weapon that can reach them. The most common method is to equip your fighters with polearms, or weapons with very long shafts.          BILLHOOK     The billhook is a special weapon designed for unseating combatants. It is a type of spear that has a curved hook on the end, for dragging the target down.          MOUNT FURNITURE     While there are those who would ride bareback, there is equipment for making a ride easier. Such items are called furniture. A mount should be fitted with a harness, which includes a bit that goes in the mouth of the mount, possibly even a nose ring. A saddle is padded part of a harness which is worn on a mounts back, being fastened in place with a girth. It includes stirrups for a rider's feet, for extra stability.          MASTIFF     There are few noble houses in Calabria that would admit to not keeeping mastiffs. These bipedal hunting animals are only "mostly" domesticated; certain estates of the Chevernaise make a point of having packs of semi-domesticated mastiffs roving the grounds. It is said to "toughen up visitors." The relatively small size and high intelligence of the mastiffs has made them a favorite in flushing game and bringing it down. Their speed is the stuff of legend and a good mastiff will be bred around to local estates. Many paintings depict a mounted knight along with one or two well-bred mastiffs, on a good hunt in favorable weather. A mastiff is 8 stones.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="spine" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="spine"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="spines"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pamphlet"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the spine of a pamphlet
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The spine of a pamphlet.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:react:sigh-iob">
         X[M] \$delay(2, TRUE, "030f");              
EmitTo( \$actor, "The pamphlet does not react to you in any way except to look more daunting and self-assured in its knowledge.");
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="misc:lastdropped">
         "1099539673 Manny[tunk_bodin]"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1170616987, "necate", "E", 1221574947, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1224429188, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1224429212, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1224852830, "slurpeeslurp", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
