<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Bodyguard">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: bodyguard<br/> Important Commands: attack, search, spar, wield<br/><br/>As a bodyguard, you will wake with skills in club, observation, and shadowing. You should have an appropriate weapon in your inventory when you enter the world as your new character.<br/>To use the club skill you must first enter combat. To do this type 'SPAR'. The combat system will automatically assign your weapon to be fists unless you are wielding something else. At this time you can 'WIELD my weapon'. Now when you 'ATTACK (person)' the damage will come from your weapon rather than from your unarmed skill.<br/><br/>The observation skill by default will allow you to recognize pickpockets and thieves. There is no command as it automatically generates a response like 'you see person Y pickpocket person Z'. You may roleplay accordingly. Observation also allows you to search areas for hidden items. To do this, enter a room and type 'SEARCH HERE'. Depending on your level in the skill, you may or may not find something.<br/><br/>Bodyguards are generally used by the four Great Houses and the Constabulary. If you need a job, find out in game who represents these establishments and contact them.<br/><br/> See Also: combat, consent, manipulation<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="bodyguard"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996512, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996867, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194997705, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119324, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489067, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1509727300, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
