<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Carpenter">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: carpenter<br/> Important Commands: carve<br/><br/>As a carpenter, you have the ability to create items using a variety of woods.<br/>When you log your character into the game, you should have a carving knife in your inventory. If you do not, they are purchasable at the wheeler in Docktown or craftable by blacksmiths. This is the only tool you need for your profession, though others are available to enhance roleplay. <br/><br/>To find the woodshop from the commons go WEST three times and then NORTHEAST. You can 'ASK WHEELER FOR PRICE LIST'. The price list will show you the cost of each variety of wood. To get good quality wood, you will need to find a merchant in game to purchase it for you.<br/><br/>Once you are in possession of lumber you can type 'CARVE MY LUMBER' to see a list of available options (this list will increase the more you learn). To create an item from your lumber: CARVE MY LUMBER INTO ITEM. For example, if you want to make a sudare, the command would be: CARVE MY LUMBER INTO SUDARE.<br/><br/>At times, items can be further customized than they originally appear -- figurines are an example of this. Once you carve a figurine from your lumber, you can further carve it into a type of figurine using the command: CARVE MY FIGURINE INTO VARIATION. For example, if you want to make a fox figurine: CARVE MY FIGURINE INTO FOX.<br/><br/>Along with carpenter, you get the skill of Woodcarving. Raising this skill improves the quality of your items and lets you craft a wider variety of certain things (such as figurines). It does not give you better quality lumber - only the merchant or trade skill will aid you in that area.<br/><br/>Lacquers are also sold in the wheeler shop and can be added to your lumber with the command: ADD MY LACQUER TO MY LUMBER. If you have black lacquer, for example, and willow lumber, you would enter the command and your willow lumber would turn into black lacquered willow lumber. 1 use of lacquer would be taken from the bottle. Any items you craft from this lumber will also be 'black lacquered willow'.<br/><br/>Custom engravings can be added to your items free of charge if they are sent in by a carpenter to staff.<br/><br/>There are various guilds that hire carpenters along with the four great Houses. For more information talk to people in game about your options.<br/><br/> See Also: bulk<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="carpenter"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="woodcarver"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996466, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996478, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119406, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489071, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315244081, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727304, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
