<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="clothier">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: clothier<br/> Important Commands: add, tailor, fit, embroider<br/><br/>To see a list of items you can create: get a bolt/roll of fabric, a pair of scissors, and a needle and type: TAILOR MY FABRIC. Bolts/rolls of fabric are available for purchase through the auction house, Carmaggio in Newtown (for finer fabrics) and the seamstress shop in Docktown (for cheaper fabrics).<br/><br/>To create items: if you want to create a shirt, you would have a bolt/roll of fabric, a pair of scissors, and a needle and type: TAILOR MY FABRIC INTO SHIRT<br/><br/>To create items from base items: have a bolt/roll of fabric, a pair of scissors, and a needle. If you want to create an undertunic from a basic shirt, you would type: TAILOR MY SHIRT INTO UNDERTUNIC. Note: You have to tailor the shirt from the fabric before you try to tailor the shirt into a new garment. (Can't create something from nothing)<br/><br/>To add beads/lace/trim/fringe/other parts: ADD MY BEAD/LACE/TRIM/FRINGE TO MY GARMENT. If you wanted to add trim to a jacket, for example, it would read: ADD MY TRIM TO MY JACKET.<br/><br/>To add buttons or buckles you use the same command, just type ADD BUTTON/BUCKLE TO MY ITEM. Eg., ADD MY BUTTON TO MY JACKET.<br/> Buckles and buttons can be purchased from both Carpenters or Smiths.<br/><br/>If you are a TAILOR/SEAMSTRESS, you can add clothing fits to people's garments. To do this, the person must be wearing the garment they want fitted. Once they are, you need to get out your trusty scissors and needle. The command then to get the list of fits you can do is: FIT PERSON'S GARMENT. Eg, fit Azrael's shirt. Once a fit is selected, you type FIT PERSON'S GARMENT 'TIGHT'. Eg., fit Azrael's shirt 'tight'.<br/><br/>If you are a NEEDLEWORKER, you can add embroideries to clothing for people. To do this, you must ensure the garment is NOT being worn and that you have a spool of thread in your hands. Thread can be crafted by needleworkers in various colors and fabrics or purchased in the seamstress shop. The command to embroider is: EMBROIDER PERSON'S GARMENT WITH MY THREAD 'PATTERN'. Eg., if you are holding a skirt someone wants embroidered with skulls, you would type: embroider my skirt with my thread 'skull'.<br/><br/>New fits and embroideries for the entire playerbase can be suggested through @assists. Custom fits you do not want added to the system will cost storypoints. Custom embroideries, however, can be done by staff if sent in by a clothier character at no cost. This is only for the time being until we get the engraving and etching systems complete, at which point all custom decorations people do not want added to one of the systems will cost storypoints.<br/><br/> Your items in your item and option list will depend upon your level in tailoring, needleworking, and seamstressing.  Tailoring allows you to do items that are for men, seamstressing handles items that are for ladies, and needleworking covers accessories and odds and ends items (shoes, parasols, belts, pouches, blankets, hats, etc). The further you succeed in these careers level wise, the more you will be able to craft and the more garments you will be able to design.<br/><br/>For further assistance contact fellow tailors in game<br/><br/> See Also: alteration, manipulation, roleplaying<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="clothier"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="needleworker"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="seamstress"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="sewing"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="tailor"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="tailoring"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996512, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996867, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194997705, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998089, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998158, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998365, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194999812, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000056, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001895, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001920, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001928, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001937, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119880, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489121, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315244767, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315245424, "slurpeeslurp", "X", 1317430913, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727308, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
