<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Constable">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: constable<br/> Important Commands: wield, fight, search<br/><br/>A Constable is a local law-enforcement official who serves in the Constabulary.<br/>You will wake up with skills in club, polearm, whip, parry, and observation.<br/><br/>The club skill is given primarily for detainment purposes in this field. If you find yourself needing to enter combat, you need to type 'WIELD MY CLUB/WEAPON' and 'FIGHT (person)'. This places you both in combat mode, and defaults your club as your chosen striking weapon. To attack someone, you only need to follow the prompts when actions are assigned to you.<br/><br/>Observation assists in recognizing thieves and pickpockets. If someone attempts to steal in your presence and your observation is high enough, you will see the emit, "Player Y pickpockets Player X". You can roleplay accordingly. You can also search for hidden items in rooms using the observation skill by typing 'SEARCH HERE'. Depending on your level of skill, you may or may not find anything.<br/><br/>A large part of playing a Constable is filing evidence and knowing how to determine the severity of evidence presented to you by other player characters. Filing evidence in the @crime system is a tricky matter, as only Constables can file evidence and it must be filed without IC bias or influence. If you want to use IC influence and bias, you can do that through your own testimonies and opinions. For example, if a witness says "He smelt of squirrel" then that could be included as evidence in an assault on a squirrel. Also include evidence that the person *didn't* commit the crimes if it's presented. If the murder weapon was found to be a knife, and the accused is known to use swords, then that could be included as evidence of innocence. It is NOT evidence if someone says they saw a thing happen, or heard it. These are subjective observations and opinions and belong under testimonies. Seeing a crime is not evidence of the crime, not even if it's a Constable who saw it occur. Evidence is reserved solely for physical evidence.<br/><br/>Evidence can be if you find physical evidence in a murder, like talking to a doctor about the wound patterns, finding out what the corpse smells like to see who was in proximity with it when it died, a scroll with a testimony on it, etc. Essentially, hard core objective things that you can handle and show.<br/><br/> Severity of evidence can be:<br/><br/>Unclear evidence, which has no weight in the @crime point system, so there's really no need to file it unless you want to use it to explain more about the crime to the public. These include things like wounds, bruises, etc.<br/><br/>Circumstantial evidence, such as determining what weapon was used to commit a crime, or using scent to determine proximity to a victim or attacker.<br/><br/>Solid evidence, such as a very distinct smell. For example, if there is one character who is known for smelling like sewage and birthday cakes, and the corpse of a victim smells of sewage and birthday cakes, it's a good indicator that the character in question was present at the time of the crime; however, it's not a firm one, as scents don't last very long, and they can be picked up through any sort of interaction. An item found on the body known to belong to someone else, eg, if a dagger was used and it was found on the body of a victim and the dagger is special and known to belong to a certain person, that would qualify as solid or circumstantial evidence. Theoretically, anyone could have stolen the dagger and stabbed someone with it, but it is unlikely that would have occurred.<br/><br/>Very solid evidence would be something like if there were witnesses that say X player was standing over the dead body and in a panic, ran and left behind his very distinct dagger.<br/><br/>Indisputable evidence would include written and signed confessions, eg, a criminal writing to his best friend and saying "I killed Bob! It was bloody and awful!" Perhaps his best friend is secretly his enemy, and so hands the scroll over to the Constabulary. If the scroll is unsigned, it would be invalid evidence. If they signed it, however, and it matches details related to the case, it would be considered proving guilt or innocence.<br/><br/>People with this career are encouraged to seek employment through the Constabulary. For specific names and further information contact fellow players in game.<br/><br/> See Also: combat, consent, roleplaying<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="constable"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="constabulary"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="observation"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996057, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996071, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996105, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996151, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996506, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1295119416, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489079, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315716220, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315716314, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727312, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
