<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Dilettante">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: dilettante<br/> Important Commands: spar, @speak, wield<br/><br/>A dilettante is, by definition, someone who dabbles in a wide variety of areas. It is one of the highest paying professions in the game.<br/>You will wake up with the ability to speak five different languages, not including the language of your species. These are eastern, northern, old, southern, and western. To switch from your current language of Calabrese to old, you would type @SPEAK OLD. Now when you speak, unless the listener is fluent in this language, it will come out a string of preset letters. You can type @SPEAK FEEDBACK to see what the language looks like to other people. *Note* Just because you can speak it, doesn't mean you are fluent. People who are fluent will be able to recognize how good of a grasp you have on any given language.<br/><br/>Along with languages, you receive the skill of fencing. Generally fencers try to acquire rapiers or other light swords if they intend to use the combat system since it compliments the profession best. To do this, you need to find a blacksmith. Once you are in possession of a weapon and ready to spar, you can type 'WIELD MY WEAPON' and then 'SPAR (person)'. You are now in combat mode. To attack simply type 'ATTACK (person)'.<br/><br/>To further your knowledge of languages or to learn as much as possible in this career, you should ask in game about what guilds or Houses have the profession available through their teachers for you to advance. As always, learning from other players is highly encouraged.<br/><br/> See Also: combat, consent, language roleplaying<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="dilettante"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996057, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996071, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996105, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996151, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996235, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996438, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996448, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119429, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489089, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1509727317, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
