<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Dyer">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: dyer, dye mixer<br/> Important Commands: mix, add<br/><br/>Starter clothing dyes can be purchased from Rigelli in Newtown. Once you have two different colors of dyes, you can try to create a new color. If you have a red dye and a blue dye, for example, and want to try to create a new shade, you type: MIX MY RED DYE WITH MY BLUE DYE. Automatically, the result will spawn in your inventory, and the red dye and blue dye will be gone.<br/><br/>Hair dyes and fur dyes both can be purchased from the barber shop in Docktown. You don't need the dye mixing skill to add a clothing dye to a hair/fur dye and change the color, but it's most realistic to think you would use a dye mixer to get the color even. You can purchase any color of hair/fur dye and add any clothing dye color to it and it will automatically become the clothing dye's color. If you have a brown hair dye, for example, and a bottle of pure white dye, you type: ADD MY PURE WHITE DYE TO MY HAIR DYE. 1 use of pure white dye gets taken away from the clothing dye bottle, and the hair dye becomes the shade of pure white instead of brown. It's similar for fur dye, though if you have a brown fur dye and a bottle of green clothing dye, the command will be: MIX MY FUR DYE WITH MY GREEN DYE. 1 use of green dye gets taken away from the clothing dye bottle, and the fur dye becomes the shade of green instead of brown.<br/><br/>To add dyes to rolls/bolts of fabric, the command is: ADD MY DYE TO MY FABRIC. For example, if you have white clothing dye and a roll of leather, the command would be: add my dye to my leather. 1 use of the clothing dye gets taken away, and the leather becomes a roll of white leather.<br/><br/>See also: manipulation, roleplaying
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="dyer"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="mixer"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996466, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996478, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119406, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489071, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315244081, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315244265, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315244305, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727321, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
