<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Courtesan">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: fisherman<br/> Important Commands: fish, offer, take<br/><br/>As a fisherman, you have the ability to catch fish in the Bay of Auvrich and potentially make profits that exceed the wages of any other profession in the game.<br/>Depending on how you organized your attributes during character creation you may wake up with a spear, a fishing net, or a fishing pole. This item is what works best with your character presently. To find the Bay of Auvrich from the commons, go WEST three times and SOUTH twice. You can fish anywhere along that road where water is visible.<br/><br/>To begin fishing you need to be holding your item. Now type 'FISH IN BAY WITH MY POLE/NET/SPEAR'. If you do not target your item it will default to fishing with your hands, which does not always offer a high success rate.<br/><br/>The type of fish you catch is entirely based on your skill; the higher your skill, the bigger and better the catch. When you have a good amount of fish saved up and are ready to sell, you need to find a merchant (or get some ranks in merchant yourself) to take them to the fishmonger. The amount of money offered per fish goes down as each player sells to the monger, so if you aren't being offered what you expected, you can ask around about general prices or save them until a later time when demand goes back up.<br/><br/>
If you have a net, you will need to take your fish out of it to sell them. You can do this by typing 'EMPTY MY NET' or 'TAKE FISHES FROM MY NET'. They are now in your inventory rather than in a container.<br/><br/>To see what price the monger is willing to buy your fish for type 'OFFER MY FISHES TO MONGER'. An amount will come up with the option to accept or refuse.<br/><br/>With fisherman, you also receive the skill of fishing. This skill gives you an extra roll in the system when you're attempting to catch fish. The higher this skill is, the better chance you have of a high roll, though it will not enable you itself to catch new kinds of fish.<br/><br/>For further assistance, seek out fellow fishermen in game.<br/><br/> See Also: accept, bulk, manipulation, revoke<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="fish"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="fisherman"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="fishing"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996512, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996867, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194997744, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119436, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489094, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1509727325, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
