<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Hairstylist">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: hairstylist<br/> Hairdressers work with a pair of scissors and a comb. Scissors are available for purchase in the seamstress shop in Docktown, and combs are available in the barber shop, also in Docktown. Hairbrushes can be purchased also, but they don't influence your ability to style hair.<br/><br/>For a list of hairstyles you're capable of creating, type: STYLE MY HAIR, or STYLE PERSON'S HAIR. Once a style is selected, you simply add it to the end of your command: STYLE MY HAIR INTO BUN or STYLE PERSON'S HAIR INTO BUN. Eg., style Azrael's hair into bun.<br/><br/>For a list of hair textures you're capable of creating, type: TEXTURIZE MY HAIR, or TEXTURIZE PERSON'S HAIR. Once a texture is selected, you simply add it to the end of your command: TEXTURIZE MY HAIR INTO KINKY or TEXTURIZE PERSON'S HAIR INTO KINKY. Eg., texturize Azrael's hair into kinky. Fur textures and tail textures work exactly the same way with exactly the same commands, except you replace hair with fur or tail. They would look like: TEXTURIZE MY TAIL INTO KINKY, TEXTURIZE MY FUR INTO KINKY.<br/><br/>For a list of cuts you're capable of doing, type: CUT MY HAIR, or CUT PERSON'S HAIR. Once a cut is selected, you CUT MY HAIR INTO LENGTH or CUT PERSON'S HAIR INTO LENGTH. For example, if Azrael wanted a short haircut, it would look like: CUT AZRAEL'S HAIR INTO SHORT. It's the same with tail and fur cuts, only it would look like: CUT AZRAEL'S TAIL INTO SHORT or CUT AZRAEL'S FUR INTO SHORT. If you want to grow your hair longer than it currently is, you need to buy a potion from the barber shop and ADD MY POTION TO MY HAIR or ADD MY POTION TO PERSON'S HAIR. Eg., Add my potion to Azrael's hair. You can add it as many times as you want to reach the desired result.<br/><br/>To change the color of your hair or fur, you need to purchase a hair or fur dye from the barber shop. Dye mixers can change the colors of these dyes with clothing dyes. The command is then: ADD MY DYE TO MY HAIR or ADD MY DYE TO MY FUR. The color that comes from hair and fur dyes lasts only two weeks and then it starts fading out to your original hair color (that color being the one you chose in chargen). The only way to get your original hair color changed permanently is through purchase with storypoints at a stp sale (if you pick a stp color) or as a regular storypoint purchase.<br/><br/> See Also: consent, manipulation, roleplaying<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="hair"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="hairdresser"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="hairstyling"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="hairstylist"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996512, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996867, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194997705, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998089, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998158, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998365, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194999812, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000056, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000323, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000682, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000954, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000973, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000984, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000993, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001002, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119463, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489100, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315243392, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315243437, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727329, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
