<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Help:Node title="Smith">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: smith<br/> Smiths of any kind need a hammer, anvil, and metal rod to work with. Metal rods and variations of hammers can be purchased from the blacksmith in the Docktown smithy. This is the only place currently that an anvil is available, so all your work will have to be done in this building. To see a list of items you can create, type: FORGE MY ROD USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL.<br/><br/>If you are a weaponsmith and want to make a cutlass sword, for example, you will have to go through multiple steps to get a finished product. This is what the command string would look like:<br/><br/>FORGE MY ROD USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL INTO BLADE (this gives you a generic weapon blade)<br/>FORGE MY BLADE USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL INTO SWORD BLADE (this gives you a generic sword blade)<br/>FORGE MY BLADE USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL INTO CUTLASS BLADE (this gives you a cutlass blade)<br/><br/>Weapons are incomplete without hilts, so you now have to make a hilt to add to your cutlass blade to get a finished product.<br/>FORGE MY ROD USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL INTO HILT (this gives you a generic hilt)<br/>FORGE MY HILT USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL INTO SWEPT HILT (this gives you a swept hilt)<br/>ADD MY HILT TO MY BLADE (this gives you the finished, functioning cutlass)<br/><br/>If you are unsure what your options for customizing are, you can always type FORGE MY ITEM USING MY HAMMER, ANVIL and a list will pop up with what's available to you, if anything. Forge my blade using my hammer, anvil, for example, will give you the options of 'dagger blade' or 'sword blade', and you can choose accordingly. Various customizations are available to any smith, and are dependent on their specialty (armor, black, or weapon).<br/><br/>Within the smithy itself, there are tools/items for you to RP with that will react to your interaction. The commands for these inside the building are:<br/>PUMP BELLOWS<br/>PUMP WHEEL<br/>BEAT MY ROD<br/><br/> See Also: armorsmith, blacksmith, weaponsmith, manipulation, roleplaying<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="smith"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="smithing"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365931, "-", "SYNC", 1136676342, "rhenn", "E", 1194994792, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995226, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995269, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995650, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995662, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995688, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995711, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995720, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194995729, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194996512, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1194996867, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194997705, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998089, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998158, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194998365, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1194999812, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000056, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000323, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000682, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000954, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000973, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000984, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195000993, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1195001002, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1295119463, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309489100, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315243392, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315243437, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315243727, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727341, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
