<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="sendnoodlez">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-axehead:weaponsmith:10">
         ([ "single-bladed battle axehead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "single-bladed battle" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "Designed for hacking and hewing your enemy into large pieces, the battle axe is a common weapon in the hands of any soldier on the battlefield.  The blade on one side of the haft means there is only one way to swing this weapon." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-axehead:weaponsmith:14">
         ([ "double-bladed battle axehead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "double-bladed battle" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "Designed for hacking and hewing your enemy into large pieces, the battle axe is a common weapon in the hands of any soldier on the battlefield.  This is a more fearsome version of the battle axe, with two large blades, one on either side of the haft." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-axehead:weaponsmith:18">
         ([ "lochaber axehead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "lochaber" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "Similar in design to the halberd, the lochaber axes posses a curved cutting blade roughly eighteen inches long.  In addition a tip for thrusting and a hook on the back of the blade can be used to dismount riders or assist in scaling walls." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-axehead:weaponsmith:6">
         ([ "francisca head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "francisca" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "A smaller style of axe, the francisca is generally used as a throwing weapon due to its light weight.  It can also serve as a melee weapon when nothing else is available." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-blade:weaponsmith:2">
         ([ "dagger blade":([ "brief":"a dagger blade", "newobject":\<Allegory:Props:Weapons:Crafting:Blades:UrDaggerBlade\> ]), "sword blade":([ "brief":"a sword blade", "newobject":\<Allegory:Props:Weapons:Crafting:Blades:UrSwordBlade\> ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:13">
         ([ "ear blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "ear dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "An ear dagger is a relatively rare and exotic form of dagger, so named because the pommel of the dagger has a very distinctive shape, in some cases not unlike an ear. Ear daggers frequently have a single sharpened edge that ends in an acute point." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:17">
         ([ "kris blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "kris dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The kris or keris is an asymmetrical dagger famous for its distinctive wavy blade; but many have straight blades as well. Both a weapon and spiritual object, kris are often considered to have an essence or presence, with some blades possessing good luck and others possessing bad." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:19">
         ([ "swordbreaker blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "swordbreaker dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The sword-breaker is a very sturdy dagger that has slots on one side much like the teeth of a comb. The teeth can be used to catch the blade of the opponent's sword and hold it fast, allowing a variety of follow-up techniques." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:21">
         ([ "trident blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "trident dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "Trident daggers are built so that the quillons on each side of the blade will spring outwards. This creates a dagger capable of trapping blades more securely and more easily." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:3">
         ([ "rondel blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "rondel dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The blade is typically long and slim, measuring 12 inches (30 cm) or more; the whole dagger might be as long as 20 inches (50 cm). Rondel means round or circular; the dagger gets its name from its round (or similarly shaped, e.g. octagonal) hand guard and round or spherical pommel (knob on the end of the grip)." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:5">
         ([ "dirk blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "dirk" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "Dirks are often lavishly decorated with silver mounts and have pommels set with cairngorm  stones. The blades of most dirks measure 12 inches in length and are single edged with decorative file work known as 'jimping' on the unsharpened back edge of the blade. When worn, the dirk normally hangs by a leather strap known as a 'frog' from a dirk belt, which is a wide leather belt having a large, usually ornate buckle, that is worn around the waist with a kilt." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:7">
         ([ "gauche blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "gauche dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The main-gauche (Eastern for 'left hand') is used mainly to assist in parrying incoming thrusts, while the dominant hand wields a rapier or similar longer weapon intended for one-handed use. It may also be used for attack if an opportunity arises." \}) \}) ]), "poniard blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "poniard" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A poignard, or poniard, is a lightweight dagger primarily used for stabbing in close quarters or in conjunction with a rapier." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-daggerblade:weaponsmith:9">
         ([ "misericorde blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "misericorde dagger" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A misericorde was a long, narrow knife, used to deliver the death stroke (the mercy stroke, hence the name of the blade, derived from the Old misericordia 'mercy') to a seriously wounded knight. The blade was thin enough so that it could strike through the gaps between armour plates." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-hilt:weaponsmith:10">
         ([ "bar guard":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "bar" \}), (\{ "trait:hiltdescription", "Also known as a knucklebow, a bar or strip protecting the front of the hand. Knucklebows are useful for swords that are often carried everyday, as the guard is flat and doesn't get in the way. For this reason, knucklebowed swords are also very fast to draw." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-hilt:weaponsmith:14">
         ([ "bell guard":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "bell" \}), (\{ "trait:hiltdescription", "A development of the knucklebow. The strip protecting the hand is widened and curved around the wielders knuckles. This style of guard is popular on pirate cutlasses." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-hilt:weaponsmith:18">
         ([ "basket hilt":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "basket" \}), (\{ "trait:hiltdescription", "An intricate cage surrounds the hilt, protecting the wielder's hand. This is the hilt of choice for the Bisclavret and due to their close-fitting nature are best on cutting, rather than thrusting swords." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-hilt:weaponsmith:22">
         ([ "swept hilt":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "swept" \}), (\{ "trait:hiltdescription", "More a work of art than anything else, the swept hilt is popular on rapiers and smallswords. A swept hilt consists of an intricate knotwork of bars, designed to protect the hand from thrusting attacks." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-hilt:weaponsmith:6">
         ([ "crossguard":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "crossguard" \}), (\{ "trait:hiltdescription", "A simple cruciform device that serves to protect the wielders hand without getting in the way during fighting. This is an older style of guard, popular on large two-handed swords and antiques." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-macehead:weaponsmith:12">
         ([ "flanged macehead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "flanged" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "Designed to defeat heavy armor the main danger of a mace is the sheer weight of the head.  Of course, the spikes (or flanges) certainly help to punch through a tough plate of metal." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-macehead:weaponsmith:18">
         ([ "warhammer head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "warhammer" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "In the same vein as maces, the war hammer is a weapon that helps to meet the ever increasing demand for weapons capable of inflicting grievous injury to armored opponents." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-macehead:weaponsmith:22">
         ([ "maul head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "maul" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "If a mace is just fine, then a maul is overkill.  An enormous hammer head is attached to a haft tall as a man and swung with both hands.  Not intended for individual combat, this weapon is a dire threat on the battlefield against groups of tightly packed opponents." \}) \}) ]), "shillelagh head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "shillelagh" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "A tree-root or log hollowed out and filled with molten lead to create a mace that closely resembles a club. It has a comfortable balance and heft, but is quite primitive when compared to weaponry from more advanced cultures." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-macehead:weaponsmith:6">
         ([ "aspergillum head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "aspergillum" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "Mimicking items used in holy rituals by the penitents of S'allumer, the holy water sprinkler is a small, dainty (by comparison) weapon.  Ease of use makes it a popular weapon, similar to the morningstar." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:metalworkers:weaponsmith:13">
         ([ "ixwa head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "ixwa" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "A shorter-style javelin with a two-foot shaft and a large, broad blade extending to a foot in length. It is so named after the sound that is heard as it is withdrawn from a victim's wound, and is traditionally used as a stabbing weapon during melee attacks." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:12">
         ([ "javelin head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "javelin" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade is small, measuring only six inches in length.  Intended mainly as a weapon thrown at close range, it could also serve as a light spear in a pinch." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:16">
         ([ "hewing spearhead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "hewing" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade measures approximately eighteen inches in length from tip to base. The particular design of this spearhead allows it to thrust and cut with equal effectiveness." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:17">
         ([ "gae bolga spearhead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "gae bolga" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade measures approximately twenty inches in length from tip to base. The spearhead is broad and triangular with serrated edges that curl backwards. This weapon is sometimes called a 'disembowelling spear' for that reason. Also, the reverse edge of the spear point curves backwards in such a way that one may pick the weapon up between their toes and toss it using a kicking motion with the foot." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:4">
         ([ "leaf-bladed spearhead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "leaf-bladed" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade measures approximately fifteen inches in length from tip to base.  The shape of the spearhead widens toward the base before tapering inward at the end." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:5">
         ([ "craoiseach spearhead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "craoiseach" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade measures approximately fifteen inches in length from tip to base. The shape of the spearhead widens toward the base before tapering inward at the end. The tip of the spearhead has a steel point that is forged to sharp edges." \}) \}) ]), "harpoon head":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "harpoon" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "A harpoon is a long spear-like instrument used in fishing to catch fish or large marine mammals such as whales. It accomplishes this task by impaling the target animal, allowing the fishermen to use a rope or chain attached to the butt of the projectile to catch the animal. A harpoon can also be used as a weapon." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-spearhead:weaponsmith:8">
         ([ "broad-bladed spearhead":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "broad-bladed" \}), (\{ "trait:headdescription", "The blade measures approximately ten inches in length from tip to base.  This blade is shorter and wider than most traditional spearheads, with lugs (or wings) jutting from the base of the blade.  The lugs prevent the spear from penetrating too deeply into a foe, allowing for quick recovery of a weapon and preventing the point from snapping off inside an opponent." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:leather:weaponsmith:20">
         ([ "scythe blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "scythe sword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "An elongated, sickle shaped blade. Different than other swords, the scythe blade is only sharpened on the inside curve, making this concave blade more often a weapon used for two-handed hacking, rather than any elaborate swordplay." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:10">
         ([ "claymore blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "claymore" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The claymore is of Bisclavret design. A very wide and relatively short two-handed blade that is manouverable enough to be used easily in single combat." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:11">
         ([ "side-sword blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "side-sword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "An early evolutionary step from the arming sword to the rapier.  It features a narrower, single-edged blade with a sharp point designed for effective cutting and thrusting." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:12">
         ([ "foil blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "foil" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The foil is a fencing blade, with the end capped, to avoid injuries." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:13">
         ([ "estoc blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "estoc" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "Deviating slightly from the longsword, this weapon is intended to be used against heavily armored opponents.  The long blade, consisting of only a point with almost no cutting edge, is stiff and acutely pointed, perfect for finding weak points." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:14">
         ([ "backsword blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "backsword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A modern design that features a full, front edge and a partial back edge. As the back edge is not sharp along most of the length, this blade can be thicker and stronger." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:15">
         ([ "cutlass blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "cutlass" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A stout slashing sword, similar to a sabre.  Favored by sailors for the fact that it can slash through heavy rope, canvas and wood, it also requires less training than a rapier or small sword to use effectively." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:16">
         ([ "rapier blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "rapier" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A long, relatively narrow (but thick) blade, that sacrifices cutting power for greater reach and thrusting ability. A properly measured rapier blade should reach from the ground to bottom of the wielders ribs. The rapier blade can be quite unwieldy, and is of little use in close quarters." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:18">
         ([ "sabre blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "sabre" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The fastest of cutting sword blades, the sabre is a wedge-shaped, curved blade. A footmans sabre is generally fairly straight, and a horsemans sabre is dramatically curved, so the wielder can keep hold of the weapon while striking at the gallop." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:2">
         ([ "arming blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "arming sword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The classic double-edged knightly blade. Known as a diamond-section blade, the arming blade has a ridge in the middle, along the length of the blade." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:20">
         ([ "scimitar blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "scimitar" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "The scimitar, or shamshir, is a weapon of oriental origins. The blade is very similar to a sabre, in that it is a curved blade with a sharp front edge, however it is much wider than a traditional sabre." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:22">
         ([ "smallsword blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "smallsword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "Often with no cutting ability whatsoever, a smallsword blade is designed as a rapier, but is as short as a normal sword blade. A properly measured smallsword blade reaches from the ground to the wielder's hips." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:24">
         ([ "zweihander blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "zweihander" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "An enormously long, double-edged two-hander blade, designed for battle. Zweihander blades are particularly effective when dealing with massed spears." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:4">
         ([ "short blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "shortsword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "An older style of arming blade, featuring an indent along the middle of the blade. This design allows for reinforced edges with the indent reducing the overall weight." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:6">
         ([ "blunt blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "blunt sword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A blunt blade is used when practicing, so as not to injure the wielders opponent." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-swordblade:weaponsmith:8">
         ([ "longsword blade":([ "properties":(\{ (\{ "trait:type", "longsword" \}), (\{ "trait:bladedescription", "A longer blade designed for two-handed use. Usually longswords are double-edged." \}) \}) ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alteration:knowledge:forging-weaponhead:weaponsmith:2">
         ([ "axehead":([ "brief":"axehead", "newobject":\<Allegory:Props:Weapons:Crafting:Axes:UrAxeHead\> ]), "macehead":([ "brief":"macehead", "newobject":\<Allegory:Props:Weapons:Crafting:Clubs:UrMaceHead\> ]), "spearhead":([ "brief":"spearhead", "newobject":\<Allegory:Props:Weapons:Crafting:Pole:UrSpearHead\> ]) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1250039842, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1250040402, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1250117400, "haystack", "E", 1250117471, "haystack", "E", 1250117580, "haystack", "E", 1250117676, "haystack", "E", 1250117773, "haystack", "E", 1251988661, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1251988855, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1287183105, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186294, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186369, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186415, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186466, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186531, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1287186662, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186728, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1287186808, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186901, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287186945, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1287187014, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1287514084, "jominey", "E", 1289020318, "jominey", "E", 1289020369, "jominey", "E", 1289020434, "jominey", "E", 1289020446, "jominey", "E", 1289020453, "jominey", "E", 1289020484, "jominey", "E", 1289020484, "jominey", "E", 1289020501, "jominey", "E", 1289089426, "jominey", "E", 1289089550, "jominey", "E", 1289089581, "jominey", "E", 1289090683, "jominey", "E", 1289090712, "jominey", "E", 1289099208, "jominey", "E", 1289099264, "jominey", "E", 1289099740, "jominey", "E", 1289439287, "jominey", "E", 1298954124, "jominey", "E", 1306269156, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1306269182, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1306269217, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1308395898, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1308396086, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1308396106, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1311714571, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1311715161, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1311715257, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1311715267, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1311715639, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1319369592, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1319369620, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1321188522, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1321188545, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1321188657, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1421701216, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1421701754, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1421701763, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1421701863, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1421701889, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1421705831, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1428123991, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1456775178, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1456775250, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1458565501, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1499136238, "jominey", "E", 1561682119, "jominey", "R", 1561682141, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
