<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="jominey">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="100">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Flynn has a whip belonging to Baronet Eberhard and refuses to return it when asked by the baronet's guard", "name":"\<font color=black\>Stealing a whip  - Charges Dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="101">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil, nil \}), "description":"Sang has reported that he was attacked in the warehouse by Flynn, and Dio and the slave known as Ryan.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault against Sang - Case closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="102">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil, nil \}), "description":"The morning after the previous assault Sang claims that Decado attacked him as well, aided by an unknown accomplice.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault against Sang - Charge dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="103">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\> \}), "description":"Luciano drew a weapon on another citizen in the commons, when I told him to put it away he refused and threatened me.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disrespecting a constable and disturbing the peace - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="104">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Decardo insulted Lord Marcus and Sir Matteo", "name":"\<font color=black\>Insulting Lord Marcus and Sir Matteo - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="105">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\>, nil \}), "description":"Chinco and decado ignored a direct order to remove their weapons and keep them in their rooms", "name":"\<font color=black\>Keeping weapons when ordered to disarm - Charge dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="106">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\>, \<Chatters:AE:ni:nix\> \}), "description":"Chinco was causing trouble in the common, throwing an apple at Nix, then knocking his drink from his hand and then punching him in the face", "name":"\<font color=black\>Fight in the common - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="107">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Direct Confession from Decado:\\"As you may of heard by now on the day of (bluebook the ico date.. August 30). A armadillo called Milli a whore, and threw a pouch at me. I then went to get me weapons and ask the mate for a duel.When I returned he ran off and I chased after him, I followed him to the docks sewer enterance where I told him to say sorry to Milli. He then swung his club at my knees which responded with me badly injurying his shoulder.He ran off through the sewers after and I was unable to find him till a little later that day. After I injuried him I returned my weapons to my room.\\"This is clearly assault, as well as breaking his probation on carrying weapons.", "name":"\<font color=black\>attacking someone with a weapon - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="108">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"An amadillo (OOC: lokie) was harrassing Millia and then in the common and then punched Decado.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault - Case Open - No suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="109">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ni:nix\> \}), "description":"Nix is to be charged for the actions of his slave, Maymay, who did apparently murder the slave Caliste.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Property Damage - Maymay killing Caliste - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="110">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Dio has been accused of being a public nuisance with his appearance, talk, and evil being.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disturbing the peace by being undead - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="111">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Dio murdered his daughter.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Murder of his daughter - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="112">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:wh:whie\> \}), "description":"Whie ignored warnings to cease disrespecting the constabulary in his announcements of planning to murder Dio Goldengate.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Inciting disrespect against the constabulary - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="113">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Caelith threatened harm upon Ludwig after Ludwig threatened to shoot Sergeant Danae with an arrow.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Disturbing the peace - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="114">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Ludwig threatened to shoot sergeant Danae while in pursuit of a runaway slave, trying to stop her from doing her job.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disturbing the peace and threatening a constable - Case closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="115">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\>, nil \}), "description":"Chinco and Decado were both seen carrying weapons in the common when they have been banned from carrying weapons", "name":"\<font color=green\>carrying prohibited weapons - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="116">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Drew a weapon on Nisha, then attacked her with his hands until defeated by her and Kay.He then continued to harrass and annoy her and others", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Nisha - Case Open - No suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="117">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"The alleged, Tsubasa, is hereby accused of assualt against Captain Geradan and Admiral Flynn.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="118">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"The alleged assaulter and kidnapper Tremain kept several citizens trapped within the new Infirmary and proceeded to bully and attack while in full armor and armed.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault, Kidnapping - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="119">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Taunka walked in on Sir Edmond, Brooks, and Miss Elgin in the cafe. He interrupted their conversation, speaking to the knight. the knight asked him to wait, he would not and kept interrupting, answering back, saying it was a public place and he could enter and speak as he wished", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disturbing a noble - Criminal Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="120">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:xe:xena0\> \}), "description":"Xena came into the West commons and started insulting Taunka and yelling because he called the clothes in the box trash, said he insulted her and wanted to duel.He told her he had heard duels were illegal, so she said she will show him illegal and punched him in the face. He then left to talk to a noble of her house.\\"", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assaulting Taunka in the common - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="121">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\>, nil \}), "description":"Reports have been made that Messrs. Geradan and Flynn did on the seventh Hunter assault Mister Tsubasa.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Tsubasa - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="122">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Caelith did apparently assault Nix with a spear near the old grove.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Nix - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="123">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ni:nix\> \}), "description":"Nix did apparently try to convince Caelith to join him to the Infirmary, and a brawl did ensue. \<p\>Caelith is also attempting to charge Nix with theft for stealing his spear, which is a minor charge as it has since been returned.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault against Caelith - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="124">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"", "name":"\<font color=black\>don't look here, nothing to see\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="125">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Reports have been made that by by his writings on the public boards Mister Cosmo Esposito did cause insult and disrespect to the nobility.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disrespecting Nobles - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="126">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Keiji attacked both the slave Ryan and a constabulary member with a sharp rock.  He cut Ryan's head and bruised the constabulary member's chest.  Keiji repeatedly insulted the Constabulary during this time.  Also, the people present were disturbed by the public fighting, and it was a considerable disturbance to an otherwise peaceful day.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault, Insult to Constabulary, Disturbing the Peace - Accused fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="127">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ry:ryan\> \}), "description":"When mister Keiji assaulted him and another constabulary member with a sharp rock, the Constable moved in to stop the violence.  The slave Ryan shouted at the Constable, \\"Don't fuckin' interfere!\\"", "name":"\<font color=green\>Disrespecting the Constabulary - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="128">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Doctor Grace did reputably heal Captain Swan's slave without his consent, knowing that he was a slave and that his injuries were a punishment. This has interfered with the slave's training.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Tampering with a slave's training - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="129">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Miss Ameko was accused of pickpocketing miss Donatella.  \<br\>\<br\>", "name":"\<font color=brown\>Theft - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="130">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Geradan accused Agia of being a whore, and tried to recruit her to work at a brothel.When she refused he became insulting and cut up her shirt", "name":"\<font color=green\>Harrassing Agia - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="131">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Ameko pickpoketed ten denarii from nisha", "name":"\<font color=green\>Pickpocketing Nisha\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="132">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\> \}), "description":"Luciano was in the common. He had a disagreement with Niko, and attacked him with his rapier. He then attacked the slave Ryan who defended niko, and Faile, who defended her property.He afterwards went on to make threats against Faile, Niko and the slave Ryan", "name":"\<font color=red\>Assault of Niko and Faile in the common - CASE OPEN, LUCIANO TO BE ARRESTED\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="133">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Ameko attacked Sonya with a sword, cutting her hand. Sonya defended herself and cut Ameko in the face", "name":"\<font color=green\>attacking sonya - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="134">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Reports have been made that on ninth day of Night Gerada Cloudspinner did assault Ivante and Crina, wounding Mister Ivante and threatening Miss Crina.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Ivante and behaving in a threatening manner towards Crina - Case open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="135">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:wh:whie\> \}), "description":"During a disagreement in the common, Whie attacked Niko, injuring him.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault of Niko and ivante in the common - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="136">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil, \<Chatters:IC:cl:clover\> \}), "description":"Niko was heard in the common admitting to helping murder Rankin with some of 'Clovers boys'. Clover and his men were previously seen dragging Rankin off by witnesses.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Murder of Rankin - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="137">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"This woman did announce that she followed the old ways, and refused to acknowledge the Light in the presence of Sergeant Danae. She then continued to insult the Sergeant, calling her prey, ignorant, a clear disrespect against the authority of the constabulary.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Heresy and disrespecting constabulary - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="138">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Niko assaulted Vaan after Vaan insulted Rhea.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault on Vaan - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="139">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:tu:turvel\>, nil, \<Chatters:IC:in:inalla\> \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Ryan the slave has reported that he saw Turvel and Kalie carrying the body of Chinco away and that they said that Caelith had dueled him to the death. Inalla and Jacob were there and according to Ryan did not want to report the crime.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Murder of Chinco - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="14">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ nil \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:br:brendon0\> \}), "description":"Brendon participated in an illegal duel with Geradan which resulted in Geradan's death due to a fatal blow to the throat.", "name":" \<font color=green\>Murder of Geradan - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="140">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Kalie attacked Brenner (Assault) in the common with his sword (Disturbing the Peace by drawing a weapon), while Brenner was conversing with Noe. Other Doloreaux guards in the common made no move to stop Kalie's attacks until Brenner was taken to his knees.Brenner made no move to defend himself, other than pursaude Kalie to cease fighting.Witnesses: Yoshi, Althea, Kaitlyn, Kalie's woman, Caelith, Thompson, Gina, Lilly, Fips, Clover, Milli, and a Ramsfors.", "name":"\<font color=Red\>Assault of Brenner in the common - CASE OPEN - KALIE TO BE ARRESTED\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="141">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:va:valentin\> \}), "description":"Joshua and Lianaar were having a discussion in the common about the legal inplication of a particular plan of Valantin an Lianaar. When Joshua told them ther plans were not legal, Valantin openly suggested flouting the law, commenting to Linaaar \\"... judging by how people hack each other apart in the commons without reprimand, I doubt there will be an issue. It is very unlikely for a Constable to be around for a fight.\\"", "name":"\<font color=green\>Openly suggesting criminal activity in the common and disrespecting the constabulary - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="142">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil, nil, \<Chatters:AE:ki:kirill\> \}), "description":"Niko and Kirill were brawling in the lounge. Zeiss managed to ge them to desist. Niko left and Rhea arrived and proceeded to attack Kirill, and threaten Zeiss for trying to get her to stand down.Niko returned and Niko and Rhea threatened Kirill's life.An unknown cocker-spaniel woman was goading them all in this fight", "name":"\<font color=green\>Fighting in the Boarding house lounge - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="143">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ma:malenki\> \}), "description":"Zeiss asked Miya to write a report to the constabulary. When miya didn't want to, Zeiss yelled at him and Miya spat on Zeiss's cloak. Zeiss dragged Miya forcibly to the arena, hitting him with his whip and threatening him with a sword, before taking Miya's money, which was approximately 65 denari.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Miya - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="144">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:sw:swan\>, nil \}), "description":"Swan kidnapped Temperance until Zeiss paid him. possibly she was in on it.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Kidnapping  of Temperance and extortion of Zeiss - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="145">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Envoy Brooks was found murdered in the hallway outside his bedroom door, with his throat torn open by teeth.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Murder of Envoy Brooks - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="146">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Fin has been accused of being a pickpocket. Each separate instance will add to the severity of her crime.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Pickpocketing - Accused fled city\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="147">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ma:malenki\> \}), "description":"Whilst seeking a woman charged with theft, Sergeant Danae was harassed and insulted by Hearken Zeiss. He also accused her of serving demons.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Disrespecting the constabulary and interfering with an investigation - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="148">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:li:limwik\>, \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\> \}), "description":"Luciano was threatning Limwik with a sword. Limwik was threatning to poison Luciano.", "name":"\<font color=red\>Disturbing the peace - CASE OPEN, LUCIANO TO BE ARRESTED\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="149">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ma:mari\> \}), "description":"Pookie was teasing Mari in the common for having hair on her tounge. Mari attacked pookie with her mace", "name":"\<font color=Black\>Attacking Pookie with a mace - Case closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="15">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"He killed Dio out of spite for what he'd done to Una.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Murder of Dio - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="150">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Fin tried to pickpocket people in the common and attacked Meepers when caught.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Attempted pickpocketing and assault of Meepers - Criminal Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="151">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Jimmy was a pirate on Black Pete's ship.During the battle he turned on his Captain, and rendered him unconscious, allowing a swift victory for the Triskellion forces.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Piracy - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="152">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ma:mari\> \}), "description":"After a spar, while waiting for the healers, Mari attacked Luciano", "name":"\<font color=Green\>Attacking Luciano - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="153">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\> \}), "description":"Mari was attacked and slain in the common.", "name":"\<font color=green\>murder of mari - case open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="154">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\> \}), "description":"Luciano caused a scene in the infirmary, despite requests that he leave.", "name":"\<font color=red\>Causing a scene in the Infirmary - CASE OPEN, LUCIANO TO BE ARRESTED\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="155">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Edmond, Brenner and Noe was talking about Geradan's wife Lia, who is a slave. Geradan too offense and insulted Edmond", "name":"\<font color=black\>Insulting Sir Edmond and disturbing the peace - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="156">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ad:adonis\>, nil, \<Chatters:AE:ma:maximilian\> \}), "description":"Participating in immoral acts with other men", "name":"\<font color=green\>Immoral acts\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="157">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ad:adonis\> \}), "description":"Adonis was speaking blasphemy against the teachings of S'Allumer", "name":"\<font color=green\>Blasphemy\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="158">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Twice, masked, Tibbs the ferret assaulted an officer of the law. Once in the middle of the commons. Both times unprovoked.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault on officer of the Constabulary x 2, Fighting in Public - Accused Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="159">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ab:abel\>, nil \}), "description":"Nuit and Abel participated in immoral behaviour along with another unnamed person", "name":"\<font color=green\>Immoral Behaviour - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="16">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Disrespected him by ignoring, and being insulting by not listening to him.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Insulting Baron Reyaurd - No Suspect\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="160">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Gerald attacked and seriously wounded Kafka.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Attacking Kafka in the inn - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="161">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ab:abel\> \}), "description":"Tibbs was killed by Abel", "name":"\<font color=green\>Murder of Tibbs - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="162">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Tibbs has been accused of numerous counts of bloody assault on mister Limwik, mister Abel, miss Darlene, Deputy Kafka and various others. He caused a scence in the commons and verbally abused several nobles. ", "name":"\<font color=brown\>Assault of Limwik - Accused Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="163">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:si:silkar\> \}), "description":"Silkar killed Mari with poison tea.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Poisoning of Mari - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="164">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ab:abel\> \}), "description":"Abel insulted Kafka in the west commons", "name":"\<font color=green\>Disrespect of the Deputy Kafka- Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="165">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Darlene's body was found cut up in a box", "name":"\<font color=brown\>Murder of Darlene - No suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="166">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Snortimier is accused of attacking Liala and Miya and attempting to eat them, and injuring Gentlewoman diDraco in the event.", "name":"\<font color=orange\>Assault of Meepers, Liala and Miya - Case Active\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="19">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:sh:shania\> \}), "description":"Killed the slave Maymay, who was in moderate health, believing that it was a \\"mercy killing\\"", "name":"\<font color=black\>Property Damage - Killing Maymay - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="20">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Geradan apparently assulted Maymay and Keiji while they were in the jail. He reportedly threatened to kill them both if they didn't stop 'messing' with Lianaar.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Assault of Maymay and Keiji - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="21">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Keiji was visiting the slave maymay and expressed anger at her enforcer Geradan. Geradan was passing, overheard this, and invited Keiji to attack him if he wished. Keiji drew his weapon and attacked Geradan. Geradan drew his blade and defeated Keiji", "name":"\<font color=brown\>Assault of Geradan - Suspect Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="23">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:eb:eberhard\>, nil, \<Chatters:IC:ry:ryan\> \}), "description":"Ryan, Eberhard's slave stabbed Tobias Greeves in the Common.Because Ryan is a slave Eberhard is legally responsible for him, which is why the charges are against Eberhard, and not Ryan.Eberhard is out of town currently and has left care of his slaves to his assistant, Miss Aimi.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Ryan stabbing Greeves - Case Open for Aimi\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="24">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:gr:greeves\> \}), "description":"Greeves was howling in the West Commons constantly and I've been told hes been told to be quiet but he didn't stop and continued his howling. His smell too, violates the law of disturbing the peace", "name":"\<font color=black\>Disturbing the peace in the West Commons - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="25">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ge:gemma\> \}), "description":"She punched Brother Ximen in the west commons.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Assault - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="26">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Amidst the commons today Calvin was antagonizing my citizens (Lennox, Cullan, myself). It ended with him assaulting a Doloreaux Guard, Mister Abel. Severely bruising his stomach. [The character Calvin has been deleted]", "name":"\<font color=brown\>Assault, Insulting a Noble, Fighting in Public Places - Suspect Fled\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="27">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:va:valentin\> \}), "description":"Araceli was found dead by the docks, with dire wounds to her head and chest. Her body was found by Lian. From his statement the body was covered with a light dusting of snow and had been there for some time.", "name":"\<font color=green\>Murder of Araceli - Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="28">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:va:valentin\> \}), "description":"He has insulted Baron Tomas with his recent actions. From his behavior towards Baron Tomas's retainer Miss Araceli, to how he left his House and the Avoirdupois.", "name":"\<font color=black\>Insult to a Noble - Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="29">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:gr:greeves\> \}), "description":"Greeves stole a Constabulary uniform, and went around town claiming to be a new guard", "name":"Stealing a uniform and impersonating a constabulary officer - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="30">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Insulted nobles in the common, and pickpocketed four denarii from Sir Erwin", "name":"Theft - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="31">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Dame Morven's bodyguard, Mister Caelith, and Dame Morven herself, found Greeves lying unconscious, nude and bruised in the boarding house stairwell, and then brought him to the lounge where he was dressed and treated. During this, Greeves had a blank stare on his face and wouldn't stop drooling, and was obviously suffering from brain damaged.Following this, Greeves passed away in the lounge under the care of Dame Morven.We are looking for any leads, Anyone with any ideas who did this please come forward.", "name":"Assault and murder of Greeves \<font color=green\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="32">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"Lianaar, after noticing the disappeance of Saffi, sent her slaves Ryan and Rocher into the sewers in search of her, only to find her corpse propped up against a gate and cut at the neck.", "name":"Murder of sailor Saffi - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="33">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\>, \<Chatters:Backup:IC:cu:cullan0\>, nil \}), "description":"Valentin was found murdered on the Pier. The first people there were Geradan, Cullan, Caelith, and Tsubasa.Tsubasa came to find us.When we arrived valentin had a Rapier next to him and Had bruises and cuts all over his body.Deputy mazti was the first to make it to the scene.", "name":"Murder of Valentin - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="34">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Rhea came into the jail while officers were questioning Geradan, and was obnoxious and ignored their request to leave", "name":"Interferring with an investigation - harrassing constabulary officers - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="35">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Geradan commited various accounts of Disrespect towards an officer after his assault on Deputy Kafka during questioning, he has told Matzi to 'please eat his cock' and told us many times to 'go fook ourselves'Let it be known that the Constabulary did not oblige to any of Geradan's grotesque demands.", "name":"Assault and Disrespect of an Officer - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="36">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Kafka attacked Geradan from behind while Geradan was attempting to leave the jailhouse during questioning.", "name":"Kafka attacking Geradan - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="37">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Mister Chinco has been charged with disrespect to the Constabulary. This is because, after being summoned by Miss Althea to the site of a duel in the training courtyard, it appeared that Mister Chinco and Mister Caelith had issued challenges and the situation had not been resolved. Upon being informed that the duel was none of our (Deputy Belgarion and Deputy Arthurr) authority, we went to leave. However at that point Mister Chinco began commanding us to leave and even referred to Deputy Belgarion as an \\"idiot\\". At this point, it was considered disrespect had been given as Deputy Belgarion was only doing his duty. So, after removing weapons and belongings, he was arrested and placed in the jail for one day.", "name":"Disrespect to Constabulary - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="38">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Scroll from Dame Charlot: I write this to you on the 1st day of Grass. I have just been robbed by one Samael, a gangling rabbit, with an interesting line of chat.When I demanded the 3 denarii back, he said maybe he'd give it, but I have to catch him first. Sounds like an admission to me, and I wish him detained and charged.", "name":"Theft, Disrespect to noble - \<font color=crimson\>\<b\>CASE ACTIVE - Samael to be arrested\</b\>\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="39">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Mister Chinco attack Anrai in the west commons.I was informed of this by Mister sang. When I arrived Chinco then came after me. Sir Erwin arrived to help handle chinco.", "name":"Assault, Resisting Arrest - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="40">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Haruka was  in the commons when Samael came in and pickpocketed her.", "name":"Theft  - \<font color=GREEN\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="41">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Joshua and Brooks were talking in the common, Chinco came in and joined in the conversation, making some remarks about the constabulary. Brooks made a comment and Chinco took offese, damanging a duel, and attacking Brooks when he was refused, then Joshua who stepped in to stop him, and Nix, who stepped in to calm his down", "name":"Attacking Brooks, Joshua and Nix in the common - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="42">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco threw an apple at Nix in the common, and then attacked Nix when Nix asked if he was trying to start something.", "name":"Assault against Nix - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="43">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Samael kissed Sunta in the commons, and attempted to steal her purse while distracting her with said kiss. (See attached testimony by Sunta for more detail).", "name":"Attempted Theft and Sexual Assault - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="44">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Sang was found in an alley by a lion, his cut throat assumed to be the cause of his death.His coins were intact in his purse, and rings and bracelet were also still on his body when found. He had two injuries, a cut to the shoulder, and a significant cut to the throat. He smelt of fox, cat, and faintly of rodent. However the cat may have been from the lion carrying him, and the rodent may be from the course of investigation, my own scent.", "name":"Murder of Sang - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="45">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Wynter was found in an ally with her throat cut. Body was found by Brother Ximen", "name":"Murder of Wynter - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="46">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Kaitlyn was found dead west of the common, with her throat cut. Body was found by Captain Marcus", "name":"Murder of Kaitlyn - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="47">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Fips was found dead right after being seen along with Cale.", "name":"Murder of Fips - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="48">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Sang, Wynter, Fips and Kaitlyn were all found dead.Sang was found in an alley with his throat cut, Kaitlyn and Wynter were found the next day, killed in the same fashion and Fips was found a day later, also with his throat cut", "name":"Murders of Sang, Wynter, Fips and Kaitlyn - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="49">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"Xavios has been inciting the people to war against the church.", "name":"Heresy - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="50">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"xavios assulted a member of the church", "name":"Assault - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="51">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\>, nil \}), "description":"Caelith and Xavios attacked a group of people attempting to arrest them under Sheriff Joshua's orders.Caelith's charge has been lowered, due to being a bodyguard at the time, and acting in the defense of his client, who was reputedly attacked before being placed under arrest. ~ Sergeant Danae", "name":"Assault / Assault in Defence- \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="52">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco has spoken in a heretical manner and publicly claims to follow no religion and come from a Phelan background", "name":"Heresy - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="53">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Sade and Shyme asked Lord Marcus where the Docktown bathing area was, There Sade started stealing coins from Marcus' satchel and got away.", "name":"Pickpocket - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="54">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"Xavios attacked Ximen with the intent to murder him, leaving several people badly injured", "name":"Attempted murder and assault of Ximen - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="55">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ma:malenki\> \}), "description":"Slave Master Haerken Zeiss has confessed to the murder of the Reeve of Triskellian, the Gentry Leah. Normal Charge because Leah is of the Gentry, but he did turn himself in.If anyone believes further charges should be added, please contact Sergeant Danae, or another officer.", "name":"Murder of Leah - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="56">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco was publicly badmouthing the church and Ximen's practices.He apparently also attacked a Paladin who was attempting to calm him, and broke his nose", "name":"Acting against the Church and harrassing church members - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="57">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ma:malenki\> \}), "description":"Zeiss did attack the Triskellian Reeve, Leah, and then hold her against her will. Due to her position as a direct servant of the Don, he is also being charged for minor treason. Assault charge dropped due to already being charged with greater charge of murder.", "name":"Kidnapping of Leah and associated charges - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="58">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"The Paladin Branwen did press a blade to Abigail's throat in the commons, and caused a scene that was disrupting.", "name":"Assaulting Abigail in the commons - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="59">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\>, \<Chatters:AE:xi:ximen\>, nil \}), "description":"The Prelate was found murdered, and now rests in the cathedral.", "name":"Murder of Prelate Adriana - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="60">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ko:koz\> \}), "description":"A girl ran into the lounge of the tavern and asked for help. Then Koz ran in trying to hurt her, then everybody else tried to protect her. He harmed Sang and Meepers before being beaten himself. He then attacked Miss Lianaar.", "name":"Assault and Disturbing the peace - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="61">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"slav pickpocketed from geradan in front of witnesses. When pressured, he returned the money", "name":"pickpocketing - \<font color=black\>Charge dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="62">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Sang was standing in the commons, talking to Mistress Meepers. Then Chinco arrived, tossed a beer mug in the bin and decided he did not like Sang and pulled out his blade. He was convinced to put his blade away but he decided to punch Sang anyway.", "name":"Assault - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="63">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Mister Chinco assaulted Envoy Brooks after a mild exchange of words.  He grabbed the Envoy by his throat and choked him with Deputy Jace as witness.  After ignoring multiple attempts to diffuse Chinco's actions with words, threat of taking action was made.  Chinco then released the Envoy, and promptly drew his weapon in a threatening manner with multiple witnesses present.", "name":"Assault, Disrespecting a Constable, Disturbing the Peace - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="64">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Bek continued to provide unwelcome attention to Crina after he was asked to desist.", "name":"Harrassment - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="65">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Gerard was found dead in a room with Admiral G. Flynn, and the admiral has been accused of the victim's murder.", "name":"Murder of Gerard - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="66">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"According to witnesses, Chinco has assaulted Misters Gerard and Sang, later his insulted Baron Tomas, and refused to accompany a Deputy to the jail.", "name":"Assault, Disrespecting a Noble, and preventing an arrest - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="67">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Geradan Cloudspinner assaulted Chinco during an arrest.", "name":"Assault - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="68">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gu:gus\>, nil \}), "description":"Assaulted Harken and attempted to murder him and Lianaar.", "name":"Assault against zeiss - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="69">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Lianaar was training a slave in the common and became argumentative with Sir Bayard when he requested that she move to the company property", "name":"Public nuisance and insult to a noble - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="7">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:wh:whie\> \}), "description":"Whie attacked and wounded Sheriff Joshua, then resisted arrest and refused to give up his weapons, resulting in several people being injured trying to get him to submit, including Sir Matteo.", "name":"Assault - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="70">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\>, nil \}), "description":"Mallory was beaten at the Docks by Egaeus and Geradan.", "name":"Assualt of Mallory \<font color=brown\>Case Closed for Egaeus.\</font\>\<font color=green\> Case open for Geradan\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="71">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Meepers and Lia have reported being attacked by a masked assailant, who rambles about beauty, both received blows to the face as has Analay and Desideria.", "name":"Assault of Meepers, Assault of Lia, Murder of Analay, murder of Desideria - \<font color=green\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="72">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Body found with various wounds. Some of them puncture wounds, therefore perhaps not the same killer as the other women.", "name":"Murder of Shania - \<font color=green\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="73">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Nika was putting up broadsheets to incite rebellion against the nobles", "name":"Trying in incite rebellion against nobles - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="74">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ nil \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\>, \<Chatters:IC:gr:greeves\> \}), "description":"Geradan and Greeves had a public dispute, which turned into a brawl, during said brawl Kaine attempted to break it up, causing assaults on him from both parties and Egaeus.", "name":"Disturbing the peace and assault - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed for Egaeus. \</font\>\<font color=green\>Case open for Greeves and Geradan\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="75">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"A masked man attacked Miss Sadie on the Docks. He attacked her face and arms leaving many cuts. He also touched her improperly. Suspect is believed to be a small rodent with light-coloured fur.", "name":"Assault of Sadie - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="76">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\>, \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"Xavios and Chinco did apparently threaten the pastor, thinking his punishments not sufficient for planning the murder of the prelate.", "name":"Threatening Ximen, disturbing the peace - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="77">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Decado attacked Joshua in his office, threatening to kill him, and attacked Deputy Biggs and Kheiron when they came in and defended Joshua", "name":"Assult against Joshua, Biggs and Kheiron - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="78">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Kheiron came into the docktown arena where Dio had been sparring with Decado, and killed Dio.", "name":"Murder of Dio - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="79">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:xa:xavios\> \}), "description":"Xavios is reported to have entered the Dock Town Chapel and have murdered Ximen. He was also heard to be bragging and openly talking about it afterwards.", "name":"Murder of Presbyter Ximen - \<font color=green\>Case Open for Chinco\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="80">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Mister Kaurhen was found outside the jail house with various wounds of dire ones being to the throat and groin areas.", "name":"Murder of Kauhren - \<font color=red\>No Suspects\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="81">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:ro:roofus\> \}), "description":"Reports have been made that Mister Roofus is inciting slaves to act against free people and suggesting they hire assassins.", "name":"Inciting slaves - \<font color=green\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="82">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco and Echelon attacked multiple people in the commons, resisted arrest, and dealt lethal damage", "name":"Attempted murder in the commons \<font color=brown\>Case Closed against Chinco,\</font\>\<font color=green\> Case Open against Echelon\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="83">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\>, nil, \<Chatters:IC:ro:roofus\> \}), "description":"case closed", "name":"Distrubing the peace on the Docks - \<font color=black\>Charge dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="84">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ nil \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Reports are that Geradan assaulted the Viscountess. During the fracas Tito was also assaulted, and Cullan was killed. Geradan was assisted by Zeera", "name":"Assault of Viscountess Kenina, Murder of Cullan, Assault of Tito - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed against Geradan.\</font\>\<font color=green\> Case Open against Zeera\</font\>," ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="85">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Public posting believed to be disrespectful to Sir Matteo.", "name":"Disrespect to nobles - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="86">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Reports are that Echelon assaulted Tomar and a lion in the commons.", "name":"Assault of Tomar and one other - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="87">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco started another brawl in the commons.", "name":"Causing another ruckus in the commons - \<font color=brown\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="88">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chinco0\> \}), "description":"Chinco ran into the newtown jail, killed Zeera, and attacked Geradan, nearly killing him, and Rankin, injuring him.", "name":"Assult and murder in the newtown jail - \<font color=green\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="89">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"File describes Echelon treating officers and not sheathing a weapon when told to do so.", "name":"Disturbing the peace and disrestpecing officers in the commons. - \<font color=green\>Case closed - Echelon to be arrested, but character deleted\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="90">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":"Danae has been acting crazily in public and attacking people since being ressurected", "name":"causing a disturbance and attacking people - \<font color=green\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="91">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:gr:greeves\> \}), "description":"Greeves shot Sir Erwin with his pistol", "name":"Shooting a noble with his pistol - \<font color=green\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="92">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"Geradan assaulted Deputy Isaacs in the Gaol.", "name":"Assualt in the Gaol - \<font color=green\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="93">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:ge:geradan\> \}), "description":"No really, nothing to see here", "name":"*nothing to see here* - \<font color=green\>Charge dropped\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="94">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"A masked wolf named tattoo (OOC: Cailean) claimed in the commons that he destroyed a slave named Sophie, property of Bek, and that he assisted in the murder of Sir Matteo", "name":"Destruction of a slave and accomplice to murder of Sir Matteo by masked wolf known as tattoo - \<font color=green\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="95">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Reparts made that Malazi pickpocketed one denarii from Miss Jackie.", "name":"Pickpocketing in the east commons - \<font color=red\>No Suspect\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="96">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:sh:shania\> \}), "description":"Shania continuously disrespected me in the Boarding house, trying to countermind my investigation of a apparent crime", "name":"Disrespecting Constabulary - \<font color=red\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="97">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "description":"Echelon attacked and wounded Tomar, who was already badly injured", "name":"Assult against Tomar - \<font color=red\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="98">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:IC:sh:shania\> \}), "description":"Shania repeatedly insulted the sheriff with lies about himself, in public, and refused an order to leave the jail", "name":"Disrespecting the sheriff - \<font color=crimson\>\<b\>CASE ACTIVE - Shania to be arrested!\</font\>\</b\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="99">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ nil \}), "description":".", "name":"" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="number">167</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1232330373, "jominey", "E", 1232330398, "jominey", "E", 1232334107, "jominey", "E", 1232334122, "jominey", "E", 1232337785, "jominey", "E", 1232337807, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
