<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="referrence"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             reference for Jahren's re-build
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Doctor Jahren is a tall athletic rabbit, with short, silky light brown fur, and fine brown hair, worn in spikes. Sharp brown eyes are set above a short nose and thin lips. Short stubby claws, on strong hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his light  eyebrows and expressive  ears.  He is carrying a ripe red tomato, a clay pot, a burgundy suede money pouch, an odd mushroom, a pair of black snake skin gloves, a handsaw, an anise teabag, two packages, an invitation, a copper dagger sheath, a storm grey leather tricorn hat, a pair of silver spectacles, a sheathed steel rapier, a light red leather satchel, a light blue leather satchel, a pair of storm grey leather pants, a storm grey damask long jacket, a rich vanilla damask ruffled shirt, a black leather double-wrap belt, a pair of black leather fingerless gloves and a pair of black leather knee-high boots.  Additional notes - Scarred, scar-marred? - right side, libidinous abs, robust thighs.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Doctor Jahren is a tall athletic rabbit, with short, silky light brown fur, and fine brown hair, worn in spikes. Sharp brown eyes are set above a short nose and thin lips. Short stubby claws, on strong hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his light  eyebrows and expressive  ears.  He is carrying a ripe red tomato, a clay pot, a burgundy suede money pouch, an odd mushroom, a pair of black snake skin gloves, a handsaw, an anise teabag, two packages, an invitation, a copper dagger sheath, a storm grey leather tricorn hat, a pair of silver spectacles, a sheathed steel rapier, a light red leather satchel, a light blue leather satchel, a pair of storm grey leather pants, a storm grey damask long jacket, a rich vanilla damask ruffled shirt, a black leather double-wrap belt, a pair of black leather fingerless gloves and a pair of black leather knee-high boots. Additional notes - Scarred, scar-marred? - right side, libidinous abs, robust thighs.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052085, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1353450011, "lidiab", "K", 1353450072, "lidiab", "E", 1353450089, "lidiab", "E", 1353450176, "lidiab", "K", 1353450209, "lidiab", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="1353450072" state="Open" user="lidiab">
           Garden room == [Ironclaw:World:DockTown:Buildings:BoardingHouse:GuestRoom:Garden]#82017
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
