<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="0.7" density="1.5"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0.2" maxweight="1" verb2="contain" verb3="contains"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="tome"/>
            <Base:SName sname="book"/>
            <Base:SName sname="history"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="stuff"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="tomes"/>
            <Base:PName pname="books"/>
            <Base:PName pname="histories"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="everything"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="blue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="bound"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="leather"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="steel"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome. On the upper portion of the cover is the title of 'A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Learned Personages'. The border of the cover neatly displays blue embossed water ripples. There are eleven chapters contained within these pages.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome. On the upper portion of the cover is the title of 'A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Learned Personages'. The border of the cover neatly displays blue embossed water ripples. There are eleven chapters contained within these pages.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="tome:chapter:count">
             11
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             On the upper portion of the cover is the title of 'A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Learned Personages'.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter01" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="one"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Contents
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> The Contents:<br/><br/> Page Two: Introduction to the History of the Avoirdupois<br/> Page Three: The Ecorcheurs<br/> Page Four: The Creation of the Monarchy<br/> Page Five: The Early Kings<br/> Page Six: Famine and Rebellion<br/> Page Seven: The War of Leaves<br/> Page Eight: Religious Strife<br/> Page Nine: The Siege of Triskellian<br/> Page Ten: The Growth of S'allumer<br/> Page Eleven: The Bisclavret and the Eteignoirs<br/><br/> OOC (Out of Character): Warning, some pages are extremely long.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The Contents:<br/><br/> Page Two: Introduction to the History of the Avoirdupois<br/> Page Three: The Ecorcheurs<br/> Page Four: The Creation of the Monarchy<br/> Page Five: The Early Kings<br/> Page Six: Famine and Rebellion<br/> Page Seven: The War of Leaves<br/> Page Eight: Religious Strife<br/> Page Nine: The Siege of Triskellian<br/> Page Ten: The Growth of S'allumer<br/> Page Eleven: The Bisclavret and the Eteignoirs<br/><br/> OOC (Out of Character): Warning, some pages are extremely long.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter02" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="two"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="beginning"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="opening"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Introduction to the History of the Avoirdupois
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> The oldest histories of the Avoirdupois describe how the twelve original families set sail from their homeland in the wake of numerous portents and omens. Seven more families followed in their wake a year later, and together these settlers colonized the southeastern plains of Calabria.<br/><br/> The most complete records of these early years come from the family histories of these settlers themselves. Traditionally, each of the lineages kept its own record on mats and tightly-plaited grass, passing the growing account from generation to generation. Only a few of the original records still exist. The most complete is the record of the Sabot family: it is now over fifteen paces in length, and the earliest portions, written in a language only distantly similar to modern Calabrese, are over a thousand years old.<br/><br/> The success of the original settlers encouraged further migration, and over the next fifty years, another fourteen houses (including the Boulanger and the Marteau) arrived on the shores of Calabria. Unless the original records are inaccurate, the swamps of the Paludestris must have been neither as expansive nor as dangerous as they are today, for records of that era refer to farms and villages in areas that are now inhabitable.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The oldest histories of the Avoirdupois describe how the twelve original families set sail from their homeland in the wake of numerous portents and omens. Seven more families followed in their wake a year later, and together these settlers colonized the southeastern plains of Calabria.<br/><br/> The most complete records of these early years come from the family histories of these settlers themselves. Traditionally, each of the lineages kept its own record on mats and tightly-plaited grass, passing the growing account from generation to generation. Only a few of the original records still exist. The most complete is the record of the Sabot family: it is now over fifteen paces in length, and the earliest portions, written in a language only distantly similar to modern Calabrese, are over a thousand years old.<br/><br/> The success of the original settlers encouraged further migration, and over the next fifty years, another fourteen houses (including the Boulanger and the Marteau) arrived on the shores of Calabria. Unless the original records are inaccurate, the swamps of the Paludestris must have been neither as expansive nor as dangerous as they are today, for records of that era refer to farms and villages in areas that are now inhabitable.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter03" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="three"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Ecorcheurs
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> The early years of growth and prosperity ended suddenly when the colonists encountered a powerful band of nomads. The histories use the name Ecorcheur interchangeably for both the tribe as a whole and for its leader, a rhinoceros of enormous size and strength.<br/><br/> At first, the Ecorcheurs seemed unstoppable. They moved freely across the countryside, looting as they pleased and killing anyone who resisted them in a variety of gruesome ways. The annals of the Sabot family show a sizable tribute paid to the Ecorcheur; the histories of the other surviving families are suspiciously silent on the matter.<br/><br/> The following tear, the Ecorcheurs moved on to the north, where their rampages continued. Though undefeated in battle, they were unable to cross the Loire and their wanderings eventually brought them back to the lands of the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The Avoirdupois had not been idle during their two-year respite. Ruined villages and towns were rebuilt with simple fortifications, and some were even abandoned in favor of more defensible sites. Perhaps more importantly, the survivors of the previous raids were hardened by the experience and were now determined to resist the invaders.<br/><br/> These changes slowed the advance of the Ecorcheurs but were not sufficient to stop them. Despite the bravery of the defenders, the nomadic horde sacked town after town. One summer morning (traditionally the 2nd day of the month of Thunder, in the year 123 of the S'allumer Calendar), twelve lords met in the ruins of Sauldre to discuss their common plight. A monument now stands in the public square where they pledged their mutual support. Unable to agree on a leader from their own number, they named Gage l'Amorce general of their combined forces.<br/><br/> Gage had long advocated combined action against the nomads. His only son had been killed during the first incursion of the Ecorcheursand he had spent the intervening years writing letters attempting to unite his fellows against the threat that he knew would eventually return. Copies of his correspondence attest to the deep divisions present among the various families, and despite the eloquence of his appeals, they were given little attention while the Ecorcheur were away.<br/><br/> One famous letter tells how Gage, overwhelmed by despair and about to abandon his dream of unification, was overcome by a "fantastic light, purer and more powerful than the sun," renewing his purpose and leaving him feeling "as if the pain of all the years had been burned away." While some would believe that this was a sign that Gage--who was at least nominally a Heliodrome--had had a vision of S'allumer, the letter's authenticity is considered suspect, even by official Church historians.<br/><br/> Once named general of the allied forces, Gage requisitioned every available jennet, courser, and palfrey and recognized the various family militias as mounted infantry. Some popular accounts portray Gage as leading a host of cavalry, but historical sources clearly show that the battles of this period were primarily fought on foot. Gage also established a network of messengers and signal towers that kept him well apprised of developments across the realm. Together, these innovations allowed him to follow the movements of the Ecorcheurs from a safe distance and to maneuver his forces swiftly in response.<br/><br/> By the following spring, Gage was ready to confront the Ecorcheurs directly. More families had joined his alliance, and his troops had gained much-needed experience and confidxence from skirmishes with the nomads. Gage maneuvered carefully: he had no intention of engaging in any battles not of his choosing. On the last day of the month of Flowers, he attacked the Ecorcheur near the shores of Lake Aube.<br/><br/> The battle was fierce and bloody, with heavy losses on both sides. Gage lost his shield hand, and even the mighty leader of the Ecorcheur was wounded. By the end of the day, it was the Ecorcheur who were forced to withdraw from the field. While technically victorious, Gage is said to have remarked that "another such victory will leave us a nation of ghosts." Nevertheless, he grimly set about preparing for a second battle.<br/><br/> In the subsequent weeks, it was rumored that the leader of the Ecorcheurs was weakening: his wounds were not healing properly and he suffered from fevers. A popular story tells how the chief, rather than succumb to the infection that had spread throughout his body, removed himself to a "secret place" where, amidst the splendor of his plundered wealth, he killed his wives and then himself. The continuing popularity of the story is probably connected with the possibility of finding the hidden treasure. Most scholars discount the story, considering it more likely that the Ecorcheur chief either succumbed to his wounds or was murdered by an ambitious lieutenant.<br/><br/> With its great leader gone, the Ecorcheur horde began to dissolve. The process accelerated when the Avoirdupois won a decisive victory outside Sauldre later that summer, and by the end of the month of Green, the barbarian army was no more.<br/><br/><br/> For the Avoirdupois, the price of the victory was high: of the thirty-three traditional family lines, eight (including Gage's own) were extinguished in the conflict with the Ecorcheurs. None of the surviving families were without losses, and the countryside would require many years to recover from the war's devastation.<br/><br/> With the threat of the Ecorcheurs removed, Gage turned to the problem of of reconstruction. He put the army to work building roads between the larger villages and used his influence with the great families to prevent the resurgence of their petty rivalries. These achievements only increased his popularity: when the great general died at the age of 70 (in 141), he was mourned by his entire people.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The early years of growth and prosperity ended suddenly when the colonists encountered a powerful band of nomads. The histories use the name Ecorcheur interchangeably for both the tribe as a whole and for its leader, a rhinoceros of enormous size and strength.<br/><br/> At first, the Ecorcheurs seemed unstoppable. They moved freely across the countryside, looting as they pleased and killing anyone who resisted them in a variety of gruesome ways. The annals of the Sabot family show a sizable tribute paid to the Ecorcheur; the histories of the other surviving families are suspiciously silent on the matter.<br/><br/> The following tear, the Ecorcheurs moved on to the north, where their rampages continued. Though undefeated in battle, they were unable to cross the Loire and their wanderings eventually brought them back to the lands of the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The Avoirdupois had not been idle during their two-year respite. Ruined villages and towns were rebuilt with simple fortifications, and some were even abandoned in favor of more defensible sites. Perhaps more importantly, the survivors of the previous raids were hardened by the experience and were now determined to resist the invaders.<br/><br/> These changes slowed the advance of the Ecorcheurs but were not sufficient to stop them. Despite the bravery of the defenders, the nomadic horde sacked town after town. One summer morning (traditionally the 2nd day of the month of Thunder, in the year 123 of the S'allumer Calendar), twelve lords met in the ruins of Sauldre to discuss their common plight. A monument now stands in the public square where they pledged their mutual support. Unable to agree on a leader from their own number, they named Gage l'Amorce general of their combined forces.<br/><br/> Gage had long advocated combined action against the nomads. His only son had been killed during the first incursion of the Ecorcheursand he had spent the intervening years writing letters attempting to unite his fellows against the threat that he knew would eventually return. Copies of his correspondence attest to the deep divisions present among the various families, and despite the eloquence of his appeals, they were given little attention while the Ecorcheur were away.<br/><br/> One famous letter tells how Gage, overwhelmed by despair and about to abandon his dream of unification, was overcome by a "fantastic light, purer and more powerful than the sun," renewing his purpose and leaving him feeling "as if the pain of all the years had been burned away." While some would believe that this was a sign that Gage--who was at least nominally a Heliodrome--had had a vision of S'allumer, the letter's authenticity is considered suspect, even by official Church historians.<br/><br/> Once named general of the allied forces, Gage requisitioned every available jennet, courser, and palfrey and recognized the various family militias as mounted infantry. Some popular accounts portray Gage as leading a host of cavalry, but historical sources clearly show that the battles of this period were primarily fought on foot. Gage also established a network of messengers and signal towers that kept him well apprised of developments across the realm. Together, these innovations allowed him to follow the movements of the Ecorcheurs from a safe distance and to maneuver his forces swiftly in response.<br/><br/> By the following spring, Gage was ready to confront the Ecorcheurs directly. More families had joined his alliance, and his troops had gained much-needed experience and confidxence from skirmishes with the nomads. Gage maneuvered carefully: he had no intention of engaging in any battles not of his choosing. On the last day of the month of Flowers, he attacked the Ecorcheur near the shores of Lake Aube.<br/><br/> The battle was fierce and bloody, with heavy losses on both sides. Gage lost his shield hand, and even the mighty leader of the Ecorcheur was wounded. By the end of the day, it was the Ecorcheur who were forced to withdraw from the field. While technically victorious, Gage is said to have remarked that "another such victory will leave us a nation of ghosts." Nevertheless, he grimly set about preparing for a second battle.<br/><br/> In the subsequent weeks, it was rumored that the leader of the Ecorcheurs was weakening: his wounds were not healing properly and he suffered from fevers. A popular story tells how the chief, rather than succumb to the infection that had spread throughout his body, removed himself to a "secret place" where, amidst the splendor of his plundered wealth, he killed his wives and then himself. The continuing popularity of the story is probably connected with the possibility of finding the hidden treasure. Most scholars discount the story, considering it more likely that the Ecorcheur chief either succumbed to his wounds or was murdered by an ambitious lieutenant.<br/><br/> With its great leader gone, the Ecorcheur horde began to dissolve. The process accelerated when the Avoirdupois won a decisive victory outside Sauldre later that summer, and by the end of the month of Green, the barbarian army was no more.<br/><br/><br/> For the Avoirdupois, the price of the victory was high: of the thirty-three traditional family lines, eight (including Gage's own) were extinguished in the conflict with the Ecorcheurs. None of the surviving families were without losses, and the countryside would require many years to recover from the war's devastation.<br/><br/> With the threat of the Ecorcheurs removed, Gage turned to the problem of of reconstruction. He put the army to work building roads between the larger villages and used his influence with the great families to prevent the resurgence of their petty rivalries. These achievements only increased his popularity: when the great general died at the age of 70 (in 141), he was mourned by his entire people.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter04" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="four"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Creation of the Monarchy
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> Without Gage's unifying influence, old divisions began to reassert themselves. Families that had fought side by side against the Ecorcheurs now watched each other warily and bickered over imagined slights. By the year 150, eleven of the families had armies in the field actively campaigning against one another.<br/><br/> To be sure, these new armies were much smaller than the Ecorcheur horde or Gage's allied host. Lacking the manpower for large formations of the previous era, the new captains looked for ways to increase the effectiveness of their individual soldiers. Heavier weapons and armor became the norm, and increasingly intensive training for the soldiers and their mounts allowed the mounted infantry of Gage's day (who used their mounts for transport to battle) to evolve into true cavalry (who used their mounts for transport in battle).<br/><br/> Of all the families, the Boulanger were most able to take advantage of the chaos. The head of the family, Paien du Boulanger, was not only a clever tactician, but he had also married General Gage's daughter Orane. He was also advised by his younger brother Amical, one of the greatest minds of the era.<br/><br/> Unlike most of his contemporaries, Amical preferred the "soft art" of diplomacy to the ways of the war. With carefully chosen words he rewarded his allies, isolated his enemies, and turned his brother's successes on the battlefield into lasting advantages. In 155 Amical proposed a formal agreement among his allies to standardize their boundaries and laws. Over the next seven years, the other families were enticed (and in some cases, coerced) into signing a more general version of the original treaty.<br/><br/> The revised treaty was known as the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois, or the "Accord for the Governing of Owned Goods." The terms of the agreement established a common law regarding the ownership and transferal of property. Since many of the most pernicious disputes between the families were rooted in disputes over land, it was hoped that the agreement would prevent future disagreements and allow the return of peace. In time, the treaty would lend its name to the people it bound together, and the descendants of the 27 signing families would be collectively known as the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The acceptance of his accord was only the first step in Amical's plan. The fragile peace he had engineered would not last without some kind of overarching authority to enforce it. Playing upon the fears of the smaller factions, Amical cultivated support for the creation of a monarch to rule over the various families. Amical's brother Paien was considered the natural choice for the position, but he died in the spring of 165, only weeks before his planned coronation.<br/><br/> For a few harrowing days, it seemed that all of Amical's work would be wasted and the Avoirdupois would return to the fractious state that existed before the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois. In the end, after desperate negotiations by Amical, it was Paien's 19-year-old son Aubert du Boulanger who was crowned king of the Avoirdupois on Midsummer Day.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Without Gage's unifying influence, old divisions began to reassert themselves. Families that had fought side by side against the Ecorcheurs now watched each other warily and bickered over imagined slights. By the year 150, eleven of the families had armies in the field actively campaigning against one another.<br/><br/> To be sure, these new armies were much smaller than the Ecorcheur horde or Gage's allied host. Lacking the manpower for large formations of the previous era, the new captains looked for ways to increase the effectiveness of their individual soldiers. Heavier weapons and armor became the norm, and increasingly intensive training for the soldiers and their mounts allowed the mounted infantry of Gage's day (who used their mounts for transport to battle) to evolve into true cavalry (who used their mounts for transport in battle).<br/><br/> Of all the families, the Boulanger were most able to take advantage of the chaos. The head of the family, Paien du Boulanger, was not only a clever tactician, but he had also married General Gage's daughter Orane. He was also advised by his younger brother Amical, one of the greatest minds of the era.<br/><br/> Unlike most of his contemporaries, Amical preferred the "soft art" of diplomacy to the ways of the war. With carefully chosen words he rewarded his allies, isolated his enemies, and turned his brother's successes on the battlefield into lasting advantages. In 155 Amical proposed a formal agreement among his allies to standardize their boundaries and laws. Over the next seven years, the other families were enticed (and in some cases, coerced) into signing a more general version of the original treaty.<br/><br/> The revised treaty was known as the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois, or the "Accord for the Governing of Owned Goods." The terms of the agreement established a common law regarding the ownership and transferal of property. Since many of the most pernicious disputes between the families were rooted in disputes over land, it was hoped that the agreement would prevent future disagreements and allow the return of peace. In time, the treaty would lend its name to the people it bound together, and the descendants of the 27 signing families would be collectively known as the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The acceptance of his accord was only the first step in Amical's plan. The fragile peace he had engineered would not last without some kind of overarching authority to enforce it. Playing upon the fears of the smaller factions, Amical cultivated support for the creation of a monarch to rule over the various families. Amical's brother Paien was considered the natural choice for the position, but he died in the spring of 165, only weeks before his planned coronation.<br/><br/> For a few harrowing days, it seemed that all of Amical's work would be wasted and the Avoirdupois would return to the fractious state that existed before the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois. In the end, after desperate negotiations by Amical, it was Paien's 19-year-old son Aubert du Boulanger who was crowned king of the Avoirdupois on Midsummer Day.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter05" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="five"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Early Kings
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> Aubert relied heavily on the talents of his uncle Amical (now called "the Kingmaker"), whose silver tongue was instrumental in defusing a number of challenges to the new king's authority. While Amical worked in the shadows, Aubert set about ordering his kingdom. One of his first decrees made the citadel overlooking the city of Sauldre his official residence. He spent large sums beautifying the city, and encouraged his subjects to do the same. Much of the city's remarkable architecture dates from this period. Outside the capital, work on the network of roads begun by General Gage (Aubert's grandfather) resumed.<br/><br/> As the years passed, certain noble families came to resent Amical's endless manipulations, and Aubert was forced to dismiss him from his council in 183. Even in retirement, however, Amical continued to advise his nephew: the two corresponded regularly until Amical's death in 202. Aubert himself died a year later, and was succeeded by his son Paien (named for Aubert's father).<br/><br/> Under Paien I and his successors, Paien II, Aubert II, Paien III, the Avoirdupois kingdom grew steadily stronger. The Aoreilles (a tribe of rabbits in the south) and the Lissemanteau (a family of ermines in the Loire region) were absorbed during the reigns of Paien II and Aubert II, respectively. After capitulating, both families were permitted to rule their own lands as vassals of the Avoirdupois kings. Similarly, when his armies were unable to take the city of Enclume by force, Paien III granted the "free" city a royal charter, allowing the devolution of certain rights and powers to its governing council (dominated by the armadillo families known as the Casque), in return for their recognition of his supreme authority.<br/><br/> Other groups were not so fortunate: the Plessis (a family of dogs), the Wallons, and many others were conquered outright--their lands seized by the Avoirdupois nobles, their children reduced to serfdom. Hoping to prevent future rebellions, Aubert II instituted a policy of dispersing conquered peoples widely, thus cutting them off from their traditional leaders and allies.<br/><br/> Paien III died in 263, and his son Gan was crowned king. Three of Gan's older brothers had died in Paien's wars of conquest, leaving him with few illusions about the cost of his predecessors' expansionist policies. Wisely, he turned his attentions inward, reforming the Avoirdupois legal codes and generally strengthening the power of the monarchy. He encouraged learning, founding schools of law and medicine. Religiously tolerant, Gan even allowed the Penitents of S'allumer to build a chapel in the city of Sauldre.<br/><br/> Gan's policies were for the most part successful, and the Avoirdupois kingdom prospered under his rule. The city of Sauldre nearly doubled in size during his reign, spreading beyond the old walls into the countryside.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Aubert relied heavily on the talents of his uncle Amical (now called "the Kingmaker"), whose silver tongue was instrumental in defusing a number of challenges to the new king's authority. While Amical worked in the shadows, Aubert set about ordering his kingdom. One of his first decrees made the citadel overlooking the city of Sauldre his official residence. He spent large sums beautifying the city, and encouraged his subjects to do the same. Much of the city's remarkable architecture dates from this period. Outside the capital, work on the network of roads begun by General Gage (Aubert's grandfather) resumed.<br/><br/> As the years passed, certain noble families came to resent Amical's endless manipulations, and Aubert was forced to dismiss him from his council in 183. Even in retirement, however, Amical continued to advise his nephew: the two corresponded regularly until Amical's death in 202. Aubert himself died a year later, and was succeeded by his son Paien (named for Aubert's father).<br/><br/> Under Paien I and his successors, Paien II, Aubert II, Paien III, the Avoirdupois kingdom grew steadily stronger. The Aoreilles (a tribe of rabbits in the south) and the Lissemanteau (a family of ermines in the Loire region) were absorbed during the reigns of Paien II and Aubert II, respectively. After capitulating, both families were permitted to rule their own lands as vassals of the Avoirdupois kings. Similarly, when his armies were unable to take the city of Enclume by force, Paien III granted the "free" city a royal charter, allowing the devolution of certain rights and powers to its governing council (dominated by the armadillo families known as the Casque), in return for their recognition of his supreme authority.<br/><br/> Other groups were not so fortunate: the Plessis (a family of dogs), the Wallons, and many others were conquered outright--their lands seized by the Avoirdupois nobles, their children reduced to serfdom. Hoping to prevent future rebellions, Aubert II instituted a policy of dispersing conquered peoples widely, thus cutting them off from their traditional leaders and allies.<br/><br/> Paien III died in 263, and his son Gan was crowned king. Three of Gan's older brothers had died in Paien's wars of conquest, leaving him with few illusions about the cost of his predecessors' expansionist policies. Wisely, he turned his attentions inward, reforming the Avoirdupois legal codes and generally strengthening the power of the monarchy. He encouraged learning, founding schools of law and medicine. Religiously tolerant, Gan even allowed the Penitents of S'allumer to build a chapel in the city of Sauldre.<br/><br/> Gan's policies were for the most part successful, and the Avoirdupois kingdom prospered under his rule. The city of Sauldre nearly doubled in size during his reign, spreading beyond the old walls into the countryside.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter06" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="six"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Famine and Rebellion
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> "Good King Gan" died in 330, after a reign of 67 years. He had outlived both his son and his grandson, so his sickly, three-year-old great-grandson Paien IV inherited his thrown. Paien's maternal uncle Childeberd de Criniere was named regent.<br/><br/> Childeberd was already known for his sybaritic tastes, and his acts as regent did nothing to alter his reputation. His elaborate entertainments were the talk of the upper classes, and as long as the kingdom remained prosperous, nothing seemed amiss. A series of poor harvests in the late 330's, however, leg to widespread hunger. Childeberd, oblivious to the plight of the lower classes, planned ever-more extravagant affairs for his circle of intimates. In order to raise funds for his parties, Childeberd took to selling state offices and appointments.<br/><br/> Gradually, poverty and hunger turned sullen resentment into violent resistance. Riots in Sauldre left large areas of the city in ruins, and the peasants of several regions rose u[ in outright rebellion. When on lord, Aluin du Vallon, appealred to the king for help in dealing with the turmoil, he was dismissed by Childeberd as "both insolent and incompetent" and stripped of his lands and title. Infuriated, Aluin joined the rebels.<br/><br/> In the north, the Doloreaux, sensing an opportunity, provided weapons and armor to Aluin's rebels and encouraged the Lissemanteau to renounce their allegiance to the Avoirdupois. Late in the summer, a Doloreaux army crossed the Loire and annexed large areas of Avoirdupois territory.<br/><br/> As the country descended into chaos, Childeberd's tastes grew more decadent and outre. Finally, in the spring of 340, Childeberd was stabbed to death by one of his own guards.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             "Good King Gan" died in 330, after a reign of 67 years. He had outlived both his son and his grandson, so his sickly, three-year-old great-grandson Paien IV inherited his thrown. Paien's maternal uncle Childeberd de Criniere was named regent.<br/><br/> Childeberd was already known for his sybaritic tastes, and his acts as regent did nothing to alter his reputation. His elaborate entertainments were the talk of the upper classes, and as long as the kingdom remained prosperous, nothing seemed amiss. A series of poor harvests in the late 330's, however, leg to widespread hunger. Childeberd, oblivious to the plight of the lower classes, planned ever-more extravagant affairs for his circle of intimates. In order to raise funds for his parties, Childeberd took to selling state offices and appointments.<br/><br/> Gradually, poverty and hunger turned sullen resentment into violent resistance. Riots in Sauldre left large areas of the city in ruins, and the peasants of several regions rose u[ in outright rebellion. When on lord, Aluin du Vallon, appealred to the king for help in dealing with the turmoil, he was dismissed by Childeberd as "both insolent and incompetent" and stripped of his lands and title. Infuriated, Aluin joined the rebels.<br/><br/> In the north, the Doloreaux, sensing an opportunity, provided weapons and armor to Aluin's rebels and encouraged the Lissemanteau to renounce their allegiance to the Avoirdupois. Late in the summer, a Doloreaux army crossed the Loire and annexed large areas of Avoirdupois territory.<br/><br/> As the country descended into chaos, Childeberd's tastes grew more decadent and outre. Finally, in the spring of 340, Childeberd was stabbed to death by one of his own guards.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter07" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seven"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The War of Leaves
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> Paien was still only 12 years old, and could not legally rule in his own right until his 17th birthday, so another regent was needed. In the end, another of Paien's uncles--Gurlan de Marteau, half-brother of the High Priest of Anu--was chosen to replace Childeberd. Unlike his predecessor, Gurlan was not a blood relative of Paien (he had married Paien's mother's sister), but he nevertheless took his duties as regent more seriously than Childeberd ever had.<br/><br/> The new regent quickly discovered that matters were worse than anyone had suspected. Corrupt finctionaries had plundered the treasury for theor own ends. The common soldiers had not been paid in weeks, and many had deserted--some roamed the countryside as birgands, while others joined the growing rebel factions. Even some members of the nobility found their sympathy for Aluin's rebels outweighed their loyalty to the king.<br/><br/> Gurlan's first priority was to purge the government of Childeberd's corrupt appointees. His tactics were direct. On one particular day, the headsman executed 52 of the king's assessors and ministers on various charges of peculation, corruption, and connivance. Gurlan filled the vacant posts with trusted friends, many of whom were Priests of Anu.<br/><br/> Next, Gurlan turned his attention to the rebels in the countryside. Lords whose lands were in rebellion were stripped of their hereditary lands and titles by royal decree, and Gurlan authorized the creation of new peers to replace them. Letters granting patents of nobility and deeds to the estates in question were issued to Gurlan's allies and supporters.<br/><br/> Naturally, the rebels were not to be routed by simple legalisms. The first of the new nobles, Chlotar d'Avregaut, was ambushed on the way to his new lands near Moulin-a-vent. The ambush had been staged by a radical faction of the rebels known as the Denegateurs or "deniers," since they denied the rule of the king and nobility alike. The leader of the Denegateurs, Searlait, is said to have told Chlotar that he "should have brought a sword instead of these leaves," referring to the deeds and patents he carried. the word "leaf" became a popular derisive term for Gurlan's deeds, and today the civil war is known as the "War of Leaves."<br/><br/> It was soon clear that Gurlan's decrees had pushed the conflict to a new level. Ambitious commoners supported Gurlan and the king, seeing the new policy as a way to gain wealth and status, while disenfranchised nobles joined Aluin's army, and the most desperate of the peasantry supported the Denegateurs. No faction was strong enough to defeat the others outright, and the war dragged on for years. Old and famous lineages were extinguished. New families were ennobled, only to be disenfranchised or killed a month later. One stretch of land east of sauldre was the site of five distinct battles during the course of the war. Today it is known as the Neuf Lieues Maudites, the "Nine Leagues of Cursed Land," and it is said to be haunted by those who died in the fighting.<br/><br/> Paien IV became king in his own right in 345, but Gurlan remained his most trusted councilor and the war continued. Finally, in 347 Gurlan was assassinated by a priest sympathetic to the Denegateurs. Paien's chronic illness had made him more reflective and thoughtful than his hot-headed and inflexible mentor, and he had come to realize that the war was essentially a failure. His thinking was strongly influenced by a commoner who had become one of his most successful captains, Itta d'Enclume.<br/><br/> In her letters (a few of which have survived to the present day), Itta stressed that wars and battles were not won in the same way. She wrote that "mere cunning" can win battles, but only "virtue" can inspire the loyalty necessary to create peace. When Paien offered her a title, Itta declined, asking instead that the practice of issuing deeds and patents be stopped "before the entire kingdom lies barren, the fields salted with the blood of folly." Eventually, Paien agreed, and the plates that had been used to print the "leaves" were broken in a public ceremony on the 8th day of the month of Flowers, in the year 349.<br/><br/> Meanwhile, Paien's overtures of peace had steadily weakened support for the rebels, and Aluin's remaining allies were defeated by a royalist army in the fifth (and bloodiest) battle of Lieues Maudites that fall. Aluin dy Vallon fled to exile in Triskellian, and the long war was essentially over.<br/><br/> Paien did not enjoy his victory for long: he finally succumbed to his long illness a few months later. His friend Itta, who had lost an arm in the final battle, was greatly saddened by his death and became something of a recluse. She did not give up writing, however, and many years later her letters would be collected into two volumes: Feudalism, which dealt with her theories of society and government, and Chivalry, which was more concerned with personal conduct of morality.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Paien was still only 12 years old, and could not legally rule in his own right until his 17th birthday, so another regent was needed. In the end, another of Paien's uncles--Gurlan de Marteau, half-brother of the High Priest of Anu--was chosen to replace Childeberd. Unlike his predecessor, Gurlan was not a blood relative of Paien (he had married Paien's mother's sister), but he nevertheless took his duties as regent more seriously than Childeberd ever had.<br/><br/> The new regent quickly discovered that matters were worse than anyone had suspected. Corrupt finctionaries had plundered the treasury for theor own ends. The common soldiers had not been paid in weeks, and many had deserted--some roamed the countryside as birgands, while others joined the growing rebel factions. Even some members of the nobility found their sympathy for Aluin's rebels outweighed their loyalty to the king.<br/><br/> Gurlan's first priority was to purge the government of Childeberd's corrupt appointees. His tactics were direct. On one particular day, the headsman executed 52 of the king's assessors and ministers on various charges of peculation, corruption, and connivance. Gurlan filled the vacant posts with trusted friends, many of whom were Priests of Anu.<br/><br/> Next, Gurlan turned his attention to the rebels in the countryside. Lords whose lands were in rebellion were stripped of their hereditary lands and titles by royal decree, and Gurlan authorized the creation of new peers to replace them. Letters granting patents of nobility and deeds to the estates in question were issued to Gurlan's allies and supporters.<br/><br/> Naturally, the rebels were not to be routed by simple legalisms. The first of the new nobles, Chlotar d'Avregaut, was ambushed on the way to his new lands near Moulin-a-vent. The ambush had been staged by a radical faction of the rebels known as the Denegateurs or "deniers," since they denied the rule of the king and nobility alike. The leader of the Denegateurs, Searlait, is said to have told Chlotar that he "should have brought a sword instead of these leaves," referring to the deeds and patents he carried. the word "leaf" became a popular derisive term for Gurlan's deeds, and today the civil war is known as the "War of Leaves."<br/><br/> It was soon clear that Gurlan's decrees had pushed the conflict to a new level. Ambitious commoners supported Gurlan and the king, seeing the new policy as a way to gain wealth and status, while disenfranchised nobles joined Aluin's army, and the most desperate of the peasantry supported the Denegateurs. No faction was strong enough to defeat the others outright, and the war dragged on for years. Old and famous lineages were extinguished. New families were ennobled, only to be disenfranchised or killed a month later. One stretch of land east of sauldre was the site of five distinct battles during the course of the war. Today it is known as the Neuf Lieues Maudites, the "Nine Leagues of Cursed Land," and it is said to be haunted by those who died in the fighting.<br/><br/> Paien IV became king in his own right in 345, but Gurlan remained his most trusted councilor and the war continued. Finally, in 347 Gurlan was assassinated by a priest sympathetic to the Denegateurs. Paien's chronic illness had made him more reflective and thoughtful than his hot-headed and inflexible mentor, and he had come to realize that the war was essentially a failure. His thinking was strongly influenced by a commoner who had become one of his most successful captains, Itta d'Enclume.<br/><br/> In her letters (a few of which have survived to the present day), Itta stressed that wars and battles were not won in the same way. She wrote that "mere cunning" can win battles, but only "virtue" can inspire the loyalty necessary to create peace. When Paien offered her a title, Itta declined, asking instead that the practice of issuing deeds and patents be stopped "before the entire kingdom lies barren, the fields salted with the blood of folly." Eventually, Paien agreed, and the plates that had been used to print the "leaves" were broken in a public ceremony on the 8th day of the month of Flowers, in the year 349.<br/><br/> Meanwhile, Paien's overtures of peace had steadily weakened support for the rebels, and Aluin's remaining allies were defeated by a royalist army in the fifth (and bloodiest) battle of Lieues Maudites that fall. Aluin dy Vallon fled to exile in Triskellian, and the long war was essentially over.<br/><br/> Paien did not enjoy his victory for long: he finally succumbed to his long illness a few months later. His friend Itta, who had lost an arm in the final battle, was greatly saddened by his death and became something of a recluse. She did not give up writing, however, and many years later her letters would be collected into two volumes: Feudalism, which dealt with her theories of society and government, and Chivalry, which was more concerned with personal conduct of morality.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter08" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eight"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Religious Strife
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> Paien had no children, so his younger brother Evrouin became the next Avoirdupois king. During Evrouin's reign, the Avoirdupois slowly expanded their influence, recapturing lands lost during the turmoil of the civil war. While the king campaigned on the frontiers, his ministers (many of whom had been appointed by Gurlan during the regency) were increasingly influenced by the Priests of Anu.<br/><br/> The Avoirdupois had always worshiped Anu and All-Father to their family shrines, but only since the establishment of the monarchy had any kind of formal priestly heirarchy arisen. Theudebald l'Anuite, a contemporary of King Paien I, is credited with reshaping the practices of the religion into their modern forms. Leaving his home in Porteur-du-Soleil, Theudebald traveled the countryside, promulgating his interpretations of the secred lore. He endorsed a simplified form of the ancient rules of the caste, and reformed the priesthood so that women were no longer permitted within its ranks. He also encouraged the study of magic, and of Elementalism in particular. When Theudebald died in 221, his body was returned to Porteur-du-Soleil, and his followers began the construction of a memorial to house his remains. As time passed, the structure continued to grow, eventually becoming the sprawling Heliopolitan temple that dominates Porteur-du-Soleil today.<br/><br/> Until the time of the civil war, few Avoirdupois were attracted to other faiths, and the spiritual primacy of the Priests of Anu was unquestioned. However, during the tribulations of the civil war, the Penitents of S'allumer had used their white magic to provide succor to the suggering populace. Gratitude had inspired many to convert to the foreign religion, particularly among the lower classes. Women of noble birth, relegated to peripheral position in the worship of Anu, found themselves attracted to the less forbidding doctrines of S'allumer.<br/><br/> The Priests of Anu did not fail to notice the growing interest in S'allumer. When they found themselves essentially in control of Evrouin's government, the Priests seized the opportunity to suppress the rival faith.<br/><br/> A decree issued in 359 closed the Penitents' chapels and meeting places. When riots broke out in Sauldre, the chapel there (built in the time of King Gan the Great) was torn down and the resident clergy were arrested and executed for "formenting rebellion." By 364, ordination in the "treasonous faith of S'allumer" had become a crime punishable by death. Critics of the policy were pressed under heavy stones until they either recanted or died.<br/><br/> Evrouin died in 373, and was replaced by his son, Evrouin II. The Priests of Anu retained control of his councils, and the persecutions continued. The new king, an enthusiastic hunter, spent most of his time on his rural estates while his councilors enriched the temples with properties confiscated from convicted S'allumer pernitents. Despite the dangers, many adherents of the outlawed religion continued to practice in secret.<br/><br/> In the spring of 379, an over-zealous band of Akarbites (asociety of warrior-wizards based in Porteur-du-Soleil and controlled by the Priests of Anu) attacked a gathering of penitents outside the town of Fermerouge. The "battle" was entirely one-sided--the Akarbites slew scores of the faithful (many of them unarmed) without suffering a single casualty. Unfortunately, the town of Fermerouge was under the protection of the Blaireau, a family of badgers who were subjects of the Rinaldi, not the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The Blaireau retaliated swiftly, burning several nearby Avoirdupois towns. the king, alarmed, attempted to placate the Blaireau, but his councilors favored war. When the High Priest of Anu declared S'allumer "an aberration in the eyes of the All-Father," and called upon the faithful to "expunge it from creation," the situation became irretrievable. Thousands of devout "Sons of Anu" converged on Porteur-du-Soleil, where they were grouped into irregular legions led by Akarbite captains.<br/><br/> The crusaders moved quickly and were able to attack the Blaireau before the Rinaldi could bring reinforcements to the area. The badgers fought bravely, but were greatly outnumbered. after a few inconclusive skirmishes, the Blaireau were decisively defeated in a battle that took place only a few miles from Fermerouge. The Rinaldi army arrived too late to affect the outcome of the fighting, and a second battle a few days later forced them to withdraw.<br/><br/> Meanwhile, Evrouin had raised his own army. he cautiously advanced on Fermerouge, arriving shortly after the battle with the Rinaldi. The leaders of the Blaireau, on the run from the Akarbite crusadersm recognized Evrouin's royal banners and presented themselves at his camp. In a brief ceremony, they renounced their fealty to the Rinaldi and swore allegiance to the Avoirdupois king.<br/><br/> The crusaders were infuriated when they learned if the surrender. One of the Akarbite captains went so far as to accuse the king of sheltering infidels. Evrouin, no longer in the mood for mildness, had the man whipped. The king's privy council, still dominated by the Priests of Anu, was also displeased by the news. When they grumbled, Evrouin excused them from their posts, making sure that their replacements were loyal to him, and not to the High Priest of Porteur-du-Soleil.<br/><br/> While the king was putting his council in orderm the crusaders continued to advance into Rinaldi territory. The invading horde moved slowly, burning fields and killing entire families of hapless peasants and townspeople.<br/><br/> The Akarbites that led the crusader legions had been carefully trained in the arts of personal combat, but were less prepared for the challenges of organizing and leading an army. Furthermore, the average crusader--though enthusiastic--lacked discipline and training. When on the move, the crusading army tended to break up into smaller bands, often ranging far from the main column to chase peasants ("infidels") or to forage for food.<br/><br/> This weakness was seized by the Rinaldi: the avoided large battles, and instead used their knowledge of the terrain and the superior maneuverability of their forces (the Rinaldi were renowned for their well-trained cavalry, while the crusaders were almost exclusively foot soldiers) to isolate and destroy individual groups of the invaders. By the time that the onset of winter forced a hiatus in the fighting, the invading forces had been greatly weakened.<br/><br/> Over the winter, one of the harshest on the record, both sides recruited and trained new troops as best they could. However, before the fighting resumed the following spring, King Evrouin was stabbed as he passed throuh the streets of Sauldre on the way to the Fane of Anu. The assailant, a failed Akarbite named Engres de Rivillac, was killed by the king's guards in the course of the attack. Apparently, Engres had used a poisoned blade, for the king weakened quickly.<br/><br/> On his deathbed, Evrouin confessed that he had secretly married his mistress, Clarisande de Poiliere, and that their young son Aimon was therefore his ligitimate heir. Evrouin died a few days later, shortly before the High Priest of Anu decreed the marriage void, on the grounds that it had not been performed with the proper ceremonies.<br/><br/> For a few weeks, it seemed possible that question of the succession would plunge the country into another civil war. Tensions rose between the priestly and noble factions, but eventually they agreed that Duke Etienne du Sabot would be the next king of the Avoirdupois. Etienne's mother was one of King Gan's great-grandchildren and a cousin of both Paien IV and Evrouin I, so this legal claim was on sound footing, but he knew that he was not the first choice of either faction. With the coming of spring, the new king led the Avoirdupois armies into the Rinaldi heartland. The crusader legions were now protected by the jennet-mounted knights of the king's guard, and the Rinaldi lancers were no longer able to achieve the easy victories they had grown accustomed to the previous summer. The Avoirdupois advanced inexorably, pushing the Rinaldi back to the very walls of Triskellian. after a direct assault of the city failed disastrously, both sides settled in for a long siege.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Paien had no children, so his younger brother Evrouin became the next Avoirdupois king. During Evrouin's reign, the Avoirdupois slowly expanded their influence, recapturing lands lost during the turmoil of the civil war. While the king campaigned on the frontiers, his ministers (many of whom had been appointed by Gurlan during the regency) were increasingly influenced by the Priests of Anu.<br/><br/> The Avoirdupois had always worshiped Anu and All-Father to their family shrines, but only since the establishment of the monarchy had any kind of formal priestly heirarchy arisen. Theudebald l'Anuite, a contemporary of King Paien I, is credited with reshaping the practices of the religion into their modern forms. Leaving his home in Porteur-du-Soleil, Theudebald traveled the countryside, promulgating his interpretations of the secred lore. He endorsed a simplified form of the ancient rules of the caste, and reformed the priesthood so that women were no longer permitted within its ranks. He also encouraged the study of magic, and of Elementalism in particular. When Theudebald died in 221, his body was returned to Porteur-du-Soleil, and his followers began the construction of a memorial to house his remains. As time passed, the structure continued to grow, eventually becoming the sprawling Heliopolitan temple that dominates Porteur-du-Soleil today.<br/><br/> Until the time of the civil war, few Avoirdupois were attracted to other faiths, and the spiritual primacy of the Priests of Anu was unquestioned. However, during the tribulations of the civil war, the Penitents of S'allumer had used their white magic to provide succor to the suggering populace. Gratitude had inspired many to convert to the foreign religion, particularly among the lower classes. Women of noble birth, relegated to peripheral position in the worship of Anu, found themselves attracted to the less forbidding doctrines of S'allumer.<br/><br/> The Priests of Anu did not fail to notice the growing interest in S'allumer. When they found themselves essentially in control of Evrouin's government, the Priests seized the opportunity to suppress the rival faith.<br/><br/> A decree issued in 359 closed the Penitents' chapels and meeting places. When riots broke out in Sauldre, the chapel there (built in the time of King Gan the Great) was torn down and the resident clergy were arrested and executed for "formenting rebellion." By 364, ordination in the "treasonous faith of S'allumer" had become a crime punishable by death. Critics of the policy were pressed under heavy stones until they either recanted or died.<br/><br/> Evrouin died in 373, and was replaced by his son, Evrouin II. The Priests of Anu retained control of his councils, and the persecutions continued. The new king, an enthusiastic hunter, spent most of his time on his rural estates while his councilors enriched the temples with properties confiscated from convicted S'allumer pernitents. Despite the dangers, many adherents of the outlawed religion continued to practice in secret.<br/><br/> In the spring of 379, an over-zealous band of Akarbites (asociety of warrior-wizards based in Porteur-du-Soleil and controlled by the Priests of Anu) attacked a gathering of penitents outside the town of Fermerouge. The "battle" was entirely one-sided--the Akarbites slew scores of the faithful (many of them unarmed) without suffering a single casualty. Unfortunately, the town of Fermerouge was under the protection of the Blaireau, a family of badgers who were subjects of the Rinaldi, not the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> The Blaireau retaliated swiftly, burning several nearby Avoirdupois towns. the king, alarmed, attempted to placate the Blaireau, but his councilors favored war. When the High Priest of Anu declared S'allumer "an aberration in the eyes of the All-Father," and called upon the faithful to "expunge it from creation," the situation became irretrievable. Thousands of devout "Sons of Anu" converged on Porteur-du-Soleil, where they were grouped into irregular legions led by Akarbite captains.<br/><br/> The crusaders moved quickly and were able to attack the Blaireau before the Rinaldi could bring reinforcements to the area. The badgers fought bravely, but were greatly outnumbered. after a few inconclusive skirmishes, the Blaireau were decisively defeated in a battle that took place only a few miles from Fermerouge. The Rinaldi army arrived too late to affect the outcome of the fighting, and a second battle a few days later forced them to withdraw.<br/><br/> Meanwhile, Evrouin had raised his own army. he cautiously advanced on Fermerouge, arriving shortly after the battle with the Rinaldi. The leaders of the Blaireau, on the run from the Akarbite crusadersm recognized Evrouin's royal banners and presented themselves at his camp. In a brief ceremony, they renounced their fealty to the Rinaldi and swore allegiance to the Avoirdupois king.<br/><br/> The crusaders were infuriated when they learned if the surrender. One of the Akarbite captains went so far as to accuse the king of sheltering infidels. Evrouin, no longer in the mood for mildness, had the man whipped. The king's privy council, still dominated by the Priests of Anu, was also displeased by the news. When they grumbled, Evrouin excused them from their posts, making sure that their replacements were loyal to him, and not to the High Priest of Porteur-du-Soleil.<br/><br/> While the king was putting his council in orderm the crusaders continued to advance into Rinaldi territory. The invading horde moved slowly, burning fields and killing entire families of hapless peasants and townspeople.<br/><br/> The Akarbites that led the crusader legions had been carefully trained in the arts of personal combat, but were less prepared for the challenges of organizing and leading an army. Furthermore, the average crusader--though enthusiastic--lacked discipline and training. When on the move, the crusading army tended to break up into smaller bands, often ranging far from the main column to chase peasants ("infidels") or to forage for food.<br/><br/> This weakness was seized by the Rinaldi: the avoided large battles, and instead used their knowledge of the terrain and the superior maneuverability of their forces (the Rinaldi were renowned for their well-trained cavalry, while the crusaders were almost exclusively foot soldiers) to isolate and destroy individual groups of the invaders. By the time that the onset of winter forced a hiatus in the fighting, the invading forces had been greatly weakened.<br/><br/> Over the winter, one of the harshest on the record, both sides recruited and trained new troops as best they could. However, before the fighting resumed the following spring, King Evrouin was stabbed as he passed throuh the streets of Sauldre on the way to the Fane of Anu. The assailant, a failed Akarbite named Engres de Rivillac, was killed by the king's guards in the course of the attack. Apparently, Engres had used a poisoned blade, for the king weakened quickly.<br/><br/> On his deathbed, Evrouin confessed that he had secretly married his mistress, Clarisande de Poiliere, and that their young son Aimon was therefore his ligitimate heir. Evrouin died a few days later, shortly before the High Priest of Anu decreed the marriage void, on the grounds that it had not been performed with the proper ceremonies.<br/><br/> For a few weeks, it seemed possible that question of the succession would plunge the country into another civil war. Tensions rose between the priestly and noble factions, but eventually they agreed that Duke Etienne du Sabot would be the next king of the Avoirdupois. Etienne's mother was one of King Gan's great-grandchildren and a cousin of both Paien IV and Evrouin I, so this legal claim was on sound footing, but he knew that he was not the first choice of either faction. With the coming of spring, the new king led the Avoirdupois armies into the Rinaldi heartland. The crusader legions were now protected by the jennet-mounted knights of the king's guard, and the Rinaldi lancers were no longer able to achieve the easy victories they had grown accustomed to the previous summer. The Avoirdupois advanced inexorably, pushing the Rinaldi back to the very walls of Triskellian. after a direct assault of the city failed disastrously, both sides settled in for a long siege.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter09" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="nine"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Siege of Triskellian
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> The siege of Triskellian dragged on for weeks. Finally, King Etienne, aware of the growing restlessness within his own army, agreed to meet with an envoy from the Rinaldi to discuss a negotiated settlement.<br/><br/> Scholars agree that the meetings between King Etienne and Corrado di Rinaldi began the week following midsummer, but there is no reliable record of their actual deliberations. All existing accounts of the negotiations were written some years later, and are frequently contradictory.<br/><br/> The version that follows appears in the official history of the Sabot family:<br/><br/> At noon, the envoy emerged from the gates of the city, accompanied by twelve soldiers with long spears and the blue gonfalon of the Rinaldi. The king went to meet him, accompanied by his most faithful knights... [the list of the 12 knights of King Etienne is here omitted].<br/><br/> A hush fell over both armies as the delegations moved toward one another. When they met, the king and Corrado took themselves a little apart from their guards and spoke in such low tones that none could hear their words. After conversing in this manner for several minutes, the king commanded that a tent be brought forth so that they could continue their conversation in greater comfort. When these preparations were complete, they retired within...<br/><br/> Later in the day, the king confessed that he had been plagued by a series of strange dreams, saying, "each night, when I close my eyes to rest, I find myself alone in a great and ancient forest. I am thirsty, so I make my way between the gnarled trees, searching for a stream so that I might drink. After much wandering, I chance to see a light in the distance. As I draw closer, I see that it is a clearing, bathed in a pure and brilliant light. At first I am dazzled by the brilliance, but when my vision clears there is a vulpine maiden standing before me. She is dressed in purple robes, and with both hands she holds a chalice brimming with cool water... though I am unbearably thirsty, I cannot bring myself to enter the clearing. Reluctantly, I turn away into the forest. A breeze rustles the branches of the trees, and as the wind grows to a great roar I am swept away."<br/><br/> Both men fell silent as they considered the king's words. Finally, Corrado answered, saying, "Surely these are visions of Helloise, whose miracle saved our city [Triskellian] so many years ago. Alas, I lack the skill to interpret the omen more clearly." The two men then departed, each to his own camp.<br/><br/> That night, the king received word that his wife had fallen ill, and that neither the physicians nor the diviners knew what the outcome of the disease might be. The king feared not only for his beloved wife, but also for the unborn child she carried. The king still revered Anu in his heart, and commanded the chief of the Akarbites to join him in his tent, that they might pray together. All night they maintained their vigil, but in the morning the queen's condition was unchanged.<br/><br/> For three days the king offered his obeisance to Anu, praying and making sacrifices as recommended by the priests. By this time, news of the queen's illness had spread throughout the camp and from the camp to the city.<br/><br/> Finally [the news] reached the ear of Her Holiness Luzia Coldonna, Anagnost of S'allumer [several other titles are here omitted]. Taking up her staff, for she was not a young woman, she made her way to the Avoirdupois camp. As she walked, those of pure heart could discern about her a dazzling radiance that grew brighter with each step... Our soldiers stood aside for her, afraid and confused, and even the Akarbites and the Priests of Anu were cowed by her holy presence.<br/><br/> As the holy woman passed through the camp, the king was roused from his tent by the commotion. At first sight of the dazzling light, he fell to his knees... When Luzia reached the king, he stood and led her within the tent where his dear wife lay dying. Luzia took the queen's hands in her own, and the light of purity and creation enveloped them both. In barely a moment, the ravages of disease were lifted from the queen's body and she awoke, calling for her beloved husband.<br/><br/> At this, King Etienne felt warmth within his breast and a lifting of his spirit. No longer would he take heed of the ignorant superstitions of the Priests of Anu, who, in their quest to satisfy the appetites of this world, hand forsaken the next....<br/><br/> The authenticity of the official history has been challenged on many different grounds. It seems particularly strange that the king would have brougth his pregnant wife with him to a battlefield when she could have remained safe within the citadel of Sauldre.<br/><br/> Though the reasons may be unclear, the events that followed are well known: Etienne renounced the worship of Anu, converting to S'allumer in a public ceremony outside the city walls. As part of the ceremony, he acknowledged the suzerainty of the Rinaldi over the entire island of Calabria: as their vassal, he would no longer rule his lands as King, but would henceforth be known as the Archduke of the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> With Etienne's conversion, the siege of Triskellian was lifted, and the various armies returned home.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The siege of Triskellian dragged on for weeks. Finally, King Etienne, aware of the growing restlessness within his own army, agreed to meet with an envoy from the Rinaldi to discuss a negotiated settlement.<br/><br/> Scholars agree that the meetings between King Etienne and Corrado di Rinaldi began the week following midsummer, but there is no reliable record of their actual deliberations. All existing accounts of the negotiations were written some years later, and are frequently contradictory.<br/><br/> The version that follows appears in the official history of the Sabot family:<br/><br/> At noon, the envoy emerged from the gates of the city, accompanied by twelve soldiers with long spears and the blue gonfalon of the Rinaldi. The king went to meet him, accompanied by his most faithful knights... [the list of the 12 knights of King Etienne is here omitted].<br/><br/> A hush fell over both armies as the delegations moved toward one another. When they met, the king and Corrado took themselves a little apart from their guards and spoke in such low tones that none could hear their words. After conversing in this manner for several minutes, the king commanded that a tent be brought forth so that they could continue their conversation in greater comfort. When these preparations were complete, they retired within...<br/><br/> Later in the day, the king confessed that he had been plagued by a series of strange dreams, saying, "each night, when I close my eyes to rest, I find myself alone in a great and ancient forest. I am thirsty, so I make my way between the gnarled trees, searching for a stream so that I might drink. After much wandering, I chance to see a light in the distance. As I draw closer, I see that it is a clearing, bathed in a pure and brilliant light. At first I am dazzled by the brilliance, but when my vision clears there is a vulpine maiden standing before me. She is dressed in purple robes, and with both hands she holds a chalice brimming with cool water... though I am unbearably thirsty, I cannot bring myself to enter the clearing. Reluctantly, I turn away into the forest. A breeze rustles the branches of the trees, and as the wind grows to a great roar I am swept away."<br/><br/> Both men fell silent as they considered the king's words. Finally, Corrado answered, saying, "Surely these are visions of Helloise, whose miracle saved our city [Triskellian] so many years ago. Alas, I lack the skill to interpret the omen more clearly." The two men then departed, each to his own camp.<br/><br/> That night, the king received word that his wife had fallen ill, and that neither the physicians nor the diviners knew what the outcome of the disease might be. The king feared not only for his beloved wife, but also for the unborn child she carried. The king still revered Anu in his heart, and commanded the chief of the Akarbites to join him in his tent, that they might pray together. All night they maintained their vigil, but in the morning the queen's condition was unchanged.<br/><br/> For three days the king offered his obeisance to Anu, praying and making sacrifices as recommended by the priests. By this time, news of the queen's illness had spread throughout the camp and from the camp to the city.<br/><br/> Finally [the news] reached the ear of Her Holiness Luzia Coldonna, Anagnost of S'allumer [several other titles are here omitted]. Taking up her staff, for she was not a young woman, she made her way to the Avoirdupois camp. As she walked, those of pure heart could discern about her a dazzling radiance that grew brighter with each step... Our soldiers stood aside for her, afraid and confused, and even the Akarbites and the Priests of Anu were cowed by her holy presence.<br/><br/> As the holy woman passed through the camp, the king was roused from his tent by the commotion. At first sight of the dazzling light, he fell to his knees... When Luzia reached the king, he stood and led her within the tent where his dear wife lay dying. Luzia took the queen's hands in her own, and the light of purity and creation enveloped them both. In barely a moment, the ravages of disease were lifted from the queen's body and she awoke, calling for her beloved husband.<br/><br/> At this, King Etienne felt warmth within his breast and a lifting of his spirit. No longer would he take heed of the ignorant superstitions of the Priests of Anu, who, in their quest to satisfy the appetites of this world, hand forsaken the next....<br/><br/> The authenticity of the official history has been challenged on many different grounds. It seems particularly strange that the king would have brougth his pregnant wife with him to a battlefield when she could have remained safe within the citadel of Sauldre.<br/><br/> Though the reasons may be unclear, the events that followed are well known: Etienne renounced the worship of Anu, converting to S'allumer in a public ceremony outside the city walls. As part of the ceremony, he acknowledged the suzerainty of the Rinaldi over the entire island of Calabria: as their vassal, he would no longer rule his lands as King, but would henceforth be known as the Archduke of the Avoirdupois.<br/><br/> With Etienne's conversion, the siege of Triskellian was lifted, and the various armies returned home.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter10" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ten"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Growth of S'allumer
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> Etienne's first official act as Archduke was to revoke he laws restricting the practice of S'allumer. It was plain, however, that many of his subjects remained devoted to Anu. in order to keep the peace, Etienne relied upon large numbers of foreign mercenaries, who were probably paid with money supplied by the Rinaldi.<br/><br/> In years that followed, the numbers of penitents grew steadily. After 390, the redical doctrines of a group known as the Iconoclasts ("Image-Breakers") became increasingly popular. The Iconoclasts advocated the destruction of the temples of Anu and the eradication of the priests and Akarbites. However, when one of the Iconoclasts started a riot in the marketplace of Sauldre, Archduke Etienne was forced to suppress the movement.<br/><br/> In the fall of 395, Etienne issued the Edict of Toleration, which granted the Heliodromes protection from persecution within the enclave of Porteur-du-Soleil. The lands that they had controlled in other parts of the realm reverted to Etienne's ownership. He used some of the land to reward his followers, but large portions he reserved for his own use, and the great temple in Sauldre was rededicated as the Church of S'allumer.<br/><br/> Archduke Etienne died in 402. Under his successors, the Church of S'allumer continued to prosper. Since the early church lacked a central authority to impose orthodoxy, its rapid growth encouraged the development of regional variations in doctrine. Many of the most popular heterodoxies were first circulated in this era.<br/><br/> In 450, a council of bishops was held in Triskellian. Over the course of nine months, the bishops decided upon an official doctrine for the church (other views were declared either heterodox or heretical) and reorganized the church heirarchy into something similar to its current form. Henceforth, each region would be overseen by an Archbishop. The most senior Archbishop would be recognized as the official head of the church, the Pontiff of S'allumer.<br/><br/> The first Archbishop of the Avoirdupois was Bohemond of Sauldre, who had been a leading figure at the council. The first Pontiff of S'allumer was Constantine of Triskellian, but he died less than a year after the end of the council and Bohemond took his place.<br/><br/> As Pontiff, Bohemond created the Holy Order of Ardent to act as his eyes and ears across Calabria. The Ardentines were the first Capitular Order, existing outside the regular church heirarchy and responsible directly to the Pontiff. Local orders, by way of comparison, were granted their charter or typicon by the local bishop, to whom they remain responsible.<br/><br/> Bohemond died in 478, but his successors continued his work. Graceful churches were built in the towns and cities, while abbeys and monasteries sprang up across the countryside.<br/><br/> As the years passed, various political and religious factions fell into and out of favor without lasting result. The Archdukes alternately conspired with and against the Rinaldi, and the church grew rich and powerful on the largesse of the devout.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Etienne's first official act as Archduke was to revoke he laws restricting the practice of S'allumer. It was plain, however, that many of his subjects remained devoted to Anu. in order to keep the peace, Etienne relied upon large numbers of foreign mercenaries, who were probably paid with money supplied by the Rinaldi.<br/><br/> In years that followed, the numbers of penitents grew steadily. After 390, the redical doctrines of a group known as the Iconoclasts ("Image-Breakers") became increasingly popular. The Iconoclasts advocated the destruction of the temples of Anu and the eradication of the priests and Akarbites. However, when one of the Iconoclasts started a riot in the marketplace of Sauldre, Archduke Etienne was forced to suppress the movement.<br/><br/> In the fall of 395, Etienne issued the Edict of Toleration, which granted the Heliodromes protection from persecution within the enclave of Porteur-du-Soleil. The lands that they had controlled in other parts of the realm reverted to Etienne's ownership. He used some of the land to reward his followers, but large portions he reserved for his own use, and the great temple in Sauldre was rededicated as the Church of S'allumer.<br/><br/> Archduke Etienne died in 402. Under his successors, the Church of S'allumer continued to prosper. Since the early church lacked a central authority to impose orthodoxy, its rapid growth encouraged the development of regional variations in doctrine. Many of the most popular heterodoxies were first circulated in this era.<br/><br/> In 450, a council of bishops was held in Triskellian. Over the course of nine months, the bishops decided upon an official doctrine for the church (other views were declared either heterodox or heretical) and reorganized the church heirarchy into something similar to its current form. Henceforth, each region would be overseen by an Archbishop. The most senior Archbishop would be recognized as the official head of the church, the Pontiff of S'allumer.<br/><br/> The first Archbishop of the Avoirdupois was Bohemond of Sauldre, who had been a leading figure at the council. The first Pontiff of S'allumer was Constantine of Triskellian, but he died less than a year after the end of the council and Bohemond took his place.<br/><br/> As Pontiff, Bohemond created the Holy Order of Ardent to act as his eyes and ears across Calabria. The Ardentines were the first Capitular Order, existing outside the regular church heirarchy and responsible directly to the Pontiff. Local orders, by way of comparison, were granted their charter or typicon by the local bishop, to whom they remain responsible.<br/><br/> Bohemond died in 478, but his successors continued his work. Graceful churches were built in the towns and cities, while abbeys and monasteries sprang up across the countryside.<br/><br/> As the years passed, various political and religious factions fell into and out of favor without lasting result. The Archdukes alternately conspired with and against the Rinaldi, and the church grew rich and powerful on the largesse of the devout.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="chapter11" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="chapter"/>
            <Base:SName sname="section"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eleven"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="chapters"/>
            <Base:PName pname="sections"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="chapter"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eleventh"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Bisclavret and the Eteignoirs
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             <br/> The Avoirdupois were as surprised as anyone else by the sudden emergence of the Bisclavret in the late 600s. They were outraged when the Rinaldi acceded without a fight, making the upstart Bisclavret a great house, on par with the ancient nobility of the Avoirdupois. From this time forward, the Rinaldi would find the Archdukes of the Avoirdupois growing ever more restive and independent.<br/><br/> A graver crisis began with a disputed inheritance in the dimesne of the Marteau. Harbin du Marteau, a cousin of Duke Ombrage du Marteau, died in 722 and the provisions of his will left land and money for the founding of a new monastery near the village of Ascetique. There were several irregularities in the will, which had been completed in something of a rush, and Duke Ombrage--in keeping with the laws of the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois--petitioned to have it set aside. Ombrage's case was strong, and Archduke Prevoyance may well have ruled in his favor if events had not taken an unexpected turn.<br/><br/> While Ombrage was waiting for his day in court, a group of monks and surveyors from Triskellian arrived in Ascetique. Unaware that Harbin's will had been contested, they began preliminary measurements for the construction of a new monastery. When Ombrage heard that the church was already measuring the site, he went mad with rage. He rode to the construction side with his bodyguards and slaughtered the workers.<br/><br/> Once the events became known, retribution was swift. Archduke Prevoyance dispatched his soldiers to arrest Ombrage, and the Holy Order of Ardent sent their own knights in armor. When they arrived, they found the Marteau entrenched in defensive positions and ready for war.<br/><br/> Though Ombrage and his men fought fiercely, his manor house was quickly overwhelmed. The House of Marteau was abolished, and in accordance with the ancient custom, the Marteau familial weaving was taken and burned by Prevoyance in the sight of the surviving members of the family.<br/><br/> As the damaged party, the Church had a legal claim to the former holdings of the Marteau. In the end, they received many of the choicest properties, but some areas were granted to noble families, former vassals of the Marteau, who would now become direct vassals of the Archduke.<br/><br/> Despite the destruction of the Marteau, it was rumored that Ombrage had established a secret society dedicated to the destruction of the Church of S'allumer. Acts of vandalism against church properties began to increase. Mysterious figures in hoods smashed church windows and destroyed candle-making shops. In the dead of night, they forced entry into the houses of clergy, visiting violence, with their stylized hammers, upon the people within. Ombrage was betrayed by one of his cousins and arrested by the Ardentines in 749; he was executed the following year. With his death, the movement subsided, but his followers, now known as the Eteignoirs, continued to meet in secret. In recent years, the movement has experienced something of a resurgence.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The Avoirdupois were as surprised as anyone else by the sudden emergence of the Bisclavret in the late 600s. They were outraged when the Rinaldi acceded without a fight, making the upstart Bisclavret a great house, on par with the ancient nobility of the Avoirdupois. From this time forward, the Rinaldi would find the Archdukes of the Avoirdupois growing ever more restive and independent.<br/><br/> A graver crisis began with a disputed inheritance in the dimesne of the Marteau. Harbin du Marteau, a cousin of Duke Ombrage du Marteau, died in 722 and the provisions of his will left land and money for the founding of a new monastery near the village of Ascetique. There were several irregularities in the will, which had been completed in something of a rush, and Duke Ombrage--in keeping with the laws of the Accord de Gerance Avoirdupois--petitioned to have it set aside. Ombrage's case was strong, and Archduke Prevoyance may well have ruled in his favor if events had not taken an unexpected turn.<br/><br/> While Ombrage was waiting for his day in court, a group of monks and surveyors from Triskellian arrived in Ascetique. Unaware that Harbin's will had been contested, they began preliminary measurements for the construction of a new monastery. When Ombrage heard that the church was already measuring the site, he went mad with rage. He rode to the construction side with his bodyguards and slaughtered the workers.<br/><br/> Once the events became known, retribution was swift. Archduke Prevoyance dispatched his soldiers to arrest Ombrage, and the Holy Order of Ardent sent their own knights in armor. When they arrived, they found the Marteau entrenched in defensive positions and ready for war.<br/><br/> Though Ombrage and his men fought fiercely, his manor house was quickly overwhelmed. The House of Marteau was abolished, and in accordance with the ancient custom, the Marteau familial weaving was taken and burned by Prevoyance in the sight of the surviving members of the family.<br/><br/> As the damaged party, the Church had a legal claim to the former holdings of the Marteau. In the end, they received many of the choicest properties, but some areas were granted to noble families, former vassals of the Marteau, who would now become direct vassals of the Archduke.<br/><br/> Despite the destruction of the Marteau, it was rumored that Ombrage had established a secret society dedicated to the destruction of the Church of S'allumer. Acts of vandalism against church properties began to increase. Mysterious figures in hoods smashed church windows and destroyed candle-making shops. In the dead of night, they forced entry into the houses of clergy, visiting violence, with their stylized hammers, upon the people within. Ombrage was betrayed by one of his cousins and arrested by the Ardentines in 749; he was executed the following year. With his death, the movement subsided, but his followers, now known as the Eteignoirs, continued to meet in secret. In recent years, the movement has experienced something of a resurgence.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="cover" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="cover"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="covers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tome"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome cover
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome. On the upper portion of the cover is the title of 'A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Learned Personages'. The border of the cover neatly displays blue embossed water ripples.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome bordered in blue embossed water ripples.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             On the upper portion of the cover is the title of 'A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois' and printed smaller beneath it are the words 'edited and compiled by Learned Personages'.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames/>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the many pages of A Historical Account of the Great House Avoirdupois
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The many pages of a $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome are broken up into chapters.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="spine" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="spine"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="spines"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="book"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the spine of a $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The spine of a $(this.trait:color) $(this.trait:material) tome.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:color">
         "steel blue"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:material">
         "leather bound"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052085, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1236880175, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236880312, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1236880453, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236880493, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236880514, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236880526, "morwenlorelie", "R", 1236883475, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236883800, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236886845, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236888848, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236893112, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236896157, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236896363, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236899353, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236899559, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236899659, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1236901371, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236912235, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236913074, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236913098, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236913115, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1236913512, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236913621, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236916033, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236972145, "morwenlorelie", "R", 1236972246, "morwenlorelie", "R", 1236972257, "morwenlorelie", "R", 1236974486, "morwenlorelie", "X", 1236978739, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1236992263, "morwenlorelie", "K", 1528323047, "jominey", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
