<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479439300">
         ([ "body":"The buildings south of Ambassador drive, and west of Merchant's Way until Central Avenue should all be reserved for shops that various craftsman can practice and market their trades. This includes East and West Commerce and Shop Circle.\\n\\nIf someone proposes a building project within this area for a new shop, the location should be approved with minimal delay. Obviously there will be discussions still on if the specific building chosen is the best suited for this specific shop.\\n\\nIf someone wishes to have built a trade shop outside of this region a more details explanation of why they feel that location is more suitable as opposed to this zone.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"It seems very reasonable to have all the crafters gathered in one area, for easy finding by those in need of their services, as well as to keep down the inconveniences of workshops; noise, smoke, smell, sound, traffic and so on for the sake of the residents of Newtown.", "time":1479472322 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"I like the idea of specific needs being found in one section of town. we could have a space to rent town houses and larger homes, a space for shopping, restaurants, hotels, a space crafting. instead of expedited time for building in the correct zone it could be a requirement that you have to build in the purpose of the building. ", "time":1479602467 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Very good idea, I have a zoning map at my disposal currently that will be used to determine the locations of future projects as they are suggested and voted upon.\\r\\n\\r\\nWe can consider this matter settled, yes? \\r\\n\\r\\n(OOC - We will have specific locations that will be available for the building projects, so that can be explained IC as the zoning restrictions.)", "time":1479663359 ]) ]), "estimate":"None currently", "filedby":"Thais", "location":"See below", "title":"Future zoning approval" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479454417">
         ([ "body":"Due to the nature of Docktown, and the importance of the docks, it is essential that trade goods that arrive in the city can be brought to the Market in Newtown without risk or or loss.\\n\\nThe proposal is to have guards patrol Market Street as well as the Docks to ensure that no muggers assault or steal any merchandise that come in by ship.\\n\\nAlternatively, set up a corps of guards who stand ready to escort shipments to Newtown where things are safer.\\n\\n[ooc: the idea is, once shipments are actually affected by the crime and muggers in Docktown, then it should be possible to have guards protect those shipments so they can arrive in Newtown. If not, then there will be lost shipments in the auction house (from those coming in by ship which a good bunch ought to be doing). It could create some RP and some fun if we have a type of NPC shipments moving from the Docks to Newtown, that PCs can either protect or assault, or invest in to protect.]", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"Makes sense", "time":1481410702 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"--ooc-- i like this idea, it gives both lawful or guard characters a ig purpose. it also gives criminal characters a way to be criminals without inciting a mob intent on destroying your character.---\\r\\n\\r\\nI can see the need for this proposal. this will however require manpower and money. \\r\\n\\r\\nthe cost could go to the shipper or to the buyer but then prices of the import would likely raise. \\r\\n\\r\\nwe could have a place where guards could be hired as needed instead of having standby guards. ", "time":1479602979 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, the matter was voted YES and upon later communications with the Sailor's Guild, they have pledged to ensure this happens with support of the Council toward such end.\\r\\n", "time":1495590513 ]) ]), "estimate":"Daily cost of 24d, 4 patrols of 3 guards.", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"Docktown part of Market Street and the Docks", "title":"Safe passage" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479457387">
         ([ "body":"I'd like to propose a building for us to have a public ballroom. This will aid for people who'd like to have nice indoor events within newtown.\\n\\nBalls, fashion shows, plays, musical nights and much more. I think this will really bring life and entertainment into newtown. Could perhaps charge per day for those who seek to use it so we're also putting coin back into the city.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:IC:fa:faith\>:([ "comment":"I fully agree with Lady Emmaline and Miss Antonia. Coin should be spent on less vanity things like a Ballroom and more important things that help the people with the real problems of the city.", "time":1480427822 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"Given that there are a multiple amount of ballrooms available for use if you ask the right people, I don't see the need to fund a ball room with tax monies when such funds could go toward things such as the hospital or safe working places. I am sure that we of the Avoirdupois would gladly allow use of our ballroom should the one in Oldtown be unsuitable for your needs.", "time":1479876719 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading is against a Ballroom at this time, as there are already several ballrooms in the city, both with the embassies, and in Oldtown for all to use.\\r\\nThe limited resources of the Guild Council should be focused on supporting and strengthening the guilds.", "time":1480781231 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"That Ballroom I believe is owned by the Rinaldi? I could be wrong but it would be nice to have a place everyone can use without needed permission from the Houses.", "time":1479491042 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I fear I must agree with Lady Emmaline and Antonia in regards to this matter. ", "time":1480119915 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"Is the ballroom owned by the rinaldi or does it belong to the city. this is important to know. i don't believe the rinaldi embassy  have any way to block use of the ballroom anymore then they do the teashop. \\r\\n\\r\\nthough i could be wrong and suggest we find out for sure before debating the need or priority of the ballroom. ", "time":1479603183 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th of Night, this proposal was denied by vote of the assembled. It can be proposed again at a later date six months from the time of last voting.", "time":1495589595 ]) ]), "estimate":"3500 - May be able to reduce the cost with community involvement.", "filedby":"Orla", "location":"West building in Haven Alley", "title":"City Ballroom" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479458373">
         ([ "body":"I've often overheard those in newtown say they wish we had a newtown shop so they don't have to travel so far to docktown and risk being mugged.\\n\\nI think it's a good idea to have  a seamstress shop up here. I even know a good carpenter and smith to help build it.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"While I support the construction of a new Seamstress Shop, I would propose that shops for plying one's trade be kept between Central Avenue and Merchant's Way.\\r\\n\\r\\nThis section of the city contains the East and West Commerce as well as Shop Circle.", "time":1479469481 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I can appreciate wishing to make the work place safer for one's self and their customers. I think this is a fine project.", "time":1480120103 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"i believe as it stands you have to go to two merchants for all the fabrics in town. we could have a newtown seamstress shop to centralize this need and could even have lockable crates or containers for individual crafters to store stuff in. while keeping bigger trade tools looked after by a shop attendant.", "time":1479603345 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"We believe in this vision whole-heartedly and we will bring it to table for vote at the next meeting.\\r\\n", "time":1479663532 ]) ]), "estimate":"4000 perhaps ", "filedby":"Orla", "location":"East of the welcome center, north building.", "title":"Newtown Seamstress Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479471985">
         ([ "body":"An more upper scale restaurant than Mamma's in Docktown, serving traditional Triskellian foods and some specialities from other areas.\\n\\nThe Gilded Balance sells mainly seafood, so those restaurant could sell finer meats and vegetables, and be a place for the genteel to go out for dinner and business meetings without disturbing the casual gatherings in the Gilded Balance, nor have to go to Docktown for a meal.\\n\\nConverting an existing building into a finder restaurant would be rather expensive as marbles likely would need importing for the flooring, nicer woods for the walls and furniture.\\n\\nMarble: 1000d\\nWooden wall decorations: 1000d\\nFurniture: 1000d\\nDecorations: 500d\\nWorkers: 1500d\\n\\nCosts would fairly quickly be recovered through the increased number of visitors to Newtown, as well as property taxes and sales taxes on the food.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:le:leliana\>:([ "comment":"I'm in agreement with this, I would enjoy a proper restaurant where I can eat and enjoy my meal in peace.", "time":1479585030 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading hopes that a private investor will step forth with a finished business plan that the Guild Council can grant permission to, and thereby open a restaurant soon in Newtown, but I do agree that it is not a priority nor a matter for the Guild Council currently.", "time":1480781473 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"There is already a cafe and the Inn serves wonderful food. Perhaps instead we could have more food and drinks that they each serve.", "time":1479490248 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"The problem with the inn, is you have constant traffic of people coming and going from their rooms, making this a poor choice to go to get a bite to eat away from random passing people.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe problem with the Cafe is that it is not really a sit down and eat dinner sort of place, and nor should it be.\\r\\n\\r\\nWhat I believe Antonia is suggesting is an actual restaurant where two people might enjoy a dinner together. Neither the Inn nor the Cafe serve this purpose.", "time":1479520351 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"i would personally like a few restaurants that have a singular purpose of serving food. perhaps even a place to buy and sell raw food for the at home cooks. an upscale restruant where you have to put in reservations and nice attire is required would be fabulous.", "time":1479603567 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"I have it on good authority that a number of privately owned spaces in town are currently working toward opening businesses such as restaurants and cafes, and those business types do not fall under the umbrella of Guild Council affairs because our work should concentrate on those places that will directly benefit the needs of our independent craftsman and tradesman.\\r\\nThese private owners are contracting their own workforce and utilising their own resources for these projects, leaving the resources and workforce of the Guild Council to concentrate more on places that would directly benefit the workforce at large.\\r\\nWe can consider this matter settled for now.\\r\\n(OOC - ICO staff already has plans for recreational and leisure spaces. That way the council can work with guilds to design guild-related items)\\r\\n\\r\\nEDITED TO ADD - At the meeting on the 12th of Night, this proposal was denied by vote of the assembled. It can be proposed again at a later date six months from the time of last voting.", "time":1495589663 ]) ]), "estimate":"5000d", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"On Haven Street, by Haven Alley and Central Avenue", "title":"Newtown Restaurant" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479473448">
         ([ "body":"This would be a two story Coffee House, with public seating on the ground floor, serving a selection of coffees and baked goods such as scones, cupcakes, and biscotti.\\n\\nThe upper floor would be private seating for guild councilors and guild leaders so that they could quietly discuss business from recent guild council meetings in comfort and relaxation.\\n\\n(ooc: upper floor would require you to either be a guild leader or in a guild that is on the guild council.)", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading votes no to this idea at this point in time.\\r\\nWhile I as a merchant would enjoy having an inviting place to negotiate contracts and conduct business meetings, I do believe there are other things which are more important for the Guild Council to focus on at this point in time, and I hope that a private investor will see the potential and create such a place.", "time":1480781345 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I again say that the cafe is already in place and we would only need to update the menu. ", "time":1479490322 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"The Cafe near the gate of dock town is a fine cafe but, there needs to be more places in town to socialize.\\r\\nDock Town for instance already has the Brewery, Mama's, the Turret, and the Boarding House where one can get a drink.\\r\\nThere is absolutely no reason we shouldn't have multiple places to get food and drink in new town that each serve their own style of food.\\r\\nThe cafe near new town mostly serves various teas. I'm proposing a coffee house that serves various coffees and also provides an exclusive second floor for discussing business.\\r\\n\\r\\nIn Reply to Hush: Personally I'm fine with this place serving alcohol also. Though I think it should still be called the Coffee House, and among whatever drinks it serves it should still serve Coffees of various types (perhaps even a coffee with alcohol in it).", "time":1479606719 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"instead of a coffee house why not a upclass bar that serves the nicer and rarer drinks both alcohol and virgin drinks. ", "time":1479603661 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"I have it on good authority that a number of privately owned spaces in town are currently working toward opening businesses such as restaurants and cafes, and those business types do not fall under the umbrella of Guild Council affairs because our work should concentrate on those places that will directly benefit the needs of our independent craftsman and tradesman.\\r\\nThese private owners are contracting their own workforce and utlising their own resources for these projects, leaving the resources and workforce of the Guild Council to concentrate more on places that would directly benefit the workforce at large.\\r\\nWe can consider this matter settled for now.\\r\\n(OOC - ICO staff already has plans for recreational and leisure spaces. That way the council can work with guilds to design guild-related items)\\r\\nEDITED TO ADD - At the meeting on the 12th of Night, this proposal was denied by vote of the assembled. It can be proposed again at a later date six months from the time of last voting.", "time":1495589700 ]) ]), "estimate":"15000", "filedby":"Thais", "location":"The Tringle building on Thanon Road behind the Guildhouse", "title":"Northern Coffee House" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479473863">
         ([ "body":"Seeing how unsafe Docktown has become, it will be necessary to build a hospital in Newtown.\\n\\nThe suggested location is due to several considerations:\\n- it is a quiet place of town\\n- Dunwasser Field is nearby, for strolls in the park by patients so they can recover faster\\n- close to the college for students and scholarly research and experiments\\n- close to the bathhouse, which means hot water will be easy to direct to the hospital, improving in hygiene and comfort\\n- close to the cathedral for clerical aid, bringing patience for blessings and so on\\n- close to the North Gate and easy to find for guests and next of kin to visit and find\\n\\nPrice estimate is based on what the infirmary cost to create down in Docktown several  years ago, and doubled as this is Newtown and there will be running hot water also.\\n\\nThe hospital would contain:\\n- Shared infirmary with beds and partitions\\n- A couple of private rooms for those who can afford/are willing to pay for it\\n- Apothecary workshop for medications and the making of them\\n- Surgery room\\n- Running water\\n- Heating through hot-air vents\\n\\nMarble and stone would need to be imported, crafters employed to do the work, beds and furniture made, linens, towels and other things made and so on. Though some things may be able to be moved from Docktown to Newtown, as there would for instance be no need for a surgery room in Docktown if there is one in Newtown.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:ni:nicolas\>:([ "comment":"I feel having a hospital in Newtown is of the utmost importance.", "time":1479876136 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"I agree that having a hospital in Newtown is a most important goal. I would fully support this idea. Perhaps instead of charging a fee to use the facilities, the Church or College can be contacted for co-funding to assure care is available to those who are in need of such? \\r\\n", "time":1479876506 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"The fee would only be for those insisting on having a private room, which is a luxury that is not necessary for the medical treatment, but a convenience for those of means.", "time":1479930869 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I'm in agreement to this.", "time":1479490359 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"i agree with antonia, there needs to be a newtown hospital for safety if nothing else. there are often muggers locked in the infirmary where people are bed ridden.\\r\\n\\r\\ni love all of antonia's ideas but worry about the cost and upkeip of such and suggest an admission fee for patients to use the safer, cleaner, and more up to date healing location to make up for the cost of the building and the upkeep.", "time":1479603901 ]) ]), "estimate":"20000", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"Between Dunwasser Fieldway and Westend Lane", "title":"Newtown Hospital" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479701351">
         ([ "body":"I would like to build a cozy lounge for fighters in the city. The lounge would provide comfortable seating areas as well as a place to smoke for those that use smoking devices. The bar would import fine whiskeys and wines and keep a nice stock of cigars and pipe tobacco. This would be a bar to relish in past stories and experiences with people of a similar mindset. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"This isn't a Guild Council project. I could be persuaded to fund such a venture though", "time":1481410881 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"I would counsel that the City Council funding a bar that serves imports of the Houses should consult the House about these imports before circumventing the rights granted those Nations by the Don. I know that the Bisclavret and Avoirdupois are both more than willing to provide access to those drinks if they are desired. One need only ask.\\r\\n", "time":1479876607 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading does not support this idea at this point in time, and instead defers to and hopes that a private investor may step forth with a finished idea that the council can permit.", "time":1480781418 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th of Night, this proposal was denied by vote of the assembled. It can be proposed again at a later date six months from the time of last voting.", "time":1495589731 ]) ]), "estimate":"2000 denarii", "filedby":"Roofus", "location":"East Parkway", "title":"Cigar Bar" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1479721452">
         ([ "body":"A guild hall for a group of crafts, where it will be beneficial to share locales and rooms.\\n\\nThe hall would have a number of rooms that can be rented by each individual guild, and have a shared common room that is equipped for and can be used as workshop and for socializing.\\n\\nThe rented rooms could consist of a storage room for shared resources for the guild members, and a meeting room for guild meetings. All guild members would automatically have access.\\n\\nSeveral guild halls can be considered, grouping types of crafts together. Clothiers and dyers together, carpenters and stone masons together, all smiths together.\\n\\nThis idea may be a possibility instead of creating individual workshops for each craft, and by grouping crafts together, the total number of building renovations will be reduced.\\n\\n\\nThe majority of this building would be the rent-able rooms that are left unfurnished so that the guild itself can decorate within a guideline. So the cost would be fairly low.\\n\\n\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"", "time":1495592817 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"It is my understanding that the craft hall would have the workshops, and be open for all to visit, just like the smithy is now. The main difference would be that it is larger, and has room for more than just one trade to work, thereby gathering crafters together. This could mean that when a smith hosts his hours, the carpenter may also be working next to him, and the presence may inspire the customers to also purchase from the carpenter, and not only the smith. All the meanwhile the jeweller and stone mason sit in other parts of the craft hall working on their products, which may inspire the lady seeking a new necklace to also order a bathtub.", "time":1480312314 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I think this particular idea is not bad, in and of itself... But I worry it will cause those  who are seeking the masters of trade some distress as it lowers the direct availability of said crafter. Open smithys, shops and so are are part of marketing for those who deal in trade. ", "time":1480119728 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"this is more for guilds to have common safe areas to craft in. shops would be more for sales and display and taking orders. ", "time":1480231929 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Having passed with the vote at the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been approved.", "time":1495589909 ]) ]), "estimate":"", "filedby":"Doctor Hush", "location":"near guild council admin building", "title":"guild hall" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480100760">
         ([ "body":"There are many children in Triskellian who do not have the opportunity to properly learn all they can. This could be for many reasons, born into a poor family, being an orphan, or just have parents who do not care.\\n\\nThis is where I believe we should step in and aid our youth for they are our future. We should make sure they have every opportunity that they can to become something other than a beggar, mugger or something worse.\\n\\nThis could be done a number of ways, one that came to mind was perhaps having denizens volunteer to teach the children. Crafters, scholars, constables, and much more. With further discussion I'm positive something can be agreed upon.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:he:heather\>:([ "comment":"Thank you, Lady Antonia. I will contact the people you mentioned.", "time":1480693519 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"I still insist that this is something the Church should fund if they believe it to be a just cause. I also still believe it will be a wasted effort to fund a location for children who do not actually want to pursue higher education. I thought it was always operating procedure for hopefuls to become apprentices of those practicing their desired career path and not for the state to fund generalised education for all. Charity work is for philanthropists and the church. Not taxpayers. ", "time":1480127257 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Children are traditionally taken in as apprentices in various guilds, or in direct service to houses and nobles.\\r\\nMany of the children you see roaming the streets seemingly without purpose are likely part of the thieves guild or other criminal organisations, plying their trade.\\r\\nThe Church does in connection with the Orphanage teach those interested how to read and write, and the Church is normally more than willing to take in any child willing, and train them in the ways of religious and devoted life.\\r\\nI can only agree with the above statements, a matter such as this would fall under the authority of the Church, and I can only encourage you to personally bring up the matter with the Church's representatives. There should be several in the city, Mother Annemie comes to mind as one I recently saw. Valentin is in the Church, and there should be both a Mother Misandi and Prelate Theressa, though I have never personally encountered any of them.", "time":1480312084 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I believe perhaps an orphanage is more appropriate. It is always difficult to keep these types of facilities open and without proper backing, I fear it may do more harm for the City's children to have false hope in a place that may not last.", "time":1480118796 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Having been denied via vote at the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been closed.", "time":1495590376 ]) ]), "estimate":"5000 ", "filedby":"Heather", "location":"Near the College ", "title":"Public Rearing - Child Daycare" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480100985">
         ([ "body":"With Docktown becoming more dangerous by the day, I can't help but worry about the Orphans who live there. They should be moved to a safer location where they are able to live in peace.\\n\\nI hope I am not the only one who fears for the children of Triskellian.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:he:heather\>:([ "comment":"I do hope the Church joins the next meeting as I honestly think this is more important than restaurants. ", "time":1480693477 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"I agree that these charitable acts are more the territory of the Church. The orphanage is currently located where the need is highest, I believe, but I suppose those who operate it, my understanding being that that is the Church, could be contacted about seeking to move what already exists?", "time":1480127551 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"If I recall right, the orphanage is owned by the Chuch and the matter should be taken up with their representatives.\\r\\nPS. As it is a church matter, I do not believe the Guild Council necessarily have any say in these things, as the Church owns buildings in the city and can utilize those buildings and their use as they wish. You should speak to the representatives of the Church and hear.", "time":1480780293 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"Perhaps this is something to be brought before the Church as the Church typically heads such projects as orphanages.", "time":1480118947 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Having been denied via vote at the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been closed.", "time":1495590430 ]) ]), "estimate":"5000", "filedby":"Heather", "location":"Near Cathedrale", "title":"Moving the Orphanage to Newtown" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480110447">
         ([ "body":"I would like to propose the building of a smithy in Newtown to provide a safer place for smiths to do their work.\\n\\n*Brick or stone walls and floor - 500 denarii\\n*Forge - 200 denarii\\n*New door, shutters, whetstone wheel - 150 denarii\\n*Labor - 350 denarii\\n\\nMy guild is in possession of anvils to donate to this cause.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:fr:frederic\>:([ "comment":"I would like to extend an offer on behalf of the Avoirdupois embassy to reimburse Monsieur Smith and any other tradesmen involved in this project for all debts accrued during construction. Additionally, if there is interest, the embassy is prepared to donate one smithing forge from Chalon.", "time":1480174320 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"The smithy is probably the 2nd most busy craft currently after the clothiers, and therefore Liguria Trading supports the idea of a smithy in Newtown.", "time":1480781559 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I'm in agreement with this.", "time":1480138803 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I can appreciate wishing to make the work place safer for one's self and their customers. I think this is a fine project.", "time":1480120079 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Having passed with unanimous vote at the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been approved. \\r\\n\\r\\nFurthermore, the offer of the Avoirdupois embassy to handle all finances therein is a boon to the coffers of the City Council and greatly appreciated.", "time":1495589502 ]) ]), "estimate":"1200 denarii", "filedby":"Bruno", "location":"East or West Commerce Avenue", "title":"Newtown Smithy" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480358005">
         ([ "body":"A workshop for the carpenters, possibly included in a guild hall for smiths, jewellers, carpenters and stone masons.\\n\\nSame basic idea as the smithy, just another craft.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading supports a Carpentry shop, though do not feel it is an urgent matter, in particular since the carpenters of the city have not spoken up with their desire for a workshop. Should they express need and desire, Liguria Trading will re-evaluate their stance.", "time":1480781658 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Having passed with unanimous vote at the meeting that took place on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been approved.", "time":1495589801 ]) ]), "estimate":"1000", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"Next to the smithy", "title":"Carpentry shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480358065">
         ([ "body":"A workshop for jewellers to work in, possibly in the same guild hall as smithy, carpentry and stone mason.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Heather, if you are not able to communicate about these issues in a mature way perhaps you should refrain from joining in the conversations or ask your representative to express your concerns in a way that does not reflect poorly on you or your embassy. We do not have unlimited resources at our disposal and at some point we will have to decide which projects get priority over others. I am in agreement that with regards to these workshops, we should first consider which guilds are most active and will benefit the most. The GUILDS need help and our focus is on the needs of the GUILDS. No one is arguing that we shouldn't have a jewelry shop, just that it should get less priority over other shops that would be more of a benefit to the guilds of the city.", "time":1480720718 ]), \<Chatters:AE:he:heather\>:([ "comment":"Mister Bruno, I have been speaking in a mature manner and only replying based on what Her Ladyship has stated. I can understand focusing on things that are more needed, but the way she stated it was not very kind. As if you're pushing the rest of us away merely because of the fact that we work in a house. The last few comments and topics about house crafters has been nothing but mean. So yes I admit I may be a little bothered, I have given so much to this city and to feel like you're turning against me merely because I work within a house and not a guild is hurtful. Regardless, I apologize for commenting while having such feelings. It's never a wise choice", "time":1480877857 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Seeing that there are currently no jewellery guilds at this point in time, I suggest that this project be postponed to a day when there are actually independent jewellers in the city.\\r\\nCertainly the houses can invest in a workshop for their members if the members need one.\\r\\nPs. The Guild Council funds and supports workships which will support and aid the guilds in their work.\\r\\nI am sorry, Heather, but you are not a guild, nor member of one.", "time":1480614613 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"After a vote at the meeting on the 12th of NIght, this proposal has passed and been approved.", "time":1495590609 ]) ]), "estimate":"1000", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"Next to the smithy", "title":"Jewellery shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1480358132">
         ([ "body":"A workshop for the stone masons, possibly included in a guild hall for smiths, jewellers, carpenters and smiths.\\n\\nSame basic idea as the smithy, just another craft.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"Liguria Trading feels that this project is low priority and that it be postponed until there are active guild members who are Stone Maison in the city again.", "time":1480781743 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"After voting at the meeting on the 12th of Night, this proposal has been approved.", "time":1495590648 ]) ]), "estimate":"1000", "filedby":"Antonia", "location":"Next to the smithy", "title":"Stone mason shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1495349647">
         ([ "body":"This proposal is being filed on behalf of Nisha (ooc: Player has problems with popups) a smith with the Bisclavret. The smithy in Dock Town while serviceable is in a dangerous part of town. Being off the main commons, customers and smiths using the shop are at a high risk of being mugged without good citizens being around to lend a hand in their protection.\\n\\nThis proposed location is both in a safe part of new town, and would be easily accessible by gentle folk and their attendants.\\n", "estimate":"1000+", "filedby":"Thais", "location":"Newtown Shop Circle", "title":"Newtown Smithy" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1495597079">
         ([ "body":"* Carpenters (Thais): Golden Bronze Pear Wood (Import) 50D\\nWalls (x40) - 40D\\nCeiling (x10) - 10D\\n\\n* Carpenters (Thais and Steve): Pear Wood (Import) 30D\\nTable (x3)\\nx2 Chairs (x2/ = x4)\\nCounter (Hopefully with marble top)\\nClothing Rack (x3)\\nx1 Lockable Cabinets (x3/ = x?)\\nSofa (x4)\\n\\nThais: 180(8lumbers) + 250(stain):330D\\n\\n* MetalSmith (Nisha): Silver (Imported)\\n\\nx8 Lighting Sconces\\nChandelier\\n\\n30Papers(3 silver rods) + (Nisha's Pay)\\n\\n* Stonemason (Sang): Crema Marfil (Imported)\\n\\nFloor\\nCountertop\\nFireplace\\n30Papers(3 Crema Marfil Marbles) + 300(Sang)\\n\\nClothiers (Orla and Sanu): Lustrous Mocha and Cream\\n\\nCurtains\\nCushions\\nPortier\\nDecorative Pillows\\nUpholstery\\nCarpets\\n\\nEstimated Total: 900D", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I can see a lot of thought has been put into these plans and that is good! I am concerned though that if this cost is approved, it will deplete half of the council funds. It concerns me that there will not be enough left to cover the costs of the other projects we have going on. Does this concern anyone else?", "time":1496797487 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"This matter was approved. A submission to the exchequer has been filed and funds will be released upon their approval.", "time":1497496493 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"Not really having a solid estimate on what sort of budget these projects should stay within I advised Orla to keep her budget under 1000d so that there would be money left over for other projects.\\r\\nThe city does need to prioritize projects and shouldn't be trying to do every project at once. Our goal here should be to try to keep our budget enough that we can work on a couple of projects at one time and to do them right.\\r\\nIf you feel that 1000d for a project is to much, we need to try to decide how many projects we want going on at once and what sort of reserve budget we want to make sure the city keeps on hand.\\r\\nI would propose though that we have at most 2 projects active with a reserve budget in case of some emergency the city needs to spend coin on.", "time":1496825193 ]) ]), "estimate":"900D", "filedby":"Orla", "location":"Newtown", "title":"Plan and Estimate for Seamstress Shop - Orla" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1497042372">
         ([ "body":"Currently there are public warehouses that are mostly used by the dock workers, however there is really no good place for merchants and trades man to store their wares. Many rent a room in two different inns, and use the less expensive room to store such things so as not to clutter up their personal room.\\n\\nInn rooms though are not really suitable for storing large quantities of trade goods though, and rentable storage space in the warehouse would be ideal for both Merchants and Crafters in keeping their goods organized.\\n\\nAs these rentable storage areas would be owned by the city, the rent costs would go directly toward further projects the City might consider.\\n\\n(ooc: I'm thinking an Inn like rentable area in a warehouse that instead of being called an Inn room is just called a storage unit or something like that. Something nice and in-expensive for the characters)", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"This would help support growing businesses. Chesh does bring up valid concerns. Since the buildings are owned by the city, could they be inspected legally should there be reasonable cause? Regardless, I'm in favor of the idea.", "time":1497234677 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"\\r\\nThe meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below.\\r\\n\\r\\nOn the matter of the building proposals, the votes stand at;\\r\\nRoofus' headquarters: unanimous no\\r\\nRentable warehouses: unanimous in favor\\r\\n\\r\\nAs such, the office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms the outcome of the votes. Roofus Black will not be permitted to build a private headquarters and warehouses in Docktown have been opened for the use of independent guilds and groups.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\nMister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522630067 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"As for the questions about legalities, I don't see that the rules for the constables searching your rented warehouse space would be any different than for if they need to search your rented room at an Inn.", "time":1497408532 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"The Idea is a great idea. But due to my past. I can't help but to think as a criminal somedays. And I wonder. Will there be a way to keep tabs on the people renting and what they use the shed for? I know plenty of people that would probably hide illegal items if not bodies in something like this if it can't be traced or monitored. Other wise. I say it would help the crafts alot.", "time":1497234114 ]) ]), "estimate":"???", "filedby":"Thais", "location":"In Docktown not far from the gate", "title":"Rentable warehouse space" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1497234782">
         ([ "body":"I propose setting a tent on market street on the new town side just before you enter docktown. The purpose would be for my men and women to gather for hire. Anyone that is uncomfortable fighting. Not expereinced, or just rather not deal with petty mugging, would be able to hire a escort that will stop all mugging before they stop you on your way. There would be a cost for them. Say one deanr. And half of that would go to the maintenance of docktown streets and buildings. And I think this would be a great way. One denar will get you an escort that will always be on your side while in docktown. When you return to newtown..well that escort returns to the tent and waits for the next hire. Yes if you come and go alot you would pay 1d each time. But if you stay in docktown for an entire day. well one denar for a whole day protection. That is cheap. Again. half the price is for repairs of docktown. the other is merely to pay the wages of the escort.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I support this idea.", "time":1520721977 ]), \<Chatters:AE:ma:matteo\>:([ "comment":"I think it would have to cost more than one denar per visit. I think you would have to pay the person giving up their time, their training, and assisting dock town itself. I would suggest 2 to 3 denars, 1 or 2 for the guard and 1 for the city.\\r\\nI also think these escorts would have to have limited criminal pasts as well and be checked ahead of time.\\r\\n", "time":1497333547 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"I'm supportive of this idea. Though I would be curious who would be training these guards?\\r\\n\\r\\n(ooc: An idea that comes to my mind is that guilds/groups could supply the tent with martial tokens. Guilds/groups that supply tokens could then perhaps get a share of the protection money. Also as NPCs can provide testimony on crimes, these NPCs would have bias based on who is supply the tokens. But that's just my own little bit to add to this suggestion.)", "time":1497235256 ]) ]), "estimate":"Will not cost the city anything", "filedby":"Chesh", "location":"South market st \& docktown", "title":"Armed Escort for Docktown" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1517704331">
         ([ "body":"As a newly created guild we need a place to call our headquarters. We will provide protection services to those traveling outside of the city as well as collection of old relics and rare items. Having a headquarters will give us a centralized location for our business. We will employ local crafters to build our headquarters and give an opportunity for others to prosper. We have the coin to do the renovations ourselves and seek to buy the building with the money earned by our guild. If those cannot afford to pay our fees we will still provide safe passage. Docktown and travels to Three Corners are extremely dangerous and if we can reduce the deaths of our citizens this will be a win for us and a win for the citizens.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I do not think building personal headquarters for guilds would be the best use of the guild council resources. Many guilds would love to have the opportunity for their own space but the best we can do are public buildings that everyone can benefit from.", "time":1520721828 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"The meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below. On the matter of the building proposals, the votes stand at; Roofus' headquarters: unanimous no Rentable warehouses: unanimous in favor As such, the office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms the outcome of the votes. Roofus Black will not be permitted to build a private headquarters and warehouses in Docktown have been opened for the use of independent guilds and groups. In service to his Lordship, Mister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522630164 ]) ]), "estimate":"1,000 denarii", "filedby":"Roofus", "location":"Building on Thanon Road on the south side", "title":"Black Company Headquarters" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1522334221">
         ([ "body":"This proposal is for the building of the Newtown Carpenters Shop as previously approved by the Guild Council during the meeting on (OOC: 23 May 2017).  As a member of the Triskellian Woodworkers Alliance, I am offering to take the lead in organizing the work associated with this project.\\n\\nNew Town Carpenter Shop\\n\\nFor the description, I considered the entrance on the north wall but this is not a requirement just descriptive.  The overall space is 65 horizontal (H) axis by 60 vertical (V) axis.  First space would be the storefront which would be on the north end of the building, 65 (H) by 20(V).  A double door in the center of the North wall shall be the formal entrance.  To either side of the door are two, fairly sizable, windows with shutters.  Directly south of the main door is another door to the work area.  There are two display cases, underneath both windows on the north wall.  On the west side of the room is an extended ‘pad’ for the sale of larger goods (wardrobes, tables, etc...).  In the east end there is a table and chairs to hold conversations and discuss orders.  There will be a large brass chandalier to provide light to the entire space.\\n\\nAbove the center door in the south wall should be a large painted wood carving of City of Triskellian Coat of Arms.\\n\\nDirectly south of the storefront, there is a door that leads to the main carpenters work area which is 55 (H) by 40 (V).  The work area should be equiped with 4 tables/benches and 4 sconces to provide light.   \\n\\nNone of the costs listed below for wood products include labour.  As a carpenter, I am volunteering my time to generate all of these items and will negotiate the same with other carpenters who wish to help with this project for the benefit of all wood crafters of the city.\\n\\nTotal costs\\n  675 d - Storefront\\n  361 d - Work Room\\n  200 d - Triskillian Coat of Arms\\n1,236 d - Total\\n\\nStorefront (675 denarii)\\n200 d - 2x glass windows (Estimate)\\n 20 d - 4x shutters (Teak)\\n 24 d - 2x display cases (Mahogany)\\n 13 d - 1x table (Beech)\\n 10 d - 4x chairs (Ash)\\n 41 d - Parquet Floor (Oak and Mahogany)\\n 72 d - 3x Wainscot (Cedar)\\n 17 d - 1x Ceiling Panels (Maple)\\n 24 d - 2 Doors, French (Elm)\\n  4 d - Nails (Will be used for the entire project)\\n 50 d - Paint (Will be used for the entire project)\\n200 d - Chandalier, Brass (Estimate)\\n\\nWork Room (361 denarii)\\n 15 d - 4x Work Benches\\n  5 d - 1x Lumber Box\\n 60 d - 4x Wall panels (Birch)\\n 24 d - 1x Floor Board (Oak)\\n 10 d - 1x Ceiling Boards (Poplar)\\n 17 d - 1x Door (Maple)\\n200 d - 4x Sconces (Estimate)\\n 30 d - 2x Lacquer (Clear)", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"On the matter of the plans for the Carpenters shopfront located in Newtown, submitted by mister Bjorn of the Triskellian Woodworkers, the voting proceeded and resulted in a tally of 4 unanimously in favor of proceeding and has passed. \\r\\n\\r\\nHis lordship declares that he is in agreement with the estimate and the vote and it is now declared passed. Funds will be liquidated and the location opened for renovations to begin at earliest convenience. \\r\\n", "time":1526346408 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"Is this a place for carpenters to work? Or a Manor that dwarfs the Rinaldi's?", "time":1525654967 ]) ]), "estimate":"1, 236 denar", "filedby":"Bjorn", "location":"Location designated by previously approved Guild Council vote for this shop", "title":"Newtown Carpenter Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1524084187">
         ([ "body":"On behalf of the great house Doloreaux, and all of the members of the embassy here in this great city, I, Isobel Atache`, would like to propose the planting of one pendulum apricot tree in Calabria park for the use of all. \\n\\nWe are attempting to import several more plants and trees over the course of the coming moons, for the city's use, as well as our own, among which, a peach tree should arrive in our capable hands at some point in the near future.\\n\\n It is our collective wish that we share our fruitful gains with the city as a whole, so that no soul goes either hungry, nor is skinned alive in these trying times where fruits, peaches among the highest sought after, are in lack.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"On the matter of improvements made to Calabria Park, submitted by miss Izzy of the Doloreaux, the collective voted unanimously 3 in agreement. \\r\\n\\r\\nUpon consideration, his Lordship concurs and the matter is settled; work can begin at any time as convenient for those involved. ", "time":1526346453 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"Well Chinco isn't here to ravage it. So it might have a fighting chance. \\r\\n", "time":1525655016 ]) ]), "estimate":"Nothing", "filedby":"Izzy", "location":"Calabria Park", "title":"Calabria Park Additions" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1525619155">
         ([ "body":"\\nStonemason:\\n- Floor: black slate (purchased in Newtown)\\n- Walls: stone or brick, whatever the building currently has\\n\\nTotal: 75 denarii + labor (estimate 75 denarii) = 150\\n\\nCarpenter:\\n- 2 oak benches\\n- 2 oak work benches\\n- 1 oak barrel\\n- 2 oak crates\\n- Door engraved with image of St. Trahern (smith of the sky)\\n\\nTotal: 120 denarii + labor (estimate 120 denarii) = 240\\n\\nBlacksmith:\\n- 4 brass sconces\\n- Brass metal locker\\n- 1 iron tool rack\\n\\nTotal: 24 denarii + labor (estimate 24 denarii) = 48\\n\\nDonated Items:\\n- Forge: donated by Avoirdupois\\n- Grindstone: Guild resources donated by Bruno (tokens, awaiting quote)\\n- Anvil: donated by Bruno\\n\\nGrand Total: 438 denarii\\n\\nIn addition, local smiths may create pieces to hang on the walls to serve as decor and advertising of their wares. Limit one piece per smith.\\n\\n[OOC descriptions\\n\\nan open-air smithy\\n\\nA forge with a large billows dominates the center of the blacksmithâ€™s workshop, the red hot glow of the coals illuminating the austere red bricks of the wall and black slate tiles comprising the floor. Loosely arranged around the forge are a number of tables and workstations, as well as a whetstone and anvil. The light from the forge is augmented by sconces located around the periphery of the space and the barn-door style double doors set in the northern wall that can be swung wide to allow proper ventilation to the otherwise smoky workshop. The interior of the doors are each carved with an outstretched hand, giving the visual of a welcoming embrace when opened to the street north of here.\\n]", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"On the matter of the plans for the Newtown Smithy, presented by mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, the vote stands at 3 unanimously in agreement. \\r\\n\\r\\nHis lordship similarly agrees and the matter is considered passed. The matter is queues while work finishes on the Carpenters shopfront, after which point the renovations may commence.", "time":1526346497 ]) ]), "estimate":"438 denarii", "filedby":"Bruno", "location":"Newtown", "title":"Newtown Smithy" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1535506052">
         ([ "body":"Grand Vezir Ja'an of the Akoman city Kandish has requested an Akoman embassy in Triskellian for the purpose of opening trade between our respective cities. The following terms have been proposed:\\n* The Guild Council will provide a location for the embassy.\\n* Kandish will provide materials and employ local crafters for renovations.\\n* Kandish will continue employ the Sailors Guild to handle all imports and exports, as well as set up routine travel vessels between Kandish and Triskellian for paying travelers.\\n", "comments":([  ]), "estimate":"Undetermined", "filedby":"Bruno", "location":"Undetermined", "title":"Akoman Embassy" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1535508522">
         ([ "body":"This is a proposal for a pavilion to be built on the beach, attached to an upgraded pier.  This pavilion will be a pagoda style with an open center to act as a fire pit.  The pavilion will have four tables with two benches at each table.  This is something to improve the appearance and the functionality of the beach as well as providing cover during foul weather, and shade when needed.  \\nThe pier upgrade will be to improve appearance and functionality.\\n\\nI have yet to receive the estimates from the Woodworking guild, but have offered to fund this endeavor entirely.  ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Design and labor detailed breakdown.\\r\\n\\r\\nA Pavillion which is 20 feet by 20 feet, the initial roof line is 8 feet from the ground. The roof comes to a truncated point where there is a smoke hole to support the departure of smoke from the stone firepit in the center of the area beneath the pavillion. The structure of the pavilion will be constructed with clear lacquered oak with teak shingles. There will be 4 tables and 8 benches made of clear lacquered mahogany. The land around the construction point will need to be cleared prior to construction.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe dock that is currently positioned off of the beach east of the city is poor repair. Upon inspection, it was determined that 3 of the 8 pilings have significant rot and need to be replaced. The rotted pilings have allowed one of primary horizontal supports make contact with the water and is no longer structurally sound and should be replaced. Throught wear and tear, all of the boards on the deck should be replaced. There is currently oak on the deck but we are recommending teak which is a more water resistant wood.\\r\\n\\r\\nPavillion Construction\\r\\nVertical Supports (Oak) x4 - 96 denarii\\r\\nHorizontal Base Framing (Oak) x8 - 192 denarii\\r\\nSmoke Hole Framing (Oak) x2 - 48 denarii\\r\\nStringers (Oak) x24 (12 boards) - 288 denarii\\r\\nRoof Panels (Pine) x8 - 168 denarii (21d/panel)\\r\\nShingles (Teak) x16 - 112 denarii (7d/package of shingles)\\r\\nLacquer (Clear) x3 - 60 denarii\\r\\nNails x1 - 2 denarii\\r\\nPegs (Oak) x50 - 50 denarii\\r\\nFire Pit (Stone) x1 - 200 denarii\\r\\nTables (Mahogany) x4 - 32 denarii (8d/table)\\r\\nBench (Mahogany x8 - 40 denarii (5d/table)\\r\\n\\r\\nLabor - Master Carpenter - 500 denarii\\r\\nLabor - Plannning - 500 denarii\\r\\nLabor - General Carpenters x4 - 200 denarii\\r\\nLabor - General Workers (Construction) x5 - 120 denarii\\r\\nLabor - General Workers (Landscaping) x3 - 50 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\nMaterials - 1,238 denarii\\r\\nLabor - 1,320 denarii\\r\\nTotal - 2,558 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nDock Repairs\\r\\nPiling Replacement (Teak) x3 - 60 denarii (2 boards/piling)\\r\\nPrimary Stringer (Teak) x1 - 10 denarii\\r\\nFloor Boards (Teak) x16 (8 boards) - 88 denarii\\r\\nNails x1 - 2 denarii\\r\\nPegs (Teak) x20 - 20 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\nLabor - Master Carpenter - 200 denarii\\r\\nLabor - General Carpenters x2 - 50 denarii\\r\\nLabor - Diver x2 - 200 denarii\\r\\nLabor - General Workers x2 - 10 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\nMaterials - 180 denarii\\r\\nLabour - 460 denarii\\r\\nTotal - 640 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\nPavillion - 2,558 denarii Dock Repair - 640 denarii\\r\\nTotal - 3,198 denarii\\r\\n\\r\\nBjorn, Triskellian Woodworkers Alliance.", "time":1537318277 ]) ]), "estimate":"up to 4000 denarii", "filedby":"Trevyn", "location":"Beach to the east and south of docktown", "title":"Beach Upgrade" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1537309215">
         ([ "body":"Soup Kitchen\\n\\nCeiling (Ash) x2 - 25 denarii\\nWalls, Wainscot (Ash) x6 - 50 denarii\\nFloor (Oak) x2 - 24 denarii\\nShutters (Spruce) x4 - 32 denarii\\nCounter (Maple) x1 10 denarii\\nNails x1 - 2 denarii\\nTables (Poplar) x4 - 20 denarii (5d/table)\\nBench (Poplar) x8 - 24 denarii (3d/bench)\\nCupboard for storage (Poplar) x 1 15 denarii\\nBowls (birch) x20 - 20 denarii\\nPlates (birch) x20 - 20 denarii\\nLabor - General Carpenters x2 - 75 denarii\\n\\nMaterials - 242 denarii\\nLabor - 75 denarii\\nTotal - 302 denarii\\n\\nI would of course need to add costs for two pair of blue and white checked curtains, a stove, and various kitchen sundries, such as a cook would require to prepare the foods.  \\n\\nI plan to order the foodstuffs from local farmers.  My thought was to serve primarily simple but hearty fare, such as lentil stew with smoked dray ham and carrots, rustic bread, a wedge of cheese, and perhaps fruit, in season.\\n\\nThis will benefit the city by providing healthy and substantial foodstuffs to the folk who generally must be reduced to begging, or go without.  This will hopefully encourage them to apply themselves more vigorously to honest labour.  It could also perhaps provide a small bit of income to folk who wish to help take a shift in the kitchen, perhaps a denari per day, or to help sweep and do dishes.\\n", "comments":([  ]), "estimate":"Approximately 400 denarii", "filedby":"Morven", "location":"Would like to renovate a building in Docktown, near docks.", "title":"Free Soup Kitchen for Docktown" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="buildingrequests:1544390062">
         ([ "body":"As an Idea to tend to the import issues and hoarding of imports. The cost of items tends to become out of reach for any normal person.\\n\\nI suggest a public warehouse that all the houses and sailors can use. Imports entering the city will, by default go to this warehouse that will be managed and operated by the City Watch Group. What this warehouse will offer is the ability for anyone within the city to stop and see every single imported item and who owns it. Once a person finds an item of interest. they can write to the owner and negotiate a selling price on the said item. Once agreed. the owner can submit the release request with the city watch stating that said item is to be sold for X amount to X person. \\n\\nA fee for this transaction would be identical to the tent market located on market street in docktown. Each transaction will cost the seller one denarii. The consumer will pay the watch for said item and the watch will forward the coin for that sell. minus the fee. to the former owner of the import. By doing this. All houses can bring in everything they possibly can and keep it within reach of the consumers. There will be options that importers can do. If a payment agreement is made. the initial down payment will be collected by the City Watch. and the item will be released. The City Watch will pay the importer the remaining amount in full. And Within reason. the remaining amount must be paid to the city watch by the purchaser. If the purchaser fails to do so. The city watch will place a hold on said person's bank account and take what is owed. Or continue to collect from the bank account until the amount is paid in full.\\n\\nIn my opinion. I feel a start-up guild that was hired for a job that requires materials that is not regularly offered within the city. would now have a chance to negotiate a price to obtain an item. And complete the job so they can grow as a business and a guild. The City Watch can be the mediators and make sure all transactions are completed as agreed. Thus any hoarding of materials for the sole purpose of price inflation can come to an end. The current bidding wars that take place at the auctions will also come to an end and prices of goods will be reduced as a result. Thus opening up more opportunities for the common joe to succeed and not turn to a life of crime by stealing what they need.\\n    \\n In the interest in keeping houses from placing unreasonably high prices on items. In my opinion, I believe that a 30% mark up on the actual cost of import. Would be the standard benchmark for a starting price. And or the bare minimum accepted for the item. That way the house can still turn a profit. And the prices of items stay reasonable and affordable for the everyday start-up guild. After all, the entire idea of this is to end wars such as the steel wars most of us have lived through and have to pay five hundred. Even up to one thousand denarii for a single rod of plain..boring steel. Something of this nature would allow all to benefit from the import. All will make a profit. And all prices would be sane. The cost is a mere estimate. It will all depend on the location of the warehouse and what the city decides.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:wa:waylon\>:([ "comment":"As I hear, security is a concern for this.  I would be happy to post Constables for security purposes.  Also, the notion of putting those that try to mug people for coin to work as a means of paying off fines would be possible.  This could also be applied to other inmates as well, serve under the watch of the Constables as a sort of Community service.  \\r\\n\\r\\nAedile Nikona Stonehide\\r\\nConstabulary", "time":1545357493 ]), \<Chatters:AE:tr:trevyn\>:([ "comment":"As Ambassador of the Doloreaux Embassy, I think this idea has great merit.  As I said in the meeting, I think it could go a long way to improve business for all parties. This would allow for customers to ask for imports directly, and to be able to purchase them on an afore agreed to price.  These items would come to the warehouse, where the customer could make the purchase there without muss or fuss.  Special or very high end items would go to auction by discretion.\\r\\nAs to the issue of security of the items, that is not an overly complicated issue. Each Embassy could assign guards, or the city could assign constabulary guards, or this city watch, though it would take some rather vigorous oversight on such an organization.\\r\\nI also think that perhaps the funds for such a building could be raised between the four embassies, the Sailors.  I think this would be a good investment opportunity to support local guilds and trades.\\r\\n\\r\\nSir Trevyn Adalhard, Ambassador.", "time":1544918340 ]) ]), "estimate":"4000 ", "filedby":"Chesh", "location":"To be determined ", "title":"Import warehouse" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1479458669">
         ([ "body":"Material in this city is entirely too high. Specifically fabrics, as a seamstress I find it to be an utter bothersome when I have to pay so much for fabrics and hope that I'll make it back with orders.\\n\\nI think things could be reevaluated to decide on what's a fair price for all materials. I also believe that the crafters should have a voice in this.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I am not sure it is fair to tell a merchant what he should sell his wares for. Some fabrics are more difficult to create and obtain (such as silk). Then there is the cost to transport it here. Most of the items that are imported are of the rarer variety so it makes sense to me that the base cost would be higher. As Antonia said, imports will always cost what people are willing to pay.", "time":1479599949 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"The prices you charge for your creations clearly make up for the expenses you have on the materials. That is common business sense. Some materials are very expensive, others are cheap.\\r\\nAs for things on the auction house, prices reflect what people are willing to pay for them, which I do agree, is very extreme in many cases, but such cannot be regulated.", "time":1479475470 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"My opinion still stands however I have taken what you all have said and I'll do some thinking on it. I thank you for lending your opinions.\\r\\n", "time":1480138362 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"The prices of materials should be charged to the customer. Just like crafters charge a labor charge so do merchants and those who make or gather the raw material for fabrics. You are paying for the privilege to have seemingly unlimited amount of fabric available. In my opinion if we push merchants to sell for less they might sell less material to create more demand that would justify higher prices.", "time":1479602047 ]), \<Chatters:AE:ig:ignacio\>:([ "comment":"If you are talking about materials sold by the merchant of the city, it is their right to sell those at the price they deem appropriate. Free trade city and all. If you are unhappy about how high some of the auctions go, you can definitely try working out some sort of agreement with other guilds and even the houses!", "time":1480952917 ]) ]), "filedby":"Orla", "guild":"SoWeCanSew", "title":"Material pricing" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1479721443">
         ([ "body":"Newtown market circle is a great opportunity waiting to happen. This is a great gathering place for vendors, merchants, and consumers but as it stands it is under utilized.\\n\\nI believe the reason is cramped spaces and crowded faces. To this effect I think it would be best to centralize vendors and merchants in an organized manner.\\n\\nSince market circle is mostly vacant it is my suggestion that material vendors for crafters be in the south region of market circle and house vendors be in the southeast region while merchant and guild tables be in the northwest region. \\n\\nOf course we could have tents or something similar to separate the clutter and keep them in a single region of market circle as well. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I could see this benefiting the area. (ooc: Make the tents actual rooms that the various merchants are inside of?)", "time":1479772687 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"Having been denied by vote at the meeting that occurred on the 12th of NIght, this suggestion has been closed.", "time":1495593006 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"I would greatly appreciate more order at the Market Circle as it is difficult now to find the right merchant when you are looking for specific products.\\r\\nTo have them spread out and organized into groupings will make things much easier, and ensure that trade flows easily.\\r\\n[ooc: for me, anything that limits the number of NPCs in one room and sort of organizes things. Either by spreading them to different rooms on the market circle (it consists of like 5-6 different rooms I think), or by tents they are found inside.\\r\\nOn the note of tents, I've noticed the image shows you go into a tent when you go south, but you go to the  next room of the market circle instead, it's a bit confusing for new players that I think.]", "time":1479970105 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"I agree with encouraging the merchants to spread out just a bit as right now they are all working right no top of each other. [OOC: You might for instance know you need to talk with the wolf merchant for some product, but then if some player shows up you now can't just target the \\"wolf\\" and that gets frustrating. Same with any of the other race merchants.]", "time":1480440004 ]) ]), "filedby":"Doctor Hush", "guild":"Triskellian University", "title":"Market circle" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1479776507">
         ([ "body":"An embassy ambassador has recently announced that she is offering smithing services to the city. In a time where it has been difficult for crafters to obtain work, it is frustrating that houses (who already have a great source of wealth and resources at their disposal) are trying to take away what little opportunity crafting guilds have. Perhaps the ambassador does not realize how harmful this is to the guilds of the city but it is harmful nonetheless. It is not the first time an embassy has stepped on the toes of crafters and the last time it happened, an independent seamstress spoke against it and was nearly blacklisted. I have heard so many times to the point I am tired of it, that Houses fully support the independent guilds yet (with the exception of the Avoirdupois) few have SHOWN support.\\n\\n* Show support by not recruiting crafters.\\n* Show support by not offering services that should be provided by commoners.\\n* Show support by patroning the independent guilds.\\n* Show support by speaking against other embassies who do these things.\\n\\nWho truly supports independent guilds? Now is the time we need you most.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Rather than just complain about this problem, I would like to propose a solution: the council can work with the various shops to establish a consignment system. That is, orders can be taken by the shop keepers and fulfilled by guild crafters. Emphasis on GUILD. This streamlined system would better ensure that work goes to the crafting guilds of the city. (ooc: A randomly generated board of orders to represent NPCs in the city. Players can fulfill the orders for a bit of coin. There should be a limit to what someone can make per day so that one person is not taking all the orders. The council has full control over who can work under the consignment system.)", "time":1480721046 ]), \<Chatters:AE:he:heather\>:([ "comment":"As a House crafter I have to disagree entirely with this. First, I pay for everything I get from the auction on my own. My House does not pay which mean it would be the same way had I been in my own guild. The reason I joined the House in the first place is because I could not afford lessons and to buy materials due to other crafting guilds running up the price then not even using the material they bought. So, yes the house did aid me in my lessons in turn I aid them where I can with my craft. I see no problem with this. I suggest we first have crafters stop turning against each other and learn to work together. If not for certain people, the church and the Houses I would not be where I am today. The other crafters were brutal and did not wish me to pursue jewelry just because it would take away from them. Houses aren't the problem, they're the solution or in my case they were.", "time":1480102652 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"The idea of a consignment system was PASSED at the meeting on the 12th of Night, therefor I shall close this suggestion here as the consignment system shall help to alleviate the issue between Houses and Guilds.", "time":1495593191 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"It has been an issue for years. In the past houses have sat on the monopoly on crafts needing what they import, effectively making it impossible for an independent guild ot start up, as a house of course only will import what benefits their own crafters and has the resources to outbid any independent.\\r\\n\\r\\nI do not think any house, when you look at the last decade, can rightfully claim they never hired one single crafter.", "time":1479817848 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"Well I've never had a problem with this but I assume that is perhaps because it's never affected me. Maybe crafters could have some form of contract that members make before you spend coin and resources on them. ", "time":1480138531 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"This has been a complaint for a long time. Crafting guilds have a hard time getting a leg up because they can't compete with houses who offer crafting jobs and house import then take the labor and the best material for house use.", "time":1479793522 ]) ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "guild":"The Hands of St. Trahern", "title":"Houses offering services of crafters" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1479906579">
         ([ "body":"I have repeatedly noticed that slaves no longer do their duties, nor are treated with the precautions that slaves warrant.\\n\\nCan we bring this topic up and have all slave owners informed officially of what is expected of them and their slaves. Make it a public posting by the Constabulary or whomever is officially responsible for all slaves on what is expected, and if it is broken, what the consequences are.\\n\\nI have personally seen the following over the last half year or so in the city:\\nSlaves own and/or are given money. \\nSlaves do not do their duty of cleaning the garbage bins as is expected.\\nSlaves fight and attack freedmen under the excuse it is muggers and criminals.\\nSlaves are trained to fight, unarmed fighting also to get around the issue of not being allowed weapons.\\nSome slaves even have weapons. \\n\\nFrom what I can see, things have gotten very lax recently, and I choose to hope it is due to lack of education of the slave owners.\\n\\nIs it possible to have something done? This is becoming a growing problem with the increased number of privately owned slaves in the city [ooc: PC slave characters]\\n\\nThank you.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"Current project up for discussion after passing via vote at the meeting of the 12th of Night.", "time":1495593056 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"The trade with slaves falls under the guilds and thereby the council. \\r\\nThere used to be a process in the past where owners were approved to have slaves, which I believe was done by the slavery guild of the city, hence why it is my belief that it falls under the Guild Council to get such practice re-established.\\r\\n\\r\\nIf I am mistaken and others know more of these things step forth to educate me, I will gladly defer to their superior knowledge. Lianaar of old used to be the expert on these matters, so did Harken Zeiss.\\r\\n", "time":1480152938 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"Ah, perhaps it is I who am mistaken. I've never had much dealings or knowledge with the slaves in this city. ", "time":1480157754 ]) ]), "filedby":"Antonia", "guild":"Liguria Trading", "title":"Slave duties, behaviour and expectations" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1480102480">
         ([ "body":"I often notice people complaining about Houses taking on crafters but they never stop to find out why. It is entirely difficult to be a new crafter and perhaps some of you forget this so I'll refresh your memory. \\n\\nWhen I first started crafting, I was bullied, taunted and threatened by mister Clover and his members all because I did not wish to join his Jewelry guild. Before he left town he and his members did many things to try and stop my attempt to become a Jeweler unless I joined them. Refused to sell lessons, they made extremely high bets on materials and just made everything difficult. I couldn't stand on my own, I mean the church aided me but all of the coin got used on the high cost of guild teachers and the high cost of materials. \\n\\nI eventually left my guild and tried to join more established guilds. I tried three different guilds and in each one the owners left. Leaving me with not much to do since I had no say in their guild. This caused me to have to find another. Eventually a house offered aid. For my services they would provide my final lessons. I took this deal since there weren't many options and now I'm doing better than I ever have. I still pay for my own materials and I teach others either free or at a low price because unlike those before me, I'd love to see more crafters in town.\\n\\nSo the point of this lengthy complaint is that crafters need to work together and help when you can. Stop the bullying, stop being underhanded for light sakes, would people stop buying materials and then reselling them at a higher price. The Houses aren't the problems, they have only helped where others have failed to.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Who is doing the bullying exactly? You named one person who has not been present in the city in a very long time.\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen I first arrived in town, I joined a guild and very shortly after, a House made a deal with the leader and began to tell us what we were allowed to make and who we were allowed to sell to. This did not sit well with me because in this city, crafters have the RIGHT to work independently. I left all resources behind to form my own guild. I had nothing and everything I earned was by hard work and forming friendships with other independent guilds AND by working with the embassies to form mutually beneficial contracts. We did not bully or threaten, we supported each other and through this support, we were able to thrive. I do not have rebellious feelings against embassies at all but it is a FACT that labor should be performed by commoner guilds. What do you think happens when jobs are taken from the working people? They get desperate. When people get desperate, either crime goes up or they just leave the city.\\r\\n\\r\\nYou said joining the embassy was the answer yet you still pay for your own materials. How was having your own guild not an option when you pay for your own materials anyway? Just to give history on MY experiences...\\r\\n\\r\\nI have invested thousands upon thousands of denarii in lessons and materials for other smiths. I have devoted more time and energy in them than I can say. Do you know how many have left my guild at the drop of a hat because a house made them an offer they can't refuse? Six that I can name right off the top of my head. If they want to leave to form their own guilds, that is one thing. But for an embassy to benefit from the hard work and resources I dumped into an individual's training? That is wrong.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe point is that commoner guilds should not have to competed with embassies when it comes to the crafts. I can and have and will continue to work with embassies when I am able and when they allow it. But a house poaching crafters and taking work from the guilds is wrong.", "time":1480106087 ]), \<Chatters:AE:he:heather\>:([ "comment":"It's one thing for a House to take a crafter from an active guild and it's another for a House to aid a crafter who has no where else to go.\\r\\nI am uncertain on smith crafters but there has never been many Jewelers, the ones I spoke about were all in mister Clover's guild. While they are gone now they weren't when I was anew crafter and needed help because they refused to do anything kind because I didn't wish to join their guild.\\r\\nI joined the embassy because they aided me with my lessons so I could use my coin to build up my materials which was and still is difficult since people often send extreme bids. For example, the rods that are upon the boards now are not my bid. If there is only two jewelers in town why are the bidding prices going so high?\\r\\nIt's because other guilds and merchants are bidding on them, so please do not try and claim the houses are at fault. The other guilds have their faults also.\\r\\n--\\r\\nAlso, I completely understand that the items are rare and when crafters are in need it gets high. What I don't get however is that if the city only has two jewelers and neither jeweler is bidding on the material because someone made it so high then we know two things. Someone who doesn't need it is bidding and the crafters who do need it are losing out, meaning the city is also losing out.\\r\\nSo my complaint isn't that the houses are charging too much but that other guilds are buying up things they don't -need- and some crafters tend to be unkind and unhelpful to new crafters. Leaving them with no other help. We should be working together to build more cafters instead of trying keep all the work for just one person or group.\\r\\n\\r\\n--\\r\\n\\r\\nYes I can ask my house for supplies but so can anyone else, my house would not deny anyone the right to bet on materials that they need or want. It's not hard at all to write a scroll. And no, I don't have unlimited funds to throw at materials. I wish I did but no I don't.", "time":1480430227 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"Half of all active crafters in this city are held by Houses. And if the rods are high, it proves only that demand is high. And when that demand is coming from other Houses with the astronomical wealth of an entire nation to back them, yes, prices do get high. Similarly, those items you mentioned are NOT astronomically priced. In fact they are quite reasonable considering what you are purchasing. You -do- realise that nation's only break even on the cost of import taxes when an item reaches in excess of two hundred denarii, yes? These items are rare...very rare...and the cost of selling these items trickles down to cover the costs to harvest, mine, process, perfect, pack, guard, ship, import and place for sale at the markets. Every hand that touches that item before it even arrives on the shores of Triskellian needs to receive livable wages. And truly...isn't competition what drives business? Perhaps instead of complaining that other guilds are being competitive to get the wares they need to provide for their customers, you should complain about nation's throwing their kitties into the bidding wars. If they do not have a need for materials, they won't need to bid on them. And the prices won't be so high because guilds have far  more limited resources to dump into the process of buying materials. Nations are here to import their wares and operate trade embassies. Not run the crafting businesses that belong in the hands of guilds.", "time":1480128301 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"As part of the Doloreaux, you can request import of anything that you personally want, and you do not need to heed the wishes of what anyone else might want. All other crafters need to go to your house, negotiate a deal for your house to import things, and then they need to win it on the auctions. \\r\\nIf this is not a clear advantage similar to what Clover did some years ago, then I do not know what is. Clover sat on monopoly because he had an exclusive trade contract with the Doloreaux, and he had the funds to win any auction he desired.", "time":1480311301 ]), \<Chatters:AE:ig:ignacio\>:([ "comment":"As stated on another topic, the nature of this being a free trade city is that these things happen. Best thing you can do is talk to the people personally about why they are bidding up materials.", "time":1480953287 ]) ]), "filedby":"Heather", "guild":"Heavenly Jewelry", "title":"Overly Competitive Guilds" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1526267621">
         ([ "body":"I would like the Guild Council to consider establishing a process for removing inactive guild members. My proposal:\\n\\n* A council guild is considered inactive if it has not been represented at a council meeting (in person or by scroll) in a six month period.\\n* Once a council guild is considered inactive, the council will attempt to notify the guild in person, by scroll, and by public posting. The council guild will need to be represented at the next meeting or it will lose its seat on the council.\\n\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:am:amara0\>:([ "comment":"I quite agree with this proposal. ", "time":1535068815 ]) ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "guild":"The Hands of St. Trahern", "title":"Removing inactive council members" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1540174460">
         ([ "body":"I would like to propose a Triskellian City Watch group to be stationed in Docktown. This group would be comprised of volunteers who care for the safety and security of the guilds--not just in Docktown but in all of Triskellian. The City Watch would not be a law-enforcement group and so would work with the Constabulary to ensure law processes are being followed.\\n\\nPURPOSE\\nThe City Watch will look out for the safety of the people and enforce guild rights. Responsbilities include, but are not limited to:\\n* Patrolling Docktown to ensure the main streets are safe for travel.\\n* Providing escort to those who do not feel safe traveling alone.\\n* Act as mediators during House vs. Guild disputes.\\n* Enforce the trade laws that are passed to protect the rights of the guilds (reporting violations to the council, collecting fines from violators).\\n\\nThe City Watch will NOT be responsible for:\\n* Filing crime reports (only constables have this authority).\\n* Arresting wanted criminals.\\n\\nSTRUCTURE\\nThe group would be led by a council appointed Commander. The Commander would be responsible for recruiting and ensuring that the group fulfills its purpose. The Commander is free to organize the group as he or she deems fit but may be removed from the position by the Council if it is determined that:\\n* The Commander is abusing his or her position of power.\\n* The Commander takes an unannounced leave of absence.\\n* The Commander fails to fulfill the group's aforementioned purpose.\\n\\nJOINING THE WATCH\\nOnly non-House members are permitted to join. The Commander will handle the application process as he or she deems appropriate.\\n\\nHEADQUARTERS\\nI propose that the old jailhouse be used as a headquarters for this operation with no structural modifications to the building itself.\\n\\n* Main room: On-duty watchmen are stationed here. Bell that can be rang from the Newtown gate (rope/bell system).\\n* Hallway: Guard that allows/denies access to rooms.\\n* Room west of hallway: Barracks for off-duty watchmen.\\n* Cells (right of hallway): Can be used for storage, armory, medical station, etc.\\n\\nRESOURCES\\n* Guard for the hallway (~1000 denarii)\\n* Supplies, furniture, storage, whatever we need to furnish the building (~250 denarii)\\n* Rope/bell system (4 ropes, pulleys use existing bell in the main room ~200 denarii)\\n* Armbands to signify loyalty to the watch (~100 denarii)\\n* TOTAL: 1550 denarii. Bruno Smith is willing to donate the funds to support this endeavor.\\n\\nOOC Notes:\\n* This is still a public space so we should try to keep access fairly open. No one room should only be accessible by 1 or 2 people alone. If we need to restrict anything, we can use locked storage containers.\\n* All council members should be on the guard's allow list to show that the building is council controlled and not controlled by any single person or guild. We should also be unrestrictive about who can join the city watch.\\n\\nINCENTIVES AND COMPENSATION\\nThe City Watch will offer the following incentives and compensation to members:\\n* Free armor and weapon maintenance (to be handled by select guilds)\\n* Free medical treatment (to be handled by select guilds)\\n* 5% bonus to individuals who successfully collect a fine\\n* 100% of any monetary tips that are collected when providing escort or mediation services\\n", "comments":([  ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "guild":"The Hands of St. Trahern", "title":"Establishing City Watch group" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="complaints:1540861302">
         ([ "body":"I would like to propose a license requirement for all non-guild crafter who wish to conduct their trade in Triskellian. Non-guild crafters (such as House employed crafters) would need to petition to the council for a license. The license fee, once approved would cost 500 denarii and would need to be renewed annually. Any non-guild crafter discovered to be advertising their wares, such as utilizing the trade tables or public posts, would be in violation of this agreement and their respective employer would be fined 1000 denarii.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"In response to the inquiries about this suggestion, I have written up a response to the questions that were asked:\\r\\n\\r\\n1) Who is required to obtain a license?\\r\\n\\r\\nAny crafter who is employed by a Great House, Church, or Constabulary. Guild crafters do no require a license.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n2) Who is considered a crafter?\\r\\n\\r\\nAny individual who practices a the following trades:\\r\\n\\r\\nBlacksith\\r\\nWeaponsmith\\r\\nArmorsmith\\r\\nCarpenter\\r\\nTailor\\r\\nSeamstress\\r\\nDyer\\r\\nJeweler\\r\\nStonemason\\r\\nGardener (crafting of goods only)\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n3) Are non-guild crafters exempt from needing a license if they do not openly advertise their wares (such as only doing maintenance work for their organization)?\\r\\n\\r\\nNo. This still takes money out of the pockets of the guilds.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n4) Can unlicensed individuals sell their goods privately?\\r\\n\\r\\nNo. Attempting to sell good privately without a license leaves the crafter open to being fined.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n5) Does the Guild Council have the right to refuse licenses?\\r\\n\\r\\nYes.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n6) Can the Guild Council revoke a license after it has been issued?\\r\\n\\r\\nYes, if any of the terms of the licensure agreement are violated, the Council may revoke an individual's license.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n7) License Application and Terms of Agreement\\r\\n\\r\\nFill out all information completely or your application will be denied.\\r\\n\\r\\nName: \\r\\nOrganization: \\r\\nTrade(s):\\r\\n\\r\\nDo you have the authority to request imports on behalf of your organization? \\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nWhy do you feel you should be granted a license?\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n(Include a letter of recommendation from an existing crafting guild)\\r\\n\\r\\nBy signing this application:\\r\\n\\r\\n* I swear that the above information is true and accurate. Should it be discovered that the above information not be true, I understand that my application may be denied. If the discovery is made after a license is issued, my rights to said license will be revoked. \\r\\n\\r\\n* I acknowledge that it is my responsibility to update the Guild Council with the updated information if I am issued a license. Failure to do so will result in loss of license.\\r\\n\\r\\nSignature: _____________________________", "time":1541554824 ]) ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "guild":"The Hands of St. Trahern", "title":"Establishing Crafter Rights - License requirement" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1479855355">
         ([ "body":"[ooc: Copying this from the forums so we have record of it here]\\r\\n\\r\\nI, Lothario Wheeler Wright, Grand Master Elect of the Guild Council and leader of the Merchant's Guild, am announcing a meeting to be held this coming weekend to vote on the following topics;\\r\\n\\r\\nPrivateers of the Vicious Koi application\\r\\nLiguria Trade application\\r\\nSeamstress Shop building proposal\\r\\nNewtown Hospital proposal\\r\\n\\r\\nVoting will take place after a brief reading of public opinion from the discussion board. We will illustrate the approved locations for these buildings on a zoning map of available locations.\\r\\n\\r\\nPlease direct your attention to my second posting about meetings and how they will occur as well as a public record of zoning approval and building proposals.\\r\\n\\r\\nFor the people,\\r\\nMaster Lothario", "comments":([  ]), "date":"[November 26th, 2016]", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1480462865">
         ([ "body":"We will vote on all topics that are at least one week old. Will summarize those specific topics here, for convenience, one week prior to the meeting.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:ig:ignacio\>:([ "comment":"Unfortunately, we will need to postpone the Guild Council meeting to the 12th day of Night. We have a huge backlog of topics to vote on so I'd like to ask that all councilors submit their votes on these topics PRIOR to the meeting and we will use the meeting time to count the votes and also to go over current projects. You may vote: yes, no, or postpone topic (postponing means there is more information you need to collect before making a decision; please make efforts to collect this information before the meeting date and only postpone as a last resort).\\r\\n\\r\\nAll information, notes, and opinions regarding these topics can be found in the guild council building. Since the drop box is still under construction, all votes can be submitted to Master Lothario or Master Ignacio.\\r\\n\\r\\nBuilding Proposals\\r\\n* Council-funded public ballroom for Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded restaurant for Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded coffee house for Northern Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded cigar bar for Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded guild hall\\r\\n* Council-funded child daycare\\r\\n* Moving the orphanage to Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded smithy in Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded carpentry shop in Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded jewelery shop in Newtown\\r\\n* Council-funded stone mason shop in Newtown\\r\\n\\r\\nOther proposals\\r\\n* Should Market Circle be reorganized for better flow of traffic?\\r\\n* Should the Council address the issue of slave duties, behavior, and expectations?\\r\\n* Should the Council work with local shops to establish a consignment system to ensure steady workflow for independent crafters?\\r\\n* Should the Council devise a plan to ensure safe passage of goods through Docktown?\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nAfter the meeting, we will be giving a tour of properties that are currently under the jurisdiction of the council and can be used for various building projects.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nMaster Ignacio", "time":1480967992 ]) ]), "date":"[December 12th, 2016]", "filedby":"Ignacio", "time":"[9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1492415062">
         ([ "body":"This meeting will be for the discussion of the already approved Clothier's Shop Project.\\r\\n\\r\\nCraftsman and interested parties are encouraged to attend regardless of if they belong to a guild that is on the council or not.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:IC:ma:maniae\>:([ "comment":"Meeting happened, crafters told about the rooms that can be crafted, and Orla told to get in a plan for the new clothier shop by the end of the next month.", "time":1493603688 ]) ]), "date":"April 29th, 2017", "filedby":"Thais", "time":"1pm Eastern Time" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1495592167">
         ([ "body":"Building plans for:\\r\\n\\r\\nSeamstress Shop\\r\\nSmithy Shop (n/a)\\r\\nStone Masonry Shop\\r\\nJewelry Shop\\r\\n\\r\\nGuild Hall\\r\\n(and/or workshop spaces tbd?)\\r\\n\\r\\nADDITIONAL TOPICS TO DISCUSS\\r\\nAny Open Council Applications\\r\\nSafe Passage Arrangement\\r\\nAddition of Consignment Systems for Guilds\\r\\nDiscussion of Slave Duties\\r\\n\\r\\nANY ADDITIONAL PROPOSALS OR SUGGESTIONS MADE BEFORE DATE OF NEXT MEETING", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"We need to be certain that developing new craft areas in Newtown is not at the detriment of Docktown. Having said that, the Jewelry Shop being in Newtown makes sense", "time":1496803812 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Perhaps we can assign an individual to each building project so that we have rough plans in place when it comes time to focus on the other projects? I think this will save time in the future so. Can we also vote on project priority?", "time":1496798290 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"The results of the meeting have been approved and posted on the public boards to all to peruse. ", "time":1497496171 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"I have a proposal for the safe passage into docktown by those that wish to not fight. I do have enough men that I can post on duty so a person can \\"hire a escort\\" at the gate between newtown and docktown. Fee would apply to cover costs of the escort and possible tax for docktown repairs. But person would be safe from the mugging that is occurring so frequently", "time":1497203018 ]) ]), "date":"June 11", "filedby":"Topsy", "time":"9 pm est" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1516182661">
         ([ "body":"There will be a guild council meeting on Mercredi the twenty-seventh day of Yule in the year of 899 Apres le Miracle. This will be at the first late bell (1pm est - whatever time that is ig) and I will wait ten ticks for latecomers before we begin. We will be discussing the shops that were previously agreed on in the last meeting and working out how to execute them and which to start with next.\\r\\n\\r\\nFurthermore, we will discuss all guild applications and vote on them. I suggest all council members take this time to get to know the applicants if you have not already. Any other issues or questions may be brought to the council and we will discuss them if there is time or save it for the next meeting.", "date":"27th Yule", "filedby":"Fips", "time":"13:00" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1520724776">
         ([ "body":"* Voting on new membership\\r\\n* Voting on building proposals\\r\\n* Discussing current projects; their status and estimated completion dates.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"Having reviewed the notes from the meeting, his Lordship and his respective entourage have made the following decrees;\\r\\n\\r\\nThe meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe votes for new member applications stand as such;\\r\\nEye On Scales: 0 in favor, 4 against\\r\\nTresses \& Treasures: Unanimous 3 month trial, must increase membership by 2\\r\\nRoofus' Guild: 3 in favor, 1 against\\r\\n\\r\\nThe office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms agreement with the above listed outcomes and the guilds of Tresses and Treasures as well as the Black and MacDubglass Misfit Company are welcomed into the Guild Council. The Eye on Scales guild will be able to reapply in three to six months.\\r\\n\\r\\nOn the matter of the building proposals, the votes stand at;\\r\\nRoofus' headquarters: unanimous no\\r\\nRentable warehouses: unanimous in favor\\r\\n\\r\\nAs such, the office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms the outcome of the votes. Roofus Black will not be permitted to build a private headquarters and warehouses in Docktown have been opened for the use of independent guilds and groups.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe remainder of the meeting was filled with discussion about ongoing projects, of which the Seamstress shop will be nearing completion and proposals for the smithy and the carpenter's workshop will be accepted for review. The discussion of the topic of slavery was tabled for another day.\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\nMister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522629807 ]) ]), "date":"17th of Sap (March 17th)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"9PM Eastern Time" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1524334304">
         ([ "body":"Topics to be discussed:\\r\\n* Any pending council applications (at the time of this notice, there are none)\\r\\n* Newtown smithy proposal\\r\\n* Newtown carpenter shop proposal\\r\\n* Calabria Park additions\\r\\n* Slavery\\r\\n* I would also like to discuss the topic of removing inactive guilds from the council", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"Upon receipt of the minutes from this meeting, His Lordship did declare the following;;\\r\\n\\r\\nThe following members and representatives are duly noted as present at the start of the meeting. \\r\\n\\r\\nMister Bruno Smith, Hands of St Trahern\\r\\nMister Chesh Veressan, CV Guild\\r\\nMistress Azora Dillon, Dillon Mercantile \\r\\nMiss Orla, So We Can Sew\\r\\nLady Emmaline Beaumont, Avoirdupois Trade Embassy \\r\\n\\r\\nSpectators include Mister Bjorn, Triskellian Woodworkers \\r\\n\\r\\nWith the required number of members and representatives in attendance, all following topics and the votes therein are considered to be valid. \\r\\n\\r\\nOn the matter of the plans for the Carpenters shopfront located in Newtown, submitted by mister Bjorn of the Triskellian Woodworkers, the voting proceeded and resulted in a tally of 4 unanimously in favor of proceeding and has passed. \\r\\n\\r\\nHis lordship declares that he is in agreement with the estimate and the vote and it is now declared passed. Funds will be liquidated and the location opened for renovations to begin at earliest convenience. \\r\\n\\r\\nOn the matter of the plans for the Newtown Smithy, presented by mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, the vote stands at 3 unanimously in agreement. \\r\\n\\r\\nHis lordship similarly agrees and the matter is considered passed. The matter is queues while work finishes on the Carpenters shopfront, after which point the renovations may commence. \\r\\n\\r\\nOn the matter of improvements made to Calabria Park, submitted by miss Isabelle of the Doloreaux, the collective voted unanimously 3 in agreement. \\r\\n\\r\\nUpon consideration, his Lordship concurs and the matter is settled; work can begin at any time as convenient for those involved. \\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\n\\r\\nSignore Ugatta B. Kitingmay III", "time":1526346335 ]) ]), "date":"6th Day of Flower (OOC: May 6th, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"(OOC: 9pm eastern time)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1535506249">
         ([ "body":"* Akoman Embassy vote\\r\\n* Doloreaux building proposals", "comments":([  ]), "date":"3rd Day of Harvest [OOC: September 3, 2018]", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1536115842">
         ([ "body":"We will be voting on Doloreaux building proposals, as well as any other pending topics listed on the council board.\\r\\n", "comments":([  ]), "date":"11th Day of Harvest (OOC: September 11, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1536657000">
         ([ "body":"We will be voting on Doloreaux building proposals, as well as any other pending topics listed on the council board.\\r\\n", "comments":([  ]), "date":"18th Day of Harvest (OOC: September 18, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1537574695">
         ([ "body":"The Guild Council will meet on the 25th Day of Harvest (OOC: September 25th @ 9pm Eastern Time).\\r\\n\\r\\nWe will be reviewing the soup kitchen proposal, as well as any other pending topics listed on the council board.\\r\\n", "comments":([  ]), "date":"25th Day of Harvest (OOC: September 25, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1539910336">
         ([ "body":"A Guild Council meeting is scheduled for Dimache, the eighteenth day of Hunter's [ OOC - 10-18-2018 - @ 9 pm EST ].\\r\\n\\r\\nAll Guild Council members are implored to be present for this particular meeting, which will be closed to any and all public; including Trade Ambassador's, and their representatives. IE; Guild Council members only.\\r\\n\\r\\nTopics to be Discussed:\\r\\n\\r\\n- Soup Kitchen Proposal and refining details\\r\\n\\r\\n- Project Leader for Newtown Carpentry Shop\\r\\n\\r\\n- Discussion of Crafting Regulations and rights\\r\\n\\r\\n- Protection for Docktown\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nMatters of great importance and delicacy are to be discussed, and we wish to reach the bottom of said matters without any interruptions, outbursts, or other miscellaneous disruptions.\\r\\n\\r\\nWe apologize for any inconvenience or grief this may cause any of our regular attendees, but at this time we see no way to circumvent such a situation.\\r\\n\\r\\nThank you for your understanding, ", "comments":([  ]), "date":"18th Day of Hunter (OOC: October 18, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1540340130">
         ([ "body":"Topics to be Voted On:\\r\\nSoup Kitchen Proposal\\r\\nCity Watch Proposal\\r\\nAny other unresolved topics", "comments":([  ]), "date":"29th Day of Hunter (OOC: October 29, 2018)", "filedby":"Bruno", "time":"[OOC: 9pm Eastern Time]" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1542704304">
         ([ "body":"[Novemeber 27th, 7:00 PM EST]\\r\\n\\r\\n~Topics to be discussed~\\r\\nCity Watch\\r\\nCrafting Rights\\r\\n\\r\\n~Topics to be voted on~\\r\\nNone that I am aware of\\r\\n", "date":"27th day of Frost ", "filedby":"Fips", "time":"7pm" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1544138135">
         ([ "body":"Vote for leader of city watch\\r\\nDiscuses crafter rights.\\r\\nCover open projects and close them.\\r\\nTend to suggestions that still apply.\\r\\n", "date":"11th day of Night (12-11-18)", "filedby":"Chesh", "time":"7th late bell. (7pm eastern time)" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="meetings:1548383364">
         ([ "body":"", "comments":([  ]), "date":"Dimache, the seventh day of Snow (02-07-2019)", "filedby":"Azora", "time":"7th late bell. (7pm eastern time) " ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1479438732">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Ran a successful trip to Akoma, conducted most recent repairs on the docks, attended Guild Council Rally", "blacklistedby":"", "body":"This city is important to us, and while we could just sit around drinking beer and doing absolutely nothing all day, we desire to see this city grow and prosper. Furthermore we desire to be an active part in how that growth happens. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Although I have not met Thais in person, she seems to embody the passion and enthusiasm the council needs. I would hate to deny someone this opportunity because of someone who is not in town.", "time":1479772820 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"I have met the young miss Thais and found her to be eager, attentive and quite upstanding. The quality of her work is top-notch and her ideas, thoughts and discussions always proved engaging, articulate and well-thought. I would strongly support her inclusion on the Council.", "time":1479876187 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I'm in agreement with everyone, Thais is very capable, wise and kind. I think she'd make an excellent member.\\r\\n", "time":1480138000 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"After experiencing the tremendous failures of Virendra, it is a breath of fresh air to see Miss Thais handling the Vicious Koi in a poised and controlled way. I am of the opinion that she would be a fine asset.", "time":1480118372 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"i think this guild would be a good addition to the council. however i would mention and inactive member of this guild is virendra and should he return he would be the founder of this guild and could attend meeting and even sit as a councilor if the current leader is not able to. in this aspect i ask for a contract be drawn up and listed here to ensure that if virendra were to come back to town that he could not attend or vote on behalf of this guild.", "time":1479604252 ]), \<Chatters:AE:ig:ignacio\>:([ "comment":"APPROVED for the COUNCIL by the COUNCIL on the 26th day of Frost.", "time":1480463901 ]) ]), "crest":"fierce koi fish", "filedby":"Thais", "guild":"Privateers of the Vicious Koi", "kitty":"2326", "members":"Thias, Ethelinda, Rankin, Steve, Neve, Zhela", "purpose":"To serve as private contractors for others that may need assistance on land or sea. ", "teachers":"Brawler, Ranger, Sailor, Merchant, Entertainer, Squire, Assassin, Buccaneer, Enforcer, Whaler, Saboteur, Carpenter, Ranged", "tokens":"3965" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1479446050">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Apprehending notorious criminals", "blacklistedby":"CV", "body":"The constabulary is a key part to Triskellian, the enforcement of the law is crucial. The guild council has influence with laws.The constabulary needs to be up to date on what is happening within the city. With support from other members of the council, the constabulary will be able to be more effective within the city. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"The Constabulary already holds a seat on the Council, seeing they are funded by the Guild Council, and therefore the Constabulary has a vote in all matters related to the law.", "time":1479454680 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"they don't need to be voted on, as antonia says they already hold a seat as does the church. they can attend and vote on all matters regarding their groups. it might even be useful to put both the church and constables as provisional councilors on the main board.", "time":1479604028 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Since it is fact of matter that the Constabulary, funded by the Guild Council, holds a seat on the Council and can vote in matters pertaining to law and peace keeping, we can set this matter to the side as settled business.", "time":1479662975 ]) ]), "crest":"A sword and shield", "filedby":"Guardsman Roofus", "guild":"Triskellian Constabulary", "kitty":"9771", "members":"Namor, Roofus,Kegan,Nikona", "purpose":"To enforce the laws and protect the citizens", "teachers":"constable,savage,guard,bodyguard,enforcer,healer,scout,musketeer, and squire", "tokens":"46437" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1479453767">
         ([ "accomplishments":"The guild is able to train anyone to become a master merchant, as well as has connections with trade in many different locations. The guild at one point had 8 active members, though two have now permanently left the city, while two others are out of the city on business.", "blacklistedby":"Lucky Foxes", "body":"The Guild Council and the Guilds are the future of Triskellian. They need a strong presence in the city. \\n\\nAntonia is a Master Merchant with many years of experience in trade and politics before creating her own guild. Uxio has experience with the far-away seas and where to find resources and goods. His experience with sailing will be useful for overseas trade and trade connections. Kaylie and Velasco are both experienced guards and know how to protect trade. \\n\\nIt is our hope that the combined experience in both trade and the politics of the houses will serve to aid the Guild Council rise to its fullest potential, as decreed by the Don when the Council was formed, both financially and politically.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Maintaining an active roster is difficult for a guild so I am impressed that she has managed to do so. Whatever she is doing right we could use on the council.", "time":1479772945 ]), \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>:([ "comment":"Miss Antonia, over the course of the last year, has proven herself to be hardworking and dedicated to improvement. Her perseverance is encouraging and I think she would be a boon to the Council.", "time":1479876334 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"If anyone has any questions or concerns they are more than welcome to contact me and discuss matters with me personally. I will be happy to answer what questions you may  have.", "time":1480159924 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I am uncertain how Antonia would do as a council member but based on the facts she has succeeded in many of the ways that are required and if she is accepted I look forward to seeing how she does.", "time":1480157882 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:rh:rhiannon1\>:([ "comment":"I confess I can see the promise of Miss Antonia's presence on the Guild Council. However, I say this with caution as one who has personally felt the affects of poor choices made by Antonia in the past. Perhaps, however, this will be a continuation of a \\"new leaf\\", as they call it. ", "time":1480118236 ]), \<Chatters:AE:ig:ignacio\>:([ "comment":"APPROVED for the COUNCIL by the COUNCIL on the 26th day of Frost.", "time":1480464883 ]) ]), "crest":"a noble falcon perched atop three horizontal seashells", "filedby":"Antonia", "guild":"Liguria Trading", "kitty":"1861", "members":"Antonia, Uxio, Kaylie, Velasco", "purpose":"iguria Trading specializes in the trade of rare and valuable goods of the highest quality, nationally and internationally.", "teachers":"Raider, Barbarian and to be added what members are in need of.", "tokens":"5432" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1483625620">
         ([ "accomplishments":"250", "blacklistedby":"N/A", "body":"It is important to me, Nuit, and to The Purple Paw to reintroduce to the city of Triskellian the importance of creating and sharing art with our town.  I created this guild as a community for artists and artisans, and I feel that, though The Purple Paw is still in its humble beginnings, it is important for artists - whether members of our guild or not - to have a voice in the Council.\\n\\nI am eager to participate more in the workings of what makes and can make Triskellian great and thriving.\\n\\nThank you for your consideration.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"I believe Nuit has re-left the city", "time":1496802339 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I have written to the leader to learn if she is still active.", "time":1496796944 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th of Flower, this application was unanimously voted NO due to absence from the city.", "time":1497496227 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:an:antonia0\>:([ "comment":"I have been informed that Nuit has left the city again, nor have I seen any of her guild members for a very long time.\\r\\nI would think that as of now, a guild who is not even active in the city cannot join the council.", "time":1487352595 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"It is a shame that Nuit has once again left the city. Perhaps Nuit returns at that time we can consider a fresh application, but I see no reason we need keep this application open for now.", "time":1497221879 ]) ]), "crest":"a purple paw with the letter P inscribed in gold flourished lettering upon each of three pads", "filedby":"Nuit", "guild":"The Purple Paw Guild and Community of Artisans", "kitty":"250", "members":"Nuit, Spopovich, Kurtis", "purpose":"A community for artists and artisans of all skills, to learn, practice and share, for the personal and communal betterment of the City and its inhabitants. In line with its original purpose, the Purple Paw will also curate a collection of finely-crafted articles for sale to interested collectors. The Purple Paw will also have a subsidiary business called Purple Paw Productions, whose purpose is to arrange entertainment and events for the city, and which may be hired by individuals, Guilds or Houses for arrangement and promotion of events.", "teachers":"Carpenter", "tokens":"12" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1496672926">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Helped defend the city against the jadelander invasion.  Assisted in the swamp expedition to deal with the cannibals.  Helped with the excursion to the north to deal with the Jakobi.", "blacklistedby":"Constabulary", "body":"The CV has been an active guild within the city for seven years.  In that time we have switched from a standard mercenary guild to a powerful merchantile guild that also has a strong militant arm and a growing crafts section as well.  As we have been part of this city for such a long time, we feel we should have a say in helping to determine the course for the future, to speak for not only our own members, but for others whom do similar work, to see that all have a voice.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"I would concur with Bruno, CV seem to be very active and it has been a good long while since any member of their guild has caused any problems", "time":1496802486 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"It has been a few years since the situation in which the CV guild was removed from the council. I believe they are deserving of another chance and would represent the voice of Docktown well.", "time":1496796834 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th, this application was unanimously voted YES.", "time":1497496265 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"I think they should join, they're not bad people and active in the city.", "time":1497228853 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"The CV guild has been an active guild in the city for some time. I do believe that they would make a good addition to the council.", "time":1497039986 ]) ]), "crest":"a crest of a broken crown surrounded by scattered pieces of a smashed scepter", "filedby":"Alana", "guild":"CV", "kitty":"5598", "members":"Chesh, Alana, Jaeger, Dieter, Raven, Chima, Drake", "purpose":"Merchantile guild with a strong Militant arm for mercenary work", "teachers":"Armorsmith, Assassin, Buccaneer, Entertainer, Guard, Jeweler, Ranger, Savage, Scholar, Seamstress, Slaver, Spy, Squire", "tokens":"20,943" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1497215685">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Orla and Faith have been on the council before in different guilds as well as always tending to those in need while keeping the city fashionable.", "blacklistedby":"None", "body":"I believe we would make excellent members for the Council because we are the people of the city. We aid newtown and docktown alike and help all factions as needed. \\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I cannot blame Orla for wanting to start her own guild due to Meepers' absence. She was a valued member of the council before and see no reason to deny her remaining on the council.", "time":1497216082 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th, this application was unanimously voted YES", "time":1497496377 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"I look forward to seeing Orla and Faith as part of the council in their rebranded guild.", "time":1497221826 ]) ]), "crest":"A gold ring, displaying a crest of a polished, golden needle that crosses over a golden spool of thread, indicating that the wearer is a member of Couture Classique.", "filedby":"Orla", "guild":"Couture Classique", "kitty":"3600", "members":"Faith", "purpose":"The purpose of Couture Classique is to provide fashionable clothing for all ages and genders of Triskellian at a reasonable price. When you shop with us, you can always expect quality. ", "teachers":"Tailor, Dyer, Merchant", "tokens":"1767" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1513807895">
         ([ "accomplishments":"none", "blacklistedby":"none", "body":"Eyes on scales would like to join the guild council to be more active in the city and to be associated with other reputable guilds.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:pi:pier0\>:([ "comment":"I think the required number in a guild is a minimum of 3, and have the guild's account in good standing order. If they are able to proove this, I have no objections", "time":1516182772 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"\\r\\nThe meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe votes for new member applications stand as such;\\r\\nEye On Scales: 0 in favor, 4 against\\r\\nTresses \& Treasures: Unanimous 3 month trial, must increase membership by 2\\r\\nRoofus' Guild: 3 in favor, 1 against\\r\\n\\r\\nThe office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms agreement with the above listed outcomes and the guilds of Tresses and Treasures as well as the Black and MacDubglass Misfit Company are welcomed into the Guild Council. The Eye on Scales guild will be able to reapply in three to six months.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\nMister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522629898 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"I to was under the impression a guild needs to be more established and have many active members. My mind keeps thinking 12 was the number of members. But I am wrong often ", "time":1515162467 ]), \<Chatters:IC:hu:hush\>:([ "comment":"This seems like a new guild. How long have you been active and do you have more members, I thought we needed at least 3 members. I love that new guilds wish to have a seat but you have to be stable. ", "time":1514667317 ]) ]), "crest":"A circle over a simple fish shape", "filedby":"Staci", "guild":"Eyes on Scales", "kitty":"156 denarii", "members":"Rolando, Staci", "purpose":"To employ fishermen", "teachers":"Fisherman", "tokens":"344 trade tokens" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1519889444">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Actively pursued the opening of the Newtown salon for nearly a decade, throughout which time I have made valuable alliances, and business partnerships. Self-employed the use of my own rented room designated solely as a salong for many years, as the Docktown barber's setting was positively revolting. ", "blacklistedby":"", "body":"I would like to become part of the guild council to help provide, perhaps, something of a different view on matters from the specific standpoint of one who mingles in diverse groups of peoples due to the business in which I toil. \\nI know that the majority of the citizens in the city at present are relatively new to it within the last few years, or, far more 'proper' than I. I believe that I could bring a varied outlook that could help the existing guild council understand the array of needs, and wants of the whole; old and young, rich and poor, newcomer to veteran Triskellians, that they might better accomplish attainable goals, for the people of this city, rather than what a select few might find nearest to their hearts. \\nI do not claim to be a saint, nor an overly pious woman, by any means, but I would like to see this great city thrive, as it was meant to. \\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Lidia has always been involved in the goings-on in the city and has one of the more successful independent jewelry businesses. I think the council should support her however we can.", "time":1520721224 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"\\r\\nThe meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe votes for new member applications stand as such;\\r\\nEye On Scales: 0 in favor, 4 against\\r\\nTresses \& Treasures: Unanimous 3 month trial, must increase membership by 2\\r\\nRoofus' Guild: 3 in favor, 1 against\\r\\n\\r\\nThe office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms agreement with the above listed outcomes and the guilds of Tresses and Treasures as well as the Black and MacDubglass Misfit Company are welcomed into the Guild Council. The Eye on Scales guild will be able to reapply in three to six months.\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\nMister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522629966 ]) ]), "crest":"A lock of hair, adorned with a faceted bead", "filedby":"Lidia", "guild":"Tresses \& Treasures", "kitty":"", "members":"Lidia", "purpose":"Hairstyling and Jeweling", "teachers":"Myself", "tokens":"1,589" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1520285440">
         ([ "accomplishments":"", "blacklistedby":"none", "body":"Black and Macdubglass company set to serve the citizens of the trade city. We wish a seat upon the council to set up security and safety measures. We seek to help in the greatest ways we can.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"I am familiar with the person Roofus and have nothing negative to say. I think the guild would serve the city well.", "time":1520721300 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"\\r\\nThe meeting and all votes therein are duly noted as valid, given the attendance of Mistress Azora of Dillon Mercantile, mister Bruno Smith of the Hands of St Trahern, mister Chesh of the CV guild, and miss Maena of the Triskellian University bringing the number of votes above the three needed to continue. There were also absentee votes delivered that are note reflected below.\\r\\n\\r\\nThe votes for new member applications stand as such;\\r\\nEye On Scales: 0 in favor, 4 against\\r\\nTresses \& Treasures: Unanimous 3 month trial, must increase membership by 2\\r\\nRoofus' Guild: 3 in favor, 1 against\\r\\n\\r\\nThe office of his Lordship recognizes and confirms agreement with the above listed outcomes and the guilds of Tresses and Treasures as well as the Black and MacDubglass Misfit Company are welcomed into the Guild Council. The Eye on Scales guild will be able to reapply in three to six months.\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service to his Lordship,\\r\\nMister J.L Scratchems, Esq.", "time":1522630022 ]) ]), "crest":"A sword with wings emerging from the cross guard. Archaic symbols surround the sword.", "filedby":"Commander Roofus", "guild":"Black and MacDubglass Company", "kitty":"2000", "members":"Roofus,Di,Gowther,Zander", "purpose":"To protect citizens of Triskellian and acquire relics  ", "teachers":"Mercenary,Armorsmith,Weaponsmith, trading,fisherman", "tokens":"700" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1520705122">
         ([ "accomplishments":"15, 576 d", "blacklistedby":"None", "body":"Used to be a member some time ago and wish to re-apply", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"My only question is who will represent the guild at the council meetings?", "time":1520721348 ]) ]), "crest":"Needle and spool of Thread", "filedby":"Baronetess Meepers", "guild":"So You Can Sew", "kitty":"8565d", "members":"Barontessa Meepers, Miss Orla, Miss Faith, Miss Alexia and Mr. Shine", "purpose":"To provide clothes to the town", "teachers":"Seamstress, Tailor, Hairstlyist and Scholar ", "tokens":"7021 d" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="newmemberapplications:1541549670">
         ([ "accomplishments":"Treetop Horizon has engaged in several community events. Most recently the providing of entertainment at Nisha's wedding, and prior to that the painting of the mural in the Docktown. In addition we have tended to the many wounds and ills of the cities Docktown population as well as those of the Newtown.", "blacklistedby":"None", "body":"Treetop Horizons desire to join the council comes from a want to aid the city and its Rodentia more then we can now. Treetop Horizon has most certainly done quite a bit to assist the citizens of the city, and the Rodentia in particular, and we wish to do even more. To be the voice for the Rodentia and the Docktowners in the way only we can.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:IC:ro:roofus\>:([ "comment":"I support this guild on becoming part of the council", "time":1542248495 ]) ]), "crest":"A crown of treetops with the moon and sun hovering above", "filedby":"Eyriel", "guild":"Treetop Horizon", "kitty":"1801", "members":"Eyriel", "purpose":"The purpose of the Treetop Horizon is to aid those of Docktown, with a specific interest in assisting those of the Rodentia in any way possible.", "teachers":"10 teachersm, half career teachers", "tokens":"870" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="projects:1480418556">
         ([ "body":"Building a seamstress shop in the market circle. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:IC:fa:faith\>:([ "comment":"Why is there a need for a shop, when there are only two seamstresses active in the City and we spend almost all our time in the Docktown seamstress shop? I would think its better to spend money of the City somewhere it is needed. What about repairs of the docks and buildings?", "time":1480427727 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Faith, the topic has been discussed and voted upon by the council so this is not really the appropriate time or place to voice concerns about it. If you feel there are areas of the city that need work, you can fill out a building request form and will gladly address those areas.", "time":1480461301 ]), \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting on the 12th of Flower, the suggested plan and estimate was voted YES and approved. Pending release and approval of the funds from the exchequer, building can begin.\\r\\nTHE SHOP HAS BEEN COMPLETED", "time":1551146050 ]), \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>:([ "comment":"There is a need because we aren't the only seamstresses and there will be more during and after our time here. The seamstress shop is not just for -us- but for the city, so those in newtown also have a shop to utilize instead of traveling so far from home into a dangerous area.", "time":1480431283 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"Orla was made lead of this project at the last meeting and will produce plans for voting to the Council at the next meeting TBA.", "time":1495590817 ]) ]), "filedby":"Orla", "supervisor":"Orla and Council", "title":"Newtown Seamstress Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="projects:1480429860">
         ([ "body":"In progress", "comments":([ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\>:([ "comment":"At the meeting occurring on the 12th of Night, representatives of the Church stepped forward and ensured that this is a plan that they are currently working on and funding in it's entirety through the tithe of the penitents and therefore will not need the funds of the City Council to continue such a project. ", "time":1495590735 ]) ]), "filedby":"Orla", "supervisor":"Council ", "title":"Newtown Hospital" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1479345916, "jominey", "E", 1479345929, "jominey", "E", 1479345939, "jominey", "E", 1479437681, "jominey", "X" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
