<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="1520569037">
         ([ "body":"We have come into procession of information dealing with Miss Zhela and ATashi's enslavement was brought about under illegal circumstances. ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:ta:tara\>:([ "comment":"I find that my slave Miss Zhela was taken against her will.  She was in fact kidnapped. Knocked out and taken from her home and forced into slavery. ", "time":1520569570 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"Do we have proof of illegal activity? I do not wish to sound harsh but think more information is needed before acting on the statement. What can be done to determine the facts? If we start freeing every slave who claims they were taken illegally, the guild council will be very busy for a very long time.", "time":1520721626 ]), \<Chatters:Backup:IC:ch:chesh0\>:([ "comment":"Atashi and Zhela are the result of a war with so call enemies. It seem their village was opposing one of triskillians missions. A fight erupted and as a result they was taken captive and enslaved. When this happen many nobles and some of the houses all fought against this saying it was not right. But after a lot of investigating and review of laws. According to the laws of this city. It was justified. And since it happen in akoma..If I recall correctly this was many years ago.. it was Thais and her guild whom took them captive. The church was involved in the investigation also if I recall. And after all was said and done. Thais was found to be in the right for her actions and decisions. I believe there was even criminal charges brought against thais for this. And all dismissed. Meepers has a long history with slavery. And I am no stranger as I was reduced to the high rank slave known as serf. Like Meepers I do not like it. But it is the way this city operates. And it seems Meepers is the owner of one of the two slaves in question. I also own a slave now, though I try to avoid him as much as I can and let the guild use him for what they need as long as its in reason. So do I agree with how these two was captured. no. But this will be challenging the laws and life style set in this city by the Rinaldi...suppose that is the Don. There could be a chance of release. As I've seen many released just in the past few years. Releasing them will cause one thing. A need for help. what will happen? Akomian slaves will appear by the boat load. As they do not care about our laws. And they will always enslave people and sell them to the better off people of other lands. No need to mention names. But I am sure all of you can easily count ten people that would buy one without though.", "time":1520788663 ]) ]), "filedby":"Dame Meepers", "guild":"So You Can Sew", "title":"Dealing with the enslaving of one Miss Zhela and Atashi" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1540858983">
         ([ "body":"I would like to propose that crafting teachers be restricted to guilds only (ooc: NPC guilds). Non-guild organizations in need of crafting teachers would then seek out lessons from guilds. This opens up opportunity for guilds to earn more coin from offering lessons, which can then be used to spend on materials and imports. Better flow of coin will benefit everyone.\\n\\nThis, of course, would require Houses to give up their crafting instructors (ooc:  NPC teachers). Compensation can be discussed.\\n", "comments":([ \<Chatters:IC:la:lamhirh\>:([ "comment":"OOC comment: this would conform to real life guild system: obnly tose with guild aproved rank could work in the craft. a susytem for apprentice/journeyman/master would be appropriate bu kind of hard to implement ( maybe geting to level 10 would give journeyman rank, and allow to be hired by house, but i would be in favor for requiring to find a guild teacher to continue training. OR maybe the NPC trainers for house s could be rented for guilds?", "time":1542113789 ]) ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "guild":"The Hands of St. Trahern", "title":"Establishing Crafter Rights - Teacher restrictions" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1551126465">
         ([ "body":"My name is Marcos Cochiarelli, owner of Bounty of the Seas, and fishing is my means of employment, it is my method of drawing income, as I take no money from my guild.  I use what I make from fishing to support my guild and myself.  \\nI have encountered, many times now, an over saturated market due to people that possess other means of employment fishing the bay dry simply to gain extra coin.  Especially members of Embassies that possess titles and lands or guilds that are not affiliated at all with fishing.  Is there some way to impose a limit to the amount of fish that can be drawn from the sea by those that are not of a fishing guild.  \\n\\nPerhaps limit members of embassies to three fish per day, and those of none fishing guilds to five per day.  If they wish to fish for a living, then I would be happy to hire them into my guild.  I do not mind sharing the sea's bounty with others, but they are harming my livelihood and my ability to support myself and my guild.  Surely there is something that can be done to aid those of us that rely solely upon the sea to earn a living. ", "comments":([  ]), "filedby":"Marcos", "guild":"Bounty of the Seas", "title":"Fishing Rights" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1552091159">
         ([ "body":"After discussion with other fishers, we were able to come to an idea that if we had a larger market for fish to be sold to then we could all pull a fair catch from the bay.  \\nWhat we came up with is that the fishing is not the problem.  The problem is in having only a single place to sell said fish.  The fishmonger controls the entire market and keeps the prices very low.  If we could get other buyers for our catch, the prices would potentially rise as well through competitive pricing between mongers. We all believe that the addition of more buyers would increase the amount of fish that would be demanded.  This could present a more viable option than trying to impose limits that would be very hard to enforce and maintain.\\n\\noption 1. Monger for rarer fish types at higher prices.  This monger would purchase a variety of grouper, swordfish, jewfish, and other large and rare fish at a higher pay.  These fish would carry a limit as to how many would be purchased per person.  One person would be able to sell 4-6 rare fish, depending on the types. \\noption 2. Secondary Monger that buys all fish just as the current monger does at the same price.  This would double the available market. \\nOption 3. Build a fish processing cannery on the docks.  This would increase the demand for fish in that the fish would be preserved and could then be sold to all manner of travelers as rations.  Also could provide rations to various merchant vessels.  This cannery could offer barrels of fish in brine or oil.  Tins of smoked or salted fish.  These would hold for long periods and be good for rations on expeditions or just for general snacking. These could be purchased directly from the cannery, just as fish could be sold to the cannery.  Another benefit of this option would be that it would create quite a many jobs for docktown folk.  All those folk that accost everyone for coin could find gainful employment in such a place as a cannery.\\n\\nOption 4.  A combination of a cannery and additional monger.  \\n", "comments":([  ]), "filedby":"Marcos", "guild":"Owner of Bounty of the Seas", "title":"Fishing Rights" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1479254489, "jominey", "E", 1479265598, "jominey", "E", 1479437699, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
