<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="jominey">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="1495592299">
         ([ "body":"A smith's workshop located somewhere within approved location. The Avoirdupois have agreed to pay for such and thus the funds are not a Council matter.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:el:elspeth\>:([ "comment":"I can donate some granite tiles that would make a lovely floor for the smithy. obtain and donate", "time":1550215899 ]) ]), "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Newtown Smithy" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592349">
         ([ "body":"A shop for selling wares created by the carpenters and woodworkers of the City.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>:([ "comment":"This building is in progress, the Council having voted to place Bjorn as the project lead.", "time":1551146102 ]), \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"When was the meeting held where this matter was voted on? I am not seeing it in the archives.", "time":1496826086 ]), \<Chatters:AE:bj:bjorn\>:([ "comment":"Proposal submitted to lead this project under building proposals.", "time":1522519990 ]) ]), "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Newtown Carpentry Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592396">
         ([ "body":"A shop for selling the wares created by city jewelers.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"When was the meeting held where this matter was voted on? I am not seeing it in the archives.", "time":1496826097 ]), \<Chatters:AE:li:lidia\>:([ "comment":"As a jeweler myself, I would like to suggest a particular place, and style I have had in mind for some years, so that the atrocity that is the Newtown salon does not also happen in this instance. These areas were meant to be a space of comfort, and at least modest luxury for the citizens of Newtown, and upstanding peoples of note to feel both welcomed, and encouraged to spend their coin. Not a near duplicate of the space provided in Docktown, with even less character than their stale, preceding buildings. ", "time":1519887182 ]) ]), "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Newtown Jewelry Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592437">
         ([ "body":"A location for stone masons to sell their wares within the business districts of Newtown.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"When was the meeting held where this matter was voted on? I am not seeing it in the archives.", "time":1496826111 ]) ]), "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Newtown Stone Mason Shop" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592616">
         ([ "body":"A singular space for workshops and/or proposals for various workshops within pre-determined locations as per restrictions of zoning and safety.", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:th:thais\>:([ "comment":"When was the meeting held where this matter was voted on? I am not seeing it in the archives.", "time":1496826136 ]) ]), "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Guild Hall" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592676">
         ([ "body":"A discussion to take place on how the Council can oversee the proper behavior of privately owned slaves within the City.", "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Discussion of Slave Duties" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1495592783">
         ([ "body":"Discussion about a consignment system to support guilds within the city.", "filedby":"Topsy", "supervisor":"TBD", "title":"Consignment System to Support Guilds" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="1541552161">
         ([ "body":"I would like to propose a Triskellian City Watch group to be stationed in Docktown. This group would be comprised of volunteers who care for the safety and security of the guilds--not just in Docktown but in all of Triskellian. The City Watch would not be a law-enforcement group and so would work with the Constabulary to ensure law processes are being followed. PURPOSE The City Watch will look out for the safety of the people and enforce guild rights. Responsbilities include, but are not limited to: * Patrolling Docktown to ensure the main streets are safe for travel. * Providing escort to those who do not feel safe traveling alone. * Act as mediators during House vs. Guild disputes. * Enforce the trade laws that are passed to protect the rights of the guilds (reporting violations to the council, collecting fines from violators). The City Watch will NOT be responsible for: * Filing crime reports (only constables have this authority). * Arresting wanted criminals. STRUCTURE The group would be led by a council appointed Commander. The Commander would be responsible for recruiting and ensuring that the group fulfills its purpose. The Commander is free to organize the group as he or she deems fit but may be removed from the position by the Council if it is determined that: * The Commander is abusing his or her position of power. * The Commander takes an unannounced leave of absence. * The Commander fails to fulfill the group's aforementioned purpose. JOINING THE WATCH Only non-House members are permitted to join. The Commander will handle the application process as he or she deems appropriate. HEADQUARTERS I propose that the old jailhouse be used as a headquarters for this operation with no structural modifications to the building itself. * Main room: On-duty watchmen are stationed here. Bell that can be rang from the Newtown gate (rope/bell system). * Hallway: Guard that allows/denies access to rooms. * Room west of hallway: Barracks for off-duty watchmen. * Cells (right of hallway): Can be used for storage, armory, medical station, etc. RESOURCES * Guard for the hallway (~1000 denarii) * Supplies, furniture, storage, whatever we need to furnish the building (~250 denarii) * Rope/bell system (4 ropes, pulleys use existing bell in the main room ~200 denarii) * Armbands to signify loyalty to the watch (~100 denarii) * TOTAL: 1550 denarii. Bruno Smith is willing to donate the funds to support this endeavor. OOC Notes: * This is still a public space so we should try to keep access fairly open. No one room should only be accessible by 1 or 2 people alone. If we need to restrict anything, we can use locked storage containers. * All council members should be on the guard's allow list to show that the building is council controlled and not controlled by any single person or guild. We should also be unrestrictive about who can join the city watch. INCENTIVES AND COMPENSATION The City Watch will offer the following incentives and compensation to members: * Free armor and weapon maintenance (to be handled by select guilds) * Free medical treatment (to be handled by select guilds) * 5% bonus to individuals who successfully collect a fine * 100% of any monetary tips that are collected when providing escort or mediation services ", "comments":([ \<Chatters:AE:wa:waylon\>:([ "comment":"As I have resigned from the Constabulary, I may have interest in putting my name in the hat for consideration as Commander.", "time":1549034770 ]), \<Chatters:AE:br:bruno\>:([ "comment":"TO DO:\\r\\n\\r\\n* Determine leader of group\\r\\n", "time":1541554950 ]) ]), "filedby":"Bruno", "supervisor":"Bruno", "title":"Docktown Watch Group" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1479254489, "jominey", "E", 1479265598, "jominey", "E", 1479411110, "jominey", "E", 1479411141, "jominey", "E", 1479411437, "jominey", "E", 1480460695, "jominey", "E", 1480461551, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
