<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="islander"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="islander"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="a collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. writing">
             This is $(this.trait:brief). Try examining the first page, the second page ect. There are 10 pages total. There is a big logo next to the title of the newspaper of a quill scribbling a line across an outline of the island of Calabria.  This paper was compiled and edited by Suchin.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/emblem1.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief). Try examining the first page, the second page ect. There are 10 pages total. There is a big logo next to the title of the newspaper of a quill scribbling a line across an outline of the island of Calabria.  This paper was compiled and edited by Suchin.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="table"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
            <Base:PName pname="tables"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="content"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="one"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             table of content of the Islander
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Page 1. Death of an Envoy<br/><br/>Page 2. Guild Council Meeting<br/><br/>Page 3. Interview with the Rose Family<br/><br/>Page 4. Kafka Strikes Again<br/><br/>Page 5. Zombie Outbreak<br/><br/>Page 6. The Harvest Festival<br/><br/>Page 7. The University of Triskellian<br/><br/>Page 8. List of Current Criminal Charges<br/><br/>Page 9: Sinners and Saints
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             There is a list seen here telling you what page holds what content.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="two"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Death of an Envoy
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             During this last week you may have noticed my absence from the city. My dear friend Hanneman and I made a trip to Harrowgate to see what sort of news I could dig up and I came back with a few tales to tale. At the top of the news there seems to have been an assassination of a Bisclavret Envoy. Said Envoy was allegedly poisoned and a lion was seen fleeing the scene. People say the lion looked to be a savage so it is quite possible he was a member of some Scree tribe from the surrounding area around Harrowgate. The lion was also seen carrying a double-bladed steel axe. I looked around and found an eye witness to the event. It seems the Envoy was poisoned in his home and his maid came forth for an interview. <br/><br/>“Hello Miss McNeil, I thank you for taking the time to talk with me.”<br/><br/>“It’s no problem at all really, I just need to do it quick so I can get back to my duties.”<br/><br/>“Of course, so, what happened to the Envoy?”<br/><br/>“Well, he was having dinner. It was Lundi so he was having his usual meal of haggis as he always did on Lundi. Now, I ain’t the cook so I don’t know when the poison was put in but when he started eating it he said it tasted in funny. I said the cook seemed a little under the weather so maybe he did something wrong and I went to reach for the plate. He grabbed my arm and squeezed real hard and before I could react his faee was buried in his plate, he was dead.”“My, terribly sorry you had to see that Miss McNeil. I thank you for your time.”<br/><br/>Keep your eyes open for any lions matching the description if you head out that way. If you have any information, notify the local authorities.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             During this last week you may have noticed my absence from the city. My dear friend Hanneman and I made a trip to Harrowgate to see what sort of news I could dig up and I came back with a few tales to tale.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="three"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Guild Council Meeting
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             The Guild Council held a meeting this last week as well discussing the punishments for some of the city's more heinous criminals. Those criminals talked of were Chesh, "Lucky" Luciano, and Kafka. I believe that all the punishments issued were fair and justly deserved. Chesh is taking up wearing a collar and not as a fashion statement. He's entering into the world of being a serf and he needs quite a few things to become a freedman once again. Kafka is being forced to get mental health treatment whether he likes it or not. I have to agree, there is something hopelessly wrong with that man's mind and he needs serious mental help. Lucky is getting the worst punishment of all. He's being forced to wear serrated manacles so that he cannot harm anyone without harming himself as well. All citizens should applaud the Guild Council's actions in helping to keep the city safe.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The Guild Council held a meeting this last week as well discussing the punishments for some of the city's more heinous criminals.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="four"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Interview with the Rose Family
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             I have not been in this city for very long, going on a month now i do believe, but even i have heard the names doctor hush and fips thrown around quite a lot. they have a reputation for both being the best at what they do and i cannot go against that. besides their skills they are both wonderful people as i have found out through this interview.<br/><br/>hush: I've...never been interviewed before.<br/><br/>Fips: You'll get used to interruptions if you spend much time with Hush, I bet her assistance is needed again before the end of your interview. She's always busy busy busy.<br/><br/>Me: So, let's start with the basics shall we? Can you both tell me about your childhoods? Where you grew up, a bit about your family, that sort of thing.<br/><br/>Fips: You first dear."<br/><br/>Me: "Take your time."<br/><br/>Hush:"Well. I grew up in Chalon.  My mother died giving birth to me, I'm the youngest of three sisters. My eldest sister is Marissa she's from my father's first marriage.  His first wife committed suicide.  The middle sister is Shush, she is five years older than me and takes more after our mother. She is more an entertaining socialite then I am.  My father was a master surgeon in Chalon and was quite strict so he didn't tolerate children well.<br/><br/>A funny note at this time the good doctor did have to step away to treat a patient.<br/><br/>Fips: Lets see... I grew up on the Broken Coast, my parents ran a small merchant shipping company. We didn't get along so well... well at all really, so I left at the age of sixteen to travel and find work.<br/><br/>Me: I see, did you have any siblings Fips?<br/><br/>Fips: "An only child."<br/><br/>Me: "Terribly sorry, perhaps you could tell me how one of the top merchants got his start in the city?"<br/><br/>Fips: By accident really. When I first arrived in the city, aged around eighteen or so, I didn't really have many skills and was very shy. I took to fishing to earn a little money and get food, Then I met a friend, long gone from the city now, called Ada who ran the a small gardening guild, so I also started helping her with that. When I decided to live in the city permanently it became apparent that learning to haggle would be a great benefit when trying to sell catches. So that’s where I picked put both of my careers, and since then I've been mastering, teaching and practicing my skills almost daily, though I rarely have time to go fishing anymore.<br/><br/>Me:You said you left home at the age of sixteen and just now you said you arrived in the city at eighteen. What happened in those two years?<br/><br/>Fips: A little unconventional, granted, but that’s how it happened. Traveling, by foot from the Broken Coast. Staying in the odd town and city. I quite liked Chalon, but I couldn't afford to live there, so I continued down to Triskellian. It just happened to have taken two years.<br/><br/>Me:I will ask you the same as Fips. How did the cities best healer get her start?"<br/><br/>Hush: Well. From my father. I've been healing since I was five years old.  I would watch him and ask a thousand questions and even got to help by giving hugs and such the patients.  When I first came to the city I worked for the Rin for a short time, then for Temperance, then I started my own guild.<br/><br/>Me: I see and that guild was the University?<br/><br/>Hush: Mmhm. I started it from the ground up.<br/><br/>Me: Very impressive.<br/><br/>Hush: Thank you<br/><br/>Me: Okay, so, personal question time. How did you two meet and get together?<br/><br/>Fips: I had just returned to the city from retiring into the country side for a just under a year. I came back and was meeting old acquaintances and someone mentioned that the University had a new medical faculty. I thought it'd be nice to show my support, and provide herbs, salves and oils to them, and arranged to meet Hush. Once we met we really hit it off, and gradually spent more and more time together until we started formally courting, and then married. That was a year and a half ago. I had never met such a caring and compassionate person until I met Hush, I think that's what attracted me to her.”<br/><br/>Hush: "As you can see, he's very much the romantic and is just the perfect fit for me.  He is generous with his time and money to anyone who needs it, and is very charming and caring.<br/><br/>Me: Wonderful, just wonderful. Any plans to have children<br/><br/>Hush: We have been trying to adopt for about 8 months now.  We want a few children.<br/><br/>Me: You're adorable together.”<br/><br/>Hush: I am his coonfox and he my shiny magpie.<br/><br/>Hush: The Uni is not just for medicine. Sang has been my partner in crime a long time. He is the dean of arts and is a mastermind.  His talent is amazing and he can inspire his students like nothing I've seen before.<br/><br/>Me: Perhaps you could give me a brief summary of the University.<br/><br/>Hush: The Uni teaches a wide variety of subjects, ranging from medical, religious, art of all sorts, languages about 30 in fact, mercantile, and a few combat lessons. We welcome all sorts of students and work with them to find their place in life.<br/><br/>Me: And you, tell me about your guild?<br/><br/>Fips: I've had input in certain aspects, like when the parks were regenerated, I helped and funded quite a lot of the work. I all but run the cities herb shop and herb garden on behalf of the Rinaldi House, I've put in a good deal of new plants - especially if they have medical uses. Then the maintenance of the potted plants around the city are supposed to be slaves duties. I'm happy to help we ever I am able really.<br/><br/>Me: Seems you are quite the philanthropist, I applaud you both. You do so much for the city and I thank you on behalf of it's citizens.<br/><br/>Me: Now, any last things you wish to be known or what have you?<br/><br/>Hush: We love living and working here and look forward to raising our family here.<br/><br/>Me: I thank you both for your time, you'll be hearing from me soon I do believe.<br/><br/>If you see them out, I implore you do thank them for all that they do.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine:i have not been in this city for very long, going on a month now i do believe, but even i have heard the names doctor hush and fips thrown around quite a lot. they have a reputation for both being the best at what they do and i cannot go against that. besides their skills they are both wonderful people as i have found out through this interview.<br/><br/>hush">
             "I've...never been interviewed before."<br/><br/>Fips: "You'll get used to interruptions if you spend much time with Hush, I bet her assistance is needed again before the end of your interview. She's always busy busy busy."<br/><br/>Me: "So, let's start with the basics shall we? Can you both tell me about your childhoods? Where you grew up, a bit about your family, that sort of thing."<br/><br/>Fips: "You first dear."<br/><br/>Me: "Take your time."<br/><br/>Hush:"Well. I grew up in Chalon.  My mother died giving birth to me, I'm the youngest of three sisters. My eldest sister is Marissa she's from my father's first marriage.  His first wife committed suicide.  The middle sister is Shush, she is five years older than me and takes more after our mother. She is more an entertaining socialite then I am.  My father was a master surgeon in Chalon and was quite strict so he didn't tolerate children well."<br/><br/>A funny note at this time the good doctor did have to step away to treat a patient.<br/><br/>Fips: "Lets see... I grew up on the Broken Coast, my parents ran a small merchant shipping company. We didn't get along so well... well at all really, so I left at the age of sixteen to travel and find work."<br/><br/>Me: "I see, did you have any siblings Fips?"<br/><br/>Fips: "An only child."<br/><br/>Me: "Terribly sorry, perhaps you could tell me how one of the top merchants got his start in the city?"<br/><br/>Fips: "By accident really. When I first arrived in the city, aged around eighteen or so, I didn't really have many skills and was very shy. I took to fishing to earn a little money and get food, Then I met a friend, long gone from the city now, called Ada who ran the a small gardening guild, so I also started helping her with that. When I decided to live in the city permanently it became apparent that learning to haggle would be a great benefit when trying to sell catches. So that’s where I picked put both of my careers, and since then I've been mastering, teaching and practicing my skills almost daily, though I rarely have time to go fishing anymore."<br/><br/>Me: "You said you left home at the age of sixteen and just now you said you arrived in the city at eighteen. What happened in those two years?"<br/><br/>Fips: "A little unconventional, granted, but that’s how it happened. Traveling, by foot from the Broken Coast. Staying in the odd town and city. I quite liked Chalon, but I couldn't afford to live there, so I continued down to Triskellian. It just happened to have taken two years."<br/><br/>Me: "I will ask you the same as Fips. How did the cities best healer get her start?"<br/><br/>Hush: "Well. From my father. I've been healing since I was five years old.  I would watch him and ask a thousand questions and even got to help by giving hugs and such the patients.  When I first came to the city I worked for the Rin for a short time, then for Temperance, then I started my own guild."<br/><br/>Me: "I see and that guild was the University?"<br/><br/>Hush: "Mmhm. I started it from the ground up."<br/><br/>Me: “Very impressive.”<br/><br/>Hush: “Thank you.”<br/><br/>Me: “Okay, so, personal question time. How did you two meet and get together?"<br/><br/>Fips: “I had just returned to the city from retiring into the country side for a just under a year. I came back and was meeting old acquaintances and someone mentioned that the University had a new medical faculty. I thought it'd be nice to show my support, and provide herbs, salves and oils to them, and arranged to meet Hush. Once we met we really hit it off, and gradually spent more and more time together until we started formally courting, and then married. That was a year and a half ago. I had never met such a caring and compassionate person until I met Hush, I think that's what attracted me to her.”<br/><br/>Hush: "As you can see, he's very much the romantic and is just the perfect fit for me.  He is generous with his time and money to anyone who needs it, and is very charming and caring."<br/><br/>Me: "Wonderful, just wonderful. Any plans to have children?"<br/><br/>Hush: "We have been trying to adopt for about 8 months now.  We want a few children."<br/><br/>Me: “You're adorable together.”<br/><br/>Hush: "I am his coonfox and he my shiny magpie."<br/><br/>Hush: "The Uni is not just for medicine. Sang has been my partner in crime a long time. He is the dean of arts and is a mastermind.  His talent is amazing and he can inspire his students like nothing I've seen before."<br/><br/>Me: 'Perhaps you could give me a brief summary of the University.”<br/><br/>Hush: "The Uni teaches a wide variety of subjects, ranging from medical, religious, art of all sorts, languages about 30 in fact, mercantile, and a few combat lessons. We welcome all sorts of students and work with them to find their place in life."<br/><br/>Me: “And you, tell me about your guild?"<br/><br/>
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="fips">
             "I've had input in certain aspects, like when the parks were regenerated, I helped and funded quite a lot of the work. I all but run the cities herb shop and herb garden on behalf of the Rinaldi House, I've put in a good deal of new plants - especially if they have medical uses. Then the maintenance of the potted plants around the city are supposed to be slaves duties. I'm happy to help we ever I am able really."<br/><br/>Me: "Seems you are quite the philanthropist, I applaud you both. You do so much for the city and I thank you on behalf of it's citizens."<br/><br/>Me: "Now, any last things you wish to be known or what have you?"<br/><br/>Hush: "We love living and working here and look forward to raising our family here."<br/><br/>Me: “I thank you both for your time, you'll be hearing from me soon I do believe.”<br/><br/>If you see them out, I implore you do thank them for all that they do.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             I have not been in this city for very long, going on a month now I do believe, but even I have heard the names Doctor Hush and Fips thrown around quite a lot.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="five"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Kafka Strikes Again
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             It would seem that the menace Kafka struck again this past week. I don’t know about you dear reader but I was wondering when he was going to make his next move and it would seem he bit off a bit more than he could chew this time. He entered the west commons and assaulted the Presbyter Ximen in hopes of kidnapping him. When the people in the commons turned on him to help the Presbyter he took the Presbyter as a human shield to try and escape. Those in the commons advanced on him and in his panic he slit the throat of the Presbyter. Upon that action of heresy the warriors within the commons fell on him and struck him down where he stood. It was reported that the killing blow came from an arrow let loose by a one Esquire Gabrielle. I would like to personally congratulate her on the wonderful shot she made and thank her for bringing an end to the criminal known as Kafka for at least a brief time. Next issue I should have a full story concerning the Esquire and her life, I hope you look forward to reading it as much as I look forward to writing it.<br/><br/>In a surprising turn of events Kafka was resurrected by the white mages of the Church. You would think they would have left his soul in the afterlife after killing a Presbyter of the Church. He came stumbling out of his room in above the Severed Tail with no memory of anything that took place over the last few weeks so you can imagine how big of a shock it was when he was arrested on the spot when he walked into the commons. To his credit, he went peacefully enough and has yet to cause any more problems. Maybe this is the turning point for Kafak, this reporter hopes so.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             It would seem that the menace Kafka struck again this past week. I don’t know about you dear reader but I was wondering when he was going to make his next move and it would seem he bit off a bit more than he could chew this time.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="six"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Zombie Outbreak
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             One day this past week I sat down with Mister Fyros so he could tell me a bit about the sickness that spread while I was cooped up in my room.  The interview is as follows. (He of course used sign language throughout the interview.)<br/><br/>“Give me a moment to collect my thoughts.”<br/><br/>"Take all the time you need."<br/><br/>"It started with Omen. She was on a mission and came across a group of walking dead, in the form of skeletons.  I was not present for the start of it all but i heard of it later from her.  It bit her upon the wrist and infected her with a disease. A curse of a disease, literally speaking.  It eventually claimed her life.  The white mage resurrection didn’t cure it either, and she slowly changed and her appetites for flesh to consume increased.  She infected Zaria, the sheriff.   Soon after that they were quarantined in here to help prevent the spread of the disease. “<br/><br/>'Their black drool and foul blood still stains the ground.'<br/><br/>"I often tried to treat their injuries, but they were never cured, it required the talents of priests and prayer to cure them from the Church of S'allumer, but that is later.   One night, i came to the infirmary to check on patients, and there was a great deal of wounded people there.  They had been attacked by Zaria and Omen, and I'm not sure why they thought it wise to enter this room where they were being held safe but they did.  Sir Bayard among them, he took a nasty hit from the Sheriff to his collarbone, and in his struggle got her blood upon his injury and became infected shortly after.   I warned him that he should confine himself to the quarantine, while he still had the wits about him to do so, and he did. A masked tiger, I'll call him Jeff, his name is unknown publicly, also became infected. He works for Omen as well.    The four of them were in here at that point.  Omen warned me, in a moment of clarity, that the door to the jail could be easily broken down with Bayard among them.  So I spent the resources to have the door reinforced.    It came too late however, they broke out and assaulted several people, My employee Valdus included, and killed him and wounded others.   It took the royal army and the Constabulary to subdue them and put them back in a pretty large battle.  Sir Bayard is a renowned hero of the Avoirdupois and is more than a match for most people in the city.”<br/><br/>"And the sheriff is a stunning warrior as well, those two alone could have infected half the city in one night..  Once they were subdued, my smiths got to work on the door and repaired it, and reinforced it as you see there.”<br/><br/>The medic, Achlys, entered the room at some point though I didn't notice. She chimed in at this point.<br/><br/>"Shame I was busy. I treated Omen through the bars after I bound her wrists. Was easy enough, though that Avoirdupois soldier told me not to.”<br/><br/>That is the events through the eyes of Mister Fyros. If anyone else would like to come forth and give me an interview please do not hesitate.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             One day this past week I sat down with Mister Fyros so he could tell me a bit about the sickness that spread while I was cooped up in my room.  The interview is as follows. (He of course used sign language throughout the interview.)
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seven"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The Harvest Festival
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             In three weeks’ time, on the 24th of this month, the Harvest Festival will begin. You may remember my report in the first issue of this paper where I sat in on one of the festival committee’s meetings. I've finally gotten the schedule of the events. I wish to remind all that wish to be involved with the baking sale, particularly the houses, need to contact Sheriff Zaria with your entrees. Make sure to come out on and bring your friends, it sure to be a wonderful time!<br/><br/>Lundi 24th (Monday):~Opening Ceremony;~Tourney Begins;<br/><br/>Mardi 25th (Tuesday):~Fashion Show by Esquire Meepers;<br/><br/>Mercredi 26th (Wednesday):~Baking Sale by Acting Sheriff Zaria;<br/><br/>Jeudi 27th (Thursday):~Art Gala by Doctor Hush;<br/><br/>Vendredi 28th (Friday):~Mud Wrestling by Acting Sheriff Zaria;<br/><br/>Samedi 29th (Saturday):~Small/People Auction by Acting Sheriff Zaria;<br/><br/>Dimache 30th (Sunday):~Closing Ceremony
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             In three weeks’ time, on the 24th of this month, the Harvest Festival will begin.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eight"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             The University of Triskellian
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Are you looking for a new career or a new start to life. The University of Triskellian is accepting application for students in many fields. We offer classes in healing, medic, religion, scholar, merchant, entertainment, painting, music, stonemason, 30 different languages, and self defense. Write to Dr Rose or Sang for more information.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Are you looking for a new career or a new start to life. The University of Triskellian is accepting application for students in many fields.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="nine"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             List of Current Criminal Charges
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             OOC: From the forums at: http://forum.skotos.net/showthread.php?t=80797)<br/><br/>Here are the descriptions of the current charges, and a few examples of each. Please note that the examples given are merely a guideline, and not the only crimes that fall under each category. (ooc note: This does not encompass the full list of things that are actually illegal, simply the current charges that are in the @crime system. If you want to file a crime that doesn't fit into the list of these charges, or are confused about a charge, feel free to ICly ask a constable or file a @assist for clarification!)<br/><br/>Assault - Intentionally and voluntarily causing immediate harmful or offensive contact. Severity of the charge is determined both by the severity of the assault, and the identity of the person assaulted.(Assaulting a noble is a greater charge than assaulting a commoner). Examples: Attacking someone with a weapon in an area outside of the designated sparring arenas, pulling a weapon on a noble (even without contact), inappropriately grabbing or groping a woman who has expressed a desire not to be touched, hitting someone with your fists in an area outside of the designated sparring arenas, etc.<br/><br/>Assisting a Criminal - Assisting a Criminal is acting with foresight and intent to aid any person in carrying out a crime or escape justice. Severity of the charge is determined by the severity of the crime assisted and the type of assistance rendered. (Helping to hide the body of a murder victim is worse than harboring a pickpocket). Examples: Harboring fugitives, supplying weapons or medical supplies/food, or actively obstructing a constable (physically) or an investigation, etc.<br/><br/>Disrespecting Constabulary - Any remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Constabulary or any on-duty member shall constitute Disrespecting Constabulary. (Severity of the crime is determined by the severity of disrespect. (Calling an on-duty Constable an idiot is a lesser charge than speaking out against the Constabulary as a whole). Examples: Calling a Constable names, speaking out against the Constabulary to an on-duty Constable, Maligning the Constabulary as a whole, spitting on a Constable, etc.<br/><br/>Disrespecting Nobles - Any remark or action that shows an overt lack of respect to a Noble's rank and title. Drawing weapons against a Noble is a greater offense and shall be counted as Assault. Severity of the crime is determined by the severity of the disrespect. (Failing to show deference is a lesser charge than spitting on a noble). Examples: Calling noble names, refusing to show proper deference to a noble within Newtown, spitting on a noble, harassing or heckling a noble, etc.<br/><br/>Disturbing the peace - Any lewd or inflammatory act committed in a public place to either incite peaceful citizenry, to display blatant disregard for public decency, or unsettle public order. Severity of the charges is determined by the severity of the disturbance. (Being loud and disruptive is a lesser charge than inciting people to fight). Examples: Screaming at people, walking around nude, improprieties public displays of affection, egging on a fight, shouting "fire" in a public area, failing to cease a disruptive action when bid to desist, etc.<br/><br/>Illegal detainment - Illegal detainment is arresting suspects or criminals and detaining them without a legal warrant of arrest issued by a magistrate. Severity is determined by the severity of the error. (A constable trying to arrest a commoner without a proper warrant is less severe than a constable trying to arrest a ranked person without a warrant). Examples: A citizen who has not taking oaths to the Constabulary trying to arrest a criminal, a constable dragging a person to prison without a proper warrant, a constable trying to arrest someone without gathering the proper testimony, etc.<br/><br/>Kidnapping - Kidnapping is the taking away of a person by force, threat, or deceit, with intent to cause them to be detained against their will. Further charges of assault may be applied to cases where the kidnapping was violent. Severity is determined both by the nature of the kidnapping, and the person kidnapped. (Kidnapping someone by violence is worse than coercing them to follow and kidnapping a noble or a child is a greater charge than kidnapping a commoner). Examples: Tying someone up and leaving them in a private inn room, using force to take a person with you from one area to another, luring a child away with candy with the intent to trap or detain, threatening someone with harm if they do not come with you, etc.<br/><br/>Murder - The willful (non-negligent) killing of one person by another. In incidents that lead to a death as a result of self-defense or defense of another, a charge of murder can be applied. Cases of hiring a person to commit murder are also considered murder. Severity is determined mostly by the nature of the crime, and the identity of the victim. (Defending someone from an attacker resulting in the death of the attacker is a lesser crime than the violent, premeditated murder of a person. Similarly, murdering a commoner is a lesser charge than murdering a noble). Examples: Stabbing someone to death, beating someone to death, defending yourself from an attack which leads to another person's death, hiring an assassin to kill someone, protecting a third individual leading to someone's death, inappropriate medical practices that lead to a person's death, etc. (ooc: Only deaths committed by the "kill" command are considered "willful" deaths, or giving payment to a person to use the "kill" command. IE, the person who uses the "kill" command on another person is the one legally responsible for their death, even if a third person gave all the injuries).<br/><br/>Property damage - Damage or destruction done to public or private property, caused by a person who is not its owner. Severity is determined by the value of the property damaged, and the identity of the victim. (Beating a slave is a lesser charge than killing a slave, destroying someone's hat is a lesser charge than destroying a valuable piece of jewelry. Similarly, damage to a commoner's property is less severe than damaging a noble's property). Examples: Breaking someone's property, urinating on someone's property, dying or defacing someone's property, beating or killing someone's slave, burning someone's property, etc.<br/><br/>Resisting arrest - Any attempt to evade or assault a Constable performing a dutiful arrest. Severity of the charge is determined by the scope of resistance. (Running away is a lesser charge than beating a Constable to prevent him/her from arresting you). Examples: Refusing to be escorted to jail when a warrant is issued, beating up a Constable trying to make an arrest, running away from a Constable trying to make an arrest, etc.<br/><br/>Theft - The taking and removing of personal property with intent to deprive the rightful owner of it. If goods are returned, the severity of the charge may be reduced. The charge of theft should also be used in cases of purse-snatching. In cases of robbery where force is used, an additional charge of assault may be included. Severity is determined by the value of the property taken as well as the identity of the victim. Refer to Property Damage. Examples: Pickpocketing, plucking items from the dead, refusing to return House property after leaving a House, etc.<br/><br/>Treason- plotting or taking actions against the Don while a citizen or guest in his city. In incidents involving minor treason, the offender may be subjected to slavery. In serious cases of treason, the offender shall be executed. Severity is determined at the Don's will.<br/><br/>Acting against the Church - Any remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Church of S'allumer. Severity is determined by the action taken. (Insulting a church member is a lesser charge than actively working against the Church). Examples: Disrespect to a Church member, insulting the church, claiming to take action against the church, etc.<br/><br/>Apostasy - Leaving a religion after making it a profession and swearing solemn vows. This does not apply to someone who moves from one order to another, or retires legitimately. Severity is determined by the Church. Examples: A priest abandoning his/her vows without express permission from the Church, etc.<br/><br/>Heresy - The worship or preaching of a forbidden heresy. This specifically means the 'Old Faith' of Lutara, explicitly denying the tenants of S'allumer, and practicing black magic. Severity and punishment is determined by both the Constabulary and the Church together. This will vary case by case. Examples: Lingering in forbidden groves, participating in forbidden rituals, dealing in death magic, compromising one's soul, etc.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Here are the descriptions of the current charges, and a few examples of each. Please note that the examples given are merely a guideline, and not the only crimes that fall under each category.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="pnamge">pages</Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page-10" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ten"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             Sinners and Saints
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Saints among Sinners is for Hire. A mercenary company fit for many situations and activities in the field, if you need people to aid you in missions, battles, or other grand adventures of mystery and danger, Do not forget, nor hesitate to contact me, Fyros Fulke.<br/><br/>*************If you are interested in becoming employed by Saints and Sinners, contact me by scroll or in person if you know who I am. We are willing to train and make sure you find adventures to test your mind, might and abilities. Lessons in many areas will be available, or arranged for you.*************<br/><br/>Saints and Sinners, Triskellian Guild, all rights reserved. All activities are by contract and payment is due upon completion of contracts. No payments are required for incomplete contracts, but some costs may be required for heavy losses due to devastating acts of including but not limited to S'allumer, Fae, Elementals, and natural disasters. Exact terms of contracts are to be discussed in person or via scroll and signed and agreed upon by both parties. Employees are required, under penalty of punishment, to complete every contract they are assigned to the best.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             Saints among Sinners is for Hire.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "Islander newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "The Islander"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1344836303, "meandmine", "R", 1344836476, "meandmine", "X", 1344836902, "meandmine", "K", 1344836955, "meandmine", "X", 1344837337, "meandmine", "K", 1344837378, "meandmine", "K", 1344837757, "meandmine", "K", 1344837889, "meandmine", "K", 1344837998, "meandmine", "K", 1344838124, "meandmine", "K", 1344838539, "meandmine", "K", 1344838677, "meandmine", "K", 1344838807, "meandmine", "K", 1344839698, "meandmine", "K", 1344839832, "meandmine", "X", 1344840016, "meandmine", "K", 1344840568, "meandmine", "K", 1344840663, "meandmine", "K", 1344840698, "meandmine", "K", 1344840815, "meandmine", "K", 1344840845, "meandmine", "K", 1344840920, "meandmine", "K", 1344843661, "meandmine", "K", 1344843674, "meandmine", "K", 1344843935, "meandmine", "K", 1344847020, "meandmine", "K", 1344847953, "meandmine", "X", 1344850580, "meandmine", "K", 1344850664, "meandmine", "K", 1344850668, "meandmine", "E", 1344850672, "meandmine", "E", 1344850685, "meandmine", "E", 1344850687, "meandmine", "E", 1344850688, "meandmine", "E", 1344850688, "meandmine", "E", 1344851322, "meandmine", "K", 1344851471, "meandmine", "K", 1344851849, "meandmine", "X", 1346718763, "meandmine", "E", 1346718764, "meandmine", "E", 1346718764, "meandmine", "E", 1346718764, "meandmine", "E", 1346718765, "meandmine", "E", 1346718766, "meandmine", "E", 1346718766, "meandmine", "E", 1346718766, "meandmine", "E", 1346718769, "meandmine", "E", 1346718770, "meandmine", "E", 1346718770, "meandmine", "E", 1346718771, "meandmine", "E", 1346718772, "meandmine", "E", 1346718772, "meandmine", "E", 1346718773, "meandmine", "E", 1346718773, "meandmine", "E", 1346718779, "meandmine", "E", 1346718779, "meandmine", "E", 1346718779, "meandmine", "E", 1346721277, "meandmine", "K", 1346721394, "meandmine", "K", 1346722113, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
