<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="ezralee">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Effects:UrEffect)"/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-actor">
         X[S] A sudden dizzy sensation washes over you.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-audience">
         X[S] \$(person) appears to be slightly dizzy and unsteady.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:degrees">
         (\{ 0, "cured", 1, "minor", 2, "moderate", 4, "severe", 6, "grave" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:extension">
         \<Effects:Extensions:NonLethalDescribed\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:history">
         (\{ "StoryHost Roo, Wed Sep  4 21:57:14 2019", "StoryHost Roo, Wed Sep  4 22:01:55 2019", "StoryHostess Topsy, Wed Sep  4 22:02:07 2019", "StoryPuppet Kata, Sun Sep  8 22:48:52 2019" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:name">
         "dizziness"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:base">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:severity_effect">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:severity_increase">
         -1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:severity_cap">
         8
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-grave">
         X[S] \{ Your head spins, the ground rolls and before you can stop it, you topple in a heap. \| Unable to maintain your balance, you stumble and fall in a fit of overwhelming dizziness. \| Unsteady on your feet, another wave of intense vertigo causes you to fall over. \| The world spins around you as you struggle against the dizziness and eventually fall down. \| Unable to fight against it, another wave of intense vertigo causes you to fall over. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-minor">
         X[S] \{ A wave of dizziness washes over you, giving you a moment of pause. \| You feel unsteady as a wave of dizziness sweeps over you. \| A rolling sensation overwhelms your senses for a moment. \| The sensation of dizziness sweeps through you before subsiding. \| For just a moment, a subtle dizziness sweeps through your head. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-moderate">
         X[S] \{ An intense wave of dizziness overwhelms your senses. \| An intense sensation of dizziness momentarily takes your breath away. \| You find it hard to talk as another wave of dizziness overwhelms your senses. \| A dizzy sensation completely overwhelms your senses before gradually subsiding. \| The intense sensation of dizziness overwhelms your senses. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-severe">
         X[S] \{ You sway drastically as the floor feels like it is moving beneath your feet. \| Unable to control it, you sway with an overwhelming dizzy sensation. \| Without warning, the floor feels as though it is rolling and swaying as a wave of vertigo overwhelms you. \| You nearly lose your balance with another wave of intense vertigo. \| The ground feels like it about to overturn you as the vertigo nearly overwhelms you. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-grave">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ sways dangerously before toppling onto the ground. \| struggles with a dizzy expression before losing their balance. \| appears dizzy and disoriented before losing their footing and falling over. \| collapses, clearly struggling with balance amid the dizziness. \| is unable to maintain their balance, falling upon the floor after swaying for a moment. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-minor">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ appears to be slightly dizzy. \|appears to be unsteady. \|briefly pauses with a dizzy swaying. \|sways and appears to be slightly dizzy. \|pauses for a moment with a dizzy expression before regaining composure once more. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-moderate">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ pauses with a dizzy, lost expression on the face. \|  appears to be very dizzy and disoriented. \| pauses and seems to struggle with a wave of dizziness. \| seems to sway a little, appearing very dizzy. \| struggles with a wave of intense dizziness. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-severe">
         X[S] \$(person) \{ sways dangerously as though they are about to lose their footing. \| sways and nearly loses their balance. \| struggles against the swaying and dizziness. \| gasps softly while swaying with vertigo. \| appears to struggle to keep their balance. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1096581633, "zwoc", "S", 1096581671, "zwoc", "S", 1096581776, "zwoc", "S", 1096581798, "zwoc", "S", 1096581928, "zwoc", "S", 1096581974, "zwoc", "S", 1096582004, "zwoc", "S", 1096582009, "zwoc", "S", 1096582027, "zwoc", "S", 1096582856, "zwoc", "S", 1096582880, "zwoc", "S", 1096582900, "zwoc", "S", 1096582916, "zwoc", "S", 1096582933, "zwoc", "S", 1096582990, "zwoc", "S", 1096583016, "zwoc", "S", 1096583856, "zwoc", "S", 1096584545, "zwoc", "S", 1567608719, "jominey", "R", 1567647907, "ezralee", "E", 1567648711, "ezralee", "E", 1567648798, "jominey", "E", 1567648822, "ezralee", "E", 1567649846, "jominey", "E", 1567650315, "jominey", "E", 1567650394, "jominey", "E", 1567650404, "jominey", "E", 1567918898, "ezralee", "E", 1567997176, "ezralee", "E", 1587681966, "jominey", "E", 1587681972, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
