<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="tunk_bodin">
  <Help:Node title="Theme">
    <Log:Description>
       <br/>Title: Theme<br/><br/> {? equal | $(theatre.id) | IC | The Ironclaw Online game depicts a world at the crossroads of history – a Medieval society teetering at the edge of the Age of Reason. The anthropomorphic races of Calabria come together in the city of Triskellian. Here, guilds war against the noble house of Rinaldi in a battle of words and deeds. Meanwhile, ominous rumors have begun to arise from beyond the walls – of ancient enmities reignited and the forgotten magic of the Autarchs rediscovered.<br/> Ironclaw is built upon a long tradition of anthropomorphic fiction – where animals take on human characteristics. It includes classic novels like "The Wind in the Willows" and "Watership Down"; movies such as "Who Shot Roger Rabbit?" and "The Secret of NIMH"; comics from "Albedo" to "Sherman's Lagoon"; and fantasies including "Spellsinger" and "Redwall". In Ironclaw, a variety of anthropomorphic animals, from apes to wolves, vie for domination. | {? equal | $(theatre.gameid) | GES | Galactic Emperor: Succession is a science fiction game of intrigue, treachery, and war on an interstellar scale. The background is totally original but writers such as David Brin, Frank Herbert, Julian May, and Walter Jon Williams are among the influences.| Chat Theatres are built on a variety of themes, from creepy old Victorian houses to quiet oases in the middle of nowhere.}} <br/><br/> See Also: <helplink to="character"/>, <helplink to="roleplaying"/>, <helplink to="fun"/><br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="theme"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="themes"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365975, "-", "SYNC", 1136677096, "rhenn", "E", 1137626510, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1137626591, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1137634712, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1295119892, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1312328551, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1509728509, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
