<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#6600ff", "bgcolor2":"#cc0099", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#ffcc00", "fonttype":"Comic Sans MS", "h1color":"#66ff33", "h1type":"Times New Roman", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Arial", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Arial" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "Hi. This is Ditto. I can see your snooping so I'll be nice and not smite you. Instead I'll give you a tip. Go to plots in my guild and you can see previews of the next plot.  Also, I'll give you storypoints if you assist or page or write a scroll to me with your characters point of view of each plot.  \\r\\n\\r\\nLove, Ditto", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plots">
         (\{ "visitors", "I've been doing a series called dungeon escaped. The premise is a large dungeon where high station, high interest, or extremely dangerous villains go to await their fate. These criminals were recently set free by those darned foreigners and every now and again the constables get a plea for help. The last plot series was called hide and seak: level...ninja.  The next plot is called foppit and will be labor day weekend around 4 pm eastern. \\r\\n----------------\\r\\nI will be starting a church series plot where at the very end you can earn 2 free ranks (if you are below gentry and meet all requirements). This will be to increase church membership.\\r\\n-----------------\\r\\nIf you haven't been in game lately there are two vps running around. A ghost named loo and a fortune teller named Ezmeralda. Keep an eye out for these two." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
