<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#000000", "bgcolor2":"#ffcc66", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#996600", "fonttype":"Arial", "h1color":"#663300", "h1type":"Arial", "h2color":"#663300", "h2type":"Arial", "h3color":"#663300", "h3type":"Arial" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "visitors", "Welcome to the Lucky Foxes.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "This is your guest page. This is the page your visitors see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guild policies">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h1\>Pay\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Members of the Lucky Foxes will receive one half of their earnings as pay.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>Lessons\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Members are encouraged to freely each each other whatever skills may be needed.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>Rules\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>No member of the Lucky Foxes shall lie to, cheat, steal from, or commit any crime against another member.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Penalty: dishonorable discharge and blacklisting.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>No member of the Lucky Foxes shall lie to, cheat, steal from, or commit any crime against any citizen of triskellion.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Penalty: suspension of membership for three days and forfeiture of earnings during the suspension.  If the offense was also charged as a crime, the suspension continues until all outstanding punishments have been satisfied.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Exception:  The crime of disrespect to nobility is not an offense against this policy.  While it is not encouraged, it is decided that the existing criminal code punishes this act well enough.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>Clemency\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Any member who has been dishonorably discharged from the Lucky Foxes, or who is currently under censure, may have said punishment removed by a simple majority vote of all members in good standing.\</p\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
