<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="tonyd">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:Props:Books:Newspapers:UrPressSheet)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="0.02" density="0.9"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0" verb2="are carrying" verb3="is carrying"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="lying" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="objskin" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames/>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="delivery-from">
             Valentin
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             PAGE TWO: Social
 -------------------------------------------------------------------------
Pirate Menace, Defeated!
(By Sang Rouchambeau)

In a powerful alliance of the Guilds of Triskellian and the four Noble Houses the Pirate scourge responsible for plaguing our waters has now been routed. Valiant battles were fought on all ships, the bravery of our fighters won the day with no reported deaths on our sides at all.

In the words of Capitaine Brenner du Prideaux, Marshall of House Avoirdupois and squire to Sir Edmond Boulanger D'Avoirdupois, "I believe that piracy is vile, the House forces, though originally hampered by a bit of squabbling, came together and did a wonderful job." He also believes that all fighters should be commended for their efforts.

The pirate ship that was unlucky enough to tangle with the House forces lost their captain after he engaged Sir Bayard three times, the noble knight vanquishing his foe with one final and powerful blow to the face. The fighters aboard the guild ship fought just as bravely. Their ferociousness caused the pirates to turn on themselves out of fear for their lives, on of their number driving a blade into the back of Black Pete, a name that will never blight us, the citizens of Triskellian, ever again. 

Congratulations to all our brave fighters on this brave victory.
 
***A skillfully drawn cartoon depicting a noble looking horse in fine amour, the plumes of his helmet and swish of his tail give him a distinct noble baring, standing proudly on a boat, surrounded by similarly clad warriors address a band of pirates, the pirate leader stand to the fore, a face cruelly ugly and covered by a thick scraggly black beard as he spits on the noble horse. A rat dressed in a motley striped outfit and huge earrings through his ears drives a dagger through the back of the pirate leader, with much comical blood slpurting from the wound. Beneath the scene the following words are written in a flowing cursive script "Warrior: "Surrender you scoundrel!" Black Pete: "No' a chance, I've go' a crew of backstabber's, thieves and m- hurk!" in the lower left hand corner are the letters SR.***
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------
Dame Theressa Plans Springtime Event!

Dame Theressa of House Avoirdupois is planning a Springtime Feast for the end of the moon Grass.  According to the host, there will be delicacies and sweets as well as tea and refreshments.  Additionally, she hopes to incorporate games into the day of fun.  Trinkets and favors will be given to those who spend the day at this event.  Put on your springtime colors and celebrate the season with a day of fun and good company!  Watch the public boards (@forums) for an announcement regarding time and venue.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="10"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:article_title">
         "Page 2"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastsigner:object">
         \<Chatters:AE:va:valentin\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Valentin"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1239322550
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="misc:lastdropped">
         "1572980155 /usr/SkotOS/merry/2bfb8f3a9ac5886548b27853f3628ff3"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190289794, "tonyd", "X", 1193456199, "tonyd", "E", 1193456221, "tonyd", "E", 1238899241, "tonyd", "R", 1238899431, "tonyd", "R", 1238899640, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1239064709
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="966637404" state="Open" user="michaelb">
           The basic, original scroll.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
