<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(IronClaw:Props:Artist:Canvas)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="painting"/>
            <Base:SName sname="picture"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="paintings"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pictures"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="blue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="floral"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="green"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="interlaced"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="lily"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="lush"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="perennial"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="stem"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="vibrant"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             a vibrant painting of a heart-shaped floral wreath
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Situated in the center of the canvas upon a richly-colored blanket of lush, vibrant green grass is a floral arrangement comprised of intricately-stroked interlaced blossoms which form the shape of a heart. The right arch of the design begins with a perennial blue lily, arising from a rhizomatous bulb. Its slender stem trails downward in a thin braid, decorated with dark green, narrowly oblanceolate, wide leaves with whimsically whorled centers. The flower itself is slightly nodding forward, its rich blue petals hanging vulnerably in a carefully executed dip. A vibrant purple lily of similar design, but noticeably different color, nestles closely against the first, though it, dissimilarly, has been painted with its neck faintly inclined. Its petals are openly exposed, its flush white stamen craning upward toward the unseen. Just below lies a rose; soft strokes portraying showy clusters of big, vibrant red ruffled petals which furl elegantly inward, almost as if concealing a secret. Symmetically positioned to the left, a vibrant purple rose has been depicted unfurled, its broad, colorful petals relaxedly resting in multiple layers upon each other. The vivid green stems of these flowers have been plaited downward to a point and are bordered in identically hued serrated leaves, creating the tip of the heart-shaped wreath. Atop the vibrant purple rose, a pale pink lily has been created via a myriad of delicate swirls. It is dainty, and downfacing, its petals gently kissing the flower beneath almost in an aura of deference. Attached to the former through barely perceptible stems is yet another purple lily, this one shaded slightly lighter than the others. It is completely closed, it's petals folded upward in a circular and protective fashion to conceal its beauty entirely from the viewer. Strategically-placed wisps of green skirt the body of the enveloped bloom, the only real detail lent to this particular portion of the painting. The top left, and final piece of the wreath, is a spray of bright red paint strokes decorated throughout with gently-jagged tips. A portion of it tilts to the right, barely touching the body of the perennial blue lily, while the opposite side has been ruffled slightly to the left - almost as if it cannot choose one direction from the other. Within the middle of the design, darting across the upper right-hand corner and lower left-hand corner, large sprigs of pale pink clusters have been situated and dramatically painted to present the shape of an arrow with accompanying floral fringe.<br/><br/>A flamboyant X has been swiftly executed on the lower left of the canvas, in signature of the artist.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A vibrant painting of a multi-colored, heart-shaped floral wreath, set against a lush green background.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1212685827, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1212686136, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1212686169, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1213257694, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1213257706, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1213258123, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258175, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258181, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258188, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258196, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258202, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258209, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258215, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258220, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258232, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258237, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258242, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258247, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258252, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258258, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258265, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258271, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258276, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258282, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258287, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258292, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258297, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258367, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258500, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258856, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258975, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259054, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259072, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259312, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213259352, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213689838, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213690006, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213691104, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213691170, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706131, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706234, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706326, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706493, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214562337, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214562698, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214562732, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1222039422, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1222148215, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1249682552, "slurpeeslurp", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="signed">
         "with a swiftly executed, flamboyant X."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spawn:creator">
         (\{ "rorschakovacs", 1212685558 \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:brief">
         "vibrant painting of a heart-shaped floral wreath"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:examine">
         "Situated in the center of the canvas upon a richly-colored blanket of lush, vibrant green grass is a floral arrangement comprised of intricately-stroked interlaced blossoms which form the shape of a heart. The right arch of the design begins with a perennial blue lily, arising from a rhizomatous bulb. Its slender stem trails downward in a thin braid, decorated with dark green, narrowly oblanceolate, wide leaves with whimsically whorled centers. The flower itself is slightly nodding forward, its rich blue petals hanging vulnerably in a carefully executed dip. A vibrant purple lily of similar design, but noticeably different color, nestles closely against the first, though it, dissimilarly, has been painted with its neck faintly inclined. Its petals are openly exposed, its flush white stamen craning upward toward the unseen. Just below lies a rose; soft strokes portraying showy clusters of big, vibrant red ruffled petals which furl elegantly inward, almost as if concealing a secret. Symmetrically positioned to the left, a vibrant purple rose has been depicted unfurled, its broad, colorful petals relaxedly resting in multiple layers upon each other. The vivid green stems of these flowers have been plaited downward to a point and are bordered in identically hued serrated leaves, creating the tip of the heart-shaped wreath. Atop the vibrant purple rose, a pale pink lily has been created via a myriad of delicate swirls. It is dainty, and downfacing, its petals gently kissing the flower beneath almost in an aura of deference. Attached to the former through barely perceptible stems is yet another purple lily, this one shaded slightly lighter than the others. It is completely closed, it's petals folded upward in a circular and protective fashion to conceal its beauty entirely from the viewer. Strategically-placed wisps of green skirt the body of the enveloped bloom, the only real detail lent to this particular portion of the painting. The top left, and final piece of the wreath, is a spray of bright red paint strokes decorated throughout with gently-jagged tips. A portion of it tilts to the right, barely touching the body of the perennial blue lily, while the opposite side has been ruffled slightly to the left - almost as if it cannot choose one direction from the other. Within the middle of the design, darting across the upper right-hand corner and lower left-hand corner, large sprigs of pale pink clusters have been situated and dramatically painted to present the shape of an arrow with accompanying floral fringe."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:look">
         "A vibrant painting of a multi-colored, heart-shaped floral wreath, set against a lush green background."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:painting:quality">
         5
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1212791542
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
