<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="slurpeeslurp">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(IronClaw:Props:Artist:Canvas)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="painting"/>
            <Base:SName sname="picture"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="paintings"/>
            <Base:PName pname="pictures"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="black"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="green"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="hazy"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="lead"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="leafless"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="off-white"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="silver"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sooty"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             oil painting of a mushroom faerie
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             Leafless sooty black trees with outstretched skeletal branches have been sketched in lead to form the background of this painting. A thick, hazy green fog covers the entirety of the artwork and has been smeared here-and-there with hues of white and yellow to portray what look like light-induced breaks peeking through the otherwise dreary woods. The haze itself has been utilized to serve both as a duller against other colors, and to lend a greened effect to the artwork, casting a tainted hue upon all the objects depicted herein. At the forefront of the canvas, a patch of crinkled green vegetation with long shooting leaves grows in a circular fashion around the base of a mushroom. The stem of the fungus is striated and triple-layered with gentle strokes of white and black accenting its fringed body. It is attached directly to a plush, circular toadstool upon which is seated a delicate female faerie. Hers is a small frame, clad in green and off-white striped tights with pointed toes and an off-the-shoulder off-white flowing shirt which gathers around her bottom and comfortably-positioned legs. A silver-bell adorned anklet is wrapped around her right ankle while a matching silver bracelet is wound around her slender right forearm. Her short, softly shaded neck gives way to a defined roundly triangular face decorated with small, rosebud lips, high cheeks, sultry green eyes, and dark, scant eyebrows. Her ears are wide and triangular, coming to points just above the body of her long, shadowed hair. Her tresses themselves are long and straight, falling freely against the back before flowing downward into curled tips. Sprouting from behind her image is a pair of downturned, pure white wings which frame the figure and the toadstool in a subtle illumination. Four miniature faeries in mid-flight have been created toward the top of the painting in an arched fashion, each with two sets of petaled hazy wings, tiny thin bodies, and indescernible faces.<br/><br/>
A flamboyant 'X' rests in the lower-left hand corner of the canvas, in signature of the artist.<br/><br/>
[OOC Image: http://drugsrus.files.wordpress.com/2007/10/mushroom_fairy.jpg]
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A painting of a female faerie, seated upon a toadstool.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1212685827, "rorschakovacs", "X", 1212686136, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1212686169, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1213257694, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1213257706, "slurpeeslurp", "R", 1213258123, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258175, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258181, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258188, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258196, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258202, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258209, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258215, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258220, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258232, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258237, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258242, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258247, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258252, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258258, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258265, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258271, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258276, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258282, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258287, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258292, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258297, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258367, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258500, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258856, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213258975, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259054, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259072, "slurpeeslurp", "K", 1213259312, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213259352, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213689838, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213690006, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213691104, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213691170, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706131, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706234, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706326, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1213706493, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214562337, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214562486, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214982380, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1214982407, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1222148240, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1227530592, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1227530739, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1227639214, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1227639291, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1252040471, "slurpeeslurp", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="signed">
         "with a swiftly executed, flamboyant X."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="spawn:creator">
         (\{ "rorschakovacs", 1212685558 \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:brief">
         "oil painting of two sleeping lovers"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:examine">
         "A beige half-circle borders the upper left of this canvas, receding into a full coral-colored sphere upon which rests a butterfly. It has been intricately shaded; the bubble pattern on it's outspread wings filled in with careful dabbings of crimson, dark blue, and rich purple. The elongated body has been divided into three sections via black brush strokes: the top featuring a barely discernable head of blue adorned with curved, symmetrical antennae, the middle simply melting amongst the wings, and the bottom detailing a faintly pointed end with striated black accents. Just below and diagonal to this, a dragonfly gently holds the outer rim of the beige half-circle, framing it with it's broad, V-shaped, and highly-patterned wings. Stylized rippled, multi-colored shapes decorate the expanse of these appendages, some occasionally left with a swept, swirled look, others almost silkily brushed onto the canvas. The lower end of the dragonfly seemingly hovers over a cerulean wide-petaled flower which entirely covers the forehead and hair of the male figure captured underneath its fragile body. Dark eyebrows rest in a natural arch upon the shaded upper portion of his face while almond-shaped eyelids and thickly-brushed sable eyelashes peacefully conceal his gaze from the world herein. An almost bronze tint colors his narrow cheeks, dimpled chin and short neck, while an earthy neutral tone brings life to his subtly curved and closed lips. None of his clothing can be made out save for a small portion of blue collar that rests against the slender left arm of his white-gowned lover. Hers is a face clad in cream, and framed in long undulating brown tresses strung with aquamarine beads which fall freely across her back and simple white gown into the right edge of the painting. Only part of her face can be viewed; her left eye not unlike that of the males, though hers has been kissed with a hint of bronze coloration to match his hue. Her lips are small and smoothly glazed in rose red paint. Her delicate frame is gently pressed against that of her lovers, her left cheek intimately resting against his right; her left arm curled about his flower-crowned head softly. Similarly, his strong right hand is looped laxly around her back in a protective fashion; his fingers mellowly laced through her hair. The rest of this painting is a colorful rush of flowers which surround the contently sleeping couple in vibrancy and life. All manners of blue, pink, purple, green, and red tones have been utilized abstractly, making it nearly impossible to make out the variations of plants within, none having a beginning or end;  all of them winding, growing, craning, toward the center of the painting to envelop the subjects in folds of natural beauty."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:look">
         "An oil painting of two sleeping lovers enveloped in a delicate rush of flowers."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:painting:quality">
         5
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1212791542
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
