<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#336699", "bgcolor2":"#ffffcc", "bgimg1":"https://i.imgur.com/9nAbTvr.jpg", "bgimg2":"https://i.imgur.com/CpDK9V5.jpg", "fontcolor":"#003399", "fonttype":"Avant Garde", "h1color":"#003399", "h1type":"Avant Garde", "h2color":"#003399", "h2type":"Avant Garde", "h3color":"#003399", "h3type":"Avant Garde" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:avoirdupois history">
         (\{ "members", "\<html xmlns=\\"http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml\\"\>\\r\\n\<head\>\\r\\n\<style type=\\"text/css\\" media=\\"Screen\\"\>\\r\\nbody\{margin:auto;padding:auto\}\\r\\nhr\{display:block;position:relative;padding:0;margin:10px auto;height:0;width:80%;max-height:0;font-size:1px;line-height:0;clear:both;border:none;border-top:3px ridge rgb(106, 133, 160);border-bottom:3px groove rgb(39, 60, 89)\}\\r\\nnav\{line-height:1.5;margin:25px auto;width:80%;-webkit-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);-moz-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2)\}\\r\\n.menu-item \{background:#e6dec9;width:100%\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4\{border-bottom:1px solid rgba(0,0,0,0.3);border-top:1px solid rgba(255,255,255,0.2);color:#e6dec9;font-weight:500;padding:7px 12px;background:rgb(162, 185, 219)background:-moz-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(0%, rgb(162, 185, 219)), color-stop(44%,#6a85a0 ), color-stop(100%, rgb(39, 60, 89) ));background:-webkit-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160) 44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-o-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-ms-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.gradient(startColorstr=rgb(162, 185, 219), endColorstr= rgb(39, 60, 89),GradientType=0);margin:0px!important\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4 a\{color:#e6dec9;display:block;text-decoration:none\}\\r\\n.menu-item p\{padding:8px 12px;margin:0px!important\}\\r\\nh3\{color:rgb(39, 60, 89);text-align:center\}\\r\\n.material\{color:rgb(162, 185, 219)\}\\r\\n.detail \{color:#666666;font-style:italic\}\\r\\nimg\{border-radius:25px;height:200px;padding:10px\}\\r\\n\</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n\<nav\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>History\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe equine Avoirdupois claim that their noble line is the oldest and the proudest of all time. To back up their claim, the Avoirdupois maintain the oldest known castles and have the longest written records of anyone in Calabria. Steeped in tradition, members of this house are known for their unfailing courage, their unfaltering attention to their chivalric code, and their intolerance for everything not \\"Avoirdupois\\".\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois are proud and strong, fleet of hoof and of mind. They control the vast sweeping northeastern plains of Calabria. Their great vineyards and sweeping manors are responsible for most of the specialized food production on the continent. They pride themselves on having the swiftest army in the land and the most rigorously trained knights. They wish to maintain their open fields and keep their heritage intact. Despite their military stance, they are also quite concerned with the knightly virtues of loyalty and honor. None could be said to be more pious than an Avoirdupois knight on the morning of battle. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Current Affairs\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois control a large demesne of plains to the east of the City of Triskellian - but the Avoirdupois claim to have a history that dates back before any of the other cultures on Calabria. They make little secret of what they see as their \\"manifest destiny\\" - the domination of all of Calabria. At first glance, such a goal might make people unlikely to do business with them, much less ally with them. However, the Avoirdupois are nothing if not chivalrous - they always keep their word and never stab anyone in the back. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Friends \& Foes\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois are outspoken foes of the Bisclavret and the Doloreaux. They do not appreciate the Doloreaux control of the River Lyore and are rankled by having to buy timber from the Bisclavret. They tolerate the presence of the Constabulary of Triskellian as long as they \\"remember their place.\\"\\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Geography\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois control a large estate of hills and plains to the east of Triskellian. They are bordered on the south by the Paludestris, on the east by ocean cliffs, on the west by Triskellian and the Granvert River, on the north-northwest by the Lyore River and the Doloreaux. Their fields and farms are well situated in the heart of their territory, well-protected from attack. The Sauldre river feeds the farms and supplies the Avoirdupois with a small river trade.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe wind often howls across the mostly-treeless plains. While the Avoirdupois have an extensive irrigation system, it only works well in the summer. Winters in this land are notoriously harsh.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nMuch of the land is either farmland or wild grasslands. The few trees are clustered together in small forests that are zealously guarded by Avoirdupois rangers. Only small game and livestock are to be found outside of ranches. The richest Avoirdupois raise their own destriers.\\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Landmarks\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<b\>Chateau d'Avoirdupois\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nLocated at the center of their largest city, Chalon su Sauldre, it is also their ruling seat and home to the House of Avoirdupois. This oldest functioning castle in Calabria sprawls out on a wide flat plateau with treacherous sides. The plateau was shaped generations ago by the deliberate designs of clever engineers. The might of the entire Avoirdupois race was necessary to build the great plateau. The castle is in a dumbbell shape with high parapets and meticulously-maintained catapults.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>The Barrows\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nIn the center of one of the rocky hills unsuitable for farmaland is a cluster of oddly-shaped hills. If one looks around long enough, they may find the secret entrance to the tunnels below. Within the twisting corridors are interred the bones of uncountable skeletons, of various races and sizes. The people who built these barrows are unknown, and so is the reason they chose such a location. The Avoirdupois histories have yielded no clues. Some say the barrows are haunted, and that the dead walk, searching for the souls of the living. Others say it's a thief's hideout, and that villians who lurk there perpetuate the rumors to keep people away. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Economy\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois are very efficient farmers, but their lack of lumber hampers them immensely. To compensate, many farmers live in sod houses or even earthern homes. Their organization is impressive - precise records are kept, and taxes are collected on time. The skilled serfs are rewarded; the poor performers are punished. The Avoirdupois also maintain their own arms, using techniques handed down for generations. It is illegal for Avoirdupois serfs to accept denarii. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Culture\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<b\>Customs\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois lifestyle is austere--as one scholar described it, \\"first toil, the the grave.\\" Avoirdupois of all ages have a great sense of pride in their land and holdings be they serf, tradesman, merchant or noble. All of the gentry regularly drill in the arts of combat and heraldry, male and female alike. Manners and etiquette are not only valued, but mandatory. To outsiders, the Avoirdupois look humorless and severe. They use the S'allumer calender to measure their days.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Law\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nAll gentry are schooled in the precise laws of Avoirdupois rule, unchanged in over a hundred years. Ignorance of the law is no excuse, and the nobles have no patience with scofflaws. Low justice is meted out on the spot, and is usually a quick beating for light crimes, indentured servitude for greater offenses, and summary execution for murderers or worse.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Religion\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe \\"approved\\" religion of Avoirdupois nobles is Penitence of S'allumer. Serfs and underlings are expected to worship as their lord does, but this is not always the case. Local churches are small and modest, as the Avoirdupois prefer their worship to be as simple and pragmatic as their lifestyles, and not weighted down with grandiose icons, but as the influence of the Church grows, so do their buildings and estates.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Armed Forces\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nSince all gentry, save the infirm or young children, are combat-worthy and highly-disciplined, the Avoirdupois can field land-based forces more formidable than any on Calabria. Conservative by nature, they prefer not to engage a foe unless they can win a quick, decisive victory, which explains why the Avoirdupois have yet to campaign in earnest to fulfill their \\"manifest destiny\\" as rulers of all Calabria. \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Language\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe modern, pragmatic Avoirdupois speak Calabrese. The Avoirdupois have refused to translate their law books into a more common language, so as not to \\"alduterate\\" their meaning.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Names\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nExamples of male given names include Astolpho, Ignace, Somer, and Warrane. For women, Albracca, Calandre, Fanette, and Joanna.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nAvoirdupois are most likely to pay homage to their family, and will include that in their name. Some noble surnames include Boulanger, Chausse, Criniere, Enclume, and Sabot - for example, a noble's full name might be Astolpho du Sabot l'Avoirdupois. Other Avoirdupois fancy themselves as \\"knights errant\\" and drop their surname in favor of just their family, such as Anton d'Avoirdupois. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\</nav\>\\r\\n\</body\>\\r\\n\</html\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<h2\>Calendar of Events\</h2\>\\r\\n\<iframe src=\\"https://www.google.com/calendar/embed?showTitle=0\&showCalendars=0\&height=550\&wkst=1\&bgcolor=%23ffffff\&src=tdtbvec23pcs3bbcle0qmopknk%40group.calendar.google.com\&color=%23182C57\&ctz=America%2FNew_York\\" style=\\" border-width:0 \\" width=\\"550\\" height=\\"350\\" frameborder=\\"0\\" scrolling=\\"no\\"\>\</iframe\>\</center\>", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:embassy guard">
         (\{ "members", "\<html xmlns=\\"http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml\\"\>\\r\\n\<head\>\\r\\n\<style type=\\"text/css\\" media=\\"Screen\\"\>\\r\\nbody\{margin:auto;padding:auto\}\\r\\nhr\{display:block;position:relative;padding:0;margin:10px auto;height:0;width:80%;max-height:0;font-size:1px;line-height:0;clear:both;border:none;border-top:3px ridge rgb(106, 133, 160);border-bottom:3px groove rgb(39, 60, 89)\}\\r\\nnav\{line-height:1.5;margin:25px auto;width:80%;-webkit-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);-moz-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2)\}\\r\\n.menu-item \{background:#e6dec9;width:100%\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4\{border-bottom:1px solid rgba(0,0,0,0.3);border-top:1px solid rgba(255,255,255,0.2);color:#e6dec9;font-weight:500;padding:7px 12px;background:rgb(162, 185, 219)background:-moz-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(0%, rgb(162, 185, 219)), color-stop(44%,#6a85a0 ), color-stop(100%, rgb(39, 60, 89) ));background:-webkit-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160) 44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-o-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-ms-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.gradient(startColorstr=rgb(162, 185, 219), endColorstr= rgb(39, 60, 89),GradientType=0);margin:0px!important\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4 a\{color:#e6dec9;display:block;text-decoration:none\}\\r\\n.menu-item p\{padding:8px 12px;margin:0px!important\}\\r\\nh3\{color:rgb(39, 60, 89);text-align:center\}\\r\\n.material\{color:rgb(162, 185, 219)\}\\r\\n.detail \{color:#666666;font-style:italic\}\\r\\nimg\{border-radius:25px;height:200px;padding:10px\}\\r\\n\</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n\<nav\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>General Information\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois House is steeped in tradition, our soldiers world famous for their unfailing courage and unfaltering attention to the chivalric code. You would in no uncertain terms be expected to continue this tradition. It is partially this mutual understanding that cements the ranks of the Avoirdupois army together and the reason why the Avoirdupois have yet to campaign in earnest. How you handle yourself and your everyday actions reflects upon the embassy. All to often the other embassies within the city gain an unfavorable reputation upon the actions of one or two guardsmen. This will not be tolerated within our ranks. Reports of unsatisfactory behavior will be taken seriously and where necessary sanctions taken to prevent future infractions and repair public perception. Training regimes are tailored to specific careers by the captain of the embassy guard. The embassy is willing to help pay for training, and actively encourage all soldiers to spar and learn from others around the city\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nAccepted applicants will be inducted into the cities legion and placed on a probationary period of four weeks, and kitted out with a guard uniform and basic armor and weaponry if they do not possess their own. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Guard Oath\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nI, \<i\>your name here\</i\>, do solemnly swear to serve the House d'Avoirdupois loyally and faithfully.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nI shall exhibit prudence and temperance in deportment, representing the House d'Avoirdupois in the highest manner possible.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nI shall endeavor to shun all vices and adhere only to that which is virtuous, and be true in my services and reports.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nI shall conduct myself with honor, and will not forsake my honor in any case, always striving to do right toward those around myself.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nAs long as I remain in the service of the House, I shall obey the orders of those above myself without hesitation. If tasked with secrecy, I shall keep all secrets, excepting in the case of treason against the House d'Avoirdupois.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nI shall constantly seek betterment and improvement, both in mind and in body that I might serve the best as I may.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nTo this I do swear in truth and in honor, lest my honor be forsaken.\\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Response\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nSo long as you are loyal to the House d'Avoirdupois, our loyalty is similarly owed to you. When in need of aid, the House shall come. When in need of shelter, the House shall protect. When in need of care, the House shall aid. When in need of strength, the House shall support.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThis cloak is both a representation of your loyalty to the House d'Avoirdupois, and a representation of its loyalty to you. As it shields you from the elements, the cold, the rain, so do we shield you and protect you without fail and without err. Conduct yourself with honor, monsieur, and you shall always find the House there to render aid. \\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\</nav\>\\r\\n\</body\>\\r\\n\</html\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<html xmlns=\\"http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml\\"\>\\r\\n\<head\>\\r\\n\<style type=\\"text/css\\" media=\\"Screen\\"\>\\r\\nbody\{margin:auto;padding:auto\}\\r\\nhr\{display:block;position:relative;padding:0;margin:10px auto;height:0;width:80%;max-height:0;font-size:1px;line-height:0;clear:both;border:none;border-top:3px ridge rgb(106, 133, 160);border-bottom:3px groove rgb(39, 60, 89)\}\\r\\nnav\{line-height:1.5;margin:25px auto;width:80%;-webkit-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);-moz-box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2);box-shadow:2px 2px 5px rgba(0,0,0,0.2)\}\\r\\n.menu-item \{background:#e6dec9;width:100%\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4\{border-bottom:1px solid rgba(0,0,0,0.3);border-top:1px solid rgba(255,255,255,0.2);color:#e6dec9;font-weight:500;padding:7px 12px;background:rgb(162, 185, 219)background:-moz-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(0%, rgb(162, 185, 219)), color-stop(44%,#6a85a0 ), color-stop(100%, rgb(39, 60, 89) ));background:-webkit-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160) 44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-o-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:-ms-linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);background:linear-gradient(top, rgb(162, 185, 219) 0%, rgb(106, 133, 160)  44%, rgb(39, 60, 89)  100%);filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.gradient(startColorstr=rgb(162, 185, 219), endColorstr= rgb(39, 60, 89),GradientType=0);margin:0px!important\}\\r\\n.menu-item h4 a\{color:#e6dec9;display:block;text-decoration:none\}\\r\\n.menu-item p\{padding:8px 12px;margin:0px!important\}\\r\\nh3\{color:rgb(39, 60, 89);text-align:center\}\\r\\n.material\{color:rgb(162, 185, 219)\}\\r\\n.detail \{color:#666666;font-style:italic\}\\r\\nimg\{border-radius:25px;height:200px;padding:10px\}\\r\\nul\{margin:0px\}\\r\\n\</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n\<nav\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Calendar of Events\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<iframe src=\\"https://www.google.com/calendar/embed?showTitle=0\&showCalendars=0\&height=400\&wkst=1\&bgcolor=%23FFFFFF\&src=sqqaih4emmib6k7bs0i2ke5s14%40group.calendar.google.com\&color=%23875509\&ctz=America%2FNew_York\\" style=\\" border-width:0 \\" width=\\"90%\\" height=\\"400\\" frameborder=\\"0\\" scrolling=\\"no\\"\>\</iframe\>\</center\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>History\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>The equine Avoirdupois claim that their noble line is the oldest and the proudest of all time. To back up their claim, the Avoirdupois maintain the oldest known castles and have the longest written records of anyone in Calabria. Steeped in tradition, members of this house are known for their unfailing courage, their unfaltering attention to their chivalric code, and their intolerance for everything not \<i\>Avoirdupois\</i\>.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois are proud and strong, fleet of hoof and of mind. They control the vast sweeping northeastern plains of Calabria. Their great vineyards and sweeping manors are responsible for most of the specialized food production on the continent. They pride themselves on having the swiftest army in the land and the most rigorously trained knights. They wish to maintain their open fields and keep their heritage intact. Despite their military stance, they are also quite concerned with the knightly virtues of loyalty and honor. None could be said to be more pious than an Avoirdupois knight on the morning of battle.\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Other Imports\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois embassy offers the following items for import to the auction house upon request:\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nCognac\<br\>\\r\\nCologne\<br\>\\r\\nFace Powder\<br\>\\r\\nPerfume\<br\>\\r\\nSpecialty Fabrics\<br\>\\r\\nSteel\<br\>\\r\\nWigs\<br\>\\r\\nWine\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThere is a fee of twenty (20) denarii or ten (1510 tradesman papers per import.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nPlease note that this fee covers the cost of importation to the auction house. It does not guarantee receipt of the item by the individual(s) or guild who paid the fee.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>All inquiries and importation requests are to be sent to Comte Romain Lemieux.\</i\>\\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"menu-item\\"\>\\r\\n\<h4\>\<a href=\\"#\\"\>Application for Membership\</a\>\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<i\>Please send a missive to Comte Romain Lemieux with all pertinent information.\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Name:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Date of Birth:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Hometown:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Skills:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Reason(s) for Applying:\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Letters of recommendation are encouraged, but not required.\</i\>\\r\\n\</p\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\</div\>\\r\\n\</nav\>\\r\\n\</body\>\\r\\n\</html\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ "members", "ARR[2]", (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1477608353, "jominey", "E", 1477608358, "jominey", "E", 1477608382, "jominey", "E", 1571341391, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
