<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:acclamations to god ">
         (\{ "members", "I will give thanks to you, LORD, with all my heart; I will tell of all your wonderful deeds. 2 I will be glad and rejoice in you; I will sing the praises of your name, O Most High. Psalm 9:1-2\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n I will exalt you, LORD, for you lifted me out of the depths and did not let my enemies gloat over me. 2 LORD my God, I called to you for help, and you healed me. 3 You, LORD, brought me up from the realm of the dead; you spared me from going down to the pit. 4 Sing the praises of the LORD, you his faithful people; praise his holy name. 5 For his anger lasts only a moment, but his favor lasts a lifetime; weeping may stay for the night, but rejoicing comes in the morning. 11 You turned my wailing into dancing; you removed my sackcloth and clothed me with joy, 12 that my heart may sing your praises and not be silent. LORD my God, I will praise you forever. Psalm 30:1-5, 11-12\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nPraise be to the LORD, for he showed me the wonders of his love . . . . Psalm 31:21\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nPraise be to the Lord, to God our Savior, who daily bears our burdens. Our God is a God who saves; from the Sovereign LORD comes escape from death. Psalm 68:19-20\<br\>\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:confession">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>Guide\</b\> \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<p style=\\"color:MediumSeaGreen;\\"\>Priest:\</p\>\</i\> In the name of the Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit. Amen.       \\r\\n May God, who has enlightened every heart, help you to know your sins and trust in His mercy.\<br\>\<br\>     \\r\\n  \\r\\n\<i\>\<p style=\\"color:Dodgerblue;\\"\>Member:\</p\>\</I\> Bless me, Father, for I have sinned. It has been _____ (weeks, months, years) since my last confession. These are my sins: \<br\>\<br\>\<b\>(Have them declare their sins and how often they committed them. Only essential details are necessary)\</b\> \\r\\n    \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nI am sorry for these and all of my sins.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\<p style=\\"color:MediumSeaGreen;\\"\>Priest:\</p\>\<b\>Give them counsel and then assign a penance.\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n  \<i\>Have the member\</i\> recite the \<b\>Prayer of the Penitent (Act of Contrition)\</b\>, such as this:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<q\>My God, \\r\\nI am sorry for my sins with all my heart. In choosing to do wrong \\r\\nand failing to do good, I have sinned against you whom I should love above all things. I firmly intend, with your help to do penance, to sin no more,  and to avoid whatever leads me to sin. Our Savior Jesus Christ suffered and died for us. In His name, my God, have mercy.\</q\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \\r\\n\\r\\n\<p style=\\"color:MediumSeaGreen;\\"\>Priest:\</p\> \<b\>Prayer of Absolution:\</b\> \<br\>\<br\>\<q\>May our Lord and God, Jesus Christ, through the grace and mercies of his love for humankind, forgive you all your transgressions. And I, an unworthy priest, by his power given me, forgive and absolve you from all your sins, in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit. Amen.\</q\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nEnd the confession with an acclamation of praise to God and a dismissal, such as:\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p style=\\"color:MediumSeaGreen;\\"\>Priest:\</p\>  Give thanks to the Lord, for he is good.\<br\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Closing Line:\</b\> \<br\>\<br\>The Lord has freed you from your sins. Go in peace." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "This is your default guild page. This is the first page your members see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "This is your guest page. This is the page your visitors see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:prayer of absolution">
         (\{ "members", "May our Lord and God, Jesus Christ, through the grace and mercies of his love for humankind, forgive you all your transgressions. And I, an unworthy priest, by his power given me, forgive and absolve you from all your sins, in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit. Amen." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:prayer of penitent ( act of contrition)">
         (\{ "members", "My God, \\r\\nI am sorry for my sins with all my heart. \\r\\nIn choosing to do wrong \\r\\nand failing to do good, \\r\\nI have sinned against you \\r\\nwhom I should love above all things. \\r\\nI firmly intend, with your help \\r\\nto do penance, to sin no more, \\r\\nand to avoid whatever leads me to sin. \\r\\nOur Savior Jesus Christ suffered and died for us. \\r\\nIn His name, my God, have mercy." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the holy church armory inventory">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>Available Items\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n1 curved iron shortsword\<br\>\\r\\n1 dark-stained engraved maple tower shield \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Currently held by Paladin Leda\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n1 steel cuirass\<br\>\\r\\n1 steel gauntlets\<br\>\\r\\n1 steel pauldrons\<br\>\\r\\n1 steel sword\<br\>\\r\\n1 steel greaves\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Items held by Paladin-in-training Raphael\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n1 engraved silvery polished steel breastplate \<br\>\\r\\n1 engraved silvery polished steel pauldrons\<br\>\\r\\n1 engraved silvery polished steel bracers\<br\>\\r\\n1 blue hardened steel arming sword\<br\>\\r\\n1 Damascus steel dagger\<br\>\\r\\n1 Damascus steel sword scabbard\<br\>\\r\\n1 oiled, earthy leather The Holy Catholic Church armband \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
