<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="footer"/>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#787878", "bgcolor2":"#D6D6D5", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Book Antiqua", "h1color":"#000000", "h1type":"Book Antiqua", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Book Antiqua", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Book Antiqua" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:after an arrest: your incarcerated prisoner">
         (\{ "members", "After An Arrest: Your Incarcerated Prisoner" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:arrests: how to">
         (\{ "members", "\<div class=\\"header\\"\>\<b\>When a Constable May Make an Arrest:\</b\>\</div\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<div class=\\"title\\"\>* The constable has personally observed a crime;\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"title\\"\>* The constable has probable cause to believe that person arrested committed a crime;\</div\>\\r\\n\<div class=\\"title\\"\>* The constable has an arrest warrant issed by the Magistrate (@crime).\</div\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<div class=\\"header\\"\>Advise the suspect to not resist arrest; use of minimal force necessary to protect yourself to bring a suspect into custody. You may use handcuffs to ensure your safety and the safety of bystanders. Once a suspect has been brought to their cell, have them remove their personal items (bags, cloaks, weapons, belts, jewelry) and collect them into a package properly labeled with their name so that we may safely store them in the cabinet in the office. NEVER turn your back to a criminal in the cell and ALWAYS close the cell door once concluded. Be sure to inform the Magistrate of the arrest.\</div\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<div class=\\"header\\"\>(OOC: Make sure to check with the player OOCly to see if they understand @crime! If not, if you are comfortable, you can explain the quick basic functions or advise them to @assist. Otherwise, once a you've detained someone who has a warrant, please make sure to @assist to staff (AKA inform the Magistrate) that the arrest has been made so they can take over.)\</div\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\\"To the Honored Citizens of Rinascita,\<br/\>\</br\>We, the Rinascita City Guard, hereby declare our solemn duty and commitment to upholding the peace, security, and prosperity of our beloved city. As the sworn protectors of this noble community, we vow to faithfully serve and defend our people with unwavering courage and integrity.\<br/\>\</br\>It is our charge to maintain order within the city walls, safeguarding the lives and property of all who reside here. We shall be vigilant sentinels, ever watchful for threats, whether they be from foreign invaders, common criminals, or any who would seek to disrupt the harmony of our civic life.\<br/\>\</br\>With the authority granted to us by Holy Roman Empress, we shall enforce the laws of this city without fear or favor. All who dwell within these boundaries, from the highest nobleman to the humblest laborer, shall be subject to our righteous stewardship. Justice and the common good shall be our guiding principles.\<br/\>\</br\>Furthermore, we pledge to act as ambassadors of Rinascita, projecting an image of strength, discipline, and civic pride to all who encounter us. Our uniforms, bearing the honored crest and colors of this city, shall be a symbol of the power and unity that binds us together.\<br/\>\</br\>To the citizens of Rinascita, we ask for your trust and cooperation. Stand with us as we fulfill our solemn duty to safeguard this city and all that it represents. Only through our collective efforts can we ensure the continued prosperity and security of our beloved homeland.\<br/\>\</br\>May God watch over our City and grant us the wisdom and valor to carry out our sacred charge.\<br/\>\</br\>Signed,\<br/\>\</br\>The Rinascita City Guard\\"", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:oath">
         (\{ "visitors", "I, [name], swear that I will faithfully and diligently serve His Majesty Dominic di Richezza, King of Italy, his heirs and successors, without favor or affection, malice or ill-will. While a constable I will, to the best of my power, keep the peace and prevent offences against the peace, and will, to the best of my skill and knowledge, perform all the duties of the office of constable according to law. So help me God." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:personal effects and evidence">
         (\{ "members", "Personal Effects and Evidence" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:uniforms, equipment and appearance standards">
         (\{ "members", "Uniforms, Equipment and Appearance Standards\</br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>I. POLICY\\r\\nUnless otherwise directed, members of the City Guard (also referred to as \\"Department\\"), while on duty, will wear the uniforms and equipment issued to them by the City Guard. Uniforms will be worn in their entirety and in their intended fashion, and will be kept clean and pressed. The badge is to be displayed on the outermost garment being worn by the uniformed officer. Buttons and other metal accessories will be clean and bright. Members of the City Guard will be well groomed and present a professional appearance to maintain the respect and trust of the public. \</br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>II. UNIFORMS \& EQUIPMENT\\r\\n\<br/\>A. Equipment and/or property means and includes:\\r\\n\<br/\>1. All uniforms and equipment issued to members.\\r\\n\<br/\>2. Department weapons, accessories, and department-owned property contained therein.\\r\\n\<br/\>3. Department buildings, including the County-owned equipment and/or property they contain.\\r\\n\<br/\>4. All other City Guard equipment or property, which comes into the possession of a member at any time.\\r\\n\<br/\>B. The City Guard provides all sworn personnel with uniforms and equipment at no expense to the sworn officer. Replacement of worn uniforms, equipment, and clothing is available through the Quartermaster or Chief Constable Selene.\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R", 1719861292, "annemairi", "E", 1719861338, "annemairi", "E", 1719861782, "annemairi", "E", 1719867048, "annemairi", "E", 1719867106, "annemairi", "E", 1719867137, "annemairi", "E", 1719867148, "annemairi", "E", 1719867279, "annemairi", "E", 1719867302, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
