<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#000000", "bgcolor2":"#ccccff", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#6600cc", "fonttype":"Georgia", "h1color":"#000000", "h1type":"Georgia", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Georgia", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Georgia" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:constabulary oaths">
         (\{ "hidden", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Constabulary Oaths =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are copies of the oaths within the Triskellian Constabulary.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDeputy Oath\<br\>\<Br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<i\>I, (name), do solemnly swear by S'Allumer, to uphold the Laws and Ordinances of the city of Triskellian, to serve the public trust, and to defend the subjects of His Majesty the Don, without fear, favour, or thought of personal safety; to pursue evil-doers and to protect the innocent, laying down my life if necessary in the cause of said duty, so help me S'Allumer. S'Allumer bless the Don.\</i\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:constabulary policies">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Constabulary Policies =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are a number of policies all Triskellian Constabulary members must adhere to.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>As a recruit for the Constabulary there are several things to keep in mind and be aware of.  The most important points are:\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n*Know the law and the different type of charges which can be made. This is the most important part as our job is to enforce and uphold the law in Triskellian.  The law can be found publicly for all to read. Make sure you know it by heart. (OOC: Current Laws \& Charges)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n*Be aware of your responsibility to report all crimes to a superior - even if you know it might not be as they say. Subsequent investigation will determine what's right and wrong.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n*Remember that you always represent the Crown and the Constabulary. Both privately and publicly, how you behave will reflect not only upon yourself, but also on the Constabulary, thereby eventually the Crown.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n*Always be polite and proper. Greet all the same, showing proper respect for rank. Even those you suspect of crimes you show basic courtesy in public. Do not let your behaviour tarnish that of the Constabulary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n*Do not associate with unsavoury elements. Avoid fraternizing with people who're known criminals, suspected of crimes or in general disfavoured by Crown or Constabulary. In particular this is true when comes to your personal relationships. Do not under any circumstances engage in a personal relationship with a criminal or those known to associate with criminals. If you're in doubt, ask your superior for advice.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n*Do not get drunk or use illegal substances. Never engage in any criminal activities. Doing so will result in dismissal from the Constabulary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Once you've proven you're capable of performing the duties of a Constable and have nothing speaking against you, you become a full member of the Constabulary.\</b\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:constabulary positions">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Constabulary Positions =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are a number of responsibilities within Triskellian Constabulary.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Recruit\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Recruit is in training to become a Deputy. The period lasts a month, and during this month the recruit proves himself worthy of becoming a full member of the Constabulary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDuring the time the recruit assists a full member of the Constabulary, who's in charge of his training. The recruit aids with investigations, filing crimes, capturing criminals and keeping law and order.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Learn the laws of Triskellian and the duties of being part of the Constabulary\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Arrest wanted criminals and bring them to the goal\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Create new @crime files once his responsible deems him ready\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Assist in ongoing investigations\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Help maintain law and order\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Patrol Docktown\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Feed prisoners\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Is given:\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Lessons from the guild teacher\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Lessons from other Constabulary members\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Constable\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Constable is a full member of the Constabulary.\<br\>\\r\\nThe Constable's job is to act as a full member of the Constabulary, which includes arresting criminals, opening and closing files, recruiting and training of new members.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Close cases\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Mentor new members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Arrest wanted criminals and bring them to the goal\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Create new @crime files ones his responsible deems him ready\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Conduct investigations and interviews\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Maintain law and order\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Patrol Docktown\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Feed prisoners\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Is given:\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Lessons from the guild teacher\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Lessons from other Constabulary members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A uniform\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Paymaster/Clerk\</h1\>\\r\\nA person or persons who updates documents and keeps all Constable up-to-date on happenings concerning events and guild decisions.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Keep track of the Members roster\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Formally recruit into the Constabulary\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Promote and dismiss Members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Responsible for bidding on the Auction House (in cooperation with Quartermaster)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Organize archives and manage them\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Keep Members aware of archives and changes\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Other administrative work and filing\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Envoy\</h3\>\\r\\nA person or persons who mingles with House and important persons in matters of negotiation.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Communication and diplomacy with Houses and Guilds\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Manage the rosters of the Triskellian Militia\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Accept applications for the Militia\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Approve and disapprove of Militia members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Keep the Militia informed\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Quartermaster\</h3\>\\r\\nA person or persons who keeps and stores armory of the Triskellian Constabulary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Order equipment for Constables\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Distributes equipment to Members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Keeps track of who has what\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Maintain and administer the stores of the Constabulary\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Drill Master\</h3\>\\r\\nA person or persons who organizes training with and for the Constables of Triskellian Constabulary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tasks:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Organize training for recruits and Constables\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Find teachers for Members\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Keep track of progress with training sessions\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:constabulary titles">
         (\{ "hidden", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Constabulary Titles =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here is a listing of the intrinsic rank titles within Triskellian Constabulary.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n    Deputy is of a similar standing to Freedman\<br\>\\r\\n    Guardsman is of a similar standing to Yeoman\<br\>\\r\\n    Seargent is of a similar standing to Burgher\<br\>\\r\\n    Detective is of a similar standing to Thane\<br\>\\r\\n    Aedile is of a similar standing to Gentry\<br\>\\r\\n    Sheriff is of a similar standing to Armigerous gentry\<br\>\\r\\n    Tribune is of a similar standing to Knight or Dame\<br\>\\r\\n    Seargent-Major is of a similar standing to Baronet or Baronetess\<br\>\\r\\n    Brigadier is of a similar standing to Baron or Baroness\<br\>\\r\\n    Major is of a similar standing to Viscount or Viscountess\<br\>\\r\\n    Marshal is of a similar standing to Count or Countess\<br\>\\r\\n    Lieutenant General is of a similar standing to Landgrave\<br\>\\r\\n    Captain General is of a similar standing to Margrave or Margravine\<br\>\\r\\n    Field Marshal is of a similar standing to Marchion or Marchioness\<br\>\\r\\n    High Constable is of a similar standing to Duke or Duchess\<br\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:current laws & charges">
         (\{ "visitors", "http://forum.skotos.net/showthread.php?t=80797" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Triskellian Constabulary =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>=== Please don't forget to use @favor/@disfavor ===\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe more we promote the good deeds of our fellow Constables, the more rank and influence around the city we will have.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>ANNOUNCEMENTS:\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nPlease review open cases and report any new evidence or testimony.  These need to be closed soon or will be marked unresolved.\<bR\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn service of the Crown and Constabulary,\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>~Acting Sheriff Nikona\</i\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Triskellian Constabulary =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Your city guards are:\</h1\>\\r\\n\<em\>Active\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nDetective Nikona\<br/\>\\r\\nGuardsman Albers\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<em\>Inactive\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nAedile Carrot\</br\>\\r\\nDetective Kegan\<br/\>\\r\\nSergeant Brok\<br/\>\\r\\nSergeant Biggs\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nOur office is located north of the gate separating Docktown and Newtown on your first left.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:how to:  file a @crime">
         (\{ "hidden", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= How To File a @Crime =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are instructions for how to file a @crime file.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen someone approaches you wanting to press charges, you have to create the crime in the system, even if you know it's a false charge. You can also press charges yourself. Only Constables can create a new file in the system.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOnce a crime's been created, witnesses and people can give their testimonies and statements by using the system. These are what determines if a suspect is found guilty or not.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis is how you do ooc'ly:\<br\>\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Type @crime and a pop-up window will open.\\r\\n\<li\>Here you click the link \\"File a new crime for investigation\\".\\r\\n\<li\>In the first field you type in the name of the criminal (if known, if not look further down.\\r\\n\<li\>If there are any accomplices, you add their names to the list. Remember to click the Add bottom so their names are listed.\\r\\n\<li\>In the Name of Crime field you write out all the charges the the file is about.\\r\\n\<li\>In the Description of Crime box you briefly write what the crime is about. Just a few lines, no need to describe in detail, and this is -not- the place to write testimonies etc.\\r\\n\<li\>Click the bottom, File Crime.\\r\\n\<li\>You'll now be able to choose the status type in a drop down menu. The case will be open per default. If there's no suspects, you choose that.\\r\\n\<li\>Further down you can view charges and evidence for your suspects. Choose your suspect on the drop down menu.\\r\\n\<li\>If there are already charges, they'll be listed in blue, which you can click on to read the testimonies and opinions.\\r\\n\<li\>For a new crime you go to the dropdown menu below and pick the appropriate crime. One file can have more crimes.\\r\\n\<li\>You then choose severity. Most crimes will just be normal charge. There are exceptions, so check the List of Current Charges to be sure. Ask a superior if you're in doubt.\\r\\n\<li\>Click the Add crime (or change severity) bottom and you're all set.\\r\\n\<li\>If there's no criminal, you can't add charges and will have to list the crimes in the description field.\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:how to: evidence, testimony, opinion">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Evidence, Testimony and Opinion =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here is an overview on the differences between Evidence, Testimony and Opinion as used in the @crime files.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\nEvidence: Varying degrees of evidence an be found for certain cases. Since we're taking a murder case for our example, bits of evidence that might be found would be: the wounds on the body, the smell of the body, any weapon left at the scene, etc. These are all bits of physical evidence and can only be presented to the magistrate by a Constable. You might see something like this in the public record of a crime:\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>The corpse of Bill smelled like rabbit. Bill is a fox, but Roger is a rabbit. (Circumstantial evidence of guilt). This is not solid evidence, because any rabbit could have hung around Bill before he died, causing the smell.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>The corpse of Bill has several short, thin stab wounds in his torso, identified by a doctor to be dagger wounds. Roger uses a club. (Circumstantial evidence of innocence). Roger may indeed use a dagger, and no one knows about it. On the converse, there are a lot of people who use daggers, so it wasn't necessarily Roger who used a dagger against Bill, even if he did use one frequently.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>Mister George whiskers in it and a note saying that Roger is guilty (invalid evidence). The whiskers could have come from anyone, and they were sent in a vague manner with no description of how they were found or obtained.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>Roger sent a signed confession in his own hand, with his own signature, confessing to the crime. (Indisputable evidence of guilt). This one should be self-explanatory.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>If anyone opens a case file, and finds evidence that they think is suspect, please feel free to write a Constable and contest (ooc: or file an @assist). We don't promise we'll always agree with you, but we're always happy to explain why we do things.\<br\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\nTestimony: Testimony can be really tricky, since it eventually boils down to he says/she says. You should not file testimony in a case that you did not personally witness. If you did not see a crime, your \\"testimony\\" actually becomes \\"opinion\\". There are two types of testimony: solid, and circumstantial.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSolid evidence should be filed for eyewitness testimony only. Some good examples of solid testimony:\<br\>\<ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>I was in the commons with Roger when he stabbed Bill. It was messy! (solid evidence of guilt)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger was with me in my room talking about business all night when the crime was committed. He couldn't have killed Bill. (solid evidence of innocence)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>I was there when the murder occurred! I sure did see George stab Bill, not Roger! (solid evidence of innocence)\<br\>\<br\>\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOther examples that are less clear-cut, but still solid:\<br\>\<ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>I heard a scream come from the bank. Right afterward, Roger came out, covered in blood, and dragging Bill's body. There was nobody else in the bank with him. (solid evidence of guilt)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger came to check the courier. Shortly afterward, we heard a man scream from the east commons. We both rushed in, and found Billy's dead body (solid evidence of innocence)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger told me himself that he killed Bill! (solid evidence of guilt)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\nAnything else is considered Circumstantial evidence. Some good examples of circumstantial evidence:\<br\>\<ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>Bill and George got into a big fight yesterday, and today Bill is dead! (circumstantial evidence of guilt)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Bill and George have always been best buds! Just yesterday George said he'd die for Bill! (Circumstantial evidence of innocence)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Bill and George have a long history of rivalry together. They've often said they wanted to kill one another. Now Bill's dead. (circumstantial evidence of guilt)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>George cheated on Roger with Bill, and now Bill is dead! (circumstantial evidence of guilt)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOpinion: Anything that helps the magistrate establish motive, but is not direct observance of a crime is considered circumstantial and solid evidence. Anything else is considered opinion. Some bad examples of testimony, but good examples of opinions:\\r\\n\<ul\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger killed me, and so he probably killed Bill too. (This is opinion, not testimony)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>I sure do hate that Roger guy. I bet he did kill Bill. (Again, this is opinion, not testimony)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger is such a nice guy! He gets ill at the sight of blood. He couldn't have committed murder! (Opinion)\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>Roger sure does commit a lot of crimes. No doubt he committed this one, too. (Opinion)\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAnything that does not fit into the testimonial category belongs in the opinion one. PLEASE file your testimonies responsibly. Everyone who witnessed a crime is allowed to file both an opinion and a testimony. (ooc: You are allowed to lie and file testimony in a crime when you did not actually witness it. Just don't get caught!)\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:laws and charges">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Laws and Charges =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are the current Laws and Charges within Triskellian.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>24 Hour Detainment\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIf a constable witnesses a crime they may stop the crime and detain the suspect for 24 hours. This may only be done once per crime and only with probable cause. If a constable does this more than once per crime or without probable cause they may be charged with illegal detainment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Acting against the Church\</h3\>\\r\\nAny remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Church of S'allumer.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Disrespect to a Church member.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Insulting the Church.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Claiming to or taking action against the Church.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Apostasy\</h1\>\\r\\nLeaving a religion after making it a profession and swearing solemn vows. This does not apply to someone who moves from one order to another, or retires legitimately.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - A Church leader leaving before their term is expired.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - A priest abandoning his/her vows without express permission from the Church.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - A member leaving the Church for another religion.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Assault\</h3\>\\r\\nIntentionally and voluntarily causing immediate harmful or offensive contact.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Brawling without serious injury, pulling a weapon on a noble even without contact, defense of someone else where injury is sustained.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal -Brawling outside the arenas where injury is sustained, or unwanted touching of someone else.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Attacking someone with a weapon outside of the arenas where blood is drawn, maiming, attempted murder.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Assisting a Criminal\</h3\>\\r\\nActing with foresight and intent to aid any person in carrying out a crime or escape justice.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Falsifying testimony (if you say you where there and saw it all on your testimony and someone says you were not there would be acceptable), giving weapons or armor to someone who is banned from them.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Harboring fugitives, actively or physically obstructing a constable or investigation.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Planning a crime, providing the means to commit a crime, bribing a Constable, hiring an assassin.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Debt\</h3\>\\r\\nRefusing to pay a bill means you are in debt. This applies to any services rendered that go unpaid. If you are charged with this crime you do not have to pay your bill because your punishment will serve as payment rendered.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Disrespecting Constabulary\</h3\>\\r\\nAny remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Constabulary or any on-duty member.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Calling an on-duty constable names. (This must be in relation to the Constabulary. Calling a Constable an idiot to something not related to Constabulary is a personal argument and is not a crime. If it is not specific as to why you are calling a Constable an idiot your insult can be interrupted by the Constable as disrespect.)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Spitting on a Constable.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Speaking out against the Constabulary as a whole.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Disrespecting Higher Stations\</h3\>\\r\\nAny remark or action that shows an overt lack of respect to one's rank and title. This only applies to gentry and above. Drawing weapons against a Noble is a greater offense and shall be counted as Assault.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Failing to show deference in Newtown, calling ranked person names.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Spitting on or towards person.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Harassing or heckling.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Disturbing the Peace\</h3\>\\r\\nAny lewd or inflammatory act committed in a public place to either incite peaceful citizenry, to display blatant disregard for public decency, or unsettle public order.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Egging on fights, screaming at people, walking around nude.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Improprietous public displays of affection, failing to cease a disruptive action when asked to stop.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Calling fire in a public area, inciting a riot.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Heresy\</h3\>\\r\\nThe worship or preaching of a forbidden heresy. This specifically means the 'Old Faith' of Lutara, explicitly denying the tenants of S'allumer, and practicing black magic.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Lingering in forbidden groves, wearing symbols of other faith.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Participating in forbidden rituals, dealing in death magic.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Compromising one's soul.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Illegal Detainment\</h3\>\\r\\nArresting suspects or criminals and detaining them without a legal warrant of arrest issued by a magistrate or by disallowed 24 detainment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Constable arresting a criminal without a warrant.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Militia acting without a warrant.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Someone who hasn't taken an oath to the Constabulary or Militia arresting a criminal.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Kidnapping\</h3\>\\r\\nKidnapping is the taking away of a person by force, threat, or deceit, with intent to cause them to be detained against their will. Further charges of assault may be applied to cases where the kidnapping was violent.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Coercing someone to follow you, threatening someone harm if they do not come with you.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Tying someone up and leaving them in a private room, luring a child away with candy or toy with intent to trap.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Using force or violence to take one person away.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Littering\</h3\>\\r\\nThis is the act of dropping unwanted items on the ground instead of in the trash can and walking away.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Throwing trash in parks in Newtown.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Dropping fishing junk on the docks.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Intentionally spreading filth.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Murder\</h3\>\\r\\nThe willful (non-negligent) killing of one person by another. In incidents that lead to a death as a result of self-defense or defense of another, a charge of murder can be applied. (ooc: Only deaths committed by the \\"kill\\" command are considered \\"willful\\" deaths IE, the person who uses the \\"kill\\" command on another person is the one legally responsible for their death, even if a third person gave all the injuries.)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Defending someone including protecting yourself from an attack where the result is death. ( However, if there are witnesses that they were defending someone from an attack rather than trying to willfully kill, that counts as evidence of innocence.) \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Beating someone to death, inappropriate medical practices that lead to a persons death.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Stabbing someone to death, riots that result in death.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Possession of Forbidden Items or Substance\</h3\>\\r\\nPossession or consumption of any substance or item deemed illegal by the guild council. The selling/buying of any such item fulls under this crime.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Having someone buy illegal substance/item for you. \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Possession or consumption of an illegal substance/item.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Selling/buying an illegal substance/item.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Property Damage\</h3\>\\r\\nDamage or destruction done to public or private property, caused by a person who is not its owner. (In cases of slaves and serfs, the slave is an extension of their owner and may not be charged with any crime. Their owners take full and total responsibility of their actions and are thus liable for all and any crime committed by their slave/serf.)  \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Beating someone else's slave, urinating on someone's private property or public property. \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Dying or defacing someone's private property or public property.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Killing someone else's slave, burning someone else's property or public property\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Public Prostitution\</h3\>\\r\\nThe act or advertising of prostitution in public areas fulls under this law. (ooc: This means that the cathouse and private rooms are fine for such rp.)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Asking people to be a prostitute in public places. \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Advertising in public or on the forums.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Public lewdness .\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Resisting a Constable\</h3\>\\r\\nAny attempt to evade or assault a Constable performing a dutiful arrest or ignoring an official summons.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Running away from a Constable, refusing to be escorted.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - ignoring a summons either as a wittness or as a criminal. (Only applies if it's IG. Being away from game lengthily while having a summons does not count against you.) \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Beating or fighting a Constable who is trying to arrest you.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Theft\</h3\>\\r\\nThe taking and removing of personal property with intent to deprive the rightful owner of it. If goods are returned, the severity of the charge may be reduced. In cases of robbery where force is used or damage to the stolen property, additional charges may be included.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Refusing to return house/guild property after leaving. \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Pickpocketing.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Plucking items from the dead.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Treason\</h3\>\\r\\nPlotting or taking action against the Don while a citizen or guest in his city.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Trespassing\</h3\>\\r\\nEntering any private or restricted areas without permission.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Example:\</b\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Minor - Entering private inn rooms because the door was open. (this is generally ooc based but if you enter a room that is not yours and you mess with anything this applies to you.) \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Normal - Going into the Church while excommunicated.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Major - Entering the manors while blacklisted.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:militia information">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\> Current Militia Members \</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Active:\</h3\>\\r\\n- Lord Cross, House of Rinaldi \<br\>\\r\\n- Lady Kilana, House of Rinaldi \<br\>\\r\\n- Miss Mitena, House of Rinaldi \<br\>\\r\\n- Lord Ralston, House of Bisclavret \<br\>\\r\\n- Miss Aneira, House of Bisclavret \<br\>\\r\\n- Mister Jardskjalfti, House of Bisclavret \<br\>\\r\\n- Sir Trevyn, House of Doloreaux \<br\>\\r\\n- Mister Sturm, House of Doloreaux \<br\>\\r\\n- Baron Albéric Avoirdupois, House of Avoirdupois \<br\>\\r\\n- Mister Roofus Black, Black Company \<br\>\\r\\n- Esquire Brenner du Prideaux, House of Avoirdupois \<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<B\>Those who wish to join, or believe they already have an application with the Militia, or wish to make a correction to the list of active Militia are encouraged to contact Guardsman Albers or Detective Nikona\</b\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Militia Application Form\</h2\>\\r\\nFull Name:\<br\>\\r\\nDate:\<br\>\\r\\nAge:\<br\>\\r\\nPlace of birth:\<br\>\\r\\nArrived in Triskellian:\<br\>\\r\\nAffiliations:\<br\>\\r\\nCriminals Convictions:\<br\>\\r\\nReason for wanting to join:\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:recruiting:  database">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Recruit Training Database =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here is a tracking system for the training progress of the Constabulary recruits.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Blank Recruiting Template\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nRecruit Name: Y/N \<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 1 Sent: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nApplication Received: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\n3 Letters of Reference Received: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nInterview Completed By: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 2 Sent: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Kit Given: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Induction: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 1 - Basic Comportment: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 2 - Laws \& Charges: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 3 - Duties and Rounds: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 4 - How to File Reports: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 5 - Arrests, Cells and Prisoners: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3 Sent: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Kit Given: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Induction: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Training Complete\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nRecruit Name: Roofus\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 1 Sent: Y 8/20/2016\<br\>\\r\\nApplication Received: Y\<br\>\\r\\n3 Letters of Reference Received: Y\<br\>\\r\\nInterview Completed By: Tribune Namor\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 2 Sent: Y\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Kit Given: Y\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Induction: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 1 - Basic Comportment: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 2 - Laws \& Charges: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 3 - Duties and Rounds: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 4 - How to File Reports: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 5 - Arrests, Cells and Prisoners: Y\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3 Sent: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Kit Given: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Induction: Y\<br\>\\r\\nOath sworn: Y\<br/\>\\r\\nOath received by: Kegan \<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTraining Incomplete\\r\\n\<b\>Current Recruits\<br\>\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\nRecruit Name: Orto \<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 1 Sent: Y 12/27/2014\<br\>\\r\\nApplication Received: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\n3 Letters of Reference Received: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nInterview Completed By: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 2 Sent: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Kit Given: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Induction: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 1 - Basic Comportment: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 2 - Laws \& Charges: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 3 - Duties and Rounds: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 4 - How to File Reports: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 5 - Arrests, Cells and Prisoners: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3 Sent: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Kit Given: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Induction: Y/N\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nRecruit Name: Nerezza\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 1 Sent: Y 6/30/2016\<br\>\\r\\nApplication Received: Y\<br\>\\r\\n3 Letters of Reference Received: N\<br\>\\r\\nInterview Completed By: Namor\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 2 Sent: N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Kit Given: N\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Induction: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 1 - Basic Comportment: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 2 - Laws \& Charges: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 3 - Duties and Rounds: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 4 - How to File Reports: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 5 - Arrests, Cells and Prisoners: N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3 Sent: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Kit Given: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Induction: N\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nRecruit Name: Dakota O'Conchobhair \<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 1 Sent: Y 11/10/2018\<br\>\\r\\nApplication Received: Y\<br\>\\r\\n3 Letters of Reference Received: Y\<br\>\\r\\nInterview Completed By: Carrot\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 2 Sent: Y\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Kit Given: Y\<br\>\\r\\nProbationary Deputy Induction: Y\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 1 - Basic Comportment: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 2 - Laws \& Charges: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 3 - Duties and Rounds: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 4 - How to File Reports: N\<br\>\\r\\nLesson 5 - Arrests, Cells and Prisoners: N\<br\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3 Sent: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Kit Given: N\<br\>\\r\\nDeputy Induction: N\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:recruiting:  lesson 1 ">
         (\{ "members", "Our guild policy is to do the best that we can. And eat pudding. Lots of pudding." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:recruiting: standard letters">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>= Standard Letters for Recruit Training =\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nListed here are copies of standardized letters for Recruit training progress updates.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\nRecruiting Letter 1\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nFuture Recruit,\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThank you for your interest in a career with the Triskellian Constabulary.  In order to proceed with your interest, please submit the following:\<br\>\\r\\n...This completed application\<br\>\\r\\n...Three letters of reference from established citizens\<br\>\\r\\n...Interview with Constabulary officer\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nName: \<br\>\\r\\nTime in City:\<br\>\\r\\nPast Employment:\<br\>\\r\\nCriminal History:\<br\>\\r\\nMartial Background:\<br\>\\r\\nWhy Join Constables?\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nRecruiting Letter 2\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nRecruit,\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCongratulations!  If you are receiving this letter, then your application, letters of reference and interview with a Constabulary officer were all considered satisfactory.  You will now be considered a Probationary Deputy of the Triskellian Constabulary.  \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe first phase of your training will focus on your martial combat abilities, basic investigative practices, and the day-to-day duties of a Deputy in the Triskellian Constabulary.  Please be advised that while many undertake this path, not all are successful in completion of the curriculum.  It will require dedication, commitment, and perseverance to complete this training.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nYou are ordered to report to the Sheriff for your regalia and proper induction as a Probationary Deputy.  Please respond with your waking times, so that the officers of the Constabulary can schedule your training most appropriately.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nStandard Letter 3\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nProbationary Deputy,\\r\\n\\r\\nCongratulations!  If you are receiving this letter, then you have successfully completed the training required for induction as a full Deputy Constable in the Triskellian Constabulary.  You are ordered to report to the Sheriff for your regalia and proper induction as a full Deputy Constable.  Please respond with your waking times, so that your induction may be scheduled most efficiently.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1571341392, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
