<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#0000ff", "bgcolor2":"#ffffff", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Arial", "h1color":"#000000", "h1type":"Arial", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Arial", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Arial" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:becoming a knight - squire duties">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Becoming a Knight - Squire duties\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe boys who trained to be knights were generally the sons of knights or lords. (In some cases, the sons of commoners could train for knighthood) These children were cared for by the women of the castle until they turned 7, when they were placed in the house of another lord or knight. There, they were bestowed with the title of page. Huntsmen and falconers taught them how to hunt, and priests or chaplains taught them religion, reading and writing. Pages learned to fight by imitating knights and practised combat with each other using wooden swords and lances.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen a page turned 14, he could become an squire. In a religious ceremony, the new squire took a consecrated sword from a bishop or priest and swore to use it for religious and honourable purposes. After this ceremony, the squire took his place in his lord's household and attended to his duties. There were different squires for specific duties.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n- The squire of the body was the personal servant of a knight or his lady.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The squire of the chamber, or chamberlain, attended to the rooms of the castle.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The carving squire, or table squire, carved the meat and attended to the banquet tables.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The squire of the wines managed the wine cellar.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The squire of the pantry stocked and kept track of household goods in the pantry.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The squire of arms cleaned and maintained the armour and swords.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The squire of honour assisted the lord in all ceremonies and feasts.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDuring this period of squiring, the would-be knight learned to serve and mastered the intricacies of social behaviour and chivalry.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBesides carrying out their duties in the lord's household, squires learned the martial arts of being a knight. They learned how to handle horses and continued practising with wooden swords and lances -- sometimes with the knights themselves. They wore chain-mail armour to get used to its weight (and sometimes even danced in hauberks, or chain-mail shirts). As they got older, they exercised and trained in full armour. Squires would also assist the knights in combat, at tournaments and in travel to foreign lands (carrying and cleaning armour, taking care of the knight's horses, packing baggage).\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<strong\>The typical jobs of a squire included:\</strong\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Carrying the knight's armour, shield and sword\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Guarding prisoners\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Freeing the knight when taken captive\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Ensuring an honorable burial for a deceased knight\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Replacing lost or damaged equipment\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Replacing an injured or killed mount\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dressing the knight in armour\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Carrying the knight's flag\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Protecting the knight\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Taking care of the mounts\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Accompanying the knight to tournaments and the battlefield\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Maintaining the knight's equipment\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nUpon turning 21, a squire was ready to be knighted." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:becoming a knight - the knighting ceremony">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>The Knighting Ceremony\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSquires were usually invested as knights during one of the great feasts or holidays, like Christmas or Easter. Sometimes the ceremony took place on another special occasion, such as the wedding of a noble or royal. The king, nobles, knights and clergy or the squire's father (if he were a knight) could confer knighthood.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe knighting ceremony usually involved a ritual bath on the eve of the ceremony (the would-be knight usually dressed in white). Then an all-night prayer vigil would begin, sometimes with the squire's arms on the altar. The kneeling squire would swear an oath, which included some of the following points:\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n- He would always defend a lady.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would speak only the truth.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would be loyal to his lord.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would be devoted to the church.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would be charitable and defend the poor and helpless.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would be brave.\<br/\>\\r\\n- When on a quest, he would remove his armor and arms only while sleeping.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would never avoid dangerous paths out of fear.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would be on time for any engagement of arms, like a battle or tournament.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Upon returning to his home or lord's court from an adventure, he would always tell of his escapades.\<br/\>\\r\\n- If taken prisoner, he would give up his arms and horse to his opponent and not fight the opponent again without the opponent's consent.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He would fight only one-on-one against an opponent.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThen the master of the ceremony would dub the new knight on the shoulders with a sword. The knight would then dress in armor, receive his sword, mount his horse and participate in some martial games to demonstrate his skills as part of the celebration.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn times of war, a squire who had demonstrated exceptional bravery in battle could be knighted on the battlefield by another knight.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWith knighthood came several privileges. Knights obtained the title \\"sir.\\" They could own land, hire soldiers to defend it and dispense justice over the soldiers and those living on the land. They -- and their horses -- could wear armor in battle (armor was expensive, so only knights could afford it). During feasts, banquets and dinners, knights had places at the high table, where lords and royals ate. They could also bear arms inside a church because they were defenders of God and the church.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn times of war, knights were called to arms by their lords or by the king. They led foot soldiers and archers into battle, much like modern officers do with enlisted men. During peacetime, knights managed their estates, dispensed justice, trained for battle and participated in tournaments." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:becoming a knight - training and lessons">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Training and Lessons\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThere are many things a knight needs to learn in order to become an honourable knight.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Martial Skills\</h3\>\<br/\>\\r\\nA knight needs to be capable to fight and defend in order to uphold is oaths and his purpose. In times of peace, skills can be upheld through tournaments, often honouring others, such as the ruler or a maiden.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Useful skills:\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n- Dodge and parry to avoid getting hit in a fight.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Mastering a weapon, and preferably a second weapon. Sword or rapier for an honourable duel. The second weapon for back-up should the first be lost or broken.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Riding, both for swift travel, but also for the tournaments.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Armour and shield, for defensive measures, both in combat and at tournaments.\<br\>\\r\\n- Unarmed - In the instance that a weapon is broken or Knight disarmed. Being able to defend the self and others by any means is necessity.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Social skills\</h3\>\\r\\n- Dancing \<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<img src=\\"https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wIjl_ieoPy0/ViAsE37ZxgI/AAAAAAAAIkA/nywPXrrfcYc/w319-h279-no/dasha_arms.png\\" style=\\"float:right\\"\>Our oath and purpose is: \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n- To smile and laugh or to put on the face of war, each in its due season.\<br/\>\\r\\n- To always act with Honour, whether in the company of the Mighty or the Low.\<br/\>\\r\\n- To ensure Fairness and bring Justice where it is lacking.\<br/\>\\r\\n- To serve Right before Might in all circumstances, and to do Right especially when doing so is the most difficult.\<br/\>\\r\\n- To serve as a shining example of true Knighthood, and to uphold the Knightly Virtues.\<br/\>\\r\\n- To be loyal to the Don, and serve to the best of our abilities.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOur crest is the ancient di Silvi crest, given when the forefather was granted knighthood for his services upon the battlefield, embodying all the knightly values:\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA crest of a stylized argent, five-petalled wild rose, underlined by an argent horizontal sword upon a field of azure.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe symbolism is: \<br/\>\\r\\nAzure field: Truth and Loyalty, Strength and Steadfastness \<br/\>\\r\\nArgent rose: Love and Faith \<br/\>\\r\\nArgent sword: Protection, Courage, Sincerity, Justice and Military Honour \<br/\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 1. definition">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>1. Definition\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDueling is a traditional form of resolving personal disputes through a contest of arms, the rules of which are predetermined by both parties beforehand. When one party perceives an insult, or slight to their honor, they may decide to challenge the offender to settle the issue through combat.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhat passes as a slight is largely a personal matter, but typical reasons for issuing a challenge include an insult to one's person, family, affiliation or a question of one's moral character." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 2. procedure">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>2. Procedure\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe procedures of a formal duel can be separated in the challenge itself, the election of a second, the definition of the terms, the optional designation of a neutral marshal, the combat, and the final resolution.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.1. Challenge\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe offended party should publicly issue the challenge in the presence of the offender and witnesses, the moment the former learns or perceives injury to their honor. Should there be nobody else present, a public notice on the boards may be announced.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe challenged party should either offer an apology suitable to the slight, or accept the challenge. A refusal to comply in either way is a mark of dishonorable conduct, unless there is a large difference in social status between both parties (this is covered later in the essay, in article 4).\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.2 Seconds\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOnce a duel has been accepted, both parties each elect a second, who act as representatives in the definition of the terms of the duel and prevent the primaries from further interaction until the matter has been settled.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSeconds also have the function of counseling their primaries into following the formal procedures of the duel and to advise for reasonable terms, at a time in which reason may be clouded by strong emotions.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn some cases, a second may act as a champion in the primary's stead if the latter possesses no martial training or is physically unable to conduct the duel. It is also common to designate a champion specifically for this purpose while the second retains their traditional duties.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.3 Terms\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe terms include three aspects: the demands upon victory, the place and time of the duel, and the rules of combat.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTypically, a public apology upon defeat is deemed sufficient\&#8203; to put the matter at rest. In more egregious offenses, a certain course of action may be demanded by the challenger, such as resigning from a position, or severing ties with a guild. These latter examples are, however, a notorious exception.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe place of the duel should be suitable for clean combat, and be unobtrusive to normal city life. A training courtyard is best recommended for these cases. A fixed time to appear on the location should be agreed upon in which primaries can both be present with their respective seconds.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe rules of combat may encompass matching weapons, though it is generally preferred to let the opponent use the style they feel most comfortable with. The rules also should establish how the combat should end, tradition dictating that first blood is an acceptable condition, though it is just as common to duel until the opponent submits. In the most egregious of cases, duelists may declare a duel to the death.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.4 Marshaling\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhile not obligatory in a formal duel, designating a neutral marshal may be desired by one of the primaries. The marshal conducts the procedures of the combat, observing that the participants fight fairly, signaling the beginning of the duel, announcing successful strikes, and the conclusion of combat.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nFor this reason, a marshal should be elected based both on their martial knowledge as well as their fair judgment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.5 Combat\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nShould one of the parties fail to present themselves at the agreed time and location, then the duel is declared forfeit and the missing party deemed a coward.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nUpon meeting at the agreed time and location, the seconds present each other their primaries' weapons for examination and approval, so that the blades are deemed to be in order and free of poisons. One custom sees the duelists kiss their own weapons in order to demonstrate that they have not been dipped in poison.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThe weapons are passed on to their primaries, who stand before each other at the center of the arena at a distance of approximately twenty paces. Once their primaries are in position, combat may begin at the signal of the challenger's second, or a marshal if one has been named.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIt is well regarded for primaries to respectfully salute with their weapons before settling into a guarding stance.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen blood is drawn. The marshal, or a second, may signal the strike. If combat was set to first blood, then victory conditions have been met. Otherwise, the fight will come to a pause and the fighters will go back to their starting positions. The one being struck will be asked to state their desire to submit or carry on the fight. If the latter, combat resumes at the signal of the marshal, or the second.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nShould a combatant leave the boundaries of the arena, or flee the fight altogether, they will have the duel forfeit and deemed a coward. The same occurs if one of the duelists is found to use poisons or deceitful tactics during the fight.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>2.6 Resolution\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOnce combat is ruled to be over, the defeated party is expected to perform as previously agreed on the terms. If an apology has been requested, it is usually delivered on the spot and, if necessary, posted on the public boards as well.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen the terms have been met, both duelists can put the matter behind them and hold no ill will against each other, as they both have proven to conduct themselves civilly and honorably.\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 3. pistol duels">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h3\>3. Pistol duels\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWith the advent of gunpowder, and much to the opposition of master swordsmen and women, some duelists have chosen pistols as their preferred method instead of blades. Should one decide upon this course of action, it is recommended to use similar pistols so that no duelist is at an unfair disadvantage.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nTo begin the duel, the primaries should stand back to back at the center of the arena with pistol in hand. They then take twelve steps forwards, counted by one of the seconds or the marshal, and upon the last step they turn and shoot. In the event that both miss, they are prompted to reload and repeat the procedure." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 4. matters of station">
         (\{ "members", "\<h3\>4. Matters of Station\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDuels usually take place among folk of similar social status. It is largely considered improper to challenge someone several steps above or below your station. In the event that a Noble is challenged by a commoner it is not only acceptable, but also expected for the Noble to ignore the challenge altogether, as those of higher rank have nothing to prove to those far beneath them.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSimilarly, it is not expected for a Noble person to challenge a commoner, as an insult towards a Noble would be grounds for elevating charges of Disrespect for Higher Stations.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHowever, should a Noble accept a challenge from a commoner it will be seen as a gracious of them to allow a commoner to defend their person in this manner, and a compliment towards the commoner's demeanor." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 5. recommendations">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h3\>5. Recommendations\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIf at all possible, arrange for a healer to be present at the moment of the duel. This ensures that wounds may be tended to in a timely fashion, though it should be noted that the duelists may receive treatment only once a victor has been declared.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDress accordingly. Duels should be fought in a proper and unobtrusive attire.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMake sure that the area you have picked for the duel is properly cleared, so that no accidents may occur.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhen partaking of a duel, remain respectful at all times. Salute your opponent, refrain from controversial remarks, and conduct yourself with honor.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs a second, counsel your primary to the best of your abilities. Let them know if the terms they are proposing are unreasonable, or if they behave in a way that reflects poorly upon them.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs an onlooker, be respectful of tradition. Do not shout, yell, or distract the duelists while they perform." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 6. legal controversy">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h3\>6. Legal controversy\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhile a widely regarded tradition in Calabria, discussions of outlawing duels have been brought up on occasion and, in the City of Triskellian, the Constabulary's terms technically punishes the practice of duels.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHowever, an unanimous acceptance of this law has never been established, as high ranking members of the Houses have at times publicly voiced their support for the dueling tradition, and the dishonor perceived by ignoring a challenge is still tangible.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDue to its historical relevance and the importance of civilly settling matters of honor, duels are likely to be allowed to happen if proper form is respected. Failing to do so comes with the possibility of having charges of Disturbing the Peace elevated upon your person.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe reader is counseled to be mindful of local traditions if they intend to participate in the honorable practice of dueling.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nAn old practice, so as to prove that your own blade has not been tampered with poisons, was to kiss it before it is presented to your opponent." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:formal duels: 7. about the author">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>7. About the author\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe writings of this book correspond to Rinaldi Private Callais du Chalon-sur-Sauldre, aspiring Squire to Dame Dasha di Silvi, Brigadier of the Royal Rinaldi Army and founder of the di Silvi Academy.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis text is a result of Mister Callais' studies on fencing in Chalon, as well as his experiences in the City of Triskellian serving in the Rinaldi Guard under Captain Marcus and his apprenticeship under Dame Dasha.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nPenned in the year of 898, in the month of Grass." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "The purpose of the Academy is to train and educate people to behave as and eventually become honourable knights.\<br/\>Anyone who wishes to embody the Academy Manifest and the Knightly Virtues are welcome to join. Contact Dame Dasha for further information.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<img src=\\"https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wIjl_ieoPy0/ViAsE37ZxgI/AAAAAAAAIkA/nywPXrrfcYc/w319-h279-no/dasha_arms.png\\" style=\\"float:right\\";\>\\r\\nOur values are based on the Three Principles and the Eight Virtues\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Three Principles:\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Truth\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Love\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Courage\</strong\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThe 8 Knightly Virtues:\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Honesty\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Compassion\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Valour\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Justice\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Sacrifice\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Honour\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Spirituality\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<strong\>Humility\</strong\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:heraldric blazons - what coats of arms mean">
         (\{ "members", "\<font color=red\>===Work In Progress==\</font\>\</br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHeraldry is the practice of devising, granting, displaying, describing, and recording coats of arms and heraldic badges. Officers of arms (Kings of Arms, Heralds and Pursuviants) practice heraldry and also rule on questions of rank or protocol.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHeraldry dates back as long as the chivalric honor of Knighthood and some say even before. It is a universal way that Knights and soldiers identify each other upon the field of battle, based on which standard they form rank under. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nLet us take a brief look at \<b\>di Silvi armorial bearings\</b\> otherwise known as a Blazon. \\r\\n\<br\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<img src=\\"https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wIjl_ieoPy0/ViAsE37ZxgI/AAAAAAAAIkA/nywPXrrfcYc/w319-h279-no/dasha_arms.png\\"\>\<br\>\<b\>di Silvi Blazon\</b\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWhen designing a Blazon (a correct description of armorial bearings), see example above, it is important to remember the Rule of Contrast which will be discussed later. As such, you can take any metal or fur (tinctures) and set them with colors for different meanings. In the \<b\>di Silvi Blazon\</b\> you see - A crest of a stylized argent, five-petalled wild rose, underlined by an argent horizontal sword upon a field of azure. \<br/\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWhat this means is the following: \\r\\n\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\nArgent - Courage, Justice, Sincerity\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\nWild Rose - Beauty, Love, Purity, Passion\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\nHorizontal Sword - Power, Freedom, Military Honor\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\nAzure - Truth, Loyalty, Strength, Steadfastness\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nArgent is the color of white/silver. Azure is the color of Blue. So this is a silver/white wild rose, underlined with a silver/white sword on a field of blue. \<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</hr\>\\r\\n\</br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThere are many different Blazons to choose from.  If you plan to go to battle, you should seek out a shield or flag that is easy to read from afar. \<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nFirst, early coats of arms are simple because they were original and there were so few of them that elaborate differentiation was not required. More complex designs can be used to discern a specific Knight's blazonry.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSecond, punning, or canting, arms are very common, and it is notable, however, that many armorial allusions that were formerly obvious now require research for elucidation. Other allusions have been lost entirely.  This is due to the fact that so many Knights required a simple change for their Blazon to be different from another's.  Many Knights wish to Blazon their shields in the same way, requiring that, for example, a shape or line of Honor be included.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThird, in grants of arms to people bearing the same name but having no relationship with each other, difference marks were included. Again, in consequence, Blazons have become much more complicated. Like all other human creations, heraldic art has reflected the changes of fashion.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBelow are some of the more Ordinary Blazons that Kings, Queens, Knights, Soldiers choose. The reasons are their own, but being seen from far away they can tell quite a bit about who is battling, and who owns and/or claims what.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<img src=\\"http://www.underconsideration.com/speakup/archives/su_heraldry2.gif\\"\>\<br\>\<b\>Ordinary Blazons\</b\>\</img\>\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHeraldry developed the concept of this phrase: this specified the natures of certain charges, lines of division, postures, and placements. The purpose was to have the charges, tinctures, and other such details blazoned in such an order that there could be no doubt as to their arrangement, in the shield and in relation to one another.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h\>These orders are:\</h\>\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n(1) Field.\<br\>\\r\\n(2) Primary charges.\<br\>\\r\\n(3) Secondary charges immediately around (2).\<br\>\\r\\n(4) Tertiary charges on (2) or (3).\<br\>\\r\\n(5) Peripheral secondary charges.\<br\>\\r\\n(6) Tertiary charges on (5).\<br\>\\r\\n(7) Brisures.\<br\>\\r\\n(8) Augmentations.\<br/\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCharges are Blazoned in the above order; this order reflects the visual importance of each group of charges.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n 1. The blazon must be accurate. All necessary details should be blazoned. The type of charge, its posture, its tincture -- anything, if not the default, that counts for heraldic difference must be specified.\<br\>\\r\\n 2. The blazon must be unambiguous, unequivocal. The purpose of the blazon, after all, is to make possible the reconstruction of the emblazon. Ideally, a blazon should be capable of only one interpretation. A blazon that may be interpreted in more than one way is fatally flawed.\<br\>\\r\\n 3. The blazon should be elegant, euphonious. The blazon should be beautiful, as everything about heraldry should be beautiful. This is less important than the other two rules: if we must sacrifice elegance for precision, so be it. But if a blazon can be both accurate and elegant, so much the better.\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n Many blazons can be simplified by using active, rather than passive terms. \<u\>A ship, sail unfurled and facing sinister is \<i\>passive\</i\>;\</u\>\<u\> a ship sailing to sinister is \<b\>active\</b\>,\</u\> with the same picture in fewer words. \<u\>A savage maintaining over his head a club bendwise inverted is \<i\>passive and awkward\</i\>\</u\>;\<u\> a savage brandishing a club is \<b\>active\</b\>\</u\>, concise, and avoids over-blazoning the club.\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n Now, having your shield, your flag, or your men Blazoned with your specifications is a plus, and makes you well known as a King, Queen, or Knight.  You should make your decisions on your shield, your flag, or your soldiers clear enough to read, but with all the frills that you deem necessary for you to be known." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:honourable role models">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Honourable Role Models\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis is a list of people whom serve as good role models for knightly behaviour. Anyone can be nominated and listed. Their knightly qualities should be listed so they can serve as an example for others.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<strong\>Sir Kaine\</strong\> is an example:\<br/\>\\r\\n- He has high integrity and keeps his word.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He keeps his promises.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is loyal to his principles and his House.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is willing to sacrifice himself for the greater good.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<strong\>Sir Marcus\</strong\> is an example:\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is honest and truthful.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He has integrity and upholds his promises and oaths.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is loyal to his friends and his house.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is humble and doesn't brag.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<strong\>Lord Romain\</strong\> is an example:\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is gallant and considerate.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He has proper skills and always a kind word for all.\<br/\>\\r\\n- He is honourable and keeps his word with integrity and compassion. \<br/\>\\r\\n- He is loyal to his house and his principles. \</br\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:knightly virtues">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>The Three Principles\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe eight virtues are derived from the three principles of Truth, Love, and Courage. All that is good, or done with good intent, derives from the three principles.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Truth\</h3\>\\r\\nTruth is the truth that is inherent in all things. It is the truth that we discover when we are able to see clearly, free from other distractions.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Love\</h3\>\\r\\nLove is the love that we find in our hearts for all things. Love is what drives us to do acts of kindness. To love is to see beauty and joy all around.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Courage\</h3\>\\r\\nCourage is strength of spirit and determination to act for the greater good. Courage to never give up, and to face overwhelming odds bravely.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>The 8 virtues\</h2\>\\r\\nThese three principles, either separately, or in combination, form the virtues:\<br/\>\\r\\nFrom Truth comes \<strong\>Honesty\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nFrom Love comes \<strong\>Compassion\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nFrom Courage comes \<strong\>Valour\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nTruth and Love combined create \<strong\>Justice\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nLove and Courage combined create \<strong\>Sacrifice\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nCourage and Truth combined create \<strong\>Honour\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nFrom Truth, Love, and Courage comes \<strong\>Spirituality\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\nPride is caused by the absence of the Three Principles, the opposite of Pride is \<strong\>Humility\</strong\>.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Honesty\</h3\>\\r\\nHonesty is respect for Truth. A dishonest life brings unto thee a temporary gain, but forsakes the permanent.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAn honest soul need remember no lies. A few honest men are better than numbers. Speak the truth and shame the evil forces. \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA Knight is to be truthful and sincere. Honesty is a straightforwardness of conduct and speech. It is the freedom from fraud or guile that marks a knight with a strong integrity and sincerity in nature and word. A Knight should always be someone in whom you can place your trust.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHonesty and Integrity are key in the life of a Knight. This much can be taken from our sworn oath, (A knight knows only virtue, his words speak only the truth.) Honesty, however, is not only given in words, Honesty to ones self, and to one's heart are important as well. A knight must follow the correct and righteous course of action in all his deeds. This also means that if a knight should have a problem, he or she should express as such, keeping true and honest to his heart and mind. While this may not change what the knight has a problem with, he has been true to himself and all others involved.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight wields honesty in his endeavours across the land, as the beacon to light his path.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHonesty's temperance: To not tell a suffering mother who has lost her son, that he has died in long protracted agony because it is the truth, we show compassion so that her suffering not run as deep.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Compassion\</h3\>\\r\\nCompassion is Love of others. Only a detested life owes its pleasures to another's pain.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIf you treat someone else well then they will have reason to do the same.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTo be compassionate one must be aware of another's suffering and wish to relieve it. Might alone does not make right, it is the goodness and compassion behind the sword that makes the right. Tis we who are the master of the sword, not the sword the master of us.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDo not let the blade's thirst for vengeance and retribution leech from you the compassion that is the balance of our vow.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWe cannot be right when there is only might. Seek within yourself to find the reasons behind the blade and open your hearts to compassion.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight must always use compassion as a gauge to judge his actions. Enemies may repent, and allies may need patience, or to be saved. It is important that the Knight remembers that no mortal is perfect, by nature, we will make mistakes. A knight must always gauge his actions, and incorporate compassion into his decisions. While a foe that chooses to combat a knight, shows he has accepted the consequence of his actions, one who is engaged first by the knight should be shown the chance for repentance.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight is compassionate in all his dealings, and as such, is a guiding force for Goodness in the world.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCompassion's temperance: To be too compassionate may open one up to abuse of one's good nature, and to create a dependence upon one which might learn to become independent. In honestly placing a threshold on ones compassion will those who would be independent derive more benefit.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Valour\</h3\>\\r\\nValour is Courage to stand up against risk. Those who fear to try, know not their limits and thus know not themselves.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe valiant soul fears not its own visage. True valor is seen not in the force of arms, but in the force of will!\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe intangible kith and kin to courage, to be valiant in heart and deed is to seek excellence in all endeavors expected of a knight. To boldly step upon the path, grasping courage and faith in equal measures. Encounter danger with firmness, prowess, intrepidity in equal parts with justice. To be valiant is to hold a fear of base or unworthy things and harbour a spark of boldness.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight stands up for what he believes in at all times, even should he be standing alone. The Valour of the knight is well known across the land, and should always be maintained. To be valiant, is to stride forth and stand boldly for your belief in Goodness, using Justice, Honour, Compassion, and Honesty in equal parts. A knight does not necessarily need to succeed to show Valour, but can not truly succeed without showing valor. The code of the Knighthood forever shines, so long as the Valiant remain to hold it in their hearts.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight uses Valor in his stance against all that oppose him.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nValour's temperance: To not charge into the enemy with reckless valour because it is the bravest thing to do.  If one is expected to hold a line, one shows honour to ones brothers who are depending on one to hold that line.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Justice\</h3\>\\r\\nJustice is Truth, tempered by Love. Those who inflict injustice upon others, cannot expect fair treatment unto themselves.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTrue justice satisfies all, false none. Let justice be the calling not the excuse. Many a grave has been unjustly filled in the name of justice. Justice is truth in action. Justice is hardest to find at the point of a sword, the steel is an agent of justice, people are the perpetrators.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSeek always the path of right, unencumbered by bias or personal interest. Recognize that the sword of justice can be a terrible thing, so it must be tempered by humanity and mercy. Seek it out without bending to the temptation for expediency, the ends do not justify the means.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight is not a judge, a knight administers justice. He or she is a caretaker of justice, a bringer of judgement from the Gods. A knight meets out the sentence and is the harbinger of truth and goodness.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight rides out into the land, ever searching to bring Justice to those who serve malevolence. (His wrath undoes the wicked). Justice should always be what the Knight seeks when he rides out into Algoron. At all times the knight is required to be fair and just in his servitude to the Light. When going into battle, a knight must serve Justice, not vengeance, or hatred. Though our battles are tough, we fight because we mean to bring justice, not because we mean to slay or maim our foes. A repented enemy is far greater than a slain one, in any case. A Knight uses justice as the tool of his Lord or Ladies will. With it he strikes fear into his enemies, and hope into those he serves.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nJustice's temperance: To give out harsh penalties for petty crime is not justice, the crime ought to have fitting punishment. In some cases one should show lenience towards reform, as well as one who executes justice to the letter of the law. All ought to be accountable to the law, for it governs us all.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Sacrifice\</h3\>\\r\\nSacrifice is Courage to give oneself in the name of Love. None live alone, save they who will not share their fortune with those around them.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSelf preservation is the first law of nature, self sacrifice the highest rule of grace.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA Knight sacrifices all - life and liberty for the one and only war. The Knight forfeits everything to protect and defend the helpless. A Knight thinks only of gain in his or her service regardless of personal loss.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight knows Sacrifice more than most others in the realm. A knight is ready and willing to give up all he has for the one war in which we serve. A knight must be prepared to give even his life, as Sir Gunnar did to seal the rift. Sacrifice comes not to please those it is given for, it is meant to show that the knight values what he is doing, more than what he has, and is willing to give what he has, to further what he is doing. A knight can speak about how he is willing to serve and give himself, but as is the case with all things, actions speak louder than words.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight sacrifices all that he has to better the one, true war.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSacrifice's temperance: To give too much of ones self without due provocation will limit ones ability to fulfil ones duty as a Knight of Gareth. One must give of oneself as one must, but to be strong for another day where one may then give oneself again.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Honour\</h3\>\\r\\nHonour is Courage to seek and uphold the Truth. It is the guilt, not the guillotine, that constitutes the shame.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHonour is like finely polished armour. Without constant care, it will soon tarnish! Honour gives greatness - No honour, no meaning. Dignity consists not in possessing honours, but in deserving them.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTo be honourable in thought and deed. To maintain a principled uprightness of character, a personal integrity, dignity that neither strife nor hardship can waver. Honour is a virtue that can be and should be infused into each of the virtues, a courtesy that emanates from the spirit and infuses each habit.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBe respectful and gentle with equals, honour superiors, and show consideration to all. To live in a manner so that your deeds and person are not called into question and only favourably reflected upon.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHonour is perhaps one of the single most important thing a Knight must maintain in his actions. (To be noble in word and deed, to be a Champion) A knight's honour should be the single greatest thing he is known for. A success in combat is not a success if it is attained through dishonourable means, nor is any success for that matter. A knight must consistently maintain his honour in all things. Everything from tactics in combat, to dealing with others throughout the land. A knight who takes shortcuts does not only undercut himself, but those he serves as well. Honour comes from within the knight, and it is not something to be adhered to, it is something that must be lived. If a knight has trouble with finding honour, he should look to his peers, for it is always strong there. A knight with honour will not gloat, or brag over his successes, but instead realizes he has been gifted success by the Family he serves, and will work to continue to enact Their will.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight uses honour not only as his armour against deceit and trickery, but as his weapon against it, and his sustenance in life as well.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHonour's temperance: To give ones enemy who is undeserving too much honour serves no purpose. Honour and respect are earned, not given freely. One must not allow a stronger evil enemy who is known to foully murder innocent children to recover his weapon which one has disarmed if he will best one in combat because he is stronger. For justice one must defeat him to allow the evil actions of this enemy to discontinue.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Spirituality\</h3\>\\r\\nSpirituality is to seek Truth, Love and Courage from one's own self and the world around. To forsake one's inner being is to abandon thy hopes for thyself and thy world.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSpiritual is stronger than any material force. If one speaks or acts with pure thought, happiness will follow like a shadow that never leaves. Success is a journey, not a destination. Remember, no one is useless in this world who lightens the burdens of others.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight must have faith in beliefs held, for faith is at the root of the tree of hope and the very foundations of these walls. Faith is the confident belief in the truth, value, and trustworthiness of our Gods, in ideals and in each other. It is a loyalty beyond measure, an allegiance of spirit. It is a virtue defined as a secure belief and a trusting acceptance of God's will and divine purpose.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHave faith in your Gods, have faith in each other and in yourself. Tend well the divine purpose of the true path, fortify the foundations and the walls will always stand.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOur spirituality is our driving force in all we do. Our very charge is to serve the Gods and Goddesses of light. Our faith shall forever carry us through our challenges, so long as we remain faithful to those we serve. A knight should always follow the teachings of his or her chosen Deity, and remain faithful to that Deity in all their dealings. If a knight loses touch with his spirituality, he loses touch with his oaths and responsibilities, and then has lost touch completely.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nNo said faith is more important than another, as all of the Holy Family enact their will through us, and they should all equally be served by their followers. One who does not serve their Deity, will find their Deity not serving them.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOur shield against all harm comes in the way of Spirituality, to quench the flaming arrows of malevolence, vengeance, murder, darkness, and rage.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSpirituality's temperance: To stand in the altar room and hear sermon, psalm, and to sing and pray are all very fine things. But to do so too much and with too much religious fever will cheapen the act of performing these actions themselves. Many pious souls who have stood too long in the temple, or spend all their time in communion and prayer leave no time for action of the Lord's good work. One must strike a balance in communion and action.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<hr/\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Humility\</h3\>\\r\\nHumility is the opposite of Pride - the absence of Truth, Love or Courage. Pride is a vice, which Pride itself inclines one to find in others, and overlook in oneself.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nPride is the surest measure of goals never attained. Humility is the virtue that must overcome pride. Humility is to act and be humble. The first test of a great soul is humility.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWithin our hearts lies a bell of truth that when we do right it rings with as sweet a tone as a chime sent from the heavens. This same bell rings in disharmony, discord when we do something against our vows and nature. An alarm to listen to, to sound the bell against vainglory and danger. We may have committed some wrong which needs setting right, to make amends and to demonstrate our continued service to the ideals which we uphold.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight goes further, accepting responsibility for the flaw and spurning the comfort of pinning the difficulty on someone else, and sets it right. There is great power in the humility to say I was wrong, or I am sorry should they be spoken with sincerity. It is turning a weakness to a strength.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHumility confers a grace and gentleness that does not denude from strength, courage, loyalty or any virtue of a knight. A quiet excellence that enhances the bearer and harmonizes them in their lack of boasts.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWe as knights must always remain humble. We must always remember we are here to serve a purpose much greater than ourselves. We serve the Lords and Ladies of the Pantheon of Good, and without their grace and gifts, we would not exist as we do. Though we act as vessels for Their will, we are just that, the tools that enact the will of the Holy Family. To hold ourselves in higher regard than those we serve, is a sin against that which we are taught.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA knight uses Humility as a shield against pride, and a bar to hold him on his righteous path.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHumility's temperance: To be too humble in the face of ones achievements contravenes the truth. If one has a special gift for organization of a task, then one must let others who enquire for expertise in this task, who is best placed to assist them.\<br/\>\<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571341392, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
