<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#ffcc00", "bgcolor2":"#003300", "bgimg1":"http://www.mobihop.com/mobile_wallpaper/green-animated-wallpaper.gif", "bgimg2":"http://www.kinghdwallpaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Black-and-Green-Abstract-Wallpaper.jpg", "fontcolor":"#ffcc00", "fonttype":"Georgia", "h1color":"#99cc00", "h1type":"Georgia", "h2color":"#99cc00", "h2type":"Georgia", "h3color":"#99cc00", "h3type":"Georgia" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:armory">
         (\{ "members", "Laquered hickory weapon rack:\<br\>\\r\\n1 double-bladed iron battle axe of average quality\<br\>1 Sheathed iron rapier of very good quality\<br\>1 Iron axe of average quality w/strap\<br\>1 iron axe of good quality w/ strap\<br\>1 sheathed iron scimitar of exceptional quality.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nLaquered hickory weapon rack #2:\<br\>1 sheathed iron sabre of very good quality\<br\>1sheathed iron longsword of very good quality\<br\>1 sheathed iron cutlass of very good quality\<br\>1 sheathed iron sword of bad quality\<br\>1 sheathed iron arming sword of average quality.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nHuge Oak Kasten:\<br\>two pairs of green leather greaves\<br\>an embossed dark green leather breastplate\<br\>two iron kite shields\<br\>three pairs of iron ailettes\<br\>three pairs of iron greaves\<br\>two pairs of iron bracers\<br\>a pair of emerald leather greaves\<br\>three embossed green leather cuirasses\<br\>a pair of light green leather greaves\<br\>an embossed wintergreen leather breastplate\<br\>an embossed light green leather cuirass\<br\>an embossed light green leather breastplate\<br\>an embossed emerald leather breastplate\<br\>a pair of emerald leather ailettes\<br\>three pairs of green leather ailettes\<br\>a pair of wintergreen leather bracers\<br\>a pair of green leather bracers\<br\>a pair of light green leather bracers\<br\>a pair of light green leather ailettes\<br\>an embossed green leather breastplate\<br\>four pairs of dark green leather bracers\<br\>two pairs of emerald leather bracers\<br\>four pairs of dark green leather greaves\<br\>four pairs of dark green leather ailettes\<br\>two embossed dark green leather cuirasses.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nMedium Oak Kasten:\<br\>a green cloak with an embroidered symbol\<br\>a bronze Doloreaux ring\<br\>two gold-embroidered jade Doloreaux uniforms\<br\>a tattered green frogskin cloak with an embroidered symbol\<br\>a dirt-encrusted green silk cloak with an embroidered symbol\<br\>a dirt-stained green lizardskin cloak with an embroidered symbol\<br\>a soil-encrusted green silk cloak with an embroidered symbol.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSmall Oak Kasten:\<br\>One mahongany shield\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nLoaned Items:\<br\>Bayork: one green leather Cuirass and a double-bladed Iron battle axe.\<br\>Jessica: One green leather cuirass.\<br\>Dieter: One single-bladed iron battle axe.\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:contracts">
         (\{ "members", "\\r\\nDrafted this Deardaoin, the twenty-fourth day of Hawthorn in the year of 897 Apres le Miracle\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis contract confirms that Esquire Baez von Hellewedge of Great House Doloreaux has named miss Lidia of Tresses and Treasures guild a favored trade partner, with Esquire Amalasanda and miss Luria as witnesses.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBoth parties have agreed on the following terms:\<br\>\\r\\n- Tresses and Treasures will pay a reduced price of 15 trade tokens per import request\<br\>\\r\\n- Doloreaux members will pay a 25% reduced price for jewelry from Tresses and Treasures\<br\>\\r\\n- Lidia will provide lessons to Doloreaux jewelers free of charge\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIt has been signed by Baez, current Ambassador of the Doloreaux and by Lidia, current leader of Tresses and Treasures guild.\\r\\n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:direct imports list">
         (\{ "visitors", "Awaiting More Information------- Esquire Ruprecht des Griefswold - 2/6/2015\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nBucket Bag:\\r\\n this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) bucket bag. A roomy bag shaped like a bucket with an open top and thick shoulder strap. (this.trait:embroidery) It has been embroidered with \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery)\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nCollared Bodice:\\r\\n A (this.trait:color) (this.trait:material) stand-up collared bodice. This is a tight-fitting enclosure of \\\\\$(this.trait:material) fabric worn upon the torso. It features front lacing with \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) grommets and a stylish stand-up collar which fashionably encompasses the nape of the wearer's neck.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nCranach Gown:\\r\\nA (this.trait:color) (this.trait:material) floor-length and full-skirted cranach gown, complete with an elegant pair of segmented sleeves bordered in \\\\\$(this.trait:gems) and decorated with \\\\\$(this.trait:variation) lace. The top bears inch and a half wide straps and is comprised of fitted \\\\\$(this.trait:variation) faille embroidered with \\\\\$(this.trait:pattern). Thick \\\\\$(this.trait:color) cords have been horizontally strung against the abdomen of the garment, revealing the color and fabric of the chemise beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nDirndl Blouse:\\r\\n A \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) dirndl blouse. An upper body garment that boasts one-third puffed sleeves that reach just below the biceps, \\\\\$(this.trait:variation) criss-crossed front lacing, ties at the ruffled cuffs, and a scrunched, squared neckline that dips low enough reveal a hint of cleavage. This garment covers most of the torso, the hemline ending just below the navel, before folding in on itself where the criss-cross, front lacings begin.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nDrop-front Breeches:\\r\\nA pair of \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) drop front breeches. A pair of patterned pants bearing pockets, and an adjustable gusset in the back. They are secured by means of two \\\\\$(this.trait:gem) buttons at the waistline.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nFormal Drape:\\r\\n A \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) formal drape. An elegant shoulder cloak which drapes away from the back up to 5' on the floor. Elaborate \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) clasps secure the garment in place at the shoulders leaving the fabric to trail away from the body.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nGemmed Doublet:\\r\\nA \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) long-sleeved gemmed doublet. It extends down to the hips and is tightly fit to the torso and arms. It features a high-standing collar and padded shoulder rolls with sumptuous trim. Two rows of \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) buttons fasten it down the front. It has been lavishly decorated with miniature \\\\\$(this.trait:stone) gemstones.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nLederhosen:\\r\\nNative to Bruges, these knee length, short breeches are traditionally worn with a pair of suspenders that can attach front and back via four \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) buttons at the waist. These bottoms sport a \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery) embroidered drop-front flap over the lap that closes via two lines of \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) buttons to the waist, and cuffs that fold at the knees.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nPelisse:\\r\\nIt is a loose women's coat that falls just to the knees in sumptuous folds. It is fastened at the waist by a \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) clasp, and features side slits, deep armholes, and silk lined half-sleeves.  \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery) \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery). Has color, material too.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nPinafore:\\r\\n A \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) pinafore. It is a sleeveless, low-necked dress designed to protect clothing, much like an apron, and is worn most prominently by members of Great Households. This particular garment has been meticulously embroidered with gold threads to depict the symbol of the Great House Doloreaux.  \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.details:button:snames) \\\\\| You notice a set of \\\\\$(this.trait:buttons:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:buttons:material) \\\\\$(this.trait:buttons:type) buttons attached to it.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nRibboned Shawl:\\r\\n A \\\\\$(this.trait:color) faux fur ribboned shawl. A sleeveless chest covering worn primarily in winter. It wraps snugly about the shoulders and upper arms before being centrally secured with a matching ribboned bow embellishment.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSack-backed Jacket:\\r\\n\\r\\n A \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) sack-backed jacket. A thigh-length woman's jacket generally worn over a petticoat or blouse with a kerchief tied about the neck. It features winged cuffs on elbow-length sleeves that drape against the forearm before being finished with ruched \\\\\$(this.trait:variation) ribbons.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nScented gloves:\\r\\nA pair of wrist-length \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) gloves which give off the smell of \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.trait:smell) \\\\\|\\\\\$(this.trait:variation)\\\\\} to passerby. \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery) \\\\\|The back of each glove has been embroidered with \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery).\\\\\} A \\\\\$(this.trait:lining:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:lining:material) lining has been sewn along the inside contours\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSchaub Coat:\\r\\nA luxurious open-front coat that reaches to mid thigh. Loose fitting, this garment boasts long, baggy sleeves that cinch around the wrists to accentuate the fullness of the sleeves, and a wide \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material), mantle-like collar that drapes over the shoulders and frames the open front of the garment down to the hem.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSuspenders:\\r\\nTwo \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) inch wide straps worn over each shoulder that attach to a pair of pants via four button holes at each of the strap's ends. A \\\\\$(this.trait:shape) shaped chest-piece connects the two straps across the breastbone to keep them from slipping off the shoulders. Two \\\\\$(this.trait:metal) buckles adorn each side of the chest-piece, making the straps easily adjustable for any size.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nTrenker hat:\\r\\nSimilar to the fedora, the small brim of this hat is curled partially upward at the back of the head. Two indents on each side of the short crown lend a peaked appearance to the slightly rounded top of the hat. The base of the crown, and where the small brim begins to extend outward, has been wrapped twice over with twisted \\\\\$(this.trait:variation) cording that curls into a small, decorative loop upon the left side of the peaked crown.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nWar coat:\\r\\nA \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) skirted doublet with a side closure and elaborate front placket closures. A garment of decoration, it can be practically worn over a single or double layer of doublets and trews as an added protection against enemy weapons. \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.details:lining:snames) \\\\\| A \\\\\$(this.trait:lining:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:lining:material) lining has been sewn along the inside contours.\\\\\} \\\\\{? \\\\\| \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery) \\\\\|This coat has been embroidered with \\\\\$(this.trait:embroidery)\\\\\}\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nWinter wrap:\\r\\nA \\\\\$(this.trait:color) \\\\\$(this.trait:material) winter wrap. A long-sleeved evening wrap featuring a high neck and open front. It's ideal for wear in colder weather and pairs well with nearly any gown." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:doloreaux guard">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>\<u\>Rekrut Training Curriculum\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\n1. Guard Introduction (chain of command, code of conduct, daily duties) \<br\>\\r\\n2. City Tour (Newtown, Oldtown, Manor)\<br\>\\r\\n3. Escort Duty (procedures, under attack, practice)\<br\>\\r\\n4. Training Expectations: Combat and Boar fluency\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Lesson 1: Guard Introduction\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nIntroduction packet to the Guard of the Triskellian Doloreaux Embassy\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nChain of Command:\<br\>\\r\\nAmbassador: Sir Baez\<br\>\\r\\nRittmeister: (unfilled)\<br\>\\r\\nOffiker: (unfilled)\<br\>\\r\\nSoldat: Jessica, Trevyn\<br\>\\r\\nRekrut: Sturm, Shiva, Gavin\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCode of Conduct:  Rekruts will carry themselves with keen attention to Loyalty, Courtesy, Honor and Glory.  Avoid behaviors that will reflect poorly on the House such as speaking of inappropriate topics in public or fraternizing with unsavory characters.  No House information may be divulged to outsiders, and violating this expecation can result in espionage charges.  Guards must remain of sharp mind while on duty and must limit the intake of alcohol.  All members of the Guard will respect and obey their superiors in the Chain of Command.  Guardsmen will salute all Guard members, nod to civilians of equal or lesser rank and bow to civilians of greater rank.  Members of this Guard must be willing to defend House Doloreaux interests against threats from within and without, at all costs.  There is an expectation of regular activity, and if a Guard cannot meet this requirement they will forfeit any rank or position they had previously been appointed.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDaily Duties:  Rekruts must upkeep their personal appearance with short hair and facial grooming, uniform, weapons, armor and quarters on a daily basis.  Each day, Recruits will make morning, afternoon and evening rounds to ensure the security of the Doloreaux Manor and its members.  All guards are responsible to continue combat training as coordinated with the Rittmeister.  There should be an effort to establish a positive public image by conducting oneself with respect throughout Newtown. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWelcome to the Great House of the Doloreaux. There is great Glory to be had from Loyal Service.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Lesson 2: City Tour\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nLink: http://www.skotos.net/IronclawGame/images/maps/trisk.jpg\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Lesson 3: Escort Duty\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nEscort Duty:  It is our task to see to the safety of our Nobility.  When a Noble wishes to travel about town, it is our honor to ensure their security.  A guard will keep to the side and behind the noble and remain unobtrusive.  Escort duty does not end until such time that the noble is either back safely in the Manor, or has been handed to another guard.  The guard will be alert for drawn weapons, containers (pouches, purses, sacks, satchels, sporrans and the like) that can conceal weapons.  Escorts should also be watchful for uninvited movement toward the noble, suspicious activity, known criminals, or any such potential dangers.  If danger presents itself, the guard will put himself between the danger and the Noble, while getting the Noble to safety as quickly as possible.  Be alert for exits to all areas and identify possible areas of danger to the Noble well before any problems begin.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Lesson 4: Training Expectations\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nAll Guard members are required to coordinate a combat training regiment with the Rittmeister and Leutnant.  The House will pay for combat training if required through outside sources.  Whenever possible, it is preferred to seek training with fellow guards or with teachers in the city.  During combat training, guards will conduct themselves with honor and refrain from strikes to the groin, breasts or throat.  Doloreaux combatants will show honor in victory and defeat by controlling their tempers to prevent fits or outbursts.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAll Rekruts are also required to learn the Boar language to fluency, as it is proper to speak such in the presence of our Nobles.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Enlistment Oath:\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\\"I _____, do solemnly swear that I will support and defend the Great House Doloreaux against all enemies within and without; to serve honestly and loyally against all their enemies; and to obey the orders of the Doloreaux Rittmeister and chain of command.  May death and dishonor claim me, should I forsake this oath.\\"\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Officer Oath:\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\\"I _____, vow to hold those below me to the highest standard of Doloreaux excellence; and be held responsible, for better or worse, by their actions.  May death and dishonor claim me, should I forsake this oath.\\"\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Guard Regalia\</u\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nSoldat Induction Kit - Soldat  uniform, guild cloak, bronze ring, torch, map\<br\>\\r\\nGefreiter -  Officer uniform, Hunter green warcoat\<br\>\\r\\nLeutnant - Officer uniform, Hunter green warcoat, Rank insignia\<br\>\\r\\nRittmeister - Captain uniform, Midnight green warcoat, Rank insignia\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:embassy proposals">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>\<u\>Property Purchase Proposal\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nThis is a proposal to purchase a parcel of land roughly the size of our Embassy property on which we can build a variety of entertainment ideas and can be used by the public at a low cost for enjoyment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Festival Proposal\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nProposal to hold a festival with amusement games, booths, and the like.  If any members have any suggestions for this, feel free to add them here.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Volksfestessen Proposal\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nProposal to host a party and feast for the general public.  This event would be completely informal, and would feature music, lots of food, and lots of drink.  This would be held as a means of getting people to see who we are as Doloreaux, and begin to change the outward perception people have of us.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Workshop\</b\>\</u\>\\r\\nA proposed addition to the manor which includes a forge and jeweler's workshop.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Keg Cellar\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nA proposal to extend a keg cellar off of our storage room in order to keep organize kegs imported.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Signature Weapons Proposal\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nThree proposed weapons as signature weapons to the Doloreaux.  The Flamberge(rapier), the Flambart(longsword), and the Flammenschwert(zwiehander)\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guard code of conduct">
         (\{ "members", "Code of Conduct for Guards of the Great House of the Doloreaux\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSection 1: Loyalty To the House\<br\>\\r\\na) No Guard shall divulge information on House matters to any party outside of the Great House of the Doloreaux. To do so will result in immediate dismissal by Dishonorable Discharge followed by charges of espionage and potentially treason against the House.\<br\>\\r\\nb) All guards must be willing to sacrifice life to protect this Embassy and those within it.\<br\>\\r\\nc) Any member may choose to leave the guard, but must provide a minimal two week advance notice of intent to resign from the Guard. Any member doing this may remain a member of the House.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSection 2: Honor\<br\>\\r\\na) All guards will conduct themselves with utmost honor in all situations.\<br\>\\r\\nb) No lewd nor bawdy acts or discussions will be tolerated in public. No member of the Guard will engage in such conduct as it is a breach of honor, and is uncouth. Strive to put forward an image of propriety and decency.\<br\>\\r\\nb) All guards shall show proper courtesy to Nobles and peers of this house, as well as to Nobles and peers of other houses.\<br\>\\r\\nc) We shall lead by example in the ways of Honor. Guards shall always present themselves in a neat and orderly fashion with facial hair, hair and fur well maintained. Uniform and clothing shall be kept in immaculate condition. All guards will bathe at least once daily.\<br\>\\r\\nd) During spars, honor shall be kept before glory. There will be no strikes to the groin, breasts, or throat during practices. No guard shall allow themselves to become angered during a spar, as this leads to lack of control, which leads to loss of honor.\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSection 3: Glory\<br\>\\r\\nAll guards will further the glory of the name of the Great House of the Doloreaux through both training and deed. Never shall it be said that a Doloreaux suffers cowardice. All Challenges will be met with Courage.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSection 4: Activity\<br\>\\r\\nAll guards must remain active by being of service as often as possible. Any guard that becomes inactive without proper notification as to why, will be removed from service to the Embassy with the option of returning as a recruit and working back into the Guard, all former rank shall be removed and the party must begin to acquire said rank just as any other recruit must do would." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guild vault ">
         (\{ "members", "First weapon rack:\\r\\n1 Iron Rapier of very good quality with an iron swept hilt in sheath\\r\\n1 Iron Axe of average quality w/ weapon strap\\r\\n1 Iron Axe of good quality w/ weapon strap\\r\\n1 Iron Scimitar of exceptional quality with iron swept hilt and sheath.\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1571341392, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
