<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#ffffff", "bgcolor2":"#ffffff", "bgimg1":"http://i.imgur.com/yXyjJsx.jpg", "bgimg2":"http://i.imgur.com/YWY6bxf.jpg", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Palatino", "h1color":"#000000", "h1type":"Palatino", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Palatino", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Palatino" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "This is your default guild page. This is the first page your members see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:dyes">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif;text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59)\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px;text-align:left\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Dyes\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<i\>\\r\\n        All dyes are priced \<b\>per use\</b\>.\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Per pot\</b\> discount available upon request.\\r\\n    \</i\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(201,23,9)\\"\>Reds\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> red\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> blood-red, blush red, bright red, crimson, dark red, light red, ruddy red\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> vibrant red\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> rose red, strawberry red\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(199,72,117)\\"\>Pinks\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> dark pink, light pink, pink\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright pink, magenta, maroon, vibrant pink\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> soft pink\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>5 denarii:\</b\> pale pink\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(240,111,46)\\"\>Oranges\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> dark orange, light orange, orange\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright orange, burnt orange, pumpkin-colored, vibrant orange\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> bittersweet orange, ochre\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(234,203,35)\\"\>Yellows\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> dark yellow, light yellow, yellow\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright yellow, canary yellow, flaxen yellow, scuzzy yellow, vibrant yellow\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> gamboge, goldenrod\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(36,168,46)\\"\>Greens\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> green\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright green, chartreuse, dark green, light green, olive green, sage, scummy green, viridian\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> light sage, lime green, vibrant green\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> emerald\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>7 denarii:\</b\> vivid emerald\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(23,61,97)\\"\>Blues\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> blue\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> blue green, blue grey, bright blue, cobalt blue, dark blue, indigo, light blue, navy blue\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> cyan, sky blue, vibrant blue\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> sapphire, turquoise\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(118,23,89)\\"\>Purples\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> purple\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright purple, dark purple, light purple\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> periwinkle, vibrant purple\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> violet\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>7 denarii:\</b\> deep aubergine\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:#ffffff;-webkit-text-stroke:0.5px grey\\"\>Whites\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> white\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> bright white, grubby white, vibrant white\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> beige\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(97,92,86)\\"\>Greys\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> grey\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> grey, dark grey, light grey, slate grey\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Blacks\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> black\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> charcoal black, murky black\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>3 denarii:\</b\> ebony, sable\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"color:rgb(117,63,29)\\"\>Browns\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>1 denarii:\</b\> brown, dark brown, light brown\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> rich brown, russett, sienna, tan\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>7 denarii:\</b\> lustrous mocha\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3 style=\\"background:-webkit-linear-gradient(rgb(238,238,238),rgb(51,51,51));-webkit-background-clip:text;-webkit-text-fill-color:transparent\\"\>Metallics\</h3\>\\r\\n\</body\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:embroideries">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3, h4\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59);text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        h4\{font-size: 1em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Embroideries\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Apple Blossom\</b\>\<br\>Apple blossoms delicately strung in (material) display their many petals, with each flower spaced strategically throughout the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Autumn Leaf\</b\>\<br\>Dancing (material) autumn leaves scatter along the seams of the garment playfully.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Constabulary Crest\</b\>\<br\>The left side of this garment bears three seashells on a (material) shield, with two spears crossed behind.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Criss-Cross\</b\>\<br\>Criss-cross (material) patterns etch a curious design along the length of the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Destrier\</b\>\<br\>The rearing destrier representing the Avoirdupois is embroidered here in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Dot\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) dots.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Fish\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) fish.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Fist\</b\>\<br\>The fabric has been embroidered in (material) thread with a strong fist.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Flower\</b\>\<br\>The material has been embroidered in (material) thread to depict a myriad of clusters and single, detailed flowers.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Geometric\</b\>\<br\>Simplistic (material) threading covers the front of the garment in a geometric design.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Heart\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) hearts.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Knot\</b\>\<br\>Knots and crosses spatter the material in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Octogram\</b\>\<br\>The fabric has been embroidered in (material) thread with the Octogram of Creation representing the Church of S'allumer.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Poppy\</b\>\<br\>Large (material) poppy flowers are scattered liberally across the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Seashell\</b\>\<br\>The three seashells representing the Rinaldi are embroidered here in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Shield\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) shields.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Skink\</b\>\<br\>A lone (material) skink crouches upon the backside of the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Skull\</b\>\<br\>An accurately detailed skull is displayed in (material) thread on the backside of the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Smoke\</b\>\<br\>Delicate wisps of threaded (material) smoke radiate over the garment in circular patterns.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Snake\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) snakes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Spider\</b\>\<br\>The fabric boasts a crouching spider depicted in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Sword\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) swords.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Tower\</b\>\<br\>The castle tower representing the Doloreaux is embroidered here in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Turtle Dove\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) turtle doves face each other while resting peacefully on a decorative branch.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Wave\</b\>\<br\>Ribbon worked (material) waves dominate the body of the garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Wheel\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) eight spoked wheels.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>Windmill\</b\>\<br\>The windmill representing the Bisclavret is embroidered here in (material) thread.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n    \<b\>X\</b\>\<br\>The seams of this garment are lined with miniature (material) X's.\\r\\n\</body\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:fabrics">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3, h4\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59);text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        h4\{font-size: 1em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Fabrics\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<center\>\<i\>\\r\\n        All fabrics are priced \<b\>per yard\</b\>.\<br\>\\r\\n    \</i\>\</center\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>1 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>burlap, calico, canvas, gingham, hemp, linen, sackcloth, tweed, wool\</p\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>2 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>barras, broadcloth, brocade, cotton, felt, flannel, leather, satin, woolsey\</p\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>3 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>suede, whipcord\</p\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>4 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>damask, faux fur, muslin, poplin, velvet\</p\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>8 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>silk, batiste\</p\>\\r\\n    \<h4\>15 Denarii\</h4\>\\r\\n    \<p\>samite\</p\>\\r\\n\</body\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:garments">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif;text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59)\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px;text-align:left\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Garments\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Belts\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Belt\</b\>\<br\>A belt made of (material). Worn wrapped about the waist, it can be used for hanging various items such as pouches and scabbards.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Braided Belt\</b\>\<br\>A braided belt made of (material). This is a casual belt created through the braiding together of three or more strips of fabric.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Cloaks\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Capelet\</b\>\<br\>A (material) capelet. This is a miniature cape designed to be worn during warm weather. Barely covering the shoulders in the front, the top rests just under the nape of the wearer in the back to fashionably frame the neckline.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Chasuble Cape\</b\>\<br\>A (material) chasuble cape. This is a generic, circular cape with an aperture for the head.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Cloak\</b\>\<br\>A (material) cloak. It is a type of loose garment that is worn over indoor clothing and protects the wearer from the cold, rain or wind, or it may form part of a fashionable outfit or uniform.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Evening Cape\</b\>\<br\>A (material) evening cape. This is a sleeveless outer garment which is designed to fasten at the throat and fall down the back of the wearer. Worn as a formal garment, this particular cape is meant to be made from fine materials only, sometimes being constructed from lacy knit patterns or crochets, and occasionally beaded or laced with gems. It falls only partially down the back, and drapes elegantly over the shoulders.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Hooded Lacerna Cloak\</b\>\<br\>A (material) lacerna cloak. A large, semi-circular cloak draped around the shoulder, down the back and typically secured with a piece of jewelry. It serves as protection against the elements.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Robe\</b\>\<br\>A (material) robe. The loose-fitting robe boasts full, wide sleeves and reaches to the ground to completely cover the wearer. This garment is normally a mark of a humble demeanor and great accomplishments. It is usually earned via religious, magical or other secretive means.\<br\>\<br\>It comes complete with a long tailed hood and a corded waist. The hood hangs loose against the upper back.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Footwear\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) boots. These are tailored so they fit over most animals paws. Custom shoes are available to hooved animals such as horses, or animals with strangely shaped feet.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Ankle-High Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) ankle-high boots. These boots reach just to to the ankle and tie securely via lacing on the side. They feature padded soles for added comfort.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Calf-High Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) calf-high boots. These boots reach just to to the calf and are accented by a series of fashionable buttons and laces. The interior is complimented with a plush lining and padded sole, ensuring these boots are comfortable, all day pieces of apparel.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Knee-High Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) knee-high boots. These boots reach just to the knee and close via three side strap enclosures with ties. The interior features a padded sole for comfort.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Shoes\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) shoes. These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. They cover the foot and extend just to the ankle when pulled up. Custom shoes are available to hooved animals such as horses, or animals with strangely shaped feet.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Strapped Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) strapped boots. Footwear reaching just to the knees which is held in place by a myriad of primitive strings and straps wrapped about the circumference.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tall Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) tall boots. These boots reach just to the thigh and feature a back slit panel that allows them to be cuffed down. They have a 1 inch heel and are padded for comfort.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Toggle Boots\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) toggle boots. These tough boots rise to just below the calves and are excellent for peasant work as well as for wearing under armours. They slip on and then close via a pair of toggles.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Gloves\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Fingerless Gloves\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) fingerless gloves. These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These gloves are fingerless, encasing the base of the fingers to the wrists.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Gloves\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) gloves. These are tailored so they fit over most animals paws. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animals who need such things.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Handwraps\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) handwraps. Primitive protective wrappings that are bound around the hands of the wearer to encase the base of the fingers down to the wrists.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Work Gloves\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) work gloves. These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws and extend upward over the forearms for protection. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animals who need such things.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Hats\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Acorn Hat\</b\>\<br\>A (material) acorn hat. It is a somewhat rounded hat tapering upward into a blunt point.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Bandana\</b\>\<br\>A (material) bandana. A large piece of square cloth, generally worn on the head or around the neck. They are typically brightly colored with some sort of pattern or design on their surface. Around the neck, it can be pulled up to the nose and mouth to lessen the inhalation of dust and debris. Upon the head, it can prevent perspiration from running into the eyes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Bandit Hood\</b\>\<br\>A (material) bandit hood. It is a kind of headgear that covers most of the head and neck and sometimes the face.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Benda\</b\>\<br\>A (material) benda. This is a length of material used for covering, wrapping around, or intertwining with the hair.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Beret\</b\>\<br\>A (material) beret. It is a soft round cap, usually of wool or felt, with a flat crown, which is worn by both men and women.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Biretta\</b\>\<br\>A (material) biretta. It is a square cap with three or four ridges or peaks, sometimes surmounted by a tuft.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Cap\</b\>\<br\>A (material) cap. It is a form of headgear. Caps have crowns that fit closer than hats and have no brim or only a visor. They are typically designed for warmth and, when including a visor, blocking sunlight from the eyes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Flat Cap\</b\>\<br\>A (material) flat cap. It is a rounded men's cap with a small stiff brim in front.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Hood\</b\>\<br\>A (material) hood. It is a kind of headgear that covers most of the head and neck and sometimes the face.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Mitre\</b\>\<br\>A (material) mitre. The mitre is a tall folding cap, consisting of two similar parts (the front and back) rising to a peak and sewn together at the sides. Two short lappets always hang down from the back.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Padded Arming Cap\</b\>\<br\>A (material) padded arming cap. It is normally worn under the helmet or chain mail for comfort.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Phrygian Cap\</b\>\<br\>A (material) phrygian cap. It is a soft, conical cap with the top pulled forward, and usually the color red.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Sock Hat\</b\>\<br\>A (material) sock hat. This hat is similar in shape to the sock. It rests slackly about the head and the excess materials are draped to either side as the wearer prefers.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Skullcap\</b\>\<br\>A (material) skullcap. This is a small, circular cap, often with a small bit of cloth in the center looking like the tip of a beret.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Zucchetto\</b\>\<br\>A (material) zucchetto. Also called pileolus, it is a small skullcap worn by clerics of the Church. It was adopted for practical reasons to keep the clergy's tonsured heads warm in cold, damp churches. It consists of eight panels sewn together, with a stem at the top. The zucchetto continues to be worn while the mitre is being worn; it is placed inside it (a mitre is bottomless, so the zucchetto sits on the head while the mitre is around it).\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Pants\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Harem Pants\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) harem pants. Baggy pants, tied at the ankles.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Jodhpurs\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) jodhpurs. Wide-hipped riding pants of heavy cloth, fitting tightly from knee to ankle.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Pantaloons\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) pantaloons. These are baggy trousers extending from waist to ankle.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Pants\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) pants. An article of clothing covering the body from the waist down, with separate coverings for each leg that extend to the ankles. They are usually closed and fastened by either buttons or a laces, though straps with buckles or brooches are also commonplace.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Shorts\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) shorts. These are trousers that end at or above the knee, generally worn by men.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Stretch Pants\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) stretch pants. Skin-tight legwear featuring leather straps which buckle around the calves.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Shirts\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Cavalier Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) cavalier shirt. A male garment featuring full sleeves, gathered cuffs, and a stiffened collar with a lace front closure.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Fold-Neck Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) fold-neck shirt. This is a cowl-front shirt which pulls on over the head before the front is folded down across the throat and under the collar. This style of shirt protects the wearer's chest and throat from drafts and any over-collars from becoming dirty easily.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Gypsy Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) gypsy shirt. A men's straight cut shirt with full sleeves and a v-neck turned back collar.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Half-Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) half-shirt. A male upper body garment that wraps about the torso and drapes over one shoulder to leave half the chest exposed.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) shirt. This is a garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar, sleeves, and a front opening.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Slit-Neck Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) slit-neck shirt. This is a simple, loose-fitting shirt with tubular sleeves, underarm gussets, and a boat neckline.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tie-Neck Shirt\</b\>\<br\>A (material) tie-neck shirt. This is a simple, loose-fitting shirt with tubular sleeves and underarm gussets. The banded collar extends into front ties.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Socks \&amp; Stockings\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Footwraps\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) footwraps. Primitive protective wrappings that are bound around the feet of the wearer to encase the base of the toes all the way up to the calves.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Hose\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) hose. The most traditional style of male hose extending downward from the waist and encapsulating each of the feet. They are most commonly worn with dress shoes or other varieties of footwear outside boots.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Kilt Hose\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) kilt hose. These are custom knit top hose with a cabled cuff and reinforced feet. They are designed to be worn with kilts.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Leggings\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) leggings. A leg covering usually extending from the ankle to the knee and often made of material such as leather or canvas, worn especially by soldiers and workers.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Socks\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) socks. Tubes of fabric that cover the feet up to the ankle. Special socks can be crafted for those with bigger feet or hooves.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tights\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) tights. A snug stretchable garment covering the body from the waist down.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Spatterdashes\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) spatterdashes. Generally coupled with leggings, these cover the leg from the mid-shin to the top of the foot, and are typically worn by the sporting gentleman, laboring man, and the military.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Undergarments\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Underdrawers\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) underdrawers. Beginning at the waist and extending downward to the knee, these male undergarments serve as a separate lining to breeches and other pants, aiding in preservation of over garments and adding an additional layer of warmth.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Pouches\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Pouch\</b\>\<br\>A (material) pouch. It is wrapped around the waist with a string.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Miscellaneous\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Apron\</b\>\<br\>A (material) apron. It is held up by a string around the neck, and fastened around the waist with a thin belt tie.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Armwraps\</b\>\<br\>A (material) pair of armwraps. Primitive wrappings that are bound around the upper arms of the wearer for decoration.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Footed Pajamas\</b\>\<br\>A pair of (material) footed pajamas. This is a pair of basic pajamas complete with foot coverings. Designed for comfort and warmth while sleeping, these pajamas are traditionally worn by infants and children.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Loincloth\</b\>\<br\>A (material) loincloth. A garment designed for wrapping around the waist to cover the genitals. Usually a simple piece of cloth which is left to dangle downwards, it is a basic, primitive garment.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Neckerchief\</b\>\<br\>A (material) neck handkerchief. The most informal sort of neckwear generally worn by sporting gentlemen, working tradesmen, and laboring slaves. It is a square folded and tied about the neck with a simple hem.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Ribbon\</b\>\<br\>A (material) ribbon. This thin length of fabric is used for binding things such as the hair, both for decoration and to hold the object in place.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Scarf\</b\>\<br\>A (material) scarf. It is a piece of fabric worn on or near the head or around the neck for warmth, cleanliness, fashion or for religious reasons.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tail Warmer\</b\>\<br\>A (material) tail warmer. A circular tube of cloth designed to encompass the tail and protect it from the elements. It looks really comfy and warm.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Wristlet\</b\>\<br\>A (material) wristlet. This is a decorative band of fabric worn about the wrist. Pendants can be added to make it more decorative, or it can be worn alone as a simple accessory.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Add Ons\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Fringe\</b\>\<br\>Some (material) fringe, suitable to be added to clothing. It is a decorative border hanging loosely from a raveled edge.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Lace\</b\>\<br\>Some (material) lace, suitable to be added to clothing. Lace is typically very expensive, and therefore is a mark of wealth.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Trimming\</b\>\<br\>Some (material) trimming, suitable to be added to clothing. Trimming is usually made from offcuts from finer garments, or from small amounts of valuable materials.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Dolls\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n       basic doll \\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h3\>Masks\</h3\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        basic mask\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Fits\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<i\>All fittings are free of charge for customers.\</i\>\\r\\n    \<p\>amateurishly-fit, archaic, archaically-fit, basic, boot-cut, casual, casually-flung, classically-fit, comfortable, conventionally-styled, crudely cut, dirty, formal, frayed, hand-me-down, hideously-styled, ill-fitting, inappropriately cut, infant-fitted, insipidly-cut, junior-fitted, loose, messily cut, modest, offensively cut, old-fashioned, oversized, patchwork, pitiably-stitched, primitive, primitively cut, provincially styled, roomy, roughly-styled, scrappy, scuffed, shabbily-fit, shabby, shapeless, shortly-cut, simple, simply-styled, smelly, soiled, stained, tattered, threadbare, timeworn, traditional, traditionally cut, undersized, unfashionably cut, unskillfully-fit, used, weathered\</p\>\\r\\n\</body\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif;text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59)\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px;text-align:left\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<i\>\\r\\n        Please see drop-down menu for a full list of our offerings.\\r\\n    \</i\>\\r\\n\</body\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:other goods">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<head\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Homemade+Apple\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<link href=\\"https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lora\\" rel=\\"stylesheet\\"\>\\r\\n    \<style\>\\r\\n        body\{font-family:'Lora',serif;text-align:center\}\\r\\n        h1, h2, h3\{font-family:'Homemade Apple',cursive;color:rgb(74,39,59)\}\\r\\n        h3\{font-size:1.25em\}\\r\\n        p\{margin-bottom:50px;text-align:left\}\\r\\n    \</style\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n    \<h1\>Other Goods\</h1\>\\r\\n    \<p\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Beach Towel\</b\>\<br\>A (material) beach towel. An oversized absorbent square cloth capable of covering even the largest of bodies. It is designed for drying oneself after a bath or a dip in the water, and can be used for laying out on the beach or grass.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Bookmark\</b\>\<br\>A (material) bookmark. It is a thin marker used to keep one's place in a book and so be able to return to it with ease.\<br\>\<br\> \\r\\n        \<b\>Cloth\</b\>\<br\>A clean cloth made from a confiscated scrap of (material).\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Curtains\</b\>\<br\>A (material) curtains. Hung from a rod affixed to the top of the window, curtains allow a diffused light to pass through the window while offering a level of privacy. They also serve to soften the features of the room. When tied back, they swoop gracefully to pool on the floor. They can be used alone or with heavier drapes, especially during cooler months.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Cushion\</b\>\<br\>A (material) cushion. This is a padded (round, square) cushion designed for comfort while sitting. It can also be used for decorative purposes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Flag\</b\>\<br\>A (material) flag. This flag is small enough to be easily waved by hand or adorn doors and fences. Typically, images or words are embroidered into the fabric. They are often seen hanging outside residences or stores to show national pride, loyalty or affiliation.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Fluffy Towel\</b\>\<br\>A (material) fluffy towel. A fluffy and absorbent square cloth capable of covering an average-sized body. It is designed for drying oneself after a bath or a dip in the water.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Hammock\</b\>\<br\>A (material) hammock. A hammock is a sling made of fabric, rope, or netting, suspended between two points, used for swinging, sleeping, or resting. It consists of a cloth panel stretched with ropes between two firm anchor points such as trees or posts.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Handkerchief\</b\>\<br\>A (material) handkerchief. A simple, square piece of cloth used for dabbing one's lips, wiping sweat from the brow, or giving as a token of favor.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Hand Towel\</b\>\<br\>A (material) hand towel. An absorbent, rectangular piece of cloth designed for cleaning up messes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Napkin\</b\>\<br\>A (material) napkin. A square piece of cloth used at a meal to wipe the fingers or lips and to protect garments.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Pillow\</b\>\<br\>A (material) pillow. Designed to use as a comfort for the head.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Placemat\</b\>\<br\>A (material) placemat. This small rectangular swath of fabric is stiffened and starched to provide rigidity and is used to protect wooden and glass surfaces from damage caused by dishware or cutlery as well as for adding a decorative element to table settings.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Polishing Cloth\</b\>\<br\>A (material) polishing cloth. It is a square-cut piece of cloth intended for use in polishing metals and other precious items.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Portiere\</b\>\<br\>A (material) portiere. A portiere, also known as a door curtain, is a hanging placed over a door or over the doorless entrance to a room.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Quiver\</b\>\<br\>A cylindrical piece of (material), its top open to put arrows through. It has a long strap to help be worn on the back.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Streamers\</b\>\<br\>Some (material) streamers, designed to be used as a decoration for socials and other events.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Table Runner\</b\>\<br\>A (material) table runner. This decorative table runner is long enough to run the length of the table but narrow enough to still display the craftsmanship of the tabletop. It is typically used in conjunction with placemats.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tablecloth\</b\>\<br\>A (material) tablecloth. A large, square covering generally spread out over a table, especially during meals.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Tapestry\</b\>\<br\>A tapestry, ready to have something embroidered on it.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Upholstery\</b\>\<br\>A (material) upholstery. A large roll of upholstery, used for covering couches, benches and chaise lounges.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Washcloth\</b\>\<br\>A (material) washcloth. A small, square, and fluffy piece of cloth designed for washing the body or cleaning up messes.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n        \<b\>Wraps\</b\>\<br\>Some wraps made out of oilskin. Wraps of these types are typically used by sailors, who wrap them around valuable items. The wraps them protect the items should they be immersed in water.\\r\\n    \</p\>\\r\\n\</body\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571341392, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
