<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#235347", "bgcolor2":"#8EB69B", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#3F3D36", "fonttype":"Garamound", "h1color":"#3F3D36", "h1type":"Garamound", "h2color":"#3F3D36", "h2type":"Garamound", "h3color":"#3F3D36", "h3type":"Garamound" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "This is your default guild page. This is the first page your members see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:england background info">
         (\{ "members", "\<a href=\\"http://allegoryofempires.com/index.php/wiki/england/\\"\>Taken from AoE Wiki\</a\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nShe read the scroll once more, her hands shaking as she crouched down and held it over the fire in the hearth. With a hiss and crackle, the flames licked at the flimsy paper and the words began to darken and disappear. \<i\>By any means necessary\</i\>. Such a simple statement that held such an ominous weight. She knew what she must do. \\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nSteeped in tradition and yet on the forefront of new frontiers, the English are an anomalous mix of old and new with a healthy dose of influence and power to lend credence to their avant-garde and unusual practices and ideas. In recent years, they have forged a powerful alliance with the German nation, trading goods as well as military resources and soldiers. The two have found common ground in their desire for land and power along the area of northern Europe.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nAs the most powerful and influential nation actively practicing a Protestant religion, they are considered a dangerous powerhouse by the other larger nations that remain faithful to the Roman Catholic Church. With such a far reaching influence, their power in addition to their unique traditions and beliefs have caught the attention of many of the nations in the political arena. They have brought and borrowed ideas from all corners of the known world on a scale with broader reach than any other nation, although Spain is rapidly making ground on that front.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nWith the unique status of having a female ruler who inherited the throne in her own right and acts independent of a male counterpart or on behalf of a male heir, the English nation has turned heads in recent years. While it took some time for the current Queen to become a respected player in the international realm, she has proven her prowess on both the financial trade front as well as the military front. After quelling riots along the border with Scotland and sending forces to aid their allies in Germany, the Queen has proven her power and might without question among the other nations.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nDespite all this newfound change and independent thinking, the British are still notoriously traditional in many ways, often living up to the stereotype of old fashioned or prudish held by those outside the nation. With an affinity for tradition and status quo, perhaps in an effort to compensate for the radical changes made over the last few years, they enjoy more conservative roles and gatherings as opposed to the lavish and opulent affairs preferred by some of their other European counterparts. " \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:england class info">
         (\{ "members", "\<a href=\\"http://allegoryofempires.com/index.php/wiki/england/\\"\>Taken from AoE Wiki\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>English Relations at a Glance\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>FRANCE\</b\> - With their alliance to Germany, England has taken a clear stance against France. It is rumored that England and Germany are working together only to mutually conquer land from France, but no overt actions have confirmed these rumors yet.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>GERMANY\</b\> - Germany and England have forged a powerful alliance in recent years through trading goods, military resources and political support. No formal treaty or marriage ties these two nations together, but their mutual influence is well known.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>ITALY\</b\> - While civil for the most part, these two nations are occasionally tossed into contentious standing with one another as they both vie for power in the same arenas. This competition as well as their opposing alliances can cause some tension at times.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>SCOTLAND\</b\> - While they were enemies at one point in the past, their standing with one another is currently neutral's at best. Tensions from their troubled history occasionally rear their head and their shared border does nothing to curb the apprehension.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>SPAIN\</b\> - Spain makes the British nervous more than any other nation because their strong naval presence could be a massive threat to their island nation. Their powerful trade routes inspire envy and the British are eager to catch up to Spain's influence. \\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>ROMAN CATHOLIC CHURCH\</b\> - Relations between the Roman Catholic Church and the nation of England are understandably tense. Decades ago, England had a schism with the Church and developed the Church of England, making them a Protestant nation. \\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>PROTESTANT CHURCH\</b\> - In order to regain more independence and power, the English broke away from the Roman Catholic Church to create the Church of England, making them a leader among the Protestant faiths of Europe. \\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>MIDDLE CLASS\</b\> - Despite their radical ideals, some things remain very traditional in England and class status is one of those things. Compared to the other nations, England's middle class is surprisingly small in comparison to their overall population.\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\n\<b\>LOWER CLASS\</b\> - With such a small middle class, a large portion of England's population would be considered lower class, but they manage a passable quality of life and so the disparity between upper and lower class does not always cause contention." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "This is your guest page. This is the page your visitors see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ooc: aoe setting">
         (\{ "members", "\<a href=\\"http://allegoryofempires.com/index.php/wiki/setting/\\"\>Taken from AoE Wiki\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\</br\>\\r\\nSet in early 17th century, a game of intrigue unfolds amidst the backdrop of baroque-inspired Italy under the ruling Ricchezza family.  For three generations the Ricchezzas have governed the duchal territories of Italy with the aid of a Royal Chancery.  In the aftermath of her husband\&#65533;s untimely death, Empress Dowager Mirielle Ricchezza assumes the role of ruler with Crown Prince Jacoba in tow. Together, they navigate the challenges of governing a kingdom in a time of grief and uncertainty.\\r\\n\\r\\nIn this game of intrigue you have the opportunity navigate a complex web of political, religious, economic, and social dynamics in the city of Rinascita, the Royal Capital of Italy. As a port-city, it is rich in trade and serves as a vibrant hub of economic activity, facilitating the exchange of goods, services, and ideas on a significant scale. It is a bustling center where merchants, traders, and entrepreneurs converge to conduct business, creating a dynamic and prosperous environment.\\r\\n\\r\\nYou can choose from multiple career paths, allowing for exploration of various skills, passions, and life experiences. Attend l\&#65533;Universita di Rinascita, join a political  Consulate or even start your own guild! Choose your own path." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ooc: ranks">
         (\{ "members", "\<a href=\\"http://allegoryofempires.com/index.php/wiki/ranks-and-promotions/\\"\>Taken from AoE Wiki\</a\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\</br\>\\r\\nIn Allegory of Empires, there are a variety of factions that you can pledge loyalty to and/or earn ranks with. You DO NOT have to be loyal to a group to accept a promotion nor do you need to be a member of their consulate/guild (although there may be social repercussions for accepting promotions from groups you are not loyal to). There are benefits to earning ranks (extra income, access to loyalty merchants) but your decision to follow a specific path should ideally be driven by story.\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571341392, "jominey", "R", 1719963049, "annemairi", "E", 1719963196, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
