<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "visitors", "Foreword by Doctor Genvieve de Martinique, Surgeon and Doctor of General and Emergent \\r\\nMedicine ~\\r\\n\\r\\nThe primary focus of the Medicine de Martinque as a studnet is to learn the art and science of medicine and apply our skills and knowledge to save or better the lives of those around us. We tend to the sick, mend the wounded, and care for the dying. We also study diligently to learn all we can of all aspects of healing. This includes the learning of Humorisms, Gross Anatomy and the physics that give us breath and a heartbeat, and learn what can take them away. The Healer thus learns the art to repair, mend and cure the body when things are not functioning optimally or correctly. Our only goals are to learn all we can to aid those who need our care. \\r\\n\\r\\nIt takes many years of assiduous work to rise in position within the Healers; those who do not show effort, care or dedication will therefore not know the privilege and honor of saving a life for the better But those who remain diligent and keep to the path of Healing are rewarded not only with the knowledge of Medicine, but with a fulfilling career that touches and holds the lives with those who come into their care. ", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "This is your guest page. This is the page your visitors see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
