<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="footer">
         "\<br/\>\<br/\>New fights are soon coming up! Get ready for it. "
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#ffffcc", "bgcolor2":"#ffffcc", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Arial", "h1color":"#990000", "h1type":"Palatino", "h2color":"#800000", "h2type":"Palatino", "h3color":"#993300", "h3type":"Palatino" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Manifesto:\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOrganizer and Host of Martial Games in Triskellian. Let people pit themselves against each other and show their skills in the arena, safe and sane.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<em\>As something new we bring Martial Games to Triskellian.\</em\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n- Our purpose is to organize and host Martial Games where fighters can show of their skills in the arena.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Our mission is to provide entertainment to the people in a safe and sane way.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Our means will include, one-to-one fights, teams against teams, teams against individuals and also introducing wild animals to the games.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Prominent members:\</h3\>\\r\\n* Dasha di Silvi - leader and organizer\<br/\>\\r\\n* Jolene - Organizer and paper work stuff\<br/\>\\r\\n* Zaria - Fighter and Guild Council representative.\<br/\>\\r\\n* Koz - Gladiator\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nSpeak to any of them if you have ideas for the guild or any questions.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Types of fights and competition\</h3\>\\r\\n- One on one fights\<br/\>\\r\\n- Team against team\<br/\>\\r\\n- Individual against team\<br/\>\\r\\n- Individual against animal\<br/\>\\r\\n- Team against animal\<br/\>\\r\\n- Races\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Sales\</h3\>\\r\\n- Miniature weapons\<br/\>\\r\\n- Shirts\<br/\>\\r\\n- Flags/Banners\<br/\>\\r\\n- Scarves\<br/\>\\r\\n- Special armour\<br/\>\\r\\n- Shields/bucklers\<br/\>\\r\\n- All with team symbols and colours that can be sold to fighters and supporters\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Members to find\</h3\>\\r\\n- Medic, or deal with the healers so they're present at every fight\<br/\>\\r\\n- Writer to do public announcements and publish results in a captivating manner\<br/\>\\r\\n- Fighters for our team\<br/\>\\r\\n- Organizer, someone who's good at organizing things\<br/\>\\r\\n- Masseur to treat our fighters after combat\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>News and support\</h3\>\\r\\n- The Church (Father Antos) has given their official and written approval of our Games, provided we have healers present during the fights and nobody gets killed.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Lord Marcus of the Rinaldi is supporting the Guild, so obtaining permission to use the Arena for the Games will be no issue.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Doctor Hush has expressed that she'll gladly ensure that healers are available during the Games.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Caitriona has expressed desire to help create souvenirs that can be sold at the games.\<br/\>\\r\\n- Una has expressed desire to help create flags or banners for us.\<br/\>\\r\\n- The Constabulary has approved of our fights, Biggs and Zaria.\<br/\>\<br/\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h3\>As something new we bring Martial Games to Triskellian.\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<em\>Our \<strong\>purpose\</strong\> is to \<strong\>organize and host Martial Games\</strong\> where fighters can show of their skills in the arena.\</em\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<em\>Our \<strong\>mission\</strong\> is to \<strong\>provide entertainment\</strong\> to the people in a \<strong\>safe and sane\</strong\> way.\</em\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<em\>Our \<strong\>means\</strong\> will include, \<strong\>one-to-one fights\</strong\>, \<strong\>teams against teams\</strong\>, teams against individuals and also introducing \<strong\>wild animals\</strong\> to the games.\</em\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThis is a great way to display your martial skills in a safe setting, and put to practice what you have trained for and help you be ready if the day comes where you need to fight for real.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nWe will have tiers of fighters, so everybody can win their tier and be a master. \<br/\>\\r\\nWe will build a team of good fighters who can be challenged by other teams.\<br/\>\\r\\nWe even welcome teams from other towns and cities to fight against the best in Triskellian.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nReady yourself for the fights, it will be a blast and prizes and trophies can be won.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<em\>\<strong\>Will you be the next to hold the title of Master Fighter of Triskellian?\</strong\>\</em\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ideas">
         (\{ "members", "\<br/\>\<strong\>One on one fights:\</strong\>\<br/\>\\r\\n- Best fighter wins the title of Master Fighter of Triskellian and a trophy\<br/\>\\r\\n- Set up regular fights\<br/\>\\r\\n- Tiers, fighters belong to a tier so everybody gets to fight someone of their same level.\<br/\>\\r\\n-- How can we implement this, what sort of tests?\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Winner can move tiers\<br/\>\\r\\n--- But under what conditions?\<br/\>\\r\\n-- [Idea is to give everybody, even new chars, a chance of winning their tier, but how do we ooc'ly decide who belongs to which tier?]\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n- Team fights, teams fighting against each other.\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Create our own team with good fighters\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Encourage guilds, houses and groups of friends to create their own teams\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Set up how team fights are done\<br/\>\\r\\n--- Rules, conditions, victory conditions, limitations and so on\<br/\>\\r\\n-- [Need to determine how to do it ooc'ly, just all fight against all using the combat system?]\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n- Wild Animals\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Get wild animals for fighters to fight\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Trapping and hunts or purchase?\<br/\>\\r\\n--- One against one\<br/\>\\r\\n--- Group against wild animal\<br/\>\\r\\n--- [likely need tokens to get these animals, how and which?]\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n- Capture the Flag\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Team against team\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Rules and conditions\<br/\>\\r\\n-- [How would it be implemented ooc'ly so that it's fair and RP minded?]\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n- Races\<br/\>\\r\\n-- People with mounts\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Rules\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Course and track\<br/\>\\r\\n-- Allow nastiness?\<br/\>\\r\\n-- [how would this be done ooc'ly? Rolls? Something else?]" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571341393, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
