<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#800000", "bgcolor2":"#993333", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#ffff66", "fonttype":"Times New Roman", "h1color":"#ffcc66", "h1type":"Times New Roman", "h2color":"#ffff99", "h2type":"Times New Roman", "h3color":"#ffff99", "h3type":"Times New Roman" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "The Needle and Rose. All fun stuff, and lots of happiness. In theory. And needles and spools. \\r\\n", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "A tailoring business set up to serve the denizens of this fine city, Rinascita. Begun by Valeria d'Allessandro, Dame of the German nation, her founding wish is to bring comfort and luxury to all those who order and place their business with her.\\r\\n\\r\\nNeedles and spool and stuff. Maybe some embroidery now and then. Have fun!\\r\\n", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:~embroideries~">
         (\{ "members", "\<p\>~Floral Designs~\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<p\>Apple blossom: Apple blossoms delicately strung in black flax display their many petals, with each flower spaced strategically throughout the garment..\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Autumn leaf: Dancing black flax autumn leaves scatter along the seams of the garment playfully.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Bud: Elaborately-stitched vines adorned with freshly-sprouted black flax buds decorate the hem of this garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Dahlia: The front of this garment is embroidered with a delicate swirling pattern of black flax dahlias.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Daisy: Elaborate ivy twists and turns gracefully from one end to anoother, creating an elegant background for a splattering of five-petaled black flax daisies.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Flower: The material has been embroidered in white flax thread to depict a myriad of clusters and single, detailed flowers.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Leaf: Richly-embroidered white flax leaves are scattered liberally across the back of this garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Lily: Three elaborate blooms of black flax lilies dangle down the fabric while delicate stems and leaves weave gracefully around the flowers.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Orchid: The front of this garment is embroidered with a delicate swirling pattern of white flax orchids.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Petal: The petals of an early morning black flax bloom have been splayed openly upon the fabric.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Poppy: Large white flax poppy flowers are scattered liberally across the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Rose: Ribbon worked pink linen rose buds add a splash of decoration to this garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>~Animals~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Butterfly: Complex black flax needlework forms an elaborate butterfly across the back of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Dragon: A black flax dragon poses dramatically with wings expanded as if in flight, and mouth wide open spraying red and orange curls of fire.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Dragonfly: Crisp black flax dragonflies are carefully embroidered across the front of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Firefly: A graceful series of black flax fireflies are scattered about the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Fish: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature white flax fish.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Hummingbird: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature white flax hummingbirds.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Owl: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature white flax owls.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Skink: A lone pink linen skink crouches upon the backside of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Snake: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature pink linen snakes.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Spider: The fabric boasts a crouching spider depicted in pink linen thread.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>~Designs~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Arabesque: Elegant black flax threading subtly accents the front of the garment in an arabesque design.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Celestial: Sparkling black flax threads depict an elaborate celestial design across the back of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Criss-cross: Criss-cross black flax patterns etch a curious design along the length of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Fleur-de-lis: Elaborate white flax threading devours the garment in a fleur-de-lis design.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Geometric: Simplistic white flax threading covers the front of the garment in a geometric design.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Knot: Knots and crosses spatter the material in white flax thread.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Knotwork: Delicate white flax needlework forms a celtic knotwork across the side of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Smoke: Delicate wisps of threaded pink linen smoke radiate over the garment in circular patterns.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>~Scenery~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Cloudy mountain: A majestic black flax mountain seemingly rises from the front of the fabric, circled overhead by a halo of billowing clouds.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Foray: Some white flax embroidery depicts a cluster of butterflies and bees in a foray of pollen gathering.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Mountain: Mountains of all shapes and sizes decorate the surface of this garment in elaborate white flax threading.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n~Shapes~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Anchor: An anchor comprised of black flax threading adorns the surface. In maritime lore, this symbol represents the success of a seaman upon the ocean. It is said to guarantee stability and security in the physical world, and, by extension, also steadfastness, hope, and trust\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Circle: Complicated and delicate black flax celtic circles curve along the seams of the garment before tracing back on each other to form seemingly endless mazes.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Cloud: Meandering black flax threads forms a swirling cloud design across the side of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Dot: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature black flax dots.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Fist: The fabric has been embroidered in white flax thread with a strong fist.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Flame: Embroidered white flax flames dance across the seams of the garment with the heart of each flame emboldened by rich yellow stitching.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Heart: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature white flax hearts.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Rapier: Glinting pink linen rapiers cross to make an X on the middle of the garment. Each blade is well detailed from the hilt to the tip.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Shield: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature pink linen shields.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Ship: A ship and anchor have been elaborately embroidered in pink linen thread on the material.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Skull: An accurately detailed skull is displayed in pink linen thread on the backside of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Star: Tiny ribbon-worked pink linen stars add a touch of elegance to this garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>~Random~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Constabulary crest: The left side of this garment bears three seashells on a black flax shield, with two spears crossed behind.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Gorath: Miniature goraths in various stages of carrying, collecting, and consuming white flax berries are situated upon the body of the garment.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Idol: The seams of this garment are lined with miniature white flax Lutaran idols.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n~Seasonal~\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Ghost: Gossamer-like white flax threads depict spooky ghosts floating along the surface of the fabric.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Jack o\&#65533; lantern: The fabric has been embroidered in white flax thread with miniature jack o' lanterns.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Pumpkin: Shimmering pink linen thread portrays creepily carved pumpkin faces upon the surface of the fabric.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Spooky mansion: Super-thin pink linen threads fuse together in elaborate depictions of dilapidated mansions, complete with miniature apparitions and otherworldly details.\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:~inventory~">
         (\{ "members", "**Our guild policy is to do the best that we can. And eat pudding. Lots of pudding.**" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:~orders~">
         (\{ "members", "\<p\>\<u\>Current:\</u\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<b\>Ava\</b\>-\\r\\n\<p\> -No materials provided-\\r\\n\<p\> ~60 florins~\\r\\n\<p\> x6 aquamarine silk lilies *\\r\\n\<p\> x1 aquamarine silk lotus\\r\\n\<p\> x6 coral silk lilies *\\r\\n\<p\> x1 coral silk lotus\\r\\n\<p\> x1 pearl satin curtains *\\r\\n\<p\> x1 pearl satin drapes *\\r\\n\<p\> Flag, pearl, embroidered with custom (seaside spa, S as seahorse.)\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<br/\> \\r\\n\<p\>-Towels-\\r\\n\<p\> ~30 florins~\\r\\n\<p\> x2 aquamarine linen towels \\r\\n\<p\> x2 coral linen towels\\r\\n\<p\> x4 pearl linen towels\\r\\n\<p\> x1 persimmon velvet towel (dieter)\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\> \<b\>German Consulate-\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Outfits for all current members. \\r\\n\<p\>*several sketches are placed below, a small handful of men, and three woman* ((ooc: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1T2KxXgI3GdCxv2dbNmhNRENTY_FkbNLnXe03Tb7ISzc/edit?usp=sharing))\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<u\>Finished:\</u\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<b\> Ava- aquamarine, coral, pearl\</b\>\\r\\n\<p\> -xxx80 florins, PAID-\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x1 aquamarine silk artificial lotus (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x1 coral silk artificial lotus (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x6 coral silk artificial lilies (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x6 aquamarine silk artificial lilies (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x1 pearl satin curtains (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x1 pearl satin drapes (completed)\\r\\n\<p\> SENT x8 towels (completed)\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<b\> Heather- emerald, golden brown (complete)\</b\> \\r\\n\<p\> Req materials- 3 uses of emerald dye\\r\\n\<p\> -130 florins, PAID-\\r\\n\<p\> Full order sent - 5x rolls, 2x cushions, 2x bench cushions, 4x dec pillows. \\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
