<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#990033", "bgcolor2":"#ffcccc", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#cc3399", "fonttype":"Helvetica", "h1color":"#990033", "h1type":"Georgia", "h2color":"#990033", "h2type":"Georgia", "h3color":"#990033", "h3type":"Helvetica" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "This is your default guild page. This is the first page your members see when they come here.", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Services\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>Our services are listed below. Please reach out to schedule an appointment today!\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Hairstyling - 24 florins\</h3\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Hairstyling services are charged at a flat-rate of 24 florins, which includes a cut, texture, and styling. Please see our records for all the options available.\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Facials and Facial Hair - 12 florins\</h3\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Facials, including trims and shaves of facial hair, are priced at a flat-rate of 12 florins, which includes skin cleansing, warm towels, trims, shaves, and styling.\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Manicures - 24 florins\</h3\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Price includes hot oil treatment, cuticle care and polishing. Please see our records for available polish colors or write to request a special color and pricing for rare polishes.\</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:hairstyling options">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>AVAILABLE HAIRSTYLING OPTIONS\</h2\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>TEXTURES\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>- abundant, ample, azure-streaked\<br\>\\r\\n- balding, billowy, bleach-streaked, bouncy, bountiful, bristly, burnished, bushy\<br\>\\r\\n- caramel-streaked, cerise-streaked, chunky, clean, coarse, combed, copious, curly\<br\>\\r\\n- dark, deficient, delicate, downy\<br\>\\r\\n- feathery, feral, fine, flouncy, flowy, fluffy, fluid, frizzy, full\<br\>\\r\\n- golden-streaked, greasy, greying\<br\>\\r\\n- hazel-streaked, highlighted\<br\>\\r\\n- ill-kempt\<br\>\\r\\n- kinky\<br\>\\r\\n- light, lively, lush, lustrous\<br\>\\r\\n- messy\<br\> \\r\\n- neat\<br\>\\r\\n- opulent\<br\>\\r\\n- puffy\<br\>\\r\\n- satiny, scant, shiny, silken, silver-streaked, smooth, soft, sparse, sweeping\<br\>\\r\\n- thick\<br\>\\r\\n- unruly\<br\>\\r\\n- voluminous\<br\>\\r\\n- wavy, willowy, wiry, wispy\<br\>\</i\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>LENGTHS\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<I\>- ankle-length\<br\>\\r\\n- botched, butchered\<br\>\\r\\n- cheek-length, chin-length, close-cropped\<br\>\\r\\n- floor-length\<br\>\\r\\n- hip-length\<br\>\\r\\n- knee-length\<br\>\\r\\n- long, lopsided\<br\>\\r\\n- medium\<br\>\\r\\n- ordinary, overlong\<br\>\\r\\n- shaved, short, shoulder-length\<br\>\\r\\n- thigh-length, trimmed\<br\>\\r\\n- waist-length\<br\>\</i\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>HAIRSTYLES\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Accent Braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The hair is done up loose with a small accent braid that hangs down the side of the head.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Accent Braids\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The hair is done up loose with small accent braids that hang down the sides of the head.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Angled Partition\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A long hairstyle in which luxurious waves are molded into bold definition and positioned to surround the face. The angled side partition provides an air of sophistication and elegance to the otherwise simple design.\</i\>\<br\> \\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Beaded Braids\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A loose style in which the hair has been woven into a myriad of braids before being tied off at the ends with beads.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Billowing Curls\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>This hairstyle starts with a classic bowl cut with tapered edges and chipped-in texturing. The locks on the sides and back are then styled into coils in order to add volume and movement in the look, while the top and forward portions of the hair are kept in smooth form to provide a pleasing contrast to the textured curl.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Bobbed\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A classic style in which the hair has been cut to chin-length and tapered inward to sleekly frame the face.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Bowl Cut\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair which has been cut, literally, in the shape of a bowl. Several inches of length remain on the top of the head while the bottom features a close-cropped style with no apparent transition between the two lengths\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Braided\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair that has been split into three even portions before being neatly woven together to form a simple braid. It is secured at the bottom by a ribbon.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Braided Bun\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair which has been pulled up into a ponytail and then divided into two portions which have been individually braided. One braid is wound in a clockwise direction while the other is wound counterclockwise against the back of the head before being secured.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Braided Dome\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The hair has been manipulated into a poufed dome atop the crown of the head, with a ribbon-laced wrap braid neatly framing its circumference.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Braided Nape Knot\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair that has been braided, rolled into an elegant knot, and then fastened at the nape of the neck.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Braided Ponytail\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The hair is wholly gathered and tied up at the back of the head into a ponytail before being braided and secured anew, leaving a couple of inches of tresses hanging loose beneath the accessory.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Bun\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A style in which the hair has been pulled back from the face, twisted or plaited, and wrapped in a circular coil around itself on the back of the head.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Cascade\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The locks of hair seem to naturally flow downward in a cascade style.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Cascading Ponytail\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A women's long hairstyle where the hair has been pulled to the top of the head into a high pony with the tail cascading down the back in luxurious waves.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Centered Waves\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A male style in which the hair has been parted centrally at the front of the head to feather back above the ears. The remaining tresses are left unrestrained and hang down the back.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Chignon\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A loose coiled bun which is worn low and secured against the nape of the neck.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Circlet Braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair done in a tidy braid that is wrapped once around the upper head to resemble a circlet. It is secured with pins and offers a sturdy anchor point for tiaras or veils.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Coiled\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair done in a thick braid that is wound into a large, flat, wide bun around the top and back of the head.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Combed Back\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair which has been backwardly run through with a comb to create a neat, clean appearance.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Combover\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair which has been combed over a particular part on the head to hide a balding spot.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Crew Cut\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Hair that has been cut short on the sides and trimmed low on the top of the head.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Crimped\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>An undulating style created close to the head which presents an even flow of impressive kinks and waves.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Curl Assembly\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>Tresses clipped in layers and brought back into a relaxed assembly of curls in the crown and flowing all the way down to rest upon the neckline. Textured bangs blend effortlessly while maximizing the elegance of the style on the wearer.\\r\\nDraped Braids: A style in which the hair has been separated into two individually braided portions and then looped outward and attached underneath via pins to lend a draped appearance.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Curled\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A style in which the hair has been brushed and manipulated into soft, loose curls.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Curled Bun with Flowers\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>The hair has been curled and elegantly wound into an intricate vine-like bun design against the nape before being laced with miniature flowers.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Curled Upstyle\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A festive and stunning upstyle that combines an elegant silhouette with wild and partially free flowing curls. The hair is twirled and fastened with invisible pins before the ends are shaped to perfection.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Draped Braids\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A style in which the hair has been separated into two individually braided portions and then looped outward and attached underneath via pins to lend a draped appearance.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Dreadlocks\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>A style in which the hair is either twisted into rope-like locks or consists of long, thin braids radiating from the scalp.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>Dutch Braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>An elaborate combination of two french braids on either side of the head which join toward the back of the head to form a braided bun.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>feathery-spikes\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>festive-ringlets\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>finger-curls\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>fingerwaves\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>fishtail-braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>flat-top\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>french-braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>french-twist\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>half-and-half\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>halo-braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>laced-back\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>layered-curls\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>layers\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>looped-braids\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>loose\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>loose-bangs\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>love-lock\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>messy-knot\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>mohawk\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>mullet\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>mussed\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>nape-knot\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>natural-wave\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>pageboy\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>parted-accents\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>pigtails\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>plaited\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>ponytail\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>ponytail-bangs\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>pulled-back\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>pulled-back-with-accent\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>pulled-back-with-bangs\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>relaxed-fringe\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>rope-braid\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>shag\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>shaved-cascade\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>short-flipup\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>short-fringes\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>sideswept-wave\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>slicked-back\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>snake-braided-ponytail\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>spiked\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>spiked-swell\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>steep-crown\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>swirltop-bun\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>tiered-bun\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>tight-rows\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>tonsure\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>top-knot\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>topknot-fringe\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>tousled\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>tousled-flowers\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>two-braids\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>uncombed\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>uplifted\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>windblown\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>\<b\>worn-up\</u\>\</b\> - \<I\>\</i\>\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
