<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#660066", "bgcolor2":"#ffffcc", "bgimg1":"http://www.cazswardrobe.com/images/purple_felt.jpg", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Garamond", "h1color":"#660066", "h1type":"Georgia", "h2color":"#cc6600", "h2type":"Georgia", "h3color":"#ff9933", "h3type":"Georgia" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin: favored positions">
         (\{ "members", "\<h1\>House Favored Positions and Roles\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThese roles and positions are not Members of the Rinaldi House. They are crafters, artisans and specialists in the City that have the favor of the Rinaldi and are trusted with orders due to their integrity and craftsmanship.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Jeweler(s) - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Jeweler(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Seamstress(s) - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Seamstress(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Tailor(s)\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Tailor(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Dyer(s) - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Dyer(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Stylist(s) -  \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Stylist(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Carpenter(s)\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Carpenter(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Book-Binder(s) -  \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Carpenter(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Favored Armourer(s) - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Favored Armourer(s) have the trust and support of the Rinaldi" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin: house positions">
         (\{ "members", "\<h1\>Embassy Positions and Roles\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>Leadership of the Embassy\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Ambassador - Lady Wynter\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Ambassador oversees the House in both civil and military matters. The Ambassador sets the policies, diplomatic agendas, trades and all things related to the House. If the Ambassador is not the highest ranking member, it is the Ambassador's duty to listen to those of higher rank and take their opinion and advice into consideration; however, as it pertains to the House, the Ambassador has the final word on all related matters and issues.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Reeve -  Miss Calypso \</h4\>\\r\\nThe duties and responsibilities of the Reeve are to oversee the running of the House and it's Members. The Reeve holds authority over the Common Members and Servants and is the liaison between the Nobility and Members of the House. The Reeve organizes the day-to-day business of the Household, oversees the organization of socials and events (assisting the Master of Ceremonies if they require it). The Reeve is responsible for assigning assistants to various tasks and positions within the House. The Reeve is also the Secretary of the House as it pertains to outside citizens contacting the Nobility of the House and may act or respond on behalf of the Nobility\<br/\>\\r\\nThe duties of the Reeve include keeping the nobles and ambassador of the House informed of what is going on, making sure the nobles requests are heeded and that the House thrives. The Reeve typically oversees recruitment of new members and the payment of the civil servants of the house, normally in agreement with the ambassador.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master Liaison of Newtown - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe duties of the Master Liaison include keeping the nobles and ambassador of the House informed of political ties to other Houses and their relationships. The Master Liaison assists the Ambassador in handling important matters of politics and diplomacy. The Master Liaison is required to be skilled in the art of communication, diplomacy and courtesy. It is also expected that bonds and ties to other Houses are strengthened due to the efforts of the Master Liaison.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master Liaison to Docktown -  \</h4\>\\r\\nThe duties of the Master Liaison to Docktown include keeping the nobles and ambassador of the House informed of matters and issues pertaining to Docktown. The Master Liaison to Docktown must keep the Ambassador and Reeve informed, either through verbal word or written reports. The Master Liaison to Docktown is required to be skilled in the art of communication, diplomacy and courtesy. It is also expected that relations between Newtown and Docktown are smoothed and strengthened due to the efforts of the Master Liaison of Docktown.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master Secretary - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master Secretary is the keeper of the Secrets of the House, as well as that of the city, and ensures that the information the House has is always updated and correct. To keep these secrets the Master Secretary is also in charge of the keeping and security of a trunk/chest/or cabinet designated by the House in which to store important House documents. \</br\>\\r\\nThe Master Secretary should prepare a report of pertinent activities for the Ambassador and Reeve at least once every two months, as well as attempt to host a day to gather recent events from House members once every two weeks if not more.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>Masters of the Embassy\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Liaison of the Church - \</h4\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master of Ceremonies - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master of Ceremonies is responsible for all major and official events, socials and gatherings. From the planning stages to the execution, the Master of Ceremonies organizes them with the aid of the Reeve, House Steward and Master of the Arts. The Master of Ceremonies ensures (with the help of the aforementioned) that entertainment, decorations, refreshments and food are provided. The Master of Ceremonies oversees that the socials are conducted according to tradition and custom, including educating and informing assistants of their roles. \<br/\>\\r\\nThe duties of the Master of Ceremonies also extends to personally welcomes guests, introducing and announces guests, as well as being the formal speaker. The Master of Ceremonies is charged with maintaining a record of all events, whether annual, bi-annual or monthly.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>House Steward - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Steward is responsible for minor socials and events. He or she is in charge of overseeing that food, drink and entertainment is provided. The House Steward's major role is working alongside the Master of Ceremonies and is in affect the Assistant to the Master of Ceremonies when such a time is needed. It is the Stewards' responsibility that minor social runs smoothly. It is also the House Steward's responsibility to oversee ALL invitations are sent out in a timely manner for Major and Minor social events for the House. The House Steward may enlist the help from the Reeve and the Master of the Arts.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Mistress of the Hunt and Expeditions - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master of the Hunt is responsible for hosting and organizing hunts for the peers. It is his/her responsibility that a Hunt is appropriate and safe for all participants, and that the guests are entertained.\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Master of the Hunt will engage the aid of the Steward for foods and drinks and the Captain for security during the Hunt, as well as usage of scouts.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master Chronicler - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe responsibilities of the Master Chronicler is to record all events and happenings related to the House. He writes the present history of the House, and knows the past history of the House. Through the Master Chronicler, the life of the house is documented and organized.\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Master Chronicler should prepare a report of pertinent activities for the Ambassador and Reeve at least once every two months, as well as attempt to host a day to gather recent events from House members once every two weeks if not more. These reports could be given during House Meetings.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Cup Bearer\</h4\>\\r\\nThe duty of the cup-bearer is to serve drinks to the nobles in the House and their noble guests during socials. His responsibility is to ensure that no drink is poisoned, so will also have the duty of testing drinks served to nobles himself.\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Cup-bearer's duty is to know of poisons, their use and be able to recognize them, so that he can protect the nobles better. Through his knowledge he will advise the guard and other relevant parties to ensure safety for all House members, in particular the nobles. The Cup Bearer works alongside the Master of Botany.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>House Servant\</h4\>\\r\\nThe House Servant is essentially an assistant to the Reeve and assists as needed with the House, missives, messages, postings and other related matters.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>Personal Positions to Nobles\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Personal Secretary\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Secretary is a personal assistant to a Noble. They keep the noble's secrets, and manage all correspondence to the noble. The Secretary is the person others write to get in contact with the noble, they write missives for the noble, and keep the noble's personal calendar, sets up meetings and do other private tasks for the noble requested.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>House Valet\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Valet is responsible to ensure that the noble whom they serve has proper appearances in all areas (clothing, jewellery, hair, etc). This can include maintaining the clothes of a Noble, helping with appearances (jewellery, hair, shaving etc), running baths and serving breakfast in the room.\<br/\>\\r\\nDue to the intimate nature of the service, one of opposite gender is not appropriate.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>House Handmaiden - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Handmaiden is responsible to ensure that the noble whom they serve has proper appearances in all areas (clothing, jewellery, make-up, hair etc). This can include maintaining the clothes of a Noble, helping with appearances (make-up, jewellery, hair, shaving etc), running baths and serving breakfast in the room.\<br/\>\\r\\nDue to the intimate nature of the service, one of opposite gender is not appropriate.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Squire \</h4\>\\r\\nThe duties of a Squire includes tending the Knight, handling correspondence, aid and maintenance of weapons and armor, running errands and supporting the Knight on the field. \<br/\>\\r\\nThe purpose of Squiring is to prepare and train to become a Knight, through service and observation of a Knight.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>Artisan and Other Positions\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Mistress of Etiquette - Lady Wynter\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master of Etiquette instructs the Members of the House on all matters of Courtesy, protocols, virtues and related knowledge for the benefit and betterment of the House and it's Common Members.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master of the Arts - Baronetess Camellia\</h4\> \\r\\nThe Master of the Arts is responsible for all Art related matters, such as portraits, musicals and theatrical performances. The Master Artist works alongside the Master of Ceremonies as it pertains to House held engagements, dinners, socials and events.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master of Astronomy - \</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master of Astronomy is responsible for documenting the celestial bodies (such as moons, planets, stars, asteroids, comets, nebulae and galaxies), both scientifically and mystically. \\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master of Botany\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Master of Botany oversees the gardens of the House. In addition, they are allowed to experiment with expanding upon their knowledge of plants, herbalism and botany with the support of the House.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Master of the Linguistics- Esquire Faust \</h4\>  \\r\\nThe Master of the Linguistics is skilled in all languages and is charged with translating documents or word." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin: military positions">
         (\{ "members", "\<h3\>Military Roles\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Commander - Captain Kino\</h4\>\\r\\nThe Commander of the Guard oversees the training and instruction of the Soldiers.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>High Military Officer - Countess Kilana\</h4\>\\r\\nThe High Military Officer assists and oversees a certain garrison group and naval group. He or she recruits for the military, oversees military players, aids the Guard if required.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Ranks and Promotions\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Recruit\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThis is the lowest rank a guard can have. All recruits are initially given a cloak and a weapon and will be assessed over the following week to see if they are fit for the guard. If they are deemed fit, they will be asked to take the oath to become an official guard and will be issued a uniform.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Naval Soldier/Sailor\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThose of this rank have passed the recruit period and have officially sworn their loyalty to the House.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Guardsman\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThose of this rank have passed the recruit period and have officially sworn their loyalty to the House.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Soldier\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThose of this rank have passed the recruit period and have officially sworn their loyalty to the House.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Naval Officer\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nOfficers of the Guard have proven themselves loyal and capable of leadership. Upon being promoted to officer, a bronze Rinaldi ring and a steel dagger will be issued to the Navy. Along with basic duties of a guard, Officers will be responsible for recruiting and mentoring new members.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Guard Officer\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nOfficers of the Guard have proven themselves loyal and capable of leadership. Upon being promoted to officer, a bronze Rinaldi ring and a steel dagger will be issued to the guard. Along with basic duties of a guard, Officers will be responsible for recruiting and mentoring new members.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Army Officer\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nOfficers of the Guard have proven themselves loyal and capable of leadership. Upon being promoted to officer, a bronze Rinaldi ring and a steel dagger will be issued to the guard. Along with basic duties of a guard, Officers will be responsible for recruiting and mentoring new members.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Lieutenant\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nLieutenants of the Guard takes charge of the Guard should the Captain be absent for any reason, when the Captain is active the Lieutenant has the duty of keeping an eye on the Officers.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Captain\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThe Captain is in charge of the entire Guard. It is the Captain's responsibility to see that Guard continues to prosper and serve the House as it should.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Guard Duties\</h3\>\\r\\nThese duties are expected to be performed by all members of the Rinaldi Guard.\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Protect members of the Rinaldi\</b\> \<br\>The purpose of the Guard is to protect members of the Rinaldi and the Rinaldi's interests. If a person or building is being harrassed or harmed, it is our job to step in and handle the situation. We do not have the authority to arrest or fine anyone and we should not interfere in matters that do not involve the Rinaldi directly. That is what the Constabulary is for. If someone (with honor) is insulting the Rinaldi, we can ask for an apology. If they do not give an apology, we can challenge them to a duel. If they choose not to accept, they will be labeled a coward and it is assumed that they are taking back their offensive words. (See rules on dueling for more information)\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Patrol daily\</b\> \<br\>Upon being recruited, guards will be assigned an area in the city to patrol daily.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Write weekly reports\</b\> \<br\>Guards are to write reports of their observations. If a week has gone by without any notable events, that still needs to be reported.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Train\</b\> \<br\>All members are expected to train on their own.\<br\>\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Attend meetings\</b\> \<br\>It is unreasonable to expect all members to attend all meetings but attempts should be made. If a member is unable to attend a meeting, an Officer or Captain should be contacted and told such.\<br\>\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Pay\</h3\>\\r\\nAll members of the Guard will be paid a minimum of two denarii per day. This rate will increase at the discretion of the Captain.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<i\>\<quote\>\\"It is one thing to bring people under your yoke with a hand so strong that it makes them fear to break the word of your law. It is quite another office to convince them to travel your roads, even on the darkest night, under the aegis of your rule. The Rinaldi created a covenant of trust rather than of fear, and Calabria stands alone among all places of the world as a testament to the wisdom of these folk.\\"\</quote\> --Alyosha Yenot\</i\>", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "Baron Ruggero is the current Ambassador of the Rinaldi and Baronetess Kilana is Reeve.\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nOther members of note are:\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Baroness Wynter Donovan\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dame Isidora di Rinaldi\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Private Callais du Chalon\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:information: low favor list">
         (\{ "members", "" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi chronicler's page">
         (\{ "members", "Work In Progress... \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nTo Do: \<br\>\\r\\nChonicler's Trunk (x)\\r\\nLock for Trunk ( )\\r\\nMeeting Ground ( )" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi monthly news">
         (\{ "members", "\<i\>\<p\>This section is a monthly update of news relevant to the City of Triskellian and the Great House of Rinaldi. All members are encouraged in updating the information herein with their own experiences, or provide with information to Private Callais to perform an update.\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Flower, 898\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<p\>[May 2017]\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Dame Giavanna\</b\> has arrived to the City and joined the Rinaldi Embassy.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Callais\</b\> has earned the rank of Lancepesade and appointed as Embassy Sergeant. \<b\>Adelaide\</b\> has been added to the Guard roster and earned the probationary position of Recruit. \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Grass, 898\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<p\>[April 2017]\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Baron Ruggero\</b\> has been elected Ambassador of the Great House of Rinaldi. House Meetings have been moved to Sundays at 1pm (EST time).\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>Lady Wynter\</b\> has taken a temporary leave of absence to her private estate.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>Callais\</b\> has been promoted to the rank of Private, taken his vows as Squire to Brigadier Dasha di Silvi, and appointed as Liaison to the Constabulary.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>Julietta\</b\> has joined the House and appointed as Liaison to the Church. \<b\>Yeoman Maggie\</b\>, \<b\>Physician Suavis\</b\> and \<b\>Esquire Ellaith\</b\> have returned to the City.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA ghost of a Rinaldi servant has appeared in Oldtown. He is a wispy ghost in the shape of a red fox, clad in a purple jacket, and responds to the name of \<b\>Tomas Cavano\</b\>. He seems to be mostly harmless, though has the tendency of dropping food and drinks over people in an attempt at serving them. The records at the Triskellian Library speak of Tomas Cavano as a capable and loved valet at Rinaldi Manor that perished in the plague, nearly a century ago. With the assistance of \<b\>Baron Romain\</b\> and \<b\>Sergeant-Major Namor\</b\> of the Constabulary, the ghost was banished by the chanting of Matriloquentian prayers and Holy Water. For more information, contact \<b\>Private Callais\</b\>.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Sap, 898\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<p\>[March 2017]\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Callais\</b\> has returned to Triskellian and reappointed as an active guard in the House." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi: imports">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h1\>Imports of the Great House Rinaldi\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>General Rules:\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\> 1) You must be a member on the roster to order any of these.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> 2) If you want the price listed you must send in all material needed.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> 3) All prices listed are denarii based. You may spend (50 trade) tokens or (200d) kitty but you have to have rights to spend tokens to do this.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> 4) You may now buy materials needed for direct imports from staff, but be warned the price will go up considerably when you buy them from staff. \</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>Imports\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\> 1) Buttoned Swordsman Shirt:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\> Material Cost: 3 yards dyed fabric (note: this is a separate charge). \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Coin Cost: 200D\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Description:  Boasting full-length sleeves and traditional cuffs, this shirt falls past the waist and is adorned with a small collar accompanied by a trail of fine (shape) (metal) buttons down the front. It is designed to be loose and comfortable in the body while fitted at the wrists to ensure that the flowing fabric of the sleeves does not interfere with hand or sword movement.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\> 2) Crystal-embellished Short Dress:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\> Material Cost: 4 yards dyed fabric (note: this is a separate charge). \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Coin Cost: 200D\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Description: Adorned with a glittering, crystal-embellished bodice that catches light from every angle, this dress is a must have for fashionistas who want a look that's opulent and over-the-top. The elegant sweetheart neckline and cupcake-inspired (color) (material) skirt offer a flattering, feminine and flirty fit for many body types, while the high hemline gives ample room to show off your favorite footwear.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\> 3) Front-laced Pants:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\> Material Cost: 4 yards dyed fabric (note: this is a separate charge). \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Coin Cost: 200D\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Description: A simple trouser featuring belt loops around the waist and frontal lace fastenings. The legs are full-length and fitted to taper naturally with the shape of the wearer. The bottoms lack cuffs but can be tightened using the matching laces provided, allowing for a small measure of adjustability.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\> 4) Open-sleeved Long Dress:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\> Material Cost: 4 yards dyed fabric (note: this is a separate charge). \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Coin Cost: 200D\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> Description: An intricately designed dress featuring a (variation) beaded v-neck bodice with a flattering empire waist that flows into a luxurious A-line skirt which brushes against the floor.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi: news - jade landers">
         (\{ "members", "\<h3\>Jade Lander Updates\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>27th of Flower\</h4\>\\r\\n\\r\\nXena and I were returning home from our honeymoon and stopped by the Corsairs. We learned that the Jade Landers have been residing there. About eight months ago a large group of them sailed out but only a few came back. They have been rebuilding there ever since. The locals stay away from them as anyone who goes too close doesn't return (ships included).\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nMarcus\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>28th of Flower\</h4\>\\r\\n\\r\\nScouts were assigned the task of gathering intelligence against our enemies.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nMarcus\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>3rd of Strawberry\</h4\>\\r\\nThe scouts returned to with some information: Their force seems fairly small, at least less than a 1000, spread over several islands. Most ships are being rebuilt and repaired, not many actually sea-worthy. It seems more like a more permanent settlement, with a small village with various buildings. Barracks, granary, shipyard and stuff like that. If there are mages, they're not advertising them. There's the usual religious worship and such, but nothing remarkable. It seems like they're mostly focusing on making a strong presence where they are and keep pirates and other locals away from their homes. Their main base seems to be a small village pulled a bit away from the beach where the shipyard is located. Others are just smaller settlements, huts and the like. Some are even farming and crowing crops, and it looks like they've taken some local woman as well, either as spouses or slaves, it's impossible to tell. There are even a few crying babies in the outlying settlements. There's probably some 5-600 in the main village, the rest are more like handfuls scattered around in various settlements.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nMarcus\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>4th of Strawberry\</h4\>\\r\\nA  meeting was held to fill the town in on the situation though I was careful not to overshare what we know (we don't know who is listening and who they might be telling). We decided to recruit support in three areas: 1) Repairs to the docks so we can fortify them in the even of another attack. 2) A possible attack against the Jade Landers. 3) Defense for the city in case we do send a group out to deal with the Jade Landers.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nWe decided we aren't sure how we are going to handle them especially considering there are innocent women and children in the mix. Some suggest they are just broken and looking for a way to survive and may just want help getting home. I'm less convinced of this argument considering that months ago they wanted to take over Calabria. Either way, we need more information before we can proceed. We'll spend more time investigating and meet again on the 11th to put together everything we know and what we should do.\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThis is what we have as far as assignments and contributions:\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nCITY REPAIRS:\<br/\>\\r\\nNoire (she is overseeing the repairs)\<br/\>\\r\\nTriskellian University (stonemasons to help with repairs)\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Sailors Guild (provided stone to help with repairs)\<br/\>\\r\\nBisclavret (carpenters to help with repairs)\<br/\>\\r\\nRinaldi (we will provide what workers we can for the cause)\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nOFFENSIVE TACTICAL GROUP:\<br/\>\\r\\nRinaldi\</br\>\\r\\nBisclavret \<br/\>\\r\\nAvoirdupois \<br/\>\\r\\nSailors Guild \<br/\>\\r\\nSinners and Saints \<br/\>\\r\\nMartial Games \<br/\>\\r\\nTriskellian University \<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nCITY DEFENSE:\<br/\>\\r\\nThe constables will \<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nOTHER:\<br/\>\\r\\nSo We Can So (willing to provide men for the fight if needed and will also provide materials for healing supplies)\<br/\>\\r\\nFishamajiggers (willing to provide men for the fight if needed)\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nMarcus\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Meeting 11th of Strawberry\</h4\>\\r\\nWe met to share any information uncovered over the past week and devise new plans. Not much new information was learned although Zaria compiled some information that could prove to be quite useful. We asked ourselves what information we need to know before we can devise and definitive plan of attack. We need to know ho powerful they actually are.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>Do they have allies in Calabria?\</b\> \<br/\>\\r\\nThey previously had dealings with all the criminal organizations across the continent. The Houses will investigate their sources in their respective lands to see if those relationships still exist. \<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>Do they have allies in the Corsairs?\</b\> \<br/\>\\r\\nWe will send a group to attempt to recruit the Lowlanders (a group inhabiting the Corsairs) as allies. This effort will be led by Silvanus and Zaria with Adon leading negotations. They are in dire need of healers and healing supplies so no doubt we can arrange something there. It would be good to have them on our side in the event that we need to attack the Jade Landers there. \<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<b\>What is their purpose here?\</b\>\<br/\>\\r\\nWe have a Jade Lander leader in our custody that we plan to interrogate. Adon and I will be handling this. Doctor Hush has also tasked her scholars to learn more about the Jade Lander culture... what motivates them and such.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe constabulary will be increasing patrols in case the Jade Landers do decide to attack us first and in case there are Jade Lander spies lurking. Noire is making slow progress with the dock repairs but slow progress is better than no progress at all.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nMarcus\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h4\>Leadership Changes\</h4\>\\r\\nAfter speaking with Zaria, it became clear to me that she is better suited to oversee this Jade Lander situation. She was involved in nearly every event from the beginning and has a better understanding of what we are up against. The Rinaldi will support her fully and continue to lend aid to the situation. I will remain in contact with her and keep these notices updated as I receive the information.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h4\>What are the Jadelanders capable of?\</h4\>\\r\\n\<i\>Notes compiled by Zaria\</i\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThey have been known to employ guns such as blunderbuss and others for sniping. They've had spies planted within the city, and the Constabulary, and bribed others for information. They associate with thieves, namely Captain Hooked whom guided the ship filled with giant spiders into the Docks for a bribe.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nForeigners - West Triskellian - A small bank was started nearby, founded by gold from a foreign country to pay the following groups suggesting there are outsiders with vested interest on Calabria. The city was full of mercenaries and the remnants of the other groups once they had been dealt with. We encountered giant spiders and mounted soldiers (Zaria captured one of the higg'n dray for her own). We scouted the city, destroyed their bank, and escaped so we could conclude the battle there. They had three siege weapons, one huge and the other two in the shape of tigers. They also had wizards with command of the elements (Koz punched a dragon in the face, killing it). The elementalists had an invisible shield seemingly protecting themselves, but when it dropped they died instantly. This is not the same battle as on the outskirts of Triskellian itself.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Thieves Guild - Triskellian (Rinaldi) - A basic underground network of thieves working around and within Triskellian. - They are known to have been decimated in the sewers by Clover, Sir Bayard, Kaine and Fyros.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Assassins Blade - Bruges (Doloreaux) - Built on the foundations of children who have been kidnapped and raised to Assassinate. There was a snowbeast attack on the outskirts of Bruges, they were said to be controlled by an orb, which was destroyed. - Tended to by Sir Bayard, Zaria, Clover, Ilo, Sang, Fyros, Rickter and others.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Old Blood Purge - Chalon (Avoirdupois) - They are upper crust that believe only heritage grants land. They want to rid the land of all upstart new bloods and use any means necessary, including joining with our guilds. Most of this was trickery, spying and guns. Nothing unusual. - Those present: Esquire Meepers, Ammy, Chesh, Ilo, Hanneman, Lord Sabastien, Zanthia, Clover, Khagra, Nurse Sable, Physician Suavis, Mattimeo, Sylviane, Gane, Wynter, Fyros, Dame Xena, Kessla, Cullan and Zaria.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Minkers - Bisclavret/Phelan - A group of faux druids suspected of wanting to do ill will to people. They initially only committed petty crimes like theft, such as the instance where they robbed Dunwasser college of information about the elementals during the tsunami that hit Triskellian. Fyros et al and Zaria recovered the stolen items. They don't typically stay in one place for people to be able to learn more about them. The Minkers has artifacts that controlled the elements, having gained what they sought after. Earth Gnomes, Air Sylphs, Fire Salamanders and Water Undine. Some came back with gem-encrusted geodes, which held power to stop them. - Tended to by Aneira, Sir Bayard, Clover, Hanneman, Kaine, Sable, Dame Valara, Zaria, Rickter, Kalleah, Dasha, and Suavis.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nTogether they are the 'Four Corners', created by a council of the above leaders.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi: projects - current">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>The Rinaldi House: Current Projects, Socials and Events\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Bandit Hunt ~ House Rinaldi/Privateers of the Vicious Koi\</h3\>\\r\\nLord Ruggero and Miss Thais of the Vicious Koi are discussing the possibility of a joint effort to disrupt organized bandits outside of the City of Triskellian. More details will be provided later.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Contact:\</b\> ---\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Time:\</b\> ---\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Place:\</b\> ---\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Requirements:\</b\> ---" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi: projects - past">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>The Rinaldi recently finished these projects\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Akoman Cultural Festival ~ 15th Sap - 20th Sap, 897\</h3\>\\r\\nDame Ravenna hosted a week-long festival celebrating the culture of Akoma and the presence of Master Jalal bin Tawfiq. A feast kicked off events and mingling with House Rinaldi followed by days of trade, belly dancing lessons, and food and drink sampling.\<br/\>\\r\\nThis was initiated to increase cultural awareness and discuss a proposed marriage contract.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Black and White Ball ~ 25 Sap, 897\</h3\>\\r\\nHosted by Esquire Leliana; held in the Newtown ballroom. Music and basic food and drinks were provided much to the satisfaction of all.\<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rinaldi: the virtues">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>\<b\>THE HONOR VIRTUES\</b\>\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<h4\>The Honor Virtues are based on various lists and definitions of Chivalric Virtues.\</h4\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Prowess\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nProwess is a character's strength in endeavors, whether they are martial, mental or social. It is striving to be the best that you can be, at all times, in your endeavors. Improper use of Prowess could be seen as arrogance.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Gallantry\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nGallantry is related to Prowess in that it could almost be viewed as the artistic side of that prior Virtue. Gallantry says that your endeavors must not just be workmanlike and rote, but that they should be achieved in a manner that is stylish, accomplished, and celebratory, and that 'good enough' is never good enough. Inordinate or inappropriate Gallantry could result in being labeled a show-off.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Justice\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nJustice, as an Honor Virtue, speaks to due rewards, to proper compensation or consequence for actions, whatever they are, and not just as punishment for wrongdoing. Justice requires proper reward for service, kindness... as well as proper punishment for misdeeds and crimes. Justice is often tied to lawfulness as a goal, but they can work against each other when some do not believe what the Law requires is Just. Excessive Justice can, unfortunately, result in Vengefulness.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Fortitude\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nOne who is displays Fortitude is determined and dedicated, steadfast. Simple adversity does not daunt or slow them. Those who follow this Honor Virtue can be relied upon to finish what they begin. Irrational Fortitude, however, can result in Stubbornness.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Mercy\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nMercy is the Honor Virtue of compassion and forgiveness. It is what drives one to extend due regard to those who are weak, injured, impoverished, impeded, impaired, or defeated. In a sense it says that one must honor those who have fallen, symbolically or literally, and aid in building them up rather than exploiting their weakness.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Courage\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nCourage can be, and is often viewed, in relation to Fortitude, but where that Honor Virtue speaks to determination and conviction, Courage is the that which propels us against greater odds. Prowess is related as well, but Courage - since it is of the spirit and not the body - is often viewed as a greater Virtue. (Courage is easy when you have Prowess, but the reverse is not true.) Courage is not the absence of fear, but doing what needs to be done despite fear. Courage should also not be confused with stupidity, a wise man knows when he is beat, and when to stand his ground, get re-enforcement, or even retreat if that there are things greater than himself at stake. Excessive Courage can lead to recklessness.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Honesty\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nA man's word is his bond and you must guard against swearing lightly, as what is sworn must be done. You should also be honest in witness, being careful not to let your feelings or desires about something color your interpretation of recollection of events. Equally important, you must be honest with yourself and not let excuses or unfulfilled desires color your beliefs. Being honest and truthful, however, are two separate things. You can be honest while ignorantly being untruthful, but you cannot be dishonest without being untruthful. Some argue that avoiding truth is dishonesty, such as in avoiding speaking about a subject that one does have knowledge of. This, however, is a lesser error than being directly dishonest. Too much Honesty can lead to callousness.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Loyalty\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nThe Honor Virtue Loyalty speaks to the debt that we all owe those who assist us or to a cause we believe in. Loyalty is, of course, held to one's liege, but it can also be held to a friend, a patron or sponsor, provider, supervisor, or leader that you choose to follow. Often you may need to make personal sacrifices to support a person or ideal to which you are Loyal. Loyalty is also inherited in that it is hierarchical to some regard. If one has Loyalty toward an individual who in turn has Loyalty toward another, you inherit (so to speak) some of that Loyalty. (So, for example, if you are a squire to a knight who is loyal to Prince Bertram you have loyalty to Bertram as well.) To much Loyalty, however, can be a dangerous things as it can blind you to following along without thought or regard to how some action or instruction might be against one of the other Honor Virtues.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Charity\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nCharity is related in many ways to Mercy and Justice. It is not only Charity of goods and holdings ('largesse'), but is also open-mindedness, tolerance, benefit-of-the-doubt, and carrying a non-judgmental view. Too much Charity, however, can disrupt the proper balances of influence, favor, and Justice in the sense of one receiving their just reward, and no more.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Franchise\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nThe Honor Virtue of Franchise is that of a greater purpose, of a higher calling, to follow the other Honor Virtues for the betterment not only of your self but of home and kingdom as well. It is also faith that those around you are true to the Honor Virtues and a belief that your peers and betters, even those who oppose you, are nothing less than honorable (in that sense.) Franchise also says that some degree of this honor must exist even in the lowest commoner, in some form, if they are to ever have the potential to raise themselves up higher than they are. The result of excessive Franchise is Self-Righteousness, and narrow mindedness, leaving you too focused on yourself rather than the world.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Courtesy\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nCourtesy simply states that all those who follow the Honor Virtues are worthy of regard and respect. It is, on some level, recognition of Franchise in others and that they too follow the Honor Virtues. If Charity and Mercy are also to be followed then it can be easily seen why insult or belittlement is something to avoid in public and judgment reserved for a time when emotions are kept cooler and reasoned discussion can be had. The true test of Courtesy comes in attempting courtesy in the face of discourtesy. Another's poor behavior is no reason for one to follow suite, for to do so would only go against one's own Honor. It is best to try and see instances of discourtesy as tests of one's own Virtues and an opportunity to show one's Honor. He who successfully shows the grace under pressure of courtesy in the face of discourtesy is truly noble. For example, if someone who is your lesser insults you, it is more honorable to handle the situation with courtesy, and properly with lashings or a duel than reducing yourself to their level. You have to, of course, be careful that excessive Courtesy does not twist itself into Dishonesty.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Humility\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\nHumility comes from performing deeds, whether great or small, without calling attention to yourself or the good works that have been performed. \\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Faith\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Grace\</b\>\</li\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h2\>\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\nooc: taken from http://wiki.marrach.skotos.net/bin/view/Public/CMHonorDocument" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:schedules: house members">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>The Rinaldi House: Schedules of Members\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Baroness Wynter Donovan - Ambassador\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Availability: Monday thru Friday, Noon to 6PM (EST)\</i\>\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Mistress Calypso - Reeve\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Availability: \</i\>\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Master Kino - Captain\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>Availability: \</i\>\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:storage">
         (\{ "members", "\<h4\> Storage Inventory \</h4\>\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<i\>I've written to mister Fred of the Bisclavret House and ordered a trunk in which these items can be stored. I'll have a lock created to keep the items within secure and will pass out duplicate keys to members of high rank or those who have a hand in event planning. Once I determine where in the manor is the best place to put it, I will update here with the location.\<br/\>--Ravenna--\</i\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h1\>Main Storage\</h1\>\\r\\n\<h2\> Blankets \</h2\>\\r\\n    \<ul\>\\r\\n    \<li\> light blue velvet blanket \</li\>\\r\\n    \</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\> Cushions \</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 3 glossy garnet silk windmill-shaped cushions \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 1 light blue velvet overstuffed cushion \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 3 midnight green silk tower-shaped cushions \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 3 sparkling pale blue silk destrier-shaped cushions \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 4 wysteria silk seashell-shaped cushions \</li\>\\r\\n    \</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\> Miscellaneous \</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n    \<li\> 7 sets of cheering flags \</li\>\\r\\n    \</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h2\> Streamers \</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n    \<li\> glossy garnet embroidered silk streamers \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> midnight green embroidered silk streamers \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> sparkling pale blue silk embroidered streamers \</li\>\\r\\n    \<li\> wysteria embroidered silk streamers \</li\>\\r\\n    \</ul\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<h1\>Barracks Storage\</h1\>\\r\\n\<i\>(Last updated by Sergeant Callais on 15th of Flower, 898)\</i\> \\r\\n\<h2\>Weapons: Large poplar crate\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n     \<li\>6x sheathed iron longswords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x steel sword\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x iron swords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x copper sword\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x curved iron sword\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x iron short swords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>5x sheathed iron arming swords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x iron arming swords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x iron daggers\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x steel daggers\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x steel rapier\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>5x sheathed iron rapiers\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x sheathed copper rapier\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron sabre\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron smallsword\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron backsword\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron foil\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x sheathed iron scimitar\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x bronze cutlasses\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x sheathed iron cutlass\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>5x iron spears hanging from a black leather weapon strap\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x myrtle staff\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x aged black oak longbow\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x oakwood longbow\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>4x stacks of arrows\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>4x metal hatchets\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x mahogany flat box: Wooden swords\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x yew flat box: Wooden daggers\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Armor \& Shields: Medium white-lacquered hickory crate\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron codpiece\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron ailettes\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron schynbalds\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron lorica\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x iron gauntlets\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x iron bracers\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x green snakeskin bracers\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x iron greaves\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron helmet\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x iron sabatons\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x bronze cuirass\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x fancy steel plain arming caps\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x steel bevor\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x purple leather cuirass \</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x purple engraved leather ailettes\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron vambraces\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron chainmail coif\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron rerebraces\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron cuisses\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron pauldrons\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron chainmail aventail\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron burgonet\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron chainmail brigandine \</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron spangenhelm\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron gorget\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron spaulders\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron poleyns\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron couters\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron rondel\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>2x iron besagews\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron culet\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron hounskull\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>26x ash shields\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x copper shield\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>9x sugar maple shields\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>3x pine shields\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron heater shield\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x iron buckler\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Miscellaneous: Black Locust cabinet\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x purple leather manual\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x willow weapon blade\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x bolt of satin\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x roll of iron chainmail\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x purple velvet right arm sling\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x canvas left arm sling\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x large roll of white woolsey woven carpet\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x crimson leather satchel: Empty\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x blood red leather satchel: Empty\</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x ash grey suede satchel: Empty \</li\>\\r\\n     \<li\>1x package: Miscellaneous clothing\</li\> \\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trade deals">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Trading Deals\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h4\>Trading Deal: 22 March 2016\</h4\>\\r\\nApproved by Ambassador Wynter\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Sailor's Guild to receive 5 Cartouches every Month for the next 12 Months\<br/\>\\r\\n\<em\>Per Trade Agreement.\<br/\>\\r\\nYou read a lavender contract.\<br/\>\\r\\nIt is addressed to Xena.\<br/\>\\r\\nIt says:\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nComposed this Jeudi, the Twenty-Second Day of Sap in the Year of 897 Apres le Miracle.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\n~~~ Contract of Trade Goods ~~~\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Great House Rinaldi does hereby contractually agree to trade Five Cartouches every Month, beginning the date of this Contract, and for the next Eleven Months thereafter to the Sailors Guild for a total of Sixty Cartouches.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nThis Contract shall satisfy and conclude on Vendredi, the Twenty-Second Day of Sap in the Year of 898 Apres le Miracle.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nBy my hand,\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nWynter Donovan, Ambassador and Knight of the Great House of the Rinaldi.\<br/\>\\r\\n\<br/\>\\r\\nIt is signed by Dame Wynter.\</em\>\<br/\<br/\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:z - ooc info">
         (\{ "members", "HTML is pretty simple to work with, once you know how it works.\<br/\>\\r\\nWe're working with tags, that has to surround the text you want to make special. You can learn more by going here: \<a href=\\"http://www.w3schools.com/html/default.asp\\"\>http://www.w3schools.com/html/default.asp\</a\> \<br/\>\\r\\nBelow I will give a run-down of the most common and useful commands for editing @guild pages. \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\nYou'll have to go in and edit page to see precisely how it looks like though. All tags are enclosed by a \< tag \> and all tags have to end with a \< / tag \> (take out the spaces)\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\> \< h1 \> Header 1 \< /h1 \> \</h1\>\\r\\n\<h2\> \< h2 \> Header 2 \< /h2 \> \</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\> \< h3 \> Header 3 \< /h3 \> \</h3\>\\r\\n\<h4\> \< h4 \> Header 4 \< /h4 \> \</h4\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHeaders are done with the h1, h2, h3 and so on tags \<br/\> \<br/\>\\r\\nLinebreak \< br/ \> - here it's like two tags into one, so that's why the / comes after the br inside the \<\> You use them like you'd use it when you hit [enter] in a word processor. \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\<p\>\< p \>This is a paragraph. You can use the \< br/ \> tag inside a paragraph, as well as the italic and bold tags also as you want to. \<br/\> It's like a paragraph in a book really. It'll give you space around the block of text. You can also use two \< br/ \> tags right after each other to achieve the same effect.\< /p \>\</p\> \\r\\nTo make a list, you first make an \< ul \> tag, then for each point on the list do an \< li \> tag. Remember to close the tags\\r\\n\<ul\> \< ul \>\\r\\n\<li\> \< li \> line one \< /li \>\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>\< li \>line two \< /li \> \</li\>\\r\\n\<li\> \< li \>line three\< /li \>\</li\>\\r\\n\< /ul \>\</ul\>\\r\\nTo write a text in \<b\> \< b\> bold \< /b \>\</b\> you use the b tag. To write it in \<i\>\< i \>italic \< /i \>\</i\> you use the i tag." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1347142417, "jominey", "E", 1347142431, "jominey", "E", 1571341466, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
