<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="footer">
         "~%u2665%uD835%uDC3F%uD835%uDCBE%uD835%uDCBB%uD835%uDC52 %uD835%uDCBE%uD835%uDCC8 %uD835%uDCB6 %uD835%uDCBB%uD835%uDCB6%uD835%uDCC8%uD835%uDCBD%uD835%uDCBE%uD835%uDC5C%uD835%uDCC3 %uD835%uDCC8%uD835%uDCBD%uD835%uDC5C%uD835%uDCCC %uD835%uDCB6%uD835%uDCC3%uD835%uDCB9 %uD835%uDCC9%uD835%uDCBD%uD835%uDC52 %uD835%uDCCC%uD835%uDC5C%uD835%uDCC7%uD835%uDCC1%uD835%uDCB9 %uD835%uDCBE%uD835%uDCC8 %uD835%uDCCE%uD835%uDC5C%uD835%uDCCA%uD835%uDCC7 %uD835%uDCC8%uD835%uDCC9%uD835%uDCB6%uD835%uDC54%uD835%uDC52%u2665~\\n\</center\> "
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#ff6699", "bgcolor2":"#ff99cc", "bgimg1":"https://i.imgur.com/Dk5owyf.png", "bgimg2":"https://i.imgur.com/yOesO6b.png", "fontcolor":"#ffffff", "fonttype":"Avant Garde", "h1color":"#ffffff", "h1type":"Avant Garde", "h2color":"#ffffff", "h2type":"Avant Garde", "h3color":"#ffffff", "h3type":"Avant Garde" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page: ..:: miscellaneous ::..">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Miscellaneous\\"\>Miscellaneous\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Gloves\\"\>Gloves\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Belts\\"\>Belts\</a\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Miscellaneous\\"\>Miscellaneous\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<font size=\\"2\\"\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Apron*\</b\> It is held up by a string around the neck, and fastened around the waist with a thin belt tie.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Armwraps*\</b\> Primitive wrappings that are bound around the upper arms of the wearer for decoration.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Beach Towel*\</b\> An oversized absorbent square cloth capable of covering even the largest of bodies. It is designed for drying oneself after a bath or a dip in the water, and can be used for laying out on the beach or grass.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Benda*\</b\> This is a length of material used for covering, wrapping around, or intertwining with the hair.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tapestry*\</b\> A tapestry, ready to have something embroidered on it.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bookmark*\</b\> It is a thin marker used to keep one's place in a book and so be able to return to it with ease.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Blanket*\</b\> Designed to cover the body and provide warmth.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Braies*\</b\> A masculine lightweight undergarment complete with a drawstring waist and a bottom tie. The tie is flexible and can be drawn below the knee or bloused up and tied on the upper thigh.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Carpet*\</b\> A large, firm carpet. It looks just big enough to cover an average-sized room.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pile Carpet*\</b\> A large swath of plush pile carpet. It looks big enough to cover the entirety of an average-sized room.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Choker*\</b\> This is a collar that fastens around the neck.\\r\\nA eye mask. A stretch of fabric which conforms to the bridge of the nose and wraps about the eye area before tying behind the head. It is generally worn to conceal the upper portion of the face, allowing an individual to more freely socialize outside the bounds of identity.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cloth*\</b\> A clean cloth made from a confiscated scrap of [material].\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Codpiece*\</b\> A supportive pouch of fabric worn over the groin by men. Inconspicuous laces at the sides hold the garment in place.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Comforter*\</b\> It is a fiber filled or quilted bed covering which spreads over top of mattress but does not cover pillows or hang all the way to the floor; often paired with a bed skirt and pillow shams. A comforter is smaller than a bedspread and larger than a coverlet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Polishing Cloth*\</b\> It is a square-cut piece of cloth intended for use in polishing metals and other precious items.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cushion*\</b\> This is a padded [shape] cushion designed for comfort while sitting. It can also be used for decorative purposes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Artificial flower*\</b\> A handmade flower accessory designed to be added to clothing for decorative purposes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Footed Pajamas*\</b\> This is a pair of basic pajamas complete with foot coverings. Designed for comfort and warmth while sleeping, these pajamas are traditionally worn by infants and children.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Footwraps*\</b\> Primitive protective wrappings that are bound around the feet of the wearer to encase the base of the toes all the way up to the calves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fringe*\</b\> Suitable to be added to clothing. It is a decorative border hanging loosely from a raveled edge.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mask*\</b\> A full mask that bends around the curves of the wearer's face to conceal most identifiable features. Masks are useful for a variety of purposes, some of them illicit or criminal, others just personal, such as romantic encounters.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hammock*\</b\> A hammock is a sling made of fabric, rope, or netting, suspended between two points, used for swinging, sleeping, or resting. It consists of a cloth panel stretched with ropes between two firm anchor points such as trees or posts.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hand Towel*\</b\> An absorbent, rectangular piece of cloth designed for cleaning up messes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fan*\</b\> This is an implement of semi-circular cloth or wood designed for waving lightly in the hand to create a cooling current of air about a person.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Handkerchief*\</b\> A simple, square piece of cloth used for dabbing one's lips, wiping sweat from the brow, or giving as a token of favor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Lace*\</b\> Suitable to be added to clothing. Lace is typically very expensive, and therefore is a mark of wealth.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Lining*\</b\> This is a length of fabric is used for lining items of clothing.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Loincloth*\</b\> A garment designed for wrapping around the waist to cover the genitals. Usually a simple piece of cloth which is left to dangle downwards, it is a basic, primitive garment.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Napkin*\</b\> A square piece of cloth used at a meal to wipe the fingers or lips and to protect garments.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Neck Handkerchief*\</b\> The most informal sort of neckwear generally worn by sporting gentlemen, working tradesmen, and laboring slaves. It is a square folded and tied about the neck with a simple hem.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pajamas*\</b\> It's a garment usually worn by men and conservatively made, designed mostly for comfort when sleeping.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Parasol*\</b\> This is an indispensable adjunct to a lady of fashion. It features a canopy device designed to protect from precipitation or sunlight. The shade is artfully decorated.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pillow*\</b\> Designed to use as a comfort for the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Decorative Pillow*\</b\> A fairly firm pillow variation designed to be thrown upon furniture for decorative purposes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Portiere*\</b\> A portiere, also known as a door curtain, is a hanging placed over a door or over the doorless entrance to a room.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ribbon*\</b\> This thin length of fabric is used for binding things such as the hair, both for decoration and to hold the object in place.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Robe*\</b\> The loose-fitting robe is reaching to the ground and completely covers the wearer. This garment is normally a mark of a humble demeanor and great accomplishments. It is usually earned via religious, magical or other secretive means. It comes complete with a long tailed hood and a corded waist. The hood hangs loose against the upper back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Decorative Rug*\</b\> A decorative collection of cloth designed to cover a small area of flooring.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Smith Apron*\</b\> A long piece of protective cloth which is held up by a string around the neck, and fastened around the waist with a buckled belt. It is split along the bottom to allow the legs to move freely.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Streamers*\</b\> Designed to be used as a decoration for socials and other events.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Swaddling Gown*\</b\> This is a simple infant's gown that encompasses the body and gathers at the feet via a drawstring. It is designed for comfort, warmth, and protection from the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tablecloth*\</b\> A large, square covering generally spread out over a table, especially during meals.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tail Warmer*\</b\> A circular tube of cloth designed to encompass the tail and protect it \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fluffy Towel*\</b\> A fluffy and absorbent square cloth capable of covering an average-sized body. It is designed for drying oneself after a bath or a dip in the water.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Trimming*\</b\> Suitable to be added to clothing. Trimming is usually made from offcuts from finer garments, or from small amounts of valuable materials.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Umbrella*\</b\> This is an indispensable adjunct to a man of fashion. It features a canopy device designed to protect from precipitation. The shade is snazzily decorated with pinstripes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Washcloth*\</b\> A small, square, and fluffy piece of cloth designed for washing the body or cleaning up messes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wraps*\</b\> Made out of oilskin. Wraps of these types are typically used by sailors, who wrap them around valuable items. The wraps them protect the items should they be immersed in water.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wristlet*\</b\> This is a decorative band of fabric worn about the wrist. Pendants can be added to make it more decorative, or it can be worn alone as a simple accessory. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Gloves\\"\>Gloves\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gloves*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animals paws. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animals who need such things.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Archery gloves*\</b\> A palmless, thumbless glove designed for archers. The fingers are encased to the second knuckle. It is tied at the wrist with a leather thong.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fingerless gloves*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These gloves are fingerless, encasing the base of the fingers to the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Formal gloves*\</B\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These gloves are full-fingered, encasing the tips of the digits to just above the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Handwraps*\</b\> Primitive protective wrappings that are bound around the hands of the wearer to encase the base of the fingers down to the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Long, fingerless gloves*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These gloves are fingerless, encasing the base of the fingers to the elbows.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Long gloves*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws and are lengthened to go just beyond the elbow, making them perfect for wear with sleeveless garments. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animals who need such things.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mittens*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws and stretch just over the wrists. They bundle the hands entirely to provide warmth during the cold seasons, and, unlike regular gloves, do not have a separate sheath for each finger. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animal's who need such things.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Swordsman gloves*\</b\> These simple, yet elegant gloves bear reinforced palms and thumbs for additional sturdiness and grip, with a high-cuff extending just over the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Work gloves*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws and extend upward over the forearms for protection. Custom fingerless gloves are available for clawed animals who need such things. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Belts\\"\>Belts\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Belt*\</b\> Worn wrapped about the waist, it can be used for hanging various items such as pouches and scabbards.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Braided*\</b\> This is a casual belt created through the braiding together of three or more strips of fabric.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Double-wrap*\</b\> Worn wrapped about the waist, it can be used for hanging various items such as pouches and scabbards.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Garter belt*\</b\> A swath of cloth worn around the waist and designed to accompany garters which clasp onto stockings or socks to keep them from falling down. The back of this garment is adjustable to fit different waist sizes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Girdle belt*\</b\> It is a scanty belt-shaped textile for men and/or women worn about the waist.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gladiator belt*\</b\> A thick belt wraps the waist and abdomen of the wearer, with three smaller belts lying atop securing the piece closed with small buckles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shoulder sash*\</b\> It is designed to be worn diagonally across the chest from shoulder to hip.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tankard strap*\</b\> A strap designed to snap onto a belt for holding keys or miscellaneous items, worn around the waist. (container)\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tie belt*\</b\> This is a strip of fabric generally used for keeping a robe closed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tool belt*\</b\> A belt is a flexible band or strap, typically made of leather or heavy cloth, and worn around the waist. A belt supports trousers or other articles of clothing. This particular belt is used to contain work tools. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Waist sash*\</b\> A swath of fabric that loops around the waist and ties into a knot or bow.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Waist cord*\</b\> This garment is traditionally worn wrapped about the waist with a corded piece of cloth fashionably dangling toward the thighs. It can be used for hanging various items such as pouches and scabbards. \\r\\n\<br\> \<font\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: about us ::..">
         (\{ "members", "Our guild policy is to do the best that we can. And eat pudding. Lots of pudding." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: members ::..">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"8C528C \\"\>\<br\>\<b\>Welcome to SoWeCanSew!\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Available Members:\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>* Meepers (Leader) - Master Seamstress, Master Dyer \& Merchant\\r\\n\<br\>* Orla - Master Dyer \& Seamstress\\r\\n\<br\>* Una - Master Seamstress \& Master Tailor\\r\\n\<br\>* Faith - Tailor, Seamstress \& Dyer\\r\\n\\r\\n\</FONT\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<center\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"8C528C0  \\"\>\<hr\>~*~SoWeCanSew~*~\<hr\>\</FONT\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<br\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"8C528C0  \\"\>Unavailable Members:\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>* Carolyn - Master Seamstress \& Master Tailor\\r\\n\<br\>* Helen - Seamstress\\r\\n\<br\>* Nan - Master Hairstylist and Seamstress\\r\\n\<br\>* Tomasso - Tailor\\r\\n\<br\>* Narcissa - Seamstress\\r\\n\<br\>* Quintin - Tailor\</FONT\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>*If you wish to join, contact any available members.*\</center\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: prices ::..">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Fabrics\\"\>Fabrics\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#0C090A \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Blacks\\"\>Blacks\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#357EC7 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Blues\\"\>Blues\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#4A2500 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Browns\\"\>Browns\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#4AA02C \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Greens\\"\>Greens\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#808080 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Greys\\"\>Greys\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#E6E6E6 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Metallics\\"\>Metallics\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#E56717 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Oranges\\"\>Oranges\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Others\\"\>Others\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#F52887 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Pinks\\"\>Pinks\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#7D1B7E \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Purples\\"\>Purples\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#800517 \\"\>\<a href=\\"#Reds\\"\>Reds\</a\>\</b\>\</FONT\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#FEFCFF \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Whites\\"\>Whites\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#FBB917 \\"\> \<a href=\\"#Yellows\\"\>Yellows\</a\> \</b\>\</FONT\> \</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Fabrics\\"\>Fabrics\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Barras, Burlap, Calico, Cotton, Felt, Flannel, Gingham, Hemp, Linen \& Sackcloth.\\r\\n\<br\>2 Denarii: Tweed, Wool, Woolsey \& Whipcord.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Broadcloth, Leather, Satin \& Suede.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Faux Fur, Muslin, Poplin \& Brocade.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Batiste, Damask, Velvet \& Silk.\\r\\n\<br\>10 Denarii: Samite\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Quality of fabrics can always be upgraded.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>35 Denarii:\\r\\n\<br\> auburn cordovan fabric\\r\\n\<br\> bright white tulle fabric\\r\\n\<br\> brilliant brickfire red samite fabric\\r\\n\<br\> bronzed chocolate flannelette fabric\\r\\n\<br\> cinder smoke batiste fabric\\r\\n\<br\> cocoa-colored broadcloth fabric\\r\\n\<br\> cocoa-colored leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> coffee brown angora wool fabric\\r\\n\<br\> foam white silk fabric\\r\\n\<br\> frosted berry cordovan fabric\\r\\n\<br\> glittery icterine checkery fabric\\r\\n\<br\> golden bourbon fleece fabric\\r\\n\<br\> golden peach blossom suede fabric\\r\\n\<br\> heavy red and silver plaid wool fabric\\r\\n\<br\> iced pink merino fabric\\r\\n\<br\> imperial purple pashmina fabric\\r\\n\<br\> madder red jamdani muslin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> magnolia white lawn fabric\\r\\n\<br\> metallic brocade fabric\\r\\n\<br\> midnight ruby damask fabric\\r\\n\<br\> midnight ruby lawn fabric\\r\\n\<br\> midnight ruby leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> misty moss green silk fabric\\r\\n\<br\> misty rose poplin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> monochromatic lilac damask fabric\\r\\n\<br\> opalescent blue silk fabric\\r\\n\<br\> opalescent pearl dragonfly-embroidered lutestring fabric\\r\\n\<br\> opaline waterlily blue batiste fabric\\r\\n\<br\> opaline waterlily blue brocade fabric\\r\\n\<br\> rainbow-colored leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> resplendent ruby red leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> resplendent ruby red muslin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> rich toffee brown velvet fabric\\r\\n\<br\> rose dust brocade fabric\\r\\n\<br\> rosedust brocade fabric\\r\\n\<br\> shimmering berry damask fabric\\r\\n\<br\> shimmering ice blue faux fur fabric\\r\\n\<br\> silhouette black leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> silhouette black satin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> silhouette black velvet fabric\\r\\n\<br\> smoky ember coutille satin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> smoky grey damask fabrics\\r\\n\<br\> snowdrop white pashmina fabric\\r\\n\<br\> snowflake-pattern smalt velveteen fabric\\r\\n\<br\> sparkling azure leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> spritely spearmint leather fabric\\r\\n\<br\> sunburst muslin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> sunset violet himroo fabric\\r\\n\<br\> twilight black alligator skin fabric\\r\\n\<br\> twilight black mudcloth fabric\\r\\n\<br\> tyrian purple twilled wool fabric\\r\\n\<br\> virulent green gauze fabric\\r\\n\<br\> waterlily blue silk fabric\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> 100 DENARRI PER YARD\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> frosted silver serpent hide fabric\\r\\n\<br\> electric blue slitheen scale hide\\r\\n\<br\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\>\<center\>\<hr\>SoWeCanSew\<hr\>\</FONT\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<center\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\>Colors \& Prices:\</FONT\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#0C090A \\"\>\<a name=\\"Blacks\\"\>Blacks\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Black.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Charcoal black, ebony \& murky black.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Obsidian black.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#357EC7 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Blues\\"\>Blues\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Blue, cyan, dark blue \& light blue.\\r\\n\<br\>2 Denarii: Indigo, blue-green \& blue-grey.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Cobalt blue, sapphire \& navy blue.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Turquoise, dark turquoise \& baby blue.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Teal, cadet blue \& blue-violet.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Royal blue, peacock blue \& aquamarine.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Azure, midnight blue, cerulean \& ocean blue.\\r\\n\<br\>8 Denarii: Cornflower blue.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#4A2500 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Browns\\"\>Browns\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Brown, dark brown \& light brown.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Sable, russet \& tan.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Sienna \& rich brown.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Sandy brown \& khaki.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Chocolate \& wheat colored.\\r\\n\<br\>8 Denarii: Dark chocolate \& bistre.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#4AA02C \\"\> \<a name=\\"Greens\\"\>Greens\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Dark green, green, light green.\\r\\n\<br\>2 Denarii: Light sage, olive green \& sage.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Emerald, chartreuse \& vibrant green.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Apple green, peacock green \& viridian.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Mint green \& clover green.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Pale mint green \& jade.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarri: Sea green, spring green \& myrtle green.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#808080 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Greys\\"\>Greys\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Dark grey, grey \& light grey.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Slate grey.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Ash grey \& dusky grey.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Smokey-grey.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#0C090A \\"\> \<a name=\\"Metallics\\"\>Metallics\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>6  Denarii: Silver, bronze-colored, copper-colored.\\r\\n\<br\>12 Denarii: Metallic gold\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#E56717 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Oranges\\"\>Oranges\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Dark orange, light orange \& orange.\\r\\n\<br\>2 Denarii: Bright orange \& burnt orange.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Vibrant orange \& bittersweet orange.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Gamboge \& pumpkin-colored.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Tangerine \& carrot orange\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Saffron \& peach.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Apricot \& sunset orange.\\r\\n\<br\>8 Denarii: Coral.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#8C528C \\"\> \<a name=\\"Rare\\"\>Rare\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> 35 Denarri Per Use\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>smoke white\\r\\n\<br\>lapis blue\\r\\n\<br\>shimmering blue-green\\r\\n\<br\>pearlescent black\\r\\n\<br\>twilight black\\r\\n\<br\>molten red\\r\\n\<br\>iridescent moonglow\\r\\n\<br\>coffee brown\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> 45 Denarri per Use\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>pristine white\\r\\n\<br\>opaline waterlily blue\\r\\n\<br\>silhouette black\\r\\n\<br\>shadow black\\r\\n\<br\>brandywine\\r\\n\<br\>blush rose\\r\\n\<br\>glistening cherry-blossom pink\\r\\n\<br\>resplendent ruby red\\r\\n\<br\>midnight ruby\\r\\n\<br\>raspberry glace\\r\\n\<br\>lavender mauve\\r\\n\<br\>deep aubergine\\r\\n\<br\>iridescent iris\\r\\n\<br\>bronzed bisque\\r\\n\<br\>glossy garnet\\r\\n\<br\>sparkling azure\\r\\n\<br\>gold champagne\\r\\n\<br\>golden peach blossom\\r\\n\<br\>warm ginger\\r\\n\<br\>aureolin apricot\\r\\n\<br\>spritely spearmint\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> 55 Denarri Per Use\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>prismatic starlight\\r\\n\<br\>slittery icterine\\r\\n\<br\>shimmering berry\\r\\n\<br\>irisan grey\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#F52887 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Pinks\\"\>Pinks\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Light pink, bright pink \& pink.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Dark pink \& magenta.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Soft pink \& vibrant pink.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Pastel pink \& pale pink.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Hot pink \& carnation pink.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#7D1B7E \\"\> \<a name=\\"Purples\\"\>Purples\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Light purple, purple \& vibrant purple.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Violet, pale-violet \& red-violet.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Imperial purple, amethyst \& lavender.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Plum, lavender grey \& blue-violet.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Indigo purple, lavender rose, \& orchid purple.\\r\\n\<br\>8 Denarii: Tyrian purple, lilac \& wysteria.\\r\\n\<br\>9 Denarii: Dusky violet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#800517 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Reds\\"\>Reds\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Dark red, light red \& red.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Ruddy red, blush-red \& vibrant red.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Blood-red, crimson \& strawberry red.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Red-violet, rose red \& rose grey.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Scarlet, dark scarlet \& pale rose red.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Wine, cherry red \& cardinal red.\\r\\n\<br\>8 Denarii: dark wine \& carmine.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#FEFCFF \\"\> \<a name=\\"Whites\\"\>Whites\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Grubby white \& white.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Bright white \& vibrant white.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarii: Ivory \& milk white.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Pearly white, ecru \& alabaster.\\r\\n\<br\>7 Denarii: Pure white, pearl \& chalky white.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<FONT COLOR=\\"#FBB917 \\"\> \<a name=\\"Yellows\\"\>Yellows\</FONT\>\</b\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>1 Denarii: Dark yellow, light yellow \& yellow.\\r\\n\<br\>3 Denarii: Bright yellow, vibrant yellow.\\r\\n\<br\>4 Denarii: Flaxen yellow \& scuzzy yellow.\\r\\n\<br\>5 Denarri: Cream, canary yellow \& goldenrod.\\r\\n\<br\>6 Denarii: Buff \& sunglow.\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: seamstress patterns ::..">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Seamstress Patterns:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Hats\\"\>Hats\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Cloaks, Coats and Jackets\\"\>Cloaks, Coats and Jackets\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Blouses\\"\>Blouses\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Skirts\\"\>Skirts\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Dresses\\"\>Dresses\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Gowns\\"\>Gowns\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Undergarments\\"\>Undergarments\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Shoes\\"\>Shoes\</a\> \\r\\n\</center\> \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<font size=\\"2\\"\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Hats\\"\>Hats\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Attifet*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a type of close-fitting cap called a coif; many were embroidered and bobbin-lace-trimmed. In the east the coif was wired or starched into a slight heart-shape, this is now known as the attifet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Beribboned Garland*\</b\>\\r\\nDelicate aquamarine velvet flowers are tactically positioned on the hat. It is an elaborately woven circular ribbon arrangement, which is worn upon a woman's head primarily to hold the hair or veil in place. Pretty, fluttering ribbons hang loosely off the back of the garland.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bonnet*\</b\>\\r\\nThis headwear is primarily worn by women and is knitted, and tied under the chin. It covers the hair, ears and back of the head, but not the forehead. Cut atop the bonnet are small slits, allowing for women to comfortably slide their ears through.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Braided Hairband*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a clothing accessory worn in the hair or around the forehead, usually to hold hair away from the face or eyes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Butterfly Hat*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a hat crafted from a truncated cone and veil or handkerchief covering wired to look like butterfly wings.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Caul*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a headress worn by women that covers tied-up hair. A fancy caul could be made of satin, velvet, fine silk or brocade, although a simple caul would commonly be made of white linen or cotton. The caul could be covered by a crespine or a mesh net to secure it from falling off.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chaperon*\</b\>\\r\\nInitially a utilitarian garment, it first grew a long partly decorative tail behind, and then developed into a complex, versatile and expensive headgear after what was originally the vertical opening for the face began to be used as a horizontal opening for the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Coif*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a rectangular hat, with the fold of the fabric going around the back of the head and the seam running along the top of the head. The bottom is gathered and tied at the back of the neck while the front edge curves around the head in the shape of a horseshoe, before tapering down and forward toward the jawline into a blunt, rounded point. The excess material at the crown of the head is gathered tightly together and stitched down while the front edge is fancily decorated with either lace or an intricate braid.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cornet Hat*\</b\>\\r\\nIt has an upstanding frill in front and lappets at the back. The veil is wired to stand up above the forehead. A topknot of wired ribbon is pinned at the front of the cap.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Coronet Hat*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a border, fitting close round the head, that curves forward on either side to end over the ears; the hair is exposed above this limit only. The back of the crown is raised into a horseshoe-shaped curve over the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ear-Shaped Caul*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a headress worn by women that covers tied-up hair. A fancy caul could be made of satin, velvet, fine silk or brocade, although a simple caul would commonly be made of white linen or cotton. This style of caul has two separate ear coverings and link at the top of the head with a ribbon.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Face Veil*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is an article of clothing, worn almost exclusively by women, that is intended to cover some part of the head or face. As a religious item, it is intended to show honor to an object or space.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gable Hood*\</b\>\\r\\nA gable hood, is a woman's headdress, so-called because its pointed shape resembles the gable of a house. It is a complex construct with a box-shaped back and two tube-shaped hanging veils at 90-degree angles; the hanging veils and lappets can be pinned up in a variety of ways to make complex headdresses.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Head Roll*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a a padded circle worn on the head to hold a veil in place.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Head Veil*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is an article of clothing, worn almost exclusively by women, that is intended to cover some part of the head or face. As a religious item, it is intended to show honor to an object or space.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Nebulae Headdress*\</b\>\\r\\nA narrow, halo-shaped headdress, traditionally made from gauze.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Paste*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a strip of cloth primarily used for being secured over a coif.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pillbox Hat*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a small woman's hat with a flat crown and straight, upright sides.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruffled Veil*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is an article of clothing, worn almost exclusively by women, that is intended to cover some part of the head or face. As a religious item, it is intended to show honor to an object or space. This particular veil appears to be ruffled at the framing of the face.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Snood*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a lacy-looking, knitted or crocheted net that holds the hair back from the wearer's face.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Steeple Hat*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a headdress in the shape of a cone or 'steeple'. The hennin is typically 12 to 18 inches (30 to 45 cm) high, but can be considerably higher. The hennin is worn tilted backward at an angle and features a cloth lappet, a short loop in the front and a veil that emerges from the cone.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wide-Brimmed Coif*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a rectangular hat, with the fold of the fabric going around the back of the head and the seam running along the top of the head. The bottom is gathered and tied at the back of the neck while the front edge curves around the head in the shape of a horseshoe, before tapering down and forward toward the jawline into a blunt, rounded point. The excess material at the crown of the head is gathered tightly together and stitched down while the front edge is fancily decorated with either lace or an intricate braid. In this case, the front edge has been extended into a wide brim.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wimple*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a cloth which usually covers the head and is worn around the neck and chin.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Scarfs:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Scarf*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a piece of fabric worn on or near the head or around the neck for warmth, cleanliness, fashion or for religious reasons.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Head Scarf*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a scarf covering most or all of the top of a woman's hair and her head. Head scarves may be worn for a variety of purposes, such as for warmth, for sanitation, for fashion or social distinction; with religious significance, to hide baldness, out of modesty, or other forms of social convention.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stole*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is an embroidered band of cloth, about two and a half to three meters long and seven to ten centimeters wide, whose ends are usually broadened out. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Cloaks, Coats and Jackets\\"\>Cloaks, Coats and Jackets\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a type of loose garment that is worn over indoor clothing and protects the wearer from the cold, rain or wind, or it may form part of a fashionable outfit or uniform.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Back-Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a cloak that, attached to the shoulders, falls down to the floor behind the wearer. The woman's version trails the floor in a graceful curve, while the men's cloak barely grazes the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bell Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a cloak buttoned down the front with bulky sleeves in folds of cloth. Overall, this cloak resembles a bell.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Brat Drape*\</b\>\\r\\nA basic, but versatile, upper body draping. Often highly decorated, it can be worn several ways including belted around the waist, and pinned over one shoulder.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cape*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a sleeveless outer garment which is designed to fasten at the throat and fall down the back of the wearer. Typically, luxurious materials are used to manufacture a cape, which is intended to be more fashionable than functional as a general rule. It falls only partially down the back, and drapes elegantly over the shoulders.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Capelet*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a miniature cape designed to be worn during warm weather. Barely covering the shoulders in the front, the top rests just under the nape of the wearer in the back to fashionably frame the neckline.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chasuble Cape*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a generic, circular cape with an aperture for the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Evening Cape*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a sleeveless outer garment which is designed to fasten at the throat and fall down the back of the wearer. Worn as a formal garment, this particular cape is meant to be made from fine materials only, sometimes being constructed from lacy knit patterns or crochets, and occasionally beaded or laced with gems. It falls only partially down the back, and drapes elegantly over the shoulders\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Collar Cape*\</b\>\\r\\nA round or square shoulder covering used to keep the neck and chest area warm.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hooded Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nA full, floor-length cloak bearing a deep, concealing hood. It can be tightened at the neck via drawstrings or secured with a clasp.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hooded Lacerna Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nA large, semi-circular cloak draped around the shoulder, down the back, and typically secured with a piece of jewelry. It bears a hood and serves as protection against the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Lacerna Cloak*\</b\>\\r\\nA large, semi-circular cloak draped around the shoulder, down the back and typically secured with a piece of jewelry. It serves as protection against the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mantle*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a cloak fashioned from a rectangular piece of cloth and is sleeveless. It reaches to the feet and wraps loosely around the body, shielding the wearer from the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sagum Mantle*\</b\>\\r\\nA square, rectangular mantle draped over armor and held at the shoulder with a clasp or thorn.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shawl*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a large swath of cloth which is designed to be wrapped loosely around the neck, shoulders, and upper body. It is big enough to cover the head, if the wearer so desires, to shield from the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short Buckled Jacket*\</b\>\\r\\nA short female jacket ending just below the breasts that features a deep hood and a series of three buckles that close securely upon the chest. Each of the long sleeves is laced up via a myriad of eyelets and colored string.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pleated Coat*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a short jacket with pleats radiating from the shoulder and running to the hem with the waist creating a fashionable X shape. This garment closes with hidden hooks in the center front.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Blouses\\"\>Blouses\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>*Blouse*\</b\>\\r\\nA garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar, sleeves, and a front opening.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a tightly fitted outer garment worn by women, low cut and sleeveless, hugging the torso tightly. It is reinforced with stiff reed inserts to maintain a fashionable shape and support the bust. The front is securely laced and tied.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bustier*\</b\>\\r\\nA form-fitting corset-like garment worn under clothing to push up the bust by tightening against the upper midriff while gently shaping the waist. It reaches only to the bottom of the ribs.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Camisole*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a simple garment fashioned to wear under blouses or shirts which provides a covering that extends from the bust to the waistline. Being sleeveless, this garment traditionally offers little, if any, breast support.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cloth Strip*\</b\>\\r\\nA crude upper body garment designed to cover a woman's breasts and little else. It ties simplistically around the back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Corset*\</b\>\\r\\nA garment consisting of three separate pieces laced together with a thinly twisted silken cord. It is generally snugly fitted to the upper body, but devoid of sleeves and straps. The back piece is a solid cut of fabric tied to the two front pieces of the garment. Thin, twisted cords of silk have been used to lace each piece together on the sides and at the front. Where the two front pieces meet, the cloth dips down to reveal a provocative amount of cleavage, while still maintaining coverage of the breasts themselves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cropped Shirt*\</b\>\\r\\nAn off-the-shoulder, low-cut female garment which has been cropped just beneath the breasts and hugs their lower halves tightly.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cross-Lace Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nA fitted bodice with a low, wide neckline. It features a series of criss-crossed lacing in the front which tighten to accentuate the breasts and slim the figure.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Doublet Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nA high-neckline, front-lacing bodice with a long row of grommets down the front. It features a pointed waist and padded shoulder rolls.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruched Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nA form-fitting bodice which has been gathered and stitched at its central point to create a rippled appearance. It closes via a series of laces in the back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruffled Blouse*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a garment comes with convenient ties at the wrists. Each generous sleeve ends in a fashionable ruffle.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shirred Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nA decorative bodice in which the material has been gathered along the torso to create decorative rows through parallel stitching. It closes via a series of laces in the back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-Sleeved Blouse*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a simple, loose garment for the upper part of the body with a round collar, and short breezy sleeves sometimes ending in ruffles. It pulls on and off over the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-Vested Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nA tight-fitting bodice which tapers inward at the waist to form a v-shape just above the navel. It laces up the front and along the shoulders for a dramatic look.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Skirted Bodice*\</b\>\\r\\nThis bodice variation comes with lacing at the front and a short, tapered skirt about the bottom. It is designed to be worn with skirts or pants.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleveveless Blouse*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a simple, loose garment for the upper part of the body with a round collar and flowy bottom. Void of sleeves, the fabric at the shoulders is broad and stops just at the armpits of the wearer.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Swatch Shirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female upper body garment in which two swatches of fabric have been tied together on each side of the body to serve as a covering for the breasts. It reaches to just above the navel.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Underbust Corset*\</b\>\\r\\nA decorative corset variation that begins at the bust and extends down to the hips. It is generally worn over blouses or shirts to lend a more attractive shape to the female form.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Skirts\\"\>Skirts\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA garment hanging from the waist and worn by females.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Angled Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female garment which starts scantily at the left hip with a simple side tie and then tapers diagonally downward to cover the groin and end just above the right knee. The entire left side of the lower body is left bare.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ankle-Length Kilt*\</b\>\\r\\nThis ankle-length kilt displays uniqueness of design, construction, and convention which differentiate it from other garments fitting the general description. It is tailored, and wraps around the wearer's body at the natural waist, between the lowest rib and the hip, starting from one side, around the front and back and across the front again to the opposite side. The fastenings consist of straps and buckles on both ends, the strap on the inside end passing through a slit in the waistband to be buckled on the outside. The kilt covers the body from the waist down to just above the ankles. The overlapping layers in front are called aprons and are flat; the single layer of fabric around the sides and back is pleated.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ankle-Length Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female garment hanging loosely from the waist and extending downward in a fine, draping fashion before pooling about the ankles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Flared Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a sleek, floor-length skirt that hugs the hips and legs before flaring out at the knees and cascading to the floor in voluminous, elegant folds that trail slightly behind the wearer.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Floor-Length Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a streamlined floor-length skirt. It hangs simplistically from the waist catching the natural curves of the body beneath before brushing against the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gypsy Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA skirt with three ruffled tiers and a drawstring waist.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hoop Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nAn undergarment designed to extend the outer skirt into a fashionable shape. It is comprised of wires and hoops of various shapes before being covered in cloth.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Kilt*\</b\>\\r\\nA knee-length pleated and wrap-around skirt generally worn by men as part of the traditional dress of the Bisclavret.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Knee-Length Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female garment draping from the waist to the knees in a lightweight, breezy design.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mermaid Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female garment which is fitted from the hips to the knees before flaring out to a graceful full circle trumpet with inserted gored panels.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Overskirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA garment hanging from the waist and worn by females.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Overskirt-Ruffled*\</b\>\\r\\nA female overgarment which begins at the waist and flows luxuriously outward from the hips to end in a splash of playful ruffles at the ankles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruffled Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA long, flowing female garment with six tiers of ruffles decorating from the length of the hips downward to the ankles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female garment designed to snugly clutch the lower half of the body from the waist to just below the buttocks.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Side-Split Overskirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female overgarment that luxuriously encompasses the waist and hips before splitting elaborately at the thigh and running down the length of the body.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Side-Split Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA fashionable female garment flowing gracefully from the waist to the ankles. The right side of the skirt has been split up to the middle thigh to reveal the garments beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Side-Tied Overskirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female overgarment that wraps about the waist and ties securely at the hip. It cascades downward in a slight flare to the ankles, allowing the clothing beneath to play peekaboo from the side.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Split-Front Overskirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA female overgarment which splits just below the waist and drapes down to the ankles in an upside-down V shape, allowing for a view of the clothing underneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Underskirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA full skirt which hangs from the waist. It is intended to be worn either beneath gowns or other skirts to grant a fuller look.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Underskirt-Ruffled*\</b\>\\r\\nA full, ruffled skirt which hangs from the waist to the feet. It is intended to be worn either beneath gowns or other skirts to grant a fuller, more decorative look.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Waist Wrap*\</b\>\\r\\nA unisex, skirt-like garment in which the fabric has been wrapped about the waist and centrally cinched or gathered in the front to cover the necessities. Any remaining cloth is left hanging between the legs to flutter freely toward the ground.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Yoke Skirt*\</b\>\\r\\nA full, floor-length skirt attached to a fitted hip-length yoke. This garment provides a smooth look to the waist and hips and is ideal for wearing under bodices when no bulk is desired.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Dresses\\"\>Dresses\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Dress*\</b\>\\r\\nIt's a long-sleeved garment for females fitted close to the upper part of the body, with flowing skirts extending to the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cordial*\</b\>\\r\\nA dress that skims the body luxuriously and flares out over the hips into a full skirt falling gracefully into a six-inch train at the back. The neckline is scooped and fitted sleeves extend to the wrist with a delicate point over the hands.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Couture*\</b\>\\r\\nA floor-sweeping strapless dress featuring a tonal sequin embellishment on the fitted bodice. The bodice seamlessly transitions into a flowing skirt which radiates downward to graze the feet of the wearer. A small series of hooks and eyes situated on the left side provide hidden closure for the garment.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Peplem*\</b\>\\r\\nA Tubular female garment featuring a long, basic skirt that comes around the body under the arms, and is often pinned at each shoulder.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ranger*\</b\>\\r\\nA sleeveless female garment bearing a deep hood that extends downward to just above the ankles. It features a long skirt and a myriad of eyelets and strings which lace up the central portion of the chest and sides.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Saberist*\</b\>\\r\\nA sleeveless female garment which extends downward to just above the ankles. It boasts a low-cut, circular neckline that neatly merges into a buttoned front panel before flowing out into eccentric folds below the waist. A series of eyelets and string lace up the top portion of the sides, giving way at the hips to deep slits which reveal any clothing worn underneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short Saberist*\</b\>\\r\\nA sleeveless female garment which extends downward to just above the knees. It boasts a circular neckline that neatly merges into a buttoned front panel before flowing out into eccentric folds below the waist. A series of eyelets and string lace up the top portion of the sides, giving way at the hips to deep slits which reveal any clothing worn underneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-Sleeved*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a simple short-sleeved one-piece garment worn close to the upper part of the body, with casual skirts extending to the floor\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sideless-Surcoat*\</b\>\\r\\nAn overgown with open sides; basically, very large arm holes, which reveals the gown or garments worn underneath. Some have taken to calling these \\"gates of hell\\" in reference to the way they shockingly display the female figure.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Strapless*\</b\>\\r\\nAn opulent ankle-length dress with a loose ruffle around the strapless bodice that carries down one side in a soft cascade to elegantly brush the floor. It is often accessorized with a jeweled belt or waist sash.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Strapless-Splitfront*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a light, strapless and sleeveless dress which snugly hugs the upper torso before streamlining to the top of the hips. A decorative lace lining covers the seams that connect the waistline to the body of the skirt. Just below the hips, the dress creatively splits into an upside-down V shape, to reveal the garments beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Surcoat*\</b\>\\r\\nA long and flowing gown-like sleeveless coat extending to about mid-calf and featuring slits in the bottom front and back. While traditionally worn to protect mail from the sun, and armor from the muck of the battlefield, they eventually became a fashion amongst women who wanted to display the finery of their undergarments while maintaining modesty.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wrap-Around Dress*\</b\>\\r\\nA primitive female garment in which a large swath of cloth is wrapped about one side of the body and then the other to create a V-necked, dress-like garment. It bears no sleeves and has the most basic of skirts which drags across the ground as the wearer walks.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Gowns\\"\>Gowns\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThis article of clothing is made up of a bodice and skirt sewn together at the waist. It fastens down the front with ribbon ties.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Back Laced Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a woman's garment with a square neckline, fitted closely to the upper part of the body via a series of back laces. It features a long, basic skirt which extends to the floor, and fitted sleeves reaching to mid-hand when the arm is held loosely by the side.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Back Laced Pendant Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a woman's garment with a dipped neckline, fitted comfortably to the upper part of the body via a series of back laces. It features a long, basic skirt which extends to the floor, and long, pendant sleeves which reach to the floor when the arm is held loosely by the side.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bliaut*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a woman's garment with a v-neck collar, fitted closely to the upper part of the body by bodice side ties. Voluminous skirts extend to the floor. It is accented with light embroidery on the cuffs of the sleeves and hem of the skirt. The long, flowing, open sleeves reach to mid-calf when the arm is held loosely by the side.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Burgundian*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a full-skirted gown with long, tapered sleeves extending to the wrist and ending in fur trim. The neckline makes a plunging V to the waist, inset with beautifully beaded material to maintain modesty. The tapered waist of the gown is accented with a decorative braided cord.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Corset gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThe upper portion is comprised of two separate pieces and a mid panel laced together with a thinly twisted cord. The corset is smoothly fitted to the wearer's shape and features thin decorative straps that hang off the shoulder and drape just above the elbow. The upper rim conforms to the curves of the bust to reveal a marginal amount of cleavage. The lower portion of the gown features a split-front skirt which tapers widely toward the floor before hanging in elegant folds.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Colette*\</b\>\\r\\nA woman's sleeveless, square-necked overgown. The body of the gown is fitted closely, as it is secured with lacing down the center of the front panel from the low square neckline to the hip. The laced area exposes the garments underneath. The gown consists mainly of two pieces of material made for the front and back and sewn at the sides. Rather than a bodice and skirt, the garment consists of a skirt gathered at the waist.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Evening Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nAn elegant evening gown, form-fitting and accented with dagged net sleeves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fancy Ruff Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThis elaborate gown bears long sleeves edged with lace at the wrists. A matching ruff extends along the sides, shoulders, and back of the gown's square neckline. A fitted bodice creates a v-shaped waist, which is accentuated by the exaggerated fullness of the elegant floor-length skirts.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Filigreed Slinky Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nA filigreed gown is a form fitting formal garment. The necklace would be considered modest as it covers everything from cleavage to neck. Instead intricate lace stretches from the neck, over the shoulders and arms, and across the decolletage. The rest of the gown seamlessly flows from the bodice to the skirt in one slinky piece that forms around the body tightly. The skirt has a modest train in the back and gradually volumizes as it reaches the ground.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Front Laced Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a woman's garment with a square neckline, fitted closely to the upper part of the body via a series of front laces. It features a long, basic skirt which extends to the floor, and cut-out, elbow-length sleeves which circle partially around the mid-arm before hanging loosely at the sides.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Full, Floor Length Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThis full, elegant, floor-length gown features a laced ruff at the neck and flaring bell sleeves which cascade over the wrist to mid-hand. It comes complete with a decorative lace overlay bodice that tapers downward into a cinched waist and stylish streamlined skirt.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hanging Sleeved Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is an ankle-length gown uniquely-cut to produce fine draping on the body. The wrist-length sleeves are stitched to the back of the armholes only, enabling the wearer to pull them onto the arm or allow them to hang free from the shoulders.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Kirtle*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a floor-length gown with full, flowing skirts and a scooped neckline. It is fitted at the waist and bodice by means of lacing at the back. The sleeves are long and extend halfway down the hand. They are buttoned from mid-arm to cuff.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Long Sleeved Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThe collar falls down into a slight dip, falling low enough to reveal the collarbone, but not enough to reveal any true cleavage. Long bell sleeves fall to either side, cut from a separate fabric and attached from the top of the shoulders, falling down to the top of the hips. A decorative lace lining covers the seams that connects the sleeves to the body of the dress. The hem of the gown falls just below the ankles and sweeps gracefully along the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>*\<b\>Hooded Overgown*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is an elegant woman's over-garment that conforms and accentuates the curves of the wearer with a row of small, decorative buttons that run halfway down the front and ends at the skirt. The full skirt has a split down the center front, subtly fanning out into a V at the back and gracefully draping down to the floor. It has a plunging neckline and a deep hood that drapes the wearer's head and dramatically flares at the shoulders when raised. The sleeves hug the upper arms and taper to a point halfway down the hand and button from the middle of the forearm to the cuff of the sleeve. The long skirt cascades to the floor to pool around the feet and then extends into a short train.\\r\\nThe coffee brown poplin hooded overgown \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>*\<b\>Partlet Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nVertical lacing extend on either side of the square-necked bodice area, enabling for a more comfortable and snug fit. Underneath the bodice lies a high-necked, frilled partlet which modestly covers the chest. A single column of buttons extends along the partlet from the base of the neck to the bust. The gown bears full sleeves which end at the elbow, giving way to fitted undersleeves which extend to the wrist. The flowing skirts of the gown are tapered dramatically from the waist to the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Petal Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nA sleeveless gown bearing eight large, overlapping, triangular petals which fall from the low waistline to the feet. The bodice is princess cut to accommodate the curviest of figures, while the deep v-shaped back can be left open or trimmed with decorative lacing for a more interesting look.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Overgown*\</b\>\\r\\nA flowing overgown with a square-neck collar that falls down just below the collarbone. Large, wide bell sleeves fall to either side, cut from a separate fabric and attached from the top of the shoulders, falling down to the top of the hips. A decorative lace lining covers the seams that connects the sleeves to the body of the dress. The hem of the gown falls just below the ankles and sweeps gracefully along the floor. The front of the gown's large skirt is split to reveal the garments underneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Round Kirtle*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a sleeveless, shapeless gown that falls into a full flare toward the ground. Three wide bands of ribbon decorate the bottom of the garment, concealing the wearer's feet in entirety.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-Sleeved Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThe collar falls down into a slight dip, falling low enough to reveal the collarbone, but not enough to reveal any true cleavage. Short ruffled sleeves fall to either side, cut from a separate fabric and attached from the top of the shoulders, falling just to the chest-line. A decorative lace lining covers the seams that connects the sleeves to the body of the dress. The hem of the gown falls just below the ankles and sweeps gracefully along the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sideless Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nA simple sleeveless woman's gown tailored open from the sides to the hips.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThe collar falls down into a slight dip, falling low enough to reveal the collarbone, but not enough to reveal any true cleavage. The hem of the gown falls just below the ankles and sweeps gracefully along the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless Undergown*\</b\>\\r\\nShaped much like a strapless evening gown, this sleeveless undergown features a short, fitted bodice which controls the bustline and fillins in the front of the overgown without gapping. The bodice laces up the back for a snug fit, and has an attached A-line skirt which can be seen when the hem of the overgown is lifted.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Splint Front Gown*\</b\>\\r\\nThe collar falls down into a slight dip, falling low enough to reveal the collarbone, but not enough to reveal any true cleavage. Long bell sleeves fall to either side, cut from a separate fabric and attached from the top of the shoulders, falling down to the top of the hips. A decorative lace lining covers the seams that connects the sleeves to the body of the dress. Just below the waist, the gown luxuriously splits into an upside-down V shape, to reveal the garments beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*V-neck Overgown*\</b\>\\r\\nA simple, elegant gown with a wide \\"V\\" neckline. The bodice fits smoothly over the bust and belts under the bustline. A slim \\"Y\\" shape is achieved by confining the skirt fullness in the center front and back so the gown sides hang nearly vertical. Fitted sleeves have been carefully shaped to allow a full range of motion without binding, and end in a deep cuff. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Undergarments\\"\>Undergarments\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chemise*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a loose dresslike undergarment, flowing from the shoulder nearly to the feet, with voluminous sleeves. It is a simple garment worn close to the skin beneath other clothing to protect against bodily oils.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Camicia*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is an extra long, flowing chemise worn close to the skin beneath other clothing to protect against bodily oils. This particular style is designed with full, puffy sleeves to compliment segmented or slashed accessories and garb.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chainse*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a floor-length, pleated tunic with long sleeves tightly fitted at the wrists. It is designed to be worn under the bliaut.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chemisette*\</b\>\\r\\nA waist-length female undershirt featuring a drawstring neckline and three-quarter length sleeves trimmed with ruffled cuffs.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-Sleeved Chemise*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a loose, short-sleeved, dresslike undergarment, flowing from the shoulder nearly to the feet. It is simplistic in design and worn close to the skin beneath other clothing to protect against bodily oils.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless Chemise*\</b\>\\r\\nIt is a loose, sleeveless, dresslike undergarment, flowing from the shoulder nearly to the feet. It is simplistic in design and worn close to the skin beneath other clothing to protect against bodily oils.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Smock*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is an undergarment with long tubular sleeves, underarm gussets, and a large gored skirt designed to make an overgown hang correctly. It is shaped to fit beneath any gown with a fitted bodice and full skirt.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bloomers*\</b\>\\r\\nAn undergarment which is full cut and extending to just below the knee with a simple ruffle. Embodying comfort and femininity, they are made to wear under most any article of clothing.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bum Roll*\</b\>\\r\\nWorn underneath the clothing, this undergarment lifts open skirts to allow for air flow. It is designed to accentuate the hips of the wearer, thereby making the waist seem smaller.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stomacher*\</b\>\\r\\nThis is a decorated triangular panel that fills in the front opening of a woman's gown or bodice. The stomacher may be boned, as part of a corset, or may cover the triangular front of a corset. If simply decorative, the stomacher lies over the triangular front panel of the stays, being either stitched or pinned into place, or held in place by the lacings of the gown's bodice.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bikini-Bottom*\</b\>\\r\\nUnderpants or swimmers that reach to the hips rather than to the waist.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bikini-Bra*\</b\>\\r\\nIt wraps around the chest, and is supportive enough to allow swimming.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Nightgown*\</b\>\\r\\nA nightgown. It's a garment usually worn by women and conservatively made, designed mostly for comfort when sleeping.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Nighty*\</b\>\\r\\nIt's a garment usually worn by women and intended as sleepwear or to entice the opposite sex in private.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Garters*\</b\>\\r\\nTied just below the knee, they are used for holding up stockings.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Braided Garters*\</b\>\\r\\nThese are neat strips of braided fabric designed to be tied around the legs to hold up stockings.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ribbon Garters*\</b\>\\r\\nThese are decorative fabric ribbons designed to be tied around the legs to hold up stockings.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tie Garters*\</b\>\\r\\nThese are neat strips of fabric designed to be tied around the legs to hold up stockings.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stockings*\</b\>\\r\\nThese fitted stockings extend to the thigh and are meant to be held in place by a pair of garters.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Back-Seam Stockings*\</b\>\\r\\nThese fitted stockings feature a seam running up the back of the leg. They extend to the thigh and are meant to be held in place by a pair of garters.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Knee-High Stockings*\</b\>\\r\\nThese fitted stockings extend to just above the knee.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Thigh-High Stockings*\</b\>\\r\\nThese fitted stockings extend to the thigh and are meant to be held in place by a pair of garters.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Shoes\\"\>Shoes\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shoes*\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. They cover the foot and extend just to the ankle before tying. Custom shoes are available to hooved animals such as horses, or animals with strangely shaped feet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Dancing Slippers*\</b\> These are flat-bottomed shoes secured to the feet by added ribbons which incorporate pleats under the toes to enable dancers to leap and execute turns.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gladiator Sandals*\</b\> Banded footwear featuring t-straps, thin leather soles, low heels and several thong enclosures running across the instep and ankle.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Heeled Slippers*\</b\> These are light, low-cut shoes with a rounded toe that are easily slipped onto the feet. They feature a 2 inch wedge heel, permitting the wearer to have more support and balance than a normal slipper or heel would, while maintaining an air of femininity.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*High Heels*\</b\> A pair of female shoes which raise the heel of the wearer's foot by two inches. They lend the illusion that a woman is taller, that her legs are longer, and effectively change the wearer's gait and posture, thrusting the backside out and causing the hips to sway more than usual.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Knee-High Moccasins*\</b\> This heelless shoe features a soft and flexible sole which is brought up the sides of the foot and over the toes where it is joined by a puckered seam to a U-shaped piece lying on top of the foot. The upper part of the footwear reaches to just below the knees, and is often adorned with embroidery, beading, or other ornaments.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Latchet Shoes*\</b\> This footwear bears a round toe and extends to just above the ankle where a thong or strap is used to attach it securely to the wearer.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Maiden boots*\</b\> These boots reach just to the thigh and feature back lacing which can be adjusted for a snug or loose fit. The upper length can be folded down into a cuff to achieve the traditional 'pirate look', or left up to lend a dressier appearance. They feature 2 and a half inch heels, large enough to be obviously feminine but allowing no risk for tripping on holes or uneven ground\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Moccasins*\</b\> This heelless shoe features a soft and flexible sole which is brought up the sides of the foot and over the toes where it is joined by a puckered seam to a U-shaped piece lying on top of the foot. The upper part of the footwear is often adorned with embroidery, beading, or other ornaments.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Poulaines*\</b\> These are decorated shoes with long, pointed, and upturned toes that extend anywhere from six to twenty-four inches in length. Often the toes are stuffed with hay or inserted whalebone to support the ends.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Round-toed Shoes*\</b\> Simple, slipper-like shoes which slide onto the feet. They feature a low top-cut, and rounded toes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sandals*\</b\> Designed for warm weather wear, each shoe is made from a single piece of sturdy fabric seamlessly attached to a sole designed for comfort. The toe area is open, with adjustable criss-crossing lacing covering the top of the foot and extending just past the ankles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Slippers*\</b\> Pointed toe shoes that easily slip on and off the foot. They feature a barely noticeable heel, half cuffs in the back, and double lacing on the top sides for a secure fit.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stilettos*\</b\> Opulent, feminine footwear featuring a long, thin high heel measuring six inches in length with a diameter at the ground of less than half an inch. Stilettos give the optical illusion of a longer, slimmer leg, a smaller foot, and a greater overall height. They also alter the wearer's posture and gait, flexing the calf muscles, and making the bust and buttocks more prominent.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Strapped Sandals*\</b\> A heelless, open-toed shoe boasting eight decorative straps which reach to just below the knees. The back of the footwear is a solid piece of fabric which offers support to the feet of the wearer.\\r\\n\<br\> \</font\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: specialty items ::..">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>~*~ \<u\>\<b\>Specialty Designs\</b\>\</u\> ~*~\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Seamstresses:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<font size=\\"2\\"\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Adventurer's Corset:\</b\> A strapped adventurer's corset is an outerwear garment. It has flexible boning that supports good posture and cinches the waist via lacing in the back. This corset has a build mini jacket that covers the shoulders and upper back. Between the mini-jacket and corset is a heart shaped cut out to show off a modest amount of cleavage. The right portion of the chest of the corset is reinforced and appears darker than the rest as if to protect the heart a little better. Running from the left shoulder and draping around the torso to attach to the lower back in a decorative strap with large rings to dangle things from. There is a strap like belt that wraps around the smallest part of the waist, pouches can be attached to small rings on this belt.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Backless Blouse:\</b\> A female upper body garment in which a singular piece of fabric snugly covers the frontal necessities before draping down to rest against the hips. Two barely-there straps secure it to the arms and give way on the backside to a large, circular cut-out which exposes an ample amount of furred skin or quills, depending on the species. Luxurious folds of leftover fabric pool atop the derriere to finish the piece.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Bateau gown:\</b\> Of simple and elegant design, this gown features a low, bateau neckline adorned with a short bodice that laces at the back by wave of decorative ribbons and dips into an elegant V, creating a flattering effect at the waist. Slender sleeves have been attached to the bodice in such a way to reveal the slightest hint of the wearer's shoulders. The lower portion of the gown features two skirts, a split-front overskirt that tapers gracefully toward the floor, and the skirt that is thusly revealed beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Bell-Sleeved Shirt:\</b\> Possessed of a subdued, casual style, this garment features a versatile and variable neckline set with a lace tie at the center that allows it to be pulled tight and worn at the neck, or left loose to wear on or off the shoulders, as the lady desires. It bears full-length, bell sleeves which drape and flow past the wrists in simplistic elegance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Corsetted Hunting Frock:\</b\> A unique, knee-length frock featuring a saucy, low-cut, and front lacing skirted coat with contrasting trim at the wide cuffs. Pullback corners have been added at the front base of the skirting with customized buttons adorning the cuffs, turn back seams, and backside of the garment. It comes complete with a matching corset underneath to smooth the silhouette of the wearer and closes atop via a series of laced and cinched metal grommets.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Corsetted Jacket:\</b\> This sleeveless jacket features a built-in corset stiffened with steel bones which is secured in the front via a series of laces. A short, stiffened collar ties the back of the garment around the shoulders to the top of the corset, creating makeshift 'straps'. The garment fits snug to the torso of the wearer, with the exception of the skirt which parts at the front, mid-thigh, and tapers to mid-calf at the back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Corsetted Overlay Dress:\</b\> A knee-length dress bearing a strapless, slimming corset with a sweetheart top that snugly hugs and lifts the breasts to reveal a decent amount of cleavage. Thirteen pairs of grommets adorn the front and are laced as loosely or tightly as the wearer desires to achieve a more slender silhouette. The skirt has been sewn onto the bottom of the corset and trails down into three tiers of modest ruffles that drape about the knee in casual folds. The entire garment has been overlaid with a contrasting patterned lace to increase the vibrancy of color and shine of the fabric below.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Dress Tunic:\</b\> A long-sleeved, formal tunic of elaborate design boasting a tight-fitting neck with a split down the front for pulling over the head. Gussets are present under the arms and have been inserted around the lower half to create a flaring skirt, with tablet-woven braids further decorating the neck, hem, and wrists to lend a dressier appearance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Earmuffs:\</b\> Earmuffs are objects designed to cover a person's ears for protection from cold. They consist of a metal head-band, that fits over the top or back of the head, with a plush-covered pad at each end, that cover the external ears.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Filigreed Slinky Gown:\</b\> A filigreed gown is a form fitting formal garment. The necklace would be considered modest as it covers everything from cleavage to neck. Instead intricate lace stretches from the neck, over the shoulders and arms, and across the decolletage. The rest of the gown seamlessly flows from the bodice to the skirt in one slinky piece that forms around the body tightly. The skirt has a modest train in the back and gradually volumizes as it reaches the ground.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Hooded, Cross-Lace Dress:\</b\> This dress fits snug to the upper body of the wearer, flares out over the hips and falls in elegant folds towards the ankles. A deep hood extends from the collar and parts at the front, offering room for a panel of decorative material which fits close to the bosom with a square neckline exposing the collarbones and criss-cross lacing drawing it tight about the waist. Long, tapering sleeves reach just past the hands, lending some warmth for those seeking it with the same decorative material lining the interior.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Woven Bandage Dress:\</b\> A woven bandage dress that is both unique and whimsical. It is literally made of doubled up bandages that are woven together and sewn in place. The bandages have been criss-crossed at the chest and over the butt to emphasize the shape. The tight skirt forms around the mid-thighs, nearly reaching the knees.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Long, Fingerless Gloves:\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These gloves are fingerless, encasing the base of the fingers to the elbows.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Mermaid Gown:\</b\> This is a sleek, floor-length gown that hugs the torso, hips and legs before flaring out at the knees and cascading to the floor in voluminous, elegant folds that trail slightly behind the wearer. A sweetheart neckline offers a small glimpse of cleavage with a lack of straps or sleeves to lend coverage to the shoulders and arms.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Pixie Skirt:\</b\> A square swathe of material has been gathered at the center and secured via a thick band about the hips of the wearer, lending four free-hanging points which drape just past the knees in a loose, whimsical arrangement.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Ribbon-Laced Blouse:\</b\> A garment for the upper part of the body, with sleeves extending from the collar to the wrists in gentle ruffles. A thin ribbon draws the material in at the waist, with additional ties bunching the sleeves at the forearms and biceps.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Ruched Halter Dress:\</b\> A flowy, floor-length dress featuring curved seams and layered ruching. The top boasts an off-center twisted halter which lends a wraparound appearance to the upper piece of the garment and secures it to the wearer. An elegant slit graces the left thigh and extends down just past the feet where the fabric pools together to lightly brush the ground.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Sheer Ceiling Drape:\</b\> A swath of thin fabric centrally gathered and bound with cord, string, or fishing line before being attached to ceiling beams or overhead light fixtures. It drapes and billows toward the wall where it is secured, and, when grouped with more, affords a muted illumination to the room while adding an air of elegance to those structures where coarser elements detract from the overall feel. In smaller rooms, four drapes is enough, whereas larger venues such as halls or ballrooms may require dozens.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Thigh-Length Florescent Tutu:\</b\> A thigh-length florescent tutu. A thigh-length, full skirt. Layered, triangular ruffles puff out from a three inch band of straight fabric around the waistline and furl out and down to the thighs to form a flocculent skirt.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Tulip Dress:\</b\> A tulip dress. A short, strapless fitted dress. The bodice of this gown has boned cups built in for the bust as the whole top is snugly laced over the breastbone with the sole purpose of keeping the gown upon the wearer. The skirt of the gown is a body hugging pencil skirt, made into the shape of a tulip to conform to the curve of feminine hips, and reaches just to mid-thigh. A sheer overlay has been sewn just below the bust line and cascades in tapered layers to the backs of the calves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Underbust Jacket:\</b\> This jacket fits close to the torso, leaving the bosom uncovered, and drapes over the hips with a short overskirt. It closes at the front by a series of laces secured via grommets with a double-breasted row of buttoned tags bordering either side. The upper portion of the garment reaches up around the chest with a short, stiffened collar, then extends into tapering sleeves ending in deep turn-back cuffs at the wrists. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<hr\>SoWeCanSew\<hr\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<font\>\\r\\n\<font size=\\"2\\"\>\<br\>\<b\>Tailors:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Bedroll:\</b\> A bed roll, or sleeping bag, consists of three layers - a bottom, 'shaggy' part (a mat), a darker middle layer (usually thick and woolen, a blanket) and a third layer (usually a linen sheet) which covers the sleeping person; this creates effective insulation for the bedding.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Buckled Tunic:\</b\> A sleeveless, loose-fitting tunic, extending to the knees and worn by both men and women. It is secured at the front via a series of six evenly spaced buckles and straps, with slashes extending from the hips, which allows more freedom of movement.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Gentleman's Coat:\</b\> An ankle-length coat. It boasts neck and shoulder frills which trail into slightly puffed sleeves until just above the elbow where they give way to a series of three decorative buckles which reach to just above the wrists of the wearer. Five matching buttons grace the front with which the garment can be closed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Gladiator Belt:\</b\> A thick belt wraps the waist and abdomen of the wearer, with three smaller belts lying atop securing the piece closed with small buckles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Hooded Long Coat:\</b\> The voluminous skirt of this long coat extends to the ankles of the wearer with a single row of buttons securing the front and flared sleeves ending at the wrists. A large, deep hood ajoins the fold-back collar of the garment before nipping in at the waist and elegantly accentuating the figure.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Open-Neck Vest:\</b\> This is a sleeveless vest secured at the front via a series of loops and laces. The collar of the garment opens at the neck and extends down just past the ribcage, exposing a fair bit of chest underneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Soldier Tent:\</b\> A soldier tent. A portable structure crafted from impregnated murky black sackcloth fabric and supported from within by a framework of poles. It has two masts which give the tent a height of six and one half feet, combined with a horizontal pole - five and a half feet in length for additional stability. The fabric of the tent flares outward from the narrow top to take the rough shape of a trapezoid. Loops line the reinforced bottom edge of the tent as a means of being secured to the ground via pins in place of guy ropes, with an oval entrance at the front which can be closed by use of the curtain provided.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Swordsman Gloves:\</b\> A pair of swordsman gloves. These are tailored so they fit over most animal's paws. These simple, yet elegant gloves bear reinforced palms and thumbs for additional sturdiness, with a high-cuff extending just over the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\<font\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: tailor patterns ::..">
         (\{ "hidden", "\<center\>\<a href=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" target=\\"_blank\\"\>\</a\>\<img src=\\"http://i.imgur.com/qqv3URa.png\\" border=\\"0\\" alt=\\"SoWeCanSew\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Tailor Patterns:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Cloaks\\"\>Cloaks\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Jackets\\"\>Jackets\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Shirts\\"\>Shirts\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Pants\\"\>Pants\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\> \<a href=\\"#Shoes\\"\>Shoes\</a\>\\r\\n\</center\> \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<font size=\\"2\\"\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Cloaks\\"\>Cloaks\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Back cloak*:\</b\> It is a cloak that, attached to the shoulders, falls down to the floor behind the wearer. The woman's version trails the floor in a graceful curve, while the men's cloak barely grazes the floor.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bellcloak*:\</b\> It is a cloak buttoned down the front with bulky sleeves in folds of cloth. Overall, this cloak resembles a bell.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Brat drape*:\</b\> A basic, but versatile, upper body draping. Often highly decorated, it can be worn several ways including belted around the waist, and pinned over one shoulder.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cape*:\</B\> This is a sleeveless outer garment which is designed to fasten at the throat and fall down the back of the wearer. Typically, luxurious materials are used to manufacture a cape, which is intended to be more fashionable than functional as a general rule. It falls only partially down the back, and drapes elegantly over the shoulders.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chasuble cape*:\</b\> This is a generic, circular cape with an aperture for the head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Evening cape*:\</b\> This is a sleeveless outer garment which is designed to fasten at the throat and fall down the back of the wearer. Worn as a formal garment, this particular cape is meant to be made from fine materials only, sometimes being constructed from lacy knit patterns or crochets, and occasionally beaded or laced with gems. It falls only partially down the back, and drapes elegantly over the shoulder.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sword cape*:\</b\> This is a half circle cape extending to mid-thigh. It is traditionally worn on one side and secured by a simple, yet elegant tie.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Capelet*:\</b\> This is a miniature cape designed to be worn during warm weather. Barely covering the shoulders in the front, the top rests just under the nape of the wearer in the back to fashionably frame the neckline.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hooded cloak*:\</b\> A full, floor-length cloak bearing a deep, concealing hood. It can be tightened at the neck via drawstrings or secured with a clasp.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Collared cape*:\</b\> Typically worn as courtly attire, this particular cape has a large over-turned collar ending at the hips, and features side openings for free movement of the arms.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gollar cape*:\</b\> A round or square shoulder covering used to keep the neck and chest area warm.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hooded lacerna cloak*:\</b\> A large, semi-circular cloak draped around the shoulder, down the back, and typically secured with a piece of jewelry. It bears a hood and serves as protection against the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Lacerna cloak*:\</b\> A large, semi-circular cloak draped around the shoulder, down the back and typically secured with a piece of jewelry. It serves as protection against the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Manteau cloak*:\</b\> A type of loose, ankle-length cloak that is worn over indoor clothing to protect the wearer from the elements, or it may form part of a fashionable outfit or uniform. It features a mantle spanning the width of the shoulders and ending at the neck with a collar and drawstring ties.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mantle*:\</b\> It is a cloak fashioned from a rectangular piece of cloth and is sleeveless. It reaches to the feet and wraps loosely around the body, shielding the wearer from the elements.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sagum mantle*:\</b\> A square, rectangular mantle draped over armor and held at the shoulder with a clasp or thorn.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tebenna*:\</b\> A long, robe-like cloak that extends down to the ankles. It drapes over the left shoulder and then wraps around the torso under the right arm, where it is secured in place.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Thigh-length cloak*:\</b\> Round in shape, this cloak reaches the thigh and fastens diagonally on the right shoulder with 6 buttons to reveal the garments beneath. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Jackets\\"\>Jackets\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ankle-length jacket*:\</b\> This garment extends almost to the floor and possesses long sleeves which reach to the wearers wrists. It is intended to protect the wearer from the elements, and is held shut by laces which run from the waist to the neck.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Buttoned long coat*:\</b\> A long-sleeved garment worn about the body, it covers the chest, torso and thighs when closed. Starting from the collar and ending at the waist are a series of double-row buttons with a button at each wrist to make allowance for turn-back cuffs.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cotehardie*:\</b\> Similar to the doublet, this is a four-piece garment tailored to fit close to the body with snug sleeves ending at the wrists. It is fastened along the forearms and down the front with a row of buttons.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Courtepy*:\</b\> A close fitting tunic or surcoat ending above the knee with long, hanging sleeves, wide-slit from shoulder to wrist. It is fitted with a standing collar.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Dagged coat*:\</b\> This is a coat featuring a simple, semi-fitted body, mid-length skirts, a small standing collar, and bag sleeves. Elaborate dagging has been created along the bottom edge. This garment is traditionally worn over a doublet and hose.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Dagged doublet*:\</b\> A fashionable doublet featuring dagged, diagonal cuts and decorative metallic trim. A row of twelve buttons close the garment while laces are available to tighten the sleeves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Doublet*:\</b\> A long-sleeved garment worn about the body, it covers the chest and torso when closed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Great coat*:\</b\> A large overcoat typically made of heavy materials, designed for protection against the weather. Its collar and cuffs can be turned out to protect the face and hands from cold and rain, and the short cape around the shoulders provides extra warmth.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Long jacket*:\</b\> A long-sleeved garment worn about the body, it covers the chest, torso and thighs when closed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Padded doublet*:\</B\> This is a slightly padded pourpoint overshirt meant to be fastened down the front to cover the chest and torso.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Peascod doublet*:\</b\> A traditional doublet bearing the characteristic shape of a pot belly. It features a stiff, tight underlining, buckram to make the protruding shape, and padding to hold it out. A peplum decorates the lower portion of the garment with small wings surrounding the armholes and hiding the points that are used to tie on the sleeves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pleated coat*:\</b\> This is a short jacket with pleats radiating from the shoulder and running to the hem with the waist creating a fashionable X shape. This garment closes with hidden hooks in the center front.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pourpoint*:\</b\> A body-skimming under-doublet which closes in the front via tied points. The sleeves and collar have been ommited while eyelets have been worked in the hem to support chausses or hose.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Quilted jerkin*:\</b\> A tailored, sleeveless jacket that fits close to the torso with a short collar. The entire garment has been textured to give a quilted appearance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short buckled jacket*:\</b\> A short female jacket ending just below the breasts that features a deep hood and a series of three buckles that close securely upon the chest. Each of the long sleeves is laced up via a myriad of eyelets and colored string.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short coat*:\</b\> Similar to the pirate jacket, this particular waist-length garment features a double row of buttons, a pair of short, back-turned cuffs, and fashionable collar.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-sleeved doublet*:\</b\> A short-sleeved garment worn about the body which covers the chest and torso when closed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Silhouette jerkin*:\</b\> A sleeveless jacket that has been punched for decoration and improved fit. It buttons at the waist and remains open at the torso to reflect the fashionable narrow-waisted silhouette.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Slashed sleeved doublet*:\</b\> A hip-length doublet with long, slashed sleeves which reveal the sleeves of the garment beneath.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless doublet*:\</b\> A sleeveless garment worn about the body which covers the chest and torso when closed. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Shirts\\"\>Shirts\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Arming cotte*:\</b\> An upper torso covering featuring 8 arming points with leather rectangles at the shoulder, upper arm and leg to use for pointing your armour. It is designed to keep your arm and leg harness hanging exactly where it belongs, while distributing its weight across your entire torso.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bag-sleeved cotte*:\</b\> While being similar to the tunic and surcoat, this shirt is fitted closer to the body with bag sleeves ending in snug cuffs at the wrist.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cavalier shirt*:\</b\> A male garment featuring full sleeves, gathered cuffs, and a stiffened collar with a lace front closure.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fold-neck shirt*:\</b\> This is a cowl-front shirt which pulls on over the head before the front is folded down across the throat and under the collar. This style of shirt protects the wearer's chest and throat from drafts and any over-collars from becoming dirty easily.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Frilled shirt*:\</b\> A male shirt enriched with a single frill and front-lying eyelets. Loose-fit sleeves extend down to the wrists where a small frill creates an elegant finish.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gambeson*:\</b\> A thick padded garment designed to be worn under a chainmail shirt to reduce the risk of injury. Adjustable laces extend from the neck to the upper chest.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gypsy shirt*:\</b\> A men's straight cut shirt with full sleeves and a v-neck turned back collar.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Half-cape frilled shirt*:\</b\> A long-sleeved male shirt decorated with a half-cape accessory that covers the front and back shoulders. Subtle frills decorate the upper chest and cuffs of the garment.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Half-shirt*:\</b\> A male upper body garment that wraps about the torso and drapes over one shoulder to leave half the chest exposed.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hooded overtunic*:\</b\> A sleeveless, layered tunic with edging around the shoulders and a matching hood secured by hidden wires to shroud the wearer's hair and head.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Infantry gambeson*:\</b\> A heavy-duty gambeson worn by knights and men-at-arms alike. The quilted body makes it a great addition over a shirt of chainmail if one is available. It features lacing up the left side along the torso and neck to lend a fitted look, and a high collar for extra protection.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Padded shirt*:\</b\> A lace-up gambeson which can be worn as a stand alone garment or as an undershirt with a jerkin. The long, fitted sleeves are decorated with a patterned thread design.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Riveted tunic*:\</b\> A generic tunic stylized with unfinished and fringed edges to give a rougher look to the wearer.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruffled shirt*:\</b\> This is a garment comes with convenient ties at the wrists. Each generous sleeve ends in a fashionable ruffle.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shirt*:\</b\> This is a garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar, sleeves, and a front opening.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Short-sleeved shirt*:\</b\> This is a garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar, short sleeves, and a buttoned front.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless shirt*:\</b\> This is a sleeveless garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar and a front opening.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sleeveless tunic*:\</b\> This loose-fitting sleeveless tunic extends to the thighs and worn by both men and women. It features a simple collar and can be dressed up with belts or worn as is for a more casual appearance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Slit-neck shirt*:\</b\> This is a simple, loose-fitting shirt with tubular sleeves, underarm gussets, and a boat neckline.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tie-neck shirt*:\</b\> This is a simple, loose-fitting shirt with tubular sleeves and underarm gussets. The banded collar extends into front ties.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tie-neck tunic*:\</b\> A simple, loose-fitting shirt with tubular sleeves and underarm gussets. The banded collar extends into front ties.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tunic*:\</b\> A loose-fitting long-sleeved tunic, extending to the thighs and worn by both men and women.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Two-toned shirt*:\</b\> A garment for the upper part of the body, with a collar and front-opening. It sports a pair of baggy, two-toned sleeves that tie snugly at the wrists.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Undertunic*:\</b\> A loose fitting, long sleeved undertunic, shorter than an over tunic, and to be worn between the body and more precious garments.\\r\\nVest: This is a sleeveless garment generally worn by men under a coat or jacket and on top of a shirt. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Pants\\"\>Pants\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Boot hose*:\</b\> Worn with breeches or trousers, these are masculine footless stockings which are traditionally turned over boot cuffs to expose a fashionable lace or trim edge.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Braccae*:\</b\> Pants made with a drawstring that tend to reach from just above the knee at the shortest, to the ankles at the longest, with length generally increasing in tribes and clans living further north.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Breeches*:\</b\> These are trousers ending just above the knee, often worn by riders, clergy, and affluent middle class.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chaps*:\</b\> Heavy trousers without a seat, worn over ordinary trousers to protect the wearer's legs.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chausses*:\</b\> These are pants designed to cover the legs, which extend downward to rest atop the feet. There are laces at the top which can be tied onto braies or laced to a supportive codpiece.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Doublet hose*:\</b\> Close-fitting leggings reaching up to the hips and usually fastened to a doublet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ensemble pants*:\</b\> Ankle-length, paneled legwear featuring open slashes and a button-up front.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Flared pants*:\</b\> These are body-hugging leg coverings that cling from the hips down to the thighs and then flare outward into belled bottoms from the calves down.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Harem pants*:\</b\> Baggy pants, tied at the ankles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Jodhpurs*:\</b\> Wide-hipped riding pants of heavy cloth, fitting tightly from knee to ankle.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pantaloons*:\</b\> These are baggy trousers extending from waist to ankle.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pants*:\</b\> An article of clothing covering the body from the waist down, with separate coverings for each leg that extend to the ankles. They are usually closed and fastened by either buttons or a laces, though straps with buckles or brooches are also commonplace.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pleated pants*:\</b\> Pleated, skirtlike trousers that fit snugly at the waist before radiating broadly toward the ankles of the wearer. They are typically worn by fighters to disguise leg movement.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Pluderhose*:\</b\> These are knee-length breeches which are baggy and paned. They are traditionally worn by men.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Puffed pants*:\</b\> Extending from waist to ankles, these pants are puffy except for the ties that hold them snug above the knees.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ruffled pants*:\</b\> Three cascading ruffles grace the lower legs of these pants, with a close-lying fit through the hip and thigh regions. They come complete with a wide waistband for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Shorts*:\</b\> These are trousers that end at or above the knee, generally worn by men.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Slops*:\</b\> Flamboyant knee-length shorts which are slashed vertically from the knee to reveal contrasting fabric underneath. There are laces at the groin which can be tied closed or laced to a supportive codpiece.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Split-hose*:\</b\> These are a transitional style of hose made of separate legs which have been bias-cut and are open from front to back through the crotch. This garment features a seam running the entire length of the wearer's rear, is lined to mid-thigh, and has a full foot. Thread eyelets located on the upper edge point the hose to a doublet or pourpoint. This style affords much more coverage of the hip and buttocks than chausses, and is often seen on soldiers and working people.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stretch pants*:\</b\> Skin-tight legwear featuring leather straps which buckle around the calves.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Swordsman pants*:\</b\> Legwear featuring drawstrings at the ankles, as well as right above the knees which can be tightened to lend a puffy and swashbuckling appearance to the wearer, or loosened for a more casual and comfortable look.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tights*:\</b\> A snug stretchable garment covering the body from the waist down.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Trews*:\</b\> A pair of lightweight trews complete with a drawstring waist and a bottom tie. The tie is flexible and can be drawn at the ankles or bloused up and tied at the knee.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Trousers*:\</b\> Loose-fitting legwear with a gusseted crotch for freedom of movement. They tie with a drawstring waist for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Two-toned pants*:\</b\> These baggy pants extend from the waist to the ankles and can be adjusted with the use of drawstrings along the entire length. The material itself is comprised of two different shades of the same colour.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Underdrawers*:\</b\> Beginning at the waist and extending downward to the knee, these male undergarments serve as a separate lining to breeches and other pants, aiding in preservation of over garments and adding an additional layer of warmth.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Waterfall pants*\</b\> Legwear featuring a drawstring waist that has been designed to portray an upside-down waterfall effect. The width of the material increases from the bottom toward the waist in a cascading fashion, creating an archetypal look on the wearer. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Shoes\\"\>Shoes\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Boots*:\</b\> These are tailored so they fit over most animals paws. Custom shoes are available to hooved animals such as horses, or animals with strangely shaped feet.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Ankle-high boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to to the ankle and tie securely via lacing on the side. They feature padded soles for added comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bucket boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to mid-leg before folding down over the knee into an elaborate 11 inch flared bell cuff. The interior features a padded sole for comfort\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Calf-high boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to to the calf and are accented by a series of fashionable straps. The interior is complimented with a plush lining and padded sole, ensuring these boots are comfortable, all day pieces of apparel.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Castle-top boots*:\</b\> These slip-on boots reach just to the knee and boast a castle-top dagged edge. The interior features a padded sole for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Dress shoes*:\</b\> This fancy footwear completely conceals the wearer's feet and extends to just above the ankle before tying or buckling securely into place. Traditionally, these are highly polished or decorated and worn to formal events.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Heeled boots*:\</b\> These 2 inch heeled boots reach just to to the knee and boast top-folded cuffs. The interior features a padded sole for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Infantry boots*:\</b\> These tough, heavy boots rise just to the calf and feature wooden toggles which can be tied to the side for a secure fit. They have been enhanced with comfort soles and a thin heel to provide good traction.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Knee-high boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to the knee and close via two front strap enclosures with lacing. The interior features a padded sole for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Maiden boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to the thigh and feature back lacing which can be adjusted for a snug or loose fit. The upper length can be folded down into a cuff to achieve the traditional 'pirate look', or left up to lend a dressier appearance. They feature 2 and a half inch heels, large enough to be obviously feminine but allowing no risk for tripping on holes or uneven ground\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Strapped boots*:\</b\> Footwear reaching just to the knees which is held in place by a myriad of primitive strings and straps wrapped about the circumference.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tall boots*:\</b\> These boots reach just to the thigh and feature a back slit panel that allows them to be cuffed down. They have a 1 inch heel and are padded for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Toggle boots*:\</b\> These tough boots rise to just below the calves and are excellent for peasant work as well as for wearing under armours. They slip on and then close via a series of four toggles.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Work boots*:\</b\> Durable footwear that has a protective reinforcement in the toe, usually combined with a sole plate, which protects the foot from falling objects and punctures from below. They extend just to the calf before tying securely. \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<a name=\\"Hats\\"\>Hats\</a\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Acorn hat*:\</b\> It is a somewhat rounded hat tapering upward into a blunt point.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Bandana*:\</b\> A large piece of square cloth, generally worn on the head or around the neck. They are typically brightly colored with some sort of pattern or design on their surface. Around the neck, it can be pulled up to the nose and mouth to lessen the inhalation of dust and debris. Upon the head, it can prevent perspiration from running into the eyes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Face bandana*:\</b\> It is an article of clothing that is intended to cover some part of the head or face to mask imperfections or conceal certain features.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Beret*:\</b\> It is a soft round cap, usually of wool or felt, with a flat crown, which is worn by both men and women.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Biretta*:\</b\> It is a square cap with three or four ridges or peaks, sometimes surmounted by a tuft.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Camauro*:\</b\> It is a cap traditionally worn by the high ranking members of the Church of S'allumer. Camauros are usually crafted of red wool or velvet with white faux fur trim and are worn, usually in winter, in place of the zucchetto, which in turn takes the place of the biretta worn by other members of the clergy.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cap*:\</b\> It is a form of headgear. Caps have crowns that fit closer than hats and have no brim or only a visor. They are typically designed for warmth and, when including a visor, blocking sunlight from the eyes.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Capotain hat*:\</b\> It is a tall-crowned, narrow-brimmed, slightly conical hat, usually black.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Cavalier hat*:\</b\> A cavalier hat is a wide-brimmed hat traditionally trimmed with a plume or feather.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Chapeau hat*:\</b\> It is flat hat - very narrow atop - with a broad brim, adorned with long silken interlaced strings; suspended from within are rows of tassels, increasing in number as they near to the outer edges of the hat.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Conical hat*:\</b\> It is a hat shaped like a cone.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Crispine*:\</b\> A cap made of a net and headband for padding hair.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Fez hat*:\</b\> It is a hat in the shape of a truncated cone; usually, it is made of red felt.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Flat cap*:\</b\> It is a rounded men's cap with a small stiff brim in front.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Gugel hood*:\</b\> It is a type of hood with a trailing point. It is tailored to fit the head and shoulders, and is usually made from wool or loden. In the fashionable style, the gugel can be worn on top of the head like a hat, with the head-part inverted inside the collar, which then hangs over the ears.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Hood*:\</b\> It is a kind of headgear that covers most of the head and neck and sometimes the face.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Jester hat*:\</b\> This head covering comes to three points, each tipped with a bell.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Mitre*:\</b\> The mitre is a tall folding cap, consisting of two similar parts (the front and back) rising to a peak and sewn together at the sides. Two short lappets always hang down from the back.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Padded arming cap*:\</b\> It is normally worn under the helmet or chain mail for comfort.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Phrygian cap*:\</b\> It is a soft, conical cap with the top pulled forward, and usually the color red.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Skullcap*:\</b\> This is a small, circular cap, often with a small bit of cloth in the center looking like the tip of a beret.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Sock hat*:\</b\> This hat is similar in shape to the sock. It rests slackly about the head and the excess materials are draped to either side as the wearer prefers.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Stuffed chaperone*:\</b\> This is a stuffed ring which encircles the head while additional material is piled atop the crown. A single length of fabric remains to drape loosely, and fashionably, around the neck.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Top hat*:\</b\> It is a tall, flat-crowned, broad-brimmed hat.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Tricorn hat*:\</b\> It is a hat with a rather broad brim, pinned up on either side of the head and at the back, producing a triangular shape. The hat was typically worn with the point facing forward, though it was not at all unusual for soldiers, who would often rest a musket on their right shoulder, to wear the tricorn pointed to the right to allow better clearance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Wide-brimmed hat*:\</b\> It is a hat with a wide brim surrounding the cap.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>*Zucchetto*:\</b\> Also called pileolus, it is a small skullcap worn by clerics of the Church. It was adopted for practical reasons to keep the clergy's tonsured heads warm in cold, damp churches. It consists of eight panels sewn together, with a stem at the top. The zucchetto continues to be worn while the mitre is being worn; it is placed inside it (a mitre is bottomless, so the zucchetto sits on the head while the mitre is around it). \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>--\\r\\n\<br\>\</font\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:..:: uniforms ::..">
         (\{ "members", "\<br\>\<center\>\<b\>\<u\>Current Uniforms\</u\>\</b\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<u\>1.) Vicious Koi\</u\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>- Creamy chocolate suede shawl\\r\\n\<br\>- Crimson poplin scarf\\r\\n\<br\>- Pearly white satin blouse\\r\\n\<br\>- Crimson poplin knee-length skirt\\r\\n\<br\>- Gold leather waist cord\\r\\n\<br\>- Gold leather maiden boots\\r\\n\<br\>- Pearly white cotton tights\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>\<u\>2.) Rinaldi Guard\</u\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<u\>\<b\>Order 1\</u\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>- A pearly white cotton blouse\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of midnight black wool pants\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of midnight black leather infantry boots\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of midnight black leather swordsman gloves\\r\\n\<br\>- A midnight black leather double wrap belt\\r\\n\<br\>- A lavender grey damask gambeson embroidered with the Rinaldi symbol\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<u\>\<b\>Order 2\</u\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>- A pearly white ruffled silk blouse\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of pearly wool pants\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of midnight black leather infantry boots\\r\\n\<br\>- A pair of midnight black leather swordsman gloves\\r\\n\<br\>- A midnight black leather double wrap belt\\r\\n\<br\>- A lavender grey damask sleeveless doublet.\\r\\n\<br\>- A lavender grey damask cavalier hat\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<u\>\<b\>Order 3\</u\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>- A silver satin shoulder sash\\r\\n\<br\>- A lavender grey damask gambeson with silver trimming, embroidered with the Rinaldi symbol\\r\\n\<br\>- A gold satin sash\\r\\n\<br\>- A lavender grey damask gambeson with gold trimming, embroidered with the Rinaldi symbol\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "visitors", "", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<html\>\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<img src=\\"https://i.imgur.com/S2TYeVC.png\\" \<width=\\"550\\" height=\\"150\\"\>\</center\>\\r\\n\</body\>\</html\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>--------------------------------------------------\</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>Our guild was created to unify clothing crafters of all forms. It is our hope to continue supplying the city with the best fashions and welcoming new clothiers to help hone their skills.\</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\> \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=3\>   \</font\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<font color=\\"black\\"\>\<font size=2\>\\r\\n~\&#9829;\&#119871;\&#119998;\&#119995;\&#119890; \&#119998;\&#120008; \&#119990; \&#119995;\&#119990;\&#120008;\&#119997;\&#119998;\&#119900;\&#120003; \&#120008;\&#119997;\&#119900;\&#120012; \&#119990;\&#120003;\&#119993; \&#120009;\&#119997;\&#119890; \&#120012;\&#119900;\&#120007;\&#120001;\&#119993; \&#119998;\&#120008; \&#120014;\&#119900;\&#120010;\&#120007; \&#120008;\&#120009;\&#119990;\&#119892;\&#119890;\&#9829;~\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1459125175, "jominey", "E", 1459125205, "jominey", "E", 1571341466, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
