<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:@commands">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>@commands (OOC Guide to @commands)\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTo get Holy Water: \<B\>*Scoop basin*\</B\>. \<I\>Please note that this only works if you are standing in the Cathedral de Temoine near the basin.\</I\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTo cure Zombie Infections: \<B\>*Apply my water to \\"persons\\" eyes*\</B\>. \<I\>If you have successfully entered the command, the victim should feel some burning.\</I\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPrayer bead emits: \<B\>*Rub my beads*\</B\>. \<I\>The parser will give you an emit saying you generate a feeling of peace.\</I\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ceremonies: baptism">
         (\{ "members", "" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ceremonies: wedding">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Wedding text suggestion\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMy dear children, you have come together in this Chapel so that S'Allumer may seal and strengthen your love in the presence of the Church's minister and this community. The Light abundantly blesses this love. It has already filled you and now it will enrich and strengthen you by a special sacrament so that you may assume the duties of marriage in mutual and lasting fidelity. And so, in the presence of the Church, I ask you to state your intentions.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nGroom and Bride, have you come here freely and without reservation to give yourselves to each other in marriage? \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWill you love and honor each other as man and wife for the rest of your lives?\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWill you accept children lovingly from S'Allumer and bring them up according to the virtues of Saint Helloise and the Church? \<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>To the audience\</u\>: Is there any of those gathered here today who see any reason that these two shall not join in Sacred marriage? If so, speak up now, or be forever silent.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>To the couple\</u\>: You have declared your consent before the Church, and none has spoken against this Union. May the Light in its goodness strengthen your consent and fill you both with its blessings.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhat S'Allumer has joined, men must not divide. Amen\\r\\n\<h3\>Blessing to married couple\</h3\>\\r\\nS'Allumer the Light keep you in love with each other, so that the peace of Saint Helloise may abide in your home.\<br/\>\<br/\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Blessing to the audience\</h3\>\\r\\nBear witness to the love of S'Allumer in this world, so that those to whom love is a stranger will find in you generous friends. \<br/\>\<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:church hierarchy">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Church Hierarchy\</h2\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Acolyte\</B\>(Yeoman equivalent): Referred to as Acolyte\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Monk\</B\>(Burgher equivalent): Referred to as Brother\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Pastor/Lay Minister\</B\>(Thane equivalent): Referred to as Pastor\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Deacon\</B\>(Gentry equivalent): Referred to as Father\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Presbyter\</B\>(Arm. gentry equivalent): Referred to as Reverend Father/Mother by people outside the church and as Father/Mother by people within\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Prelate\</B\>(Knight equivalent): Referred to as Most Reverend Father/Mother\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Bishop\</B\>(Baronet equivalent): Referred to as My Lord/My Lady\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Exarch\</B\>(Baron/Baroness equivalent): Referred to as Exarch\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Vicar General\</B\>(Viscount equivalent): Referred to as Vicar\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Archbishop\</B\>\</I\>(Earl equivalent): Referred to as Your Grace\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Metropolitan\</B\>(Landgrave equivalent): Referred to as Archbishop\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Primate\</B\>(Margrave equivalent): Referred to as Primate\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Cardinal\</B\>(Marquis equivalent): Referred to as Your Eminence\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*\<B\>Patriarch\</B\>(Duke equivalent): Referred to as Patriarch\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\\r\\nSome time ago, Presbyter Ximen had put forth the wonderful notion of attempting to increase our membership by offering helpful welcome to new city arrivals to assist them in getting on their feet and getting settled.  I would like to remind all of this great idea and encourage you to offer up an invitation to all those whom would like to walk in the Light, even if only for a brief time until they find their place within the city, hopefully taking the teachings with them to pass along to others.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n~ Father Antos Bareil ", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:definitions of church positions">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Definitions of Church Positions\</h2\>\\r\\n\<B\> Holy See \</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nThere are four Holy See of the church. Their job is to approve and revoke charters of the church (for different denominations), and they are directly responsible for promotions, hiring, and other such things of clergy. They approve new buildings, and spending of massive funds for missionary work and the like. The Holy See also preside over trials of those who are Clergymen anywhere on the hierarchy. (Though only one is needed for this trial, and Bishops can preside over trials without the presence of the Holy See. Note the Clergy cannot be tried by common law, only a Presbyter or above may hold a trial for another Clergyman). Only the Holy See, by divine guidance may change the doctrine of the Church of S'allumer, and to do so without their approval, guidance, input is stricty against the Church of S'Allumer and one will be excommunicated. They are the highest authority in the Church. \<BR\> \<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES TO CHANGE DOCTRINE AND THE LIKE FILE AN ASSIST OR CONTACT STAFF WHICH WILL GUIDE YOU IN THESE STEPS. THE SAME WITH STARTING ANOTHER DENOMINATION IN THE CHURCH SUCH AS PALADINS, INQUISITION, OR ANOTHER SECT.\</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\> Pontiff\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nThe Pontiff is a member of the Holy See, and is the leader of this group of Clergy. His vote breaks ties, his word is final as granted by The Great Light.\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Master Capitulars\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nMaster Capitulars are the leaders of their sects, denominations, and other offshoots of the Church. Each Master Capitular controls only their sect of the church. In example you can have ONE (1) Master Capitular over the Paladins. That sect would be approved by the Holy See and have it's own ranking then of Bishop Knights, Prelate Knights, Presbyters, Ordained Ministers and the like beneath them. They have the ability to interpret and teach doctrine according to their sect, though not change doctrine. Further they have the ability to preside over trials of other Clergy, hire, promote, or excommunicate persons within their own sect. (Not the church as a whole).\<BR\> \<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES TO CREATE A NEW SECT IT MUST BE APPROVED BY THE HOLY SEE. CONTACT STAFF TO CREATE A NEW SECT, FURTHERMORE IT IS A SEPARATE GUILD FROM THE HOLY CHURCH OF S'ALLUMER THOUGH STILL CONSIDERED ALLIED WITH THE MAIN CHURCH BODY.\</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Bishops\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nBishops have the power to preside over trials of other Clergymen, the ability to teach and guide those below them, reccomend those beneath them for advancement, and promote Presbyters to Prelates. A Bishop would be in charge of a region, or an entire city's clergy, diretly beneath the Master Capitulars. They can only be tried by Master Capitulars or above and only removed from office by the Holy See. They can preform blessings, weddings, funerals, exorcisms and are directly in charge of the ebb and flow of information within their sect. (IE: lessons and what not, approving who learns what and how much.)\<BR\>\<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES THEIR PURCHASEABLE TITLES ARE: BISHOP\</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Prelates\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nPrelates have the power to reside over the trial of other Clergymen who are beneath them, the ability to teach and guide those below them, reccomend those beneath them for advancement, and promote Ordained Ministers to Presbyters. A Prelate would be in charge of a city, or an section of the city's clergy, directly beneath the Bishops. They can only be tried by Bishops or above and only removed from office by the Master Capitulars or above. They can preform blessings, weddings, funerals, exorcisms and are directly in charge of monetary means, trading, and supplies within their sect.\<BR\>\<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES  THEIR PURCHASEABLE TITLES ARE: PRELATE \</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Presbyters\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nA Presbyter would be in charge a single church in a city or another type of program (such as an orphanage, or a missionary station in a far off land) and all the clergy beneath them. They are diretly beneath the Prelates. They can only be tried by Prelates or above and only removed from office by the Bishops or above. They can preform blessings, weddings, funerals, exorcisms and are directly in charge of the growth of believers and conversion to the church. They are in charge of teaching Ordained Ministers and below.\<BR\>\<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES THEIR PURCHASEABLE TITLES ARE: PRIEST, PRIESTESS, DEACON\</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Ordained Minister\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nAn Ordained would be in charge a single aspect of a church in a city. (Such as a Youth Ministry program, a Choir, Sermons, or Counseling, Theological Research groups) and all the clergy beneath them. They are diretly beneath the Presbyter. They can only be tried by Prelates or above and only removed from office by the Prelate or above. They can perform blessings, weddings, funerals, exorcisms and are directly in charge of learning doctrine, and all about the community in which they live to spread the will of The Great Light. \<BR\>\<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES THIS IS THE LOWEST RANK TO BE CONSIDERED A PRIEST. A NEW PRIEST TO THE GAME WOULD BE PLACED AS AN ORDAINED MINISTER BEFORE THEY ARE PROMOTED UPWARD. THEIR PURCHASEABLE TITLES ARE: ACOLYTE \</font\>\</I\>\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>Other Clergy\</B\>\<P\>\\r\\nAny other Clergy not recognized as a full Priest of the church belongs here. This can be clerics, squires, and healers who have decided to take the path of Clergy after converted to the Holy Church of S'Allumer. They have no oaths that bind them, nor vows that constrict them but should be upstanding members of the community who desire to become a Priest, or a devout member of the Church. These members -can- be tried by criminal law and do not afford a Church Trial. \<BR\>\<I\>\<font size=2\>OOC : For OOC PURPOSES THIS IS THE LOWEST RANK AND STILL BE WITHIN THE CHURCH. THIS CAN BE A VERY DEVOTED MEMBER WHO INSISTS ON BEING A MEMBER OF THE CHURCH YET NOT A PRIEST, FURTHERMORE IF A MEMBER OF CLERGY IS LEGALLY WED THEY ARE REDUCED TO THIS POINT. THOSE WHO DID NOT START WITH A PRIEST CAREER START HERE AND CAN LEARN THE CAREER PATH AND MOVE UPWARD. \</I\>\<P\>\</font\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:donations">
         (\{ "members", "\<center\>-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<html\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<head\>\\r\\n\<meta http-equiv=\\"Content-Language\\" content=\\"en-us\\"\>\\r\\n\<meta name=\\"GENERATOR\\" content=\\"Microsoft FrontPage 5.0\\"\>\\r\\n\<meta name=\\"ProgId\\" content=\\"FrontPage.Editor.Document\\"\>\\r\\n\<meta http-equiv=\\"Content-Type\\" content=\\"text/html; charset=windows-1252\\"\>\\r\\n\<title\>New Page 4\</title\>\\r\\n\</head\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<body\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Donations may be given to me to hold until the \\r\\ntime you need it.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWhen giving donations, please remember that there are some people that may try \\r\\nto take advantage of our generousity.\<br\>\\r\\n \</font\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</font\>\<font face=\\"Book Antiqua\\" size=\\"4\\"\>\<b\>Began with: 219\</b\>\</font\>\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n \</font\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<p align=\\"left\\"\>\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n-10: Gave donations of 5 denarii a piece to two new arrives to town.\<br\>\\r\\n+656: A generous donation given by several people.\<br\>\\r\\n+30: Two different donations \<br\>\\r\\n+48: From the seamstress Sangia\<br\>\\r\\n+62: A very generous donation from Garv after his competition, half of the prize \\r\\nmoney was given to the church.\<br\>\\r\\n+24: Given by Dominique\<br\>\\r\\n-6: Donated to a poor musician named Basinni who was robbed and new to the city.\<br\>\\r\\n-5: Donated to a skunk in need.\<br\>\\r\\n+15: Donated by Mister Twyrch\<br\>\\r\\n+240: Generously given by Mistress Vanya.\<br\>\\r\\n+160: Paid by Sir Lyam after Miss Dazrene's revival.\<br\>\\r\\n+120: Paid by Miss Meepers for Avery's revival.\<br\>\\r\\n-10: Given to Father Zaius who had just arrived in town. \<br\>\\r\\n+200: Donated by Miss Meepers for the orphanage.\<br\>\\r\\n+15: Donated by Mister Bruno.\<br\>\\r\\n-50: Used to create the guild charter for St. Helloise's Children's Home.\<br\>\\r\\n+1: Donated by Mister Brumble.\<br\>\\r\\n+70: Donated for the Children's Home by Master Zeiss\<br\>\\r\\n+1: Graciously donated by Mister Brumble. \<br\>\\r\\n+3: Given by little Lennox\<br\>\\r\\n+214: Given by Meepers for donation and for the revival of Miss Avery\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n+88: Donation given after yesterday's sermon (ooc: 4-19-07)\<br\>\\r\\n+25 and 11 bits: Donated by little Caitlin after the play\<br\>\\r\\n+355: Donated by myself (Basanti) from the winnings after the play.\<br\>\\r\\n+167: Various single donations collected by Teefs and Yarwoodle\<br\>\\r\\n+890: Yarwoodle's diligent collections\<br\>\\r\\n+1000: Yarwoodle's sales of study materials\<br\>\\r\\n+1480: Yarwoodle's further sales of study materials\<br\>\\r\\n+500: A donation from mister Thompson\<br\>\\r\\n+500: A donation from the Rinaldi, through Marcus\\r\\n\\r\\n \</font\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</font\>\<font face=\\"Book Antiqua\\" size=\\"4\\"\>\<b\>Current Donations: \<u\>7012\</u\> \\r\\nDenarii\</b\>\</font\>\<br\>\\r\\n \</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</body\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</html\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:history of the church">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>History of the Church\</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Origins of the Church: Don Raphael, Saint Helloise, and Constantin\</h3\>\\r\\n\<i\>by Friar Teefs\</i\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe faith, though often ascribed to Helloise, is actually The Witness of the life of Don Raphael. For it was his visions, his wisdom, and his sagacity which Helloise recorded in \<i\>Le Temoin\</i\> (\<i\>The Witness\</i\>). She performed miracles. Yet it was the Don himself who taught her what it meant to be a penitent. He saw in her greatness to heal. He showed her to the Light.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nShe attended to him, and learned as the Nurse of the Rinaldi. Though at first she was a healer with her hands, at the end of her life, she could heal with her spirit.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nShe always did have a knack for miracles! For when Don Raphael's son was dying, Helloise, through her natural grace and the blessings of S'allumer, lifted up the child in her arms. He would have died, had it not been for the miraculous healing power of S'allumer that coursed through the loving kind hands of Helloise.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is Helloise whom the Order of Guerisseurs emulate. Healers, both of doctoring as well as White Magics.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThat was the first miracle of her life. She then, in service of the Rinaldi, faithfully attended them, and especially the Don thoughout the rest of his life.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nShe then attended the Don at his deathbed, and recorded \<i\>Le Temoin\</i\> -- The story of his witness of the Great Light. They both knew that their faith would change the world.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nShe then had a career after his passing, still in service to the Rinaldi. For Constantin, the small fox kit she had saved from death, succeeded his father as a grown prince.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt was after that, during Constantin's reign, that the city suffered a terrible plague. Everyone was dying of it. Many had already passed on. There was no way to stop it through medicines. It was so virulent that, literally, everyone was preparing for their deaths. Everyone.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIt was during this crisis that Helloise sacrificed her life for the sake of all those around her. She prayed to the Great Light and it accepted her life. She ascended into a brilliant, blinding Light. Her vestments were all that were left behind. Empty. Immaculate. In exchange for this sacrifice, the entire city was cured of its affliction. And this sort of plague has never since affected Triskellian.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe altar here [in the Cathedrale de Temoine] has become the reliquary of her vestments from that day.\<br\>\<hr\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>The Martyrdom of Helloise\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDon Rafael passed on, unpopular in death as he was in life. What is more interesting than his death, however, is the history of his nurse, HELLOISE. On the night of her master's death, she experianced a revelation, which she perceived as a glowing white light that surrounded her body.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nDon Rafael's heir, the young CONSTANTIN, lay sick in his mother's arms, crying for release from the plague that wracked his body. Nothing the apothecaries and scholars could produce could alleviate his affliction. The nurse, Helloise, gathered up the suffering child, and then glowed with the same white light that had touched her body once before. The child was cured.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHelloise wandered through the streets of Treskellian, curing all whom she touched in the same way. She walked from house to house for four days, healing all whom she could, but each day she felt her strength ebb. On the fifth day, she collapsed from exhaustion. When she awoke, she started again, knowing that every moment more people were dying from this plague that only she could stop.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThat evening, she sank to her knees in sorrow and enervation, sick with the knowledge that, in this way, she would be unable to save everyone. Consumed with pity and selflessness, she prayed that this glowing white light should take her life in exchange for all the innocents who would perish by the plague. With that act, her body was wreathed in a flame that did not burn but rather it spread from where she knelt throughout the entire city. All who were touched by this miraculous flame found themselves cured. Once all were saved, Helloise collapsed and perished in the knowledge that her death brought others life.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIt was by this act that ignited the worship of S'ALLUMER, the life-giving luminance. All who had been touched by the altruistic Helloise began to come together under the banner of the young Don. Don Constantin's mother was declared the first Arch-Cardinal of the Church of S'allumer, and she spread the church's work beyond the lands of Rinaldi. The Don commanded that a great Cathedrale be built upon the spot of Helloise's ultimate sacrifice. The construction of the Cathedrale is the most ambitious engineering project in all of Calabria, beyond anything undertaken by the Rinaldi before or since. To support the great dome, a great spell was woven by the first apostles of the church, the power of which lasts to this day.\\r\\n\<br\>\<hr\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHis teachings were recorded by (the Nurse to the Rinaldi) Helloise. She was a commoner who became enlightened at the moment the Shining Path touched her. She became a favorite within the courts of the land, and as her fame grew she touched others with the strength of her revelation and her power. She performed miracles of healing and even brought the dead back from the grave as if they had never passed from this world. Such miracles had not been seen for thousands of years and were spoken of as myth. Her final miracle was the saving of the entire city from a disastrous plague. She so loved the inhabitants, praying so resolutely for their release from suffering, that in an act that can only be called a loving sacrifice she offered herself to the Eternal Light. At the instant of her death it is recorded that a figure of purest white appeared from the heavens and took her hand. She then dissolved completely into a cloud of white radiant light. That very day the city was completely expunged from the plague that was on the verge of destroying it.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs true witnesses to her ascension the whole of the Rinaldi court converted on the day of her death. They were soon to be followed by the Bisclavret and the Avoirdupois royal houses. The Doloreaux royals accepted the radiance only recently. Many commoners have converted and as Triskellion is home of the \\"House of Helloise,\\" as the Cathedrale is known to the common folk; it is the center of worship for the faith. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs Penitents, we work to be worthy of final release consumed in the radiance of the Eternal Light and in that comsumption to be of service to others. Only those capable of giving up all their failings and misdeeds can become one with the flame that lights all the world, realizing and atoning for all their offenses by yielding to grace and compassion for all beings." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:order of guerisseurs">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Order of Guerisseurs\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThey are one of the youngeest and smaller orders found in the Church. However, in spite of their size, they are recognized as a Capitular Order. This means that, by declaration of the Pontiff, they recieve direct indulgences of money and man-power from the Church of S'Allumer. It also means they are recognized all across Calabria as opposed to a Diocesan order which only recieves regional recognition.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nGuerisseurs are accomplished physicians as well as theologians, teaching the arts of healing to both those who are of the cloth and to those who would pay large indulgences in coin in return for the education. As a Guerisseur, your purpose is to show the miracles of restoration as practiced by the Church of S'Allumer. It is not uncommon for the Pontiff to appoint members of this order as his personal Envoy or an envoy to far-off lands to demonstrate the considerable healing power of S'Allumer.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Members of the Order\</h3\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFriar Teefs\<br\>\\r\\nPhysician Suavis\\r\\n\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:order of paladins">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>\<u\>Order of Paladins\</h2\>\</u\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThose who join the Order of Paladins are the holy warriors of S'allumer.  They live in strict accordance to the 7 Precepts that make up the Code of the Paladin. They serve as guards for Church personnel and property, as defenders and champions standing against those who assail the faith.  At times they serve as investigators of crime, necromancy or other manifestations of evil.  Miracles and White Magic have been known to assist the Order of Paladins in their holy endeavors.  \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMembers of this Order take holy vows, but not all are ordained clergy.  One can still be romantic, or even married, and be a Paladin, though those who are chaste and vowed strictly to the Church may be granted greater prestige.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Ranks of the Paladin\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Whiteguard of the Holy See is the highest rank a Paladin can achieve, answering directly to the four Holy See.  The Whiteguard also serve as the generals of the Palatini Army.  Directly below the Whiteguard is the Master Capitular, also known as the High Paladin, who is charged with recruitment and leadership for the rest of the Order. The title of \\"Paladin\\" is only awarded to Knights of the Church who have fulfilled their Duties and demonstrated mastery over the Code of the Paladin. All other holy warriors of this Order are granted the title \\"Guardian\\" until such a time they have proven themselves worthy of ascension. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWhiteguard of the Holy See\<br\>\\r\\nMaster Capitular (High Paladin)\<br\>\\r\\nPaladin\<br\>\\r\\nGuardian\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Duties of the Paladin\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>1. Protect the lives of the Church:\</b\> the Followers, the Clergy and the Guerisseurs - both the living and the dead, from both physical harm or spiritual vice.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>2. Guard the Church grounds and property:\</b\> its altars, crypts, shrines, reliquaries, statues, libraries, archives and treasuries, as well as its treasures, relics, and documents.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>3. Seek out and destroy all sources of evil in our world:\</b\> all abominations of Darkness such as zombies, skeletons, liches, wraiths, shades and more.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Code of the Paladin\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\> I. Serve the Great Light and the Holy Church of S'Allumer\</b\>. Service to other things and people such as Country, City, House, Lord and Lady are acceptable, but service to S'Allumer always comes first, followed by service to Church.  When in doubt, pause and meditate on the Light until your path becomes clear. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>II.  Live the Faith\</b\>. It is not enough to simply profess the Faith by spouting it in public and making a show of keeping Holy Days or participating in Ceremony. We must live the faith in all areas of our lives, in public and in private. In addition to understanding and following the Tenants and Virtues of our faith we must seek to understand how the Light and Darkness expresses itself in you. Live an honest life.  As faithful servants of the Light we must always seek the truth and upon finding it we must live it. Avoid lying, cheating, gossiping, stealing, and engaging in slander.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>III.  Understand Your Mind\</b\>. This includes your own appetites and temptations, your own emotions and urges, your own talents and shortcomings, and even your own defects of character. Also understand your own worth and value as a person. Living the faith without any understanding of oneself is fruitless. Only through understanding the Light and Darkness within your own heart and mind can you come to understand the Light and Darkness in others and the world as a whole. This is freedom, this is living the faith. Once you have mastered your mind, it becomes your strongest weapon and resource - as demonstrated by the Miracles and White Magics.   \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>IV.  Obey the Laws of the Church\</b\>. Never break the Laws of the Church.  Laws of the Land, however, are put in place to protect and guide.  We are subject to the Laws of the Land unless they go against the divine Will of S'Allumer. If a Law of the Land must be broken do so in the least harmful way, but accept responsibility for your actions and do not draw the Church or other Paladins into question. Obey the orders of your superiors and do your best to discharge them in a timely and effective manner unless to do so violates the laws and or the Faith. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>V.  Master Self-Control\</b\>. Always remember that our actions and words carry with them the weight to damage others, ourselves, the Church, and the faithful. Through our actions we can bring forth Light into the world or Darkness. Avoid the Vices of Selfishness, Anger, Intolerance, Overindulgence, Lust, Envy, and Pride. When dealing with others treat them with love, tolerance, understanding, equity, and respect. Even when their actions are despicable, yours should not be. Respect Authority, avoid torture, avoid fighting when possible, defend the weak, respect women, be the voice of reason when people are being unreasonable, keep your word of honor, avoid deception, and respect life. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>VI.  Show Mercy\</b\>. It is easy to show mercy to the weak and downtrodden, but we are often called to deal with those of the Darkness. Those who are our enemies, those who would seek to destroy the Light and Church. It is easy to hate the Darkness in their hearts and as such to hate the person, but we must not hate the person, no, we must love the person, for every person has the potential to come to the Light. Our once enemy can turn from the Darkness and embrace the Light and in so doing become our charge or even our ally. Show mercy to all, even to our enemies. Pray for them, ask that the Light guide them. If you must kill, do so quickly to avoid causing undue suffering. Do not take joy in the death or suffering of others, this is the path of Darkness. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>VII.  Destroy Creatures of Darkness\</b\>. There exist horrors of the Darkness that take physical form such as zombies, skeletons, liches, wraiths, shades and more. These most foul creatures are constructs of Darkness. They do not have hearts and souls. Destroy these creatures without mercy, without hesitation, and without reservations of any kind. They are an abomination and an affront to S'Allumer and must be eradicated to protect the Great Light, the Church of Sallumer and its Followers." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:priest items">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Priestly Garb and Items\</h2\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Cassocks\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nThe floor-length dark gray linen cassock is double-breasted, closely fitted through the torso and flaring out to the skirt, and with a high collar buttoned off-center.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nBolt / Roll of Cloth\<BR\>\\r\\nScissors\<BR\>\\r\\nNeedle\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>These items are easily found in the commons, and northeast of the commons in the tailors, and additional fabrics from the black merchant.\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: tailor my roll/bolt into cassock\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Epitrachelion\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nThe epitrachelion is a stole adapted for priests and bishops, worn around the neck with the two ends hanging in front which almost reach the ankles of the wearer. It is made of dark gray linen with seven embroidered Octagrams of Creation, one at the back of the neck and three down each side. They are eight point latticed crosses.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nBolt / Roll of Cloth\<BR\>\\r\\nScissors\<BR\>\\r\\nNeedle\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>These items are easily found in the commons, and northeast of the commons in the tailors, and additional fabrics from the black merchant. \<U\>Also note, this item thankfully responds to the name STOLE.\</U\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: tailor my roll/bolt into epitrachelion.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Bandages\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nThis sterile [material] bandage appears to be of [variable] quality.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nBolt / Roll of Cloth\<BR\>\\r\\nScissors\<BR\>\\r\\nNeedle\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>These items are easily found in the commons, and northeast of the commons in the tailors, and additional fabrics from the black merchant.\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: tailor my roll/bolt into bandage\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Prayer Beads (Wooden)\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nA string of highly polished [wood] beads. Each bead appears to be carved with a series of ancient symbols. These beads are held together by a thin, silken white thread.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nLumber\<BR\>\\r\\nCarving Knife\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>These items are easily found west of the commons on Market Street northeast of the first intersection at the Carpenters.\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: carve my lumber into prayerbeads\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Prayer Beads (Metal)\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nA string of highly polished [metal] beads. Each bead appears to be carved with a series of ancient symbols. These beads are held together by a thin, silken white thread.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nSmithing Hammer\<BR\>\\r\\nAnvil\<BR\>\\r\\nMetal Rod\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>These items are easily found North of the Commons, and to the southeast on Sea Street in the Black Smith's Forge. There is a public anvil there.\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: forge my rod into prayerbeads\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<I\>Flasks of Holy Water\</B\>\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nA simple silver flask with an octogram of creation engraved upon it. Priests often carry these, so they can apply them to supplicants as part of a cleansing ritual. Often herbs are added to holy water, to make poltices or potions.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n\<U\>Things Needed:\</U\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCareer: Priest 3\<br\>\\r\\nLocation: Narthex of the Cathedrale de Temoin\<br\>\\r\\nObject: Holy Water Basin\<BR\>\\r\\n\<I\>From the commons, west, until market street. North through the gates of the market. North until you reach 'Peaceful Way'. Stop at waterfall. Step through waterfall. North, Northwest, Northwest.\</I\>\<BR\>\\r\\nCommand: scoop basin\\r\\n\<P\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:sacraments">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<br\>\<br\>\<b\>\<u\>Sacraments of Initiation\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBaptism - Ritual in which an infant is formally marked a follower of S'Allumer, and cleansed of all pre-existing sins. This sacrament is only administered once in the follower's lifetime and is intended for infants, but also available to adults.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nConfirmation - Ritual in which a child transitions into spiritual adulthood by affirming their commitment to the Church of S'Allumer. This sacrament is only administered once in the follower's lifetime.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Sacraments of Service\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMatrimony - Ritual in which two baptised and confirmed followers of S'Allumer are formally joined in a lifelong union as man and wife. This sacrament should only be administered once in the follower's lifetime and is irreversible.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nHoly Orders - Ritual in which a follower of S'Allumer transitions into formal service of the Church of S'Allumer as either Clergy or Paladin. This sacrament should only be administered once in the follower's lifetime.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Sacraments of Healing\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nConfession - Ritual in which spiritual healing is offered to a contrite follower of S'Allumer who commits their sins to Clergy and completes penance. All confessed sins are secretly bound by the \\"Seal of Confession\\", and cannot be discussed under any circumstances, including to other clergy or law enforcement. This sacrament may be repeated as often as necessary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAnnointing of the Sick - Ritual in which spiritual and physical healing is offered to an ill follower of S'Allumer who may be in danger due to illness or old age. This sacrament should only be administered once, but a new illness or a worsening of health enables a person to receive the sacrament repeatedly.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nLast Rites - Ritual in which a dying follower's soul is prepared for death by providing sacramental grace in the form of Final Confession and Final Annointing. This sacrament should only be administered once, when death is imminent.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nResurrection - Ritual in which a deceased follower's soul is brought back to life from the dead. This sacrament may be repeated as often as necessary, but due to the danger and extremely taxing toll on clergy may be reserved for the most devout followers." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:tenets of helloise">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Tenets of Helloise\</h2\>\\r\\n1) Worship, love, and follow the teachings of Helloise, and the divine Great Light. Do not place anything before your persuit in being good and moral.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n2) Do not curse, or wrongfully beg to draw the divine judgement of the Great Light against anyone. Do not wrongfully bless those who are unworthy of the Great Light's blessings.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n3) Remember, respect, and revere Holy Days, and keep them Holy.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n4) Honor, respect, and obey authority of the Church, Laws, and Family as so as they do not ask you to break the tenets.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n5) Do not Lie, Cheat, Steal, or Gamble.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n6) Do not Murder, Maim, or Kill wrongfully \\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n7) Do not desire things that others own just because you do not own them. Instead be contented with what good things you do have.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n8) Do not commit adultry, fornication, or other partake in other bawdy actions.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n9) Do not judge others for their shortcomings, instead meet them with compassion and acceptance and teach them.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n10) Do not turn away those in need, hungry, sick, poor, lost, or downtrodden.\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n11) Be a good steward to the church, world, others, and yourself." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:tenets of penitence">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>Tenets of Penitence\</h2\>\\r\\nAscension: If one lives a pure life, and if one learns and accepts the teachings of Penitence, then after death one will be united with the Healing Light that is in all living things. Those souls that Ascend after death will be onbe with the purity of all-being, a joy that surpasses any experience one an have in this life\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\nAsceticism: People are, by their nature, \\"worldly\\" and subject to worldy appetites. That is merely a weight that prohits people from rising towards the healing light. Only by understanding how the four points of the material world (air, earth, fire, and water) link to the four points of the spiritual world (courage, serenity, wisdom, and undersatnding) can one truly shuffle off the prison of mortal coil and walk the shining path into the light of truth and beauty\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\nPancreationism: Where there is life, there is S'allumer. All being comes from the generative light of S'allumer\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\nMonoteism: There is only the Light of Ascension. Other gods are false gods; belief in them will deny oneself the glory of Ascension." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the nine vices">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<h2\>The Nine Vices\</h2\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Selfishness\</b\> - \<I\> Selfishness is the act of putting your wants before the needs of others. Selfishness includes refraining from helping the weak, poor, hungry, downtrodden, ill for self-serving and self glorifying reasons.\</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Anger\</b\> - \<I\> Anger in itself is not a bad thing, but what we do with our anger can be. Wrath, Vengeance, Revenge, Cruelty, Hatred, Fury, are all forms of anger which should be avoided.\</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Apathy\</b\> - \<I\> Apathy is the act of not caring, a distinct lack of interest in or concern for things, people, and situations.\</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Intolerance\</b\> - \<I\> Intolerance is the inability to accept someone, a situation, or circumstance in any form. This includes Prejudice, or the inability to listen to, assist, aid, someone due to sheer anger or disgust. \</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Overindulgence\</b\> - \<I\> Overindulgence is the act of ignoring reason or moderation. This is not limited to food (gluttony) or emotion (lust, wrath, jealousy) as you can overindulge in a variety of other things. \</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Lust\</b\> - \<I\> Lust is the act of holding in your heart feelings of wanton desire, or straight desire for someone or something and can include acting upon those feelings. \</i\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Envy\</b\> - \<I\> Envy is the act of coveting, wanting, longing for something that is not yours. Further envy can include Jealousy, Vindictiveness, Resentment. It can include the actions done to obtain what is not yours. \</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Greed\</b\> - \<I\> Greed is the hoarding of money, goods, time, or people for yourself for the sole purpose of merely having these things. It is an unquenchable desire to have more regardless how much you have.\</I\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Idleness\</b\> - \<I\> Idleness is the act of inaction. It is having the ability to do something and instead choosing to do nothing. Further it is the act of inactivity to better oneself to accomplish anything.\</I\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the twelve virtues of sallumer">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<I\> By following these virtues one can show divine Grace. We should strive to fulfill these virtues at all times, though be understanding when we, ourselves cannot. \</I\>\\r\\n\<P\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Sacrifice\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Forgiveness\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Mercy\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Strength\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Generosity\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Faith\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Wisdom\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Honesty\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Chastity\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Percerverance\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Acceptance\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n   * \<b\>Humility\</b\>\<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:weddings">
         (\{ "members", "\<h2\>Weddings\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n2015 - Feb 5th - \<b\>Tomoe and Brennus\</b\>, sanctified by Sister Nadja \<br/\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1402940256, "jominey", "E", 1402940821, "jominey", "E", 1402940898, "jominey", "E", 1402941140, "jominey", "E", 1571341466, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
