<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#0000ff", "bgcolor2":"#ffffff", "bgimg1":"", "bgimg2":"", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Arial", "h1color":"#0033cc", "h1type":"Arial Black", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Arial", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Arial" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>       STRENGTH \& LOYALTY\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\\"And lo, the times are dark, but we are a strong people, with a stronger spirit and together, we hold fast to create an unbreakable chain of might! For this home is our home and no man nor woman nor foe of the night can ever break that chain!\\"\</B\>   - Queen Jocelyn at the funeral of her husband, King Richerd, 1590\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<img src=\\"https://img.theculturetrip.com/1024x574/smart/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/7378397618_4d4ef16195_h.jpg\\" width=400 height=200\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAbout the Scottish Saltire flag:\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\\"It's believed that around 60 AD St. Andrew, who became the Patron Saint of Scotland, (and who was one of Jesus' Apostles - the younger brother of Simon Peter) was crucified.  Legend says that he felt himself unworthy of being crucified on a cross that resembled the one Jesus died on, and so he hung on a saltire, or diagonal cross. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe next part of the legend behind the flag of Scotland takes place over 700 years later, in 832 AD.  It's said that the night before the Pictish King Angus II, led his forces into battle against the English King Aethelstans' army of Angles and Saxons, King Angus had a vision or dream. In this vision, he saw St. Andrew and was promised triumph in battle.  Early the next morning Angus' troops were awestruck by the sight of a huge white Saltire cross shining against the background of a bright blue sky.  This 'omen' led the Scottish troops to victory and the Saltire found it's place in Scottish history.\\"\</i\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ "visitors", "\<img src=\\"https://img.theculturetrip.com/1024x574/smart/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/7378397618_4d4ef16195_h.jpg\\" width=400 height=200\>", (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ooc: catholic & protestant differences">
         (\{ "members", "Main Differences Between Catholic and Protestant Beliefs: \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n1. Understanding of the Bible\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCatholicism and Protestantism have distinct views on the meaning and the authority of the Bible. For Protestant Christians, Luther made clear that the Bible is the \\"Sola Skriptura,\\" God's only book, in which He provided His revelations to the people and which allows them to enter in communion with Him.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCatholics, on the other hand, do not base their beliefs on the Bible alone. Along with the Holy Scripture, they are additionally bound by the traditions of the Roman Catholic Church.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n2. Understanding the church\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCatholics and Protestants have a different view on the nature of the church. The word \\"catholic\\" means \\"all-embracing,\\" and the Catholic Church sees itself as the only true church worldwide, under the leadership of the pope.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn contrast, the Protestant Churches which have emerged from Reformation, also called \\"Evangelical,\\" which means \\"according to the Gospel,\\" do not make up one united Church. There are rather several tens of thousands of different denominations around the world. Officially, all of these many churches are considered equal.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n3. The pope\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nProtestants are not open at all to papal primacy. According to the Evangelical view, this dogma contradicts statements in the Bible.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCatholics see in the pope the successor of the Apostle Peter, the first head of their Church, who was appointed by Jesus. The papal office is justified by an allegedly unbroken chain of consecrations, ranging from the first century to the present.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nEven if many Protestants like a particular pope, they categorically reject papacy\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n4. Understanding of the office\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis continuous chain, known as the apostolic succession, is overall significant for different spiritual offices in the Catholic Church. With the Sacrament of Holy Orders, bishops, priests and deacons receive a lifelong seal of God giving them sacramental authority over Catholic laypeople. This consecration can only be given to men.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nProtestants do not consecrate specific persons into office, but rather accept the principle that priesthood can be transferred to every believer — even to women.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n5. Eucharist or Lord's Supper\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Catholics' views on the spiritual office are reflected in the Eucharist, or Holy Communion, a rite commemorating the Last Supper of Jesus with his disciples before his crucifixion. Once consecrated by a priest in the name of Jesus, bread and wine become the body and blood of Christ. Non-Catholics may not participate in Communion.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn the Protest Church, every baptized person is invited to share and is allowed to lead the Lord's Supper. This approach is not accepted by Catholics.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAdditionally, Eucharist has a different meaning for Catholics and Protestants. The bread, known as the Host, embodies Jesus and can therefore be prayed to. For Protestants, the ritual only serves to commemorate Jesus' death and resurrection. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nFor Catholics, the Host represents bread that is consecrated to represent Jesus' body \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n6. Sacraments\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn the Roman Catholic Church, there are seven solemn rites, called sacraments: baptism, confirmation, the Eucharist, matrimony, penance, holy orders and extreme unction. The church believes these sacraments were instituted by Jesus and that they confer God's grace.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMost Protestant churches only practice two of these sacraments: baptism and the Eucharist (called Lord's Supper). They are perceived as symbolic rituals through which God delivers the Gospel. They are accepted through faith.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n7. Mary dogmas and the worship of Saints\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Roman Catholic Church reveres Mary, the mother of Jesus, as \\"Queen of Heaven.\\" However, there are few biblical references to support the Catholic Marian dogmas — which include the Immaculate Conception, her perpetual virginity and her Assumption into heaven. This is why they are rejected by Protestants.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThough Protestants believe Mary was the mother of Jesus, unlike Catholics, they do not venerate her.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Catholic Church also practices the veneration of saints. Dead models of faith, recognized as \\"saint\\" by the church through canonization, can be prayed to for help in maintaining faith in God. There are over 4,000 saints. Their remains are considered holy relics which are venerated.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis veneration is also categorically by the Protestant Church as unbiblical. According to Reformation views, every person may and should pray directly to God.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n8. Celibacy\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAll main world religions integrate in some way the concept of celibacy, the vow of abstaining from marriage and sexual relations, and the Catholic and Protestant churches are no exception. In the Catholic Church, celibacy is obligatory for priests. It is seen as a symbol of the undivided succession of Christ.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe Protestant Church rejects this obligation for priests. Martin Luther already demanded its abolition as early as 1520. He made a decisive personal contribution to this end in 1525: The former monk married the former nun Katharina von Bora. Initially unsure of whether he should marry, Luther finally determined that \\"his marriage would please his father, rile the pope, cause the angels to laugh, and the devils to weep.\\"\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSource: https://www.dw.com/en/the-main-differences-between-catholics-and-protestants/a-37888597" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ooc: source material">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>\<u\>SCOTLAND\<br\>\</b\>\</u\>\\r\\nReligion: Protestant\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nImportant Figures:\<br\>\\r\\nQueen Regent Jocelyn Burhtun, born Jocelyn Hughes (Scottish, 33)\<br\>\\r\\nKing Patrik Burhtun (10)\<br\>\\r\\nLiving Heirs - Duke Malcome Burhtun (37)\<br\>\\r\\nAdvisor - Duke Willieam Hughes (33)\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n---\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nCenturies ago, the relationship between Scotland and England was one of constant struggle and strife and this history has disadvantaged Scotland in ways that remain to this day. While the relations between the two are stable at this point in time, the battles over the lands of Scotland long ago have left them with few resources and depleted forces. The size of their country and their limited resources have both been a struggle for the nation, but they are resilient and strong people with a fierce pride and a fighting spirit. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nOver the recent decades of peace, they have managed to collect themselves and gain enough influence to become a contender on the international playing field, despite their limited reach and lack of resources overall. This influence has given them a chance to improve their standing among the other larger nations and this access has improved trade enough to kick start the economy with a trend toward the positive for the first time in a long while. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs such, they are seeking an alliance to reinforce their status and provide additional security for the future of their nation. The threat of Englands power paired with their close proximity and the blood history between the two nations has kept them at the forefront of the Scottish mind and they know that the chance of struggle is never too far away.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nBecause of this history of struggle and strife, the Scottish have learned to embrace lifes small joys and will always celebrate even the smallest of successes. This vivacious and joyous outlook makes them prone to boisterous celebration and they will count every blessing as the greatest of them all. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis joy and desire to band together and share with every person of their nation made the switch to Protestantism easy for the Scottish people. The sense of community and equality that is preached by the Protestant faith as well aligned with the desires of the Scottish people to band together and stand firm against any struggle or obstacle that they could face. Their geographic distance from the Roman Catholic reach as well as their small size resulted in an effortless slip from the grasp of the Roman Catholic power, as opposed to the grand display of rebuttal that came about during the creation of the Church of England.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Scottish Relations at a Glance\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nENGLAND - With a tumultuous and blood history between these two nations, the Scottish are wary and apprehensive about what the future might hold. While relations are currently stable, that fact could easily change at any moment in the future.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nFRANCE - Closest in proximity outside of England, the Scottish are eager to forge an alliance with the nation of France for an ally against any threat the English could make. Their difference in faiths could pose an issue, but their relations are positive overall.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nGERMANY - England and Germany are known allies, and this fact is of some concern to the Scottish. With an additional powerful nation on the side of England, the Scottish are wary of the potential for a military campaign at some point in the future.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nITALY - Italy and Scotland have very little to do with one another on a large scale and their relations tend to be civil overall. Their neutral stance makes them neither friend nor foe, but the Italians occasionally have something to say about their Protestant faith.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSPAIN - As one of the most powerful nations currently not aligned with any other nation, the Scottish believe Spain to be their best bet for forging a powerful and beneficial alliance. Knowing they arent particularly fond of England doesnt hurt either. \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nROMAN CATHOLIC CHURCH - Some holdouts of Roman Catholicism still live within Scotland, but their slip into Protestantism came surprisingly easy and without much fuss from the powers of the Catholic Church, due in part to their small size and influence.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nPROTESTANT CHURCH - The Protestant faith was a perfect fit for the spirit of the Scottish people, making the transition into Protestantism easy for the nation as a whole. While some Catholics remain, they are not at odds with the overall population.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nMIDDLE CLASS - Due to the struggles of the nation of Scotland, it is not a terribly wealthy nation. The unfortunate side effect is that there is a huge disparity between the haves and the have nots and virtually no middle class to be found.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nLOWER CLASS - The overall standing of the population of Scotland is considerably poorer than any other nation and the lower class of the nation is at times truly destitute. There is a large number of people living in the lower class around the nation as a whole.\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:scottish traditions">
         (\{ "members", "\<u\>Tartan \& Kilts\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nKilts are one of the most iconic items associated with Scotland. However, kilts are much more than something men wear to weddings, ceilidhs or Highland games they are a historic piece of clothing which have stood the test of time. Tartan is a fabric made up of different coloured horizontal and vertical stripes on a coloured background. It originated in the Highlands of Scotland, with the first mention of tartan being made in 1538. Originally, clanspeople used local plants, mosses and berries to dye the wool.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA kilt is a piece of tartan which is worn around the waist. Full kilt dress is normally made up of:\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nA sporran - a small bag worn around the waist over the kilt\<br\>\\r\\nA kilt pin - the pin holds the two pieces of material together at the front of the kilt\<br\>\\r\\nSgian dubh - a small dagger which sits in the sock\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>Bagpipes\<br\>\</u\>\\r\\nThe sound of the bagpipes can often be heard all over Scottish towns and cities; whether its pipers entertaining passers-by, pipe bands in parades or at the world famous Highland games. Bagpipe music has strong connections to Gaelic culture and has played an important part in Scottish social and cultural life for centuries.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>Ceilidhs\<br\>\</u\>\\r\\nThe word ceilidh descends from the Gaelic word for gathering or party. Originally ceilidhs were simply local gatherings which developed into a form of literary entertainment with storytelling, recitations and songs. Instrumental music and dancing were added later and the ceilidh as we now know it was born. The beauty of a ceilidh is everyone can take part; young or old, beginners to experienced dancers, and even those with two left feet! The caller will run through the steps before the dance starts so you have time for a quick practise.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>Highland Games\<br\>\</u\>\\r\\nHighland games combine sport, fun and culture in a uniquely Scottish style and take place every weekend from May to September all over Scotland. Heavy contests see the competitors put their muscles to the test, while field events such as the hill race and cycling competition test speed and stamina. Highland dancers also show off their fancy footwork at the Highland games with dances such as the sword dance and the famous Highland Fling. The Cowal Highland Gathering is an event world renowned for its Highland dancing with performers from all over the world travelling to Dunoon to compete.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>Burns Supper - January 25\<br\>\</u\>\\r\\nTo celebrate the life of Robert Burns, a Scottish poet and lyricist, Burns Suppers are held on the 25th of January all over the world. The evening is filled with Burns poetry, a traditional meal of haggis, neeps and tatties, and of course, whisky! Guests often wear full kilt dress and the evening is finished with a recital of Auld Lang Syne.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>St Andrews Day - Nov 30\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nSt Andrews Day is Scotlands national day which celebrates Scotlands patron saint, St Andrew. St Andrews philosophy was simple: share what you have with those less fortunate and be kind to each other. The day is usually marked with a celebration of Scottish culture; including ceilidh dancing, food and music, and both the British Prime Minister and Scotlands First Minister give St Andrews Day messages.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<u\>Hogmanay - December 31\<br\>\</u\>\\r\\nHogmanay is the Scots word for the last day of the year and is synonymous with the celebration of the New Year. As the bells strike midnight, partygoers join hands and give a rendition of Auld Lang Syne. The Scottish festivities are often followed by further celebration on the morning of New Years Day (January 1st) and in some cases, the 2nd as well.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nSource - https://www.royalscotsclub.com/what-are-scottish-traditions/https://www.royalscotsclub.com/what-are-scottish-traditions/" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the scots guard">
         (\{ "members", "\<b\>Scots Guard Description:\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\nThe Scots Guards (SG) stand to defend the People of Scotland from all threats, foreign and domestic.  This is a historic and elite regiment within the Scottish Army.  Their origins lie in the personal bodyguards of Kings centuries ago.  The Scots Guard have assigned one military company to protect Scottish interests in Rinascita, especially the Ambassador and the Consulate.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<img src=\\"https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/f/f7/Royal_Coat_of_Arms_of_the_United_Kingdom_%28Scotland%29.svg/800px-Royal_Coat_of_Arms_of_the_United_Kingdom_%28Scotland%29.svg.png\\" width=300 height=300\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Scots Guard Rank \& Insignia:\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\nCaptain - \<br\>\\r\\nFirst Officer - \<br\>\\r\\nOfficer - \<br\>\\r\\nPrivate - \<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Scots Guard Oath:\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\nI, state your name, swear by Almighty God that I will be faithful and bear true allegiance to the People of Scotland and the Crown.  I will, as in duty bound, honestly and faithfully defend the People of Scotland and the Crown against all enemies.  I vow to observe and obey all orders of Her Majesty, Her heirs and successors, and of the generals officers set over me." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1346732354, "jominey", "E", 1346732384, "jominey", "E", 1346732454, "jominey", "E", 1571339908, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
