<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="header">
         ([ "bgcolor":"#ffffff", "bgcolor2":"#ffffff", "bgimg1":"http://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fi811.photobucket.com%2Falbums%2Fzz33%2Flidiaveressen%2FFYROSGUILDIMAGE.jpg\&h=tAQGl7Yqz", "bgimg2":"http://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fi811.photobucket.com%2Falbums%2Fzz33%2Flidiaveressen%2FFYROSGUILDIMAGE.jpg\&h=tAQGl7Yqz", "fontcolor":"#000000", "fonttype":"Comic Sans MS", "h1color":"#000000", "h1type":"Arial", "h2color":"#000000", "h2type":"Arial", "h3color":"#000000", "h3type":"Arial" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ "members", "Make sure to read the Message of the Day, for training needs and announcements. \\r\\nBe good to one another. ", (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:letter from fyre fulke">
         (\{ "visitors", "Hello!\\r\\nIf you are reading this, you may be interested in what we in Sinners and Saints are about, and curious to see if you have what it takes to be an Adventurer and Brother or Sister of the company. \<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nI can confidently assure you, that you most likely do. Mercenary companies are historically a place where people turn to for MANY reasons. Some, are looking to earn some prestige and experience for their family name, without the lifelong service to a Great House. Others, have no where else to turn, and find family and kinship serving other brothers and sisters. More still, come simply looking for combat experience, leadership experience, or 'on-the-job' training. And finally, some simply enjoy the challenge and excitement of a job that always has something new and different to do. The nature of our missions means we solve problems, the atypical events that people of less military means might come across. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nOn a personal note, I am Scree. A forest cat from the Muire forests, during a time when we still had a village there. It was a village of Great and Noble felines of many kinds, mostly of my own race. We Scree are independent and free. We will not be -owned- by anyone. We lost much of our history and culture to the cleansing by those who feared us, or wished to possess us. Similarly, I run my company as a free company. No great house will own us. No one will -force- us to be their servant and loyal subject. If we do, its of our own choice, or for as long as their coin remains as honorable as their word. Our word given, is as strong as law and no contract shall ever be broken willingly, but we will choose to accept any contract offered or refuse it. This does not mean, that we are rebellious or treasonous in our dreams, but it does mean that we will always be free to make our own path together. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nOur nature as a free company is vital to the nature of the missions we receive..and get paid well to complete. The reporter that needs protection for the stories they write. The Merchant who wants extra guards for a special caravan of goods or sentimental value. The Gardener who has a problem with runaway vines! Or even a tradesman, who learns of a rare material he wants to collect, but doesnt have the might of arms to clear the area of danger and bring it home safely. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nOur lives are dangerous, enemies seek to kill us at every turn. We face these challenges with bravery and determination, to fill the contract we are given. It does not mean we are fearless. If one is fearless, they cannot be brave. A person is only as brave as the fear he overcomes to act. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf this life sounds like it may be of benefit to you, seek me out. A fresh start, A new life, a way to improve yourself or test yourself, We have posistions available for you. Even Crafters, healers, scholars, and anyone of any walk of life is welcome to come and see what their unique talents can do for our way of life. Everyone is valuable. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nI cant wait to hear from you. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n~Fyros Fulke, Mercenary Captain of Sinners and Saints. \<br\>" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:welcoming board for guests">
         (\{ "visitors", "Thank you for visiting Sinners And Saints. We are a mercenary company, whose primary focus is Questing, Adventuring and Treasure hunting. Often times we'll work for free if we believe in the cause, but can be hired for almost any task. We have two aspects, the Sinner, and the Saint. When we are hired, you choose the aspect. Sinners will do anything required to get a job done. These usually are missions requiring stealth, trickery or other strategic warfare, where the job must be done no matter what. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nSecond, is the Saints aspect. These are important missions, that require Honor, dedication, representation of a Noble or Great House in a public setting. Need more soldiers to defend you in a fight, comporting themselves as one of your own? Request this Aspect. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWe are a flexible company, Eager to work and assist you with any project outside the city walls you need support with.\<br\>\\r\\n" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1571341466, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
