<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The first page is the table of content, the second page is advertisements, the third page is the story on the trip to the fae circle, the fourth page is the shipwrecked dock, the fifth page is the interview with Zaria, the sixth page is the constable report, the seventh page is the fashion corner, the eight page is the crafting directory, the ninth page is the funnies, the tenth page is the social page, the eleventh page is the continuation of the social page, the twelfth page is the political page, the thirteenth page is ongoing fictional story , fourteenth page is the stars of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/259aefce-e735-4da2-90a5-878846027650_zps7cc7ba8d.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is a listing of advertisements art done by Esquire Gabrielle (examine to see pop-up).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Pony Press advertisement ~<br></br><br></br> Bruno, the blacksmith, has one of the most organized guilds in the city. He has many different products for sale, all with varying costs based on material... and yet everyone who visits his shop can easily find what they want and figure out the price easily. (OOC: his @guild page has very impressive pricing lists)<br></br><br></br>Avoiurdupois smith Incudine can make the armor or weapons you need. Have a dent in that armor, a chip in that sword, loose greeves, write to Incudine today. <br></br><br></br> Need a quality merchant with a friendly smile, contact Miss Aluine today.<br></br><br></br>From jackets, pants, dresses, corsets, shoes and hats Rainbow Rags have it all. Contact Miss Brie for all your ordering needs. <br></br><br></br>Want your voice heard, advertise here for more information contact Esquire Gabrielle. <br></br><br></br>Want an exciting opportunity in chronicling and reporting ask about a job with the Pony Press News team, simply write to Esquire Gabrielle to start your journey today.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/f80986f4-f80f-43ac-8a09-e90b07691d0d_zpse3987a2e.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about trip to fae circle. Art done by Miss Una.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~When ickies attack~ art done by Miss Una<br></br><br></br> Around the midday sun people all over town reportedly saw, 'Small fairies wizzing about twinkling at people. But we couldn't tell if they were good or bad so we kinda held back.' says Meepers. These wizzing fae seemed to be in a hurry and insisted people follow them. The braves souls who did follow were: Ash, Sir Bayard, Hanneman, Una, Koz, Kaine, Cullan, Sonja, Kruix, and Lidia.<br></br><br></br>This group was lead to a fairy circle in the meadow where they reportedly feel onto moss. After fighting a building sized skink and taking in their surroundings the group realized they had been shrunk to the size of the tip of one's pinky. The fae were the same size they were and explained that ickies were threatening their way of life and they brought the big people down to help before things got out of control.<br></br><br></br> The group was lead through the fae town armed with little knowledge and three paths before them. The group went right first only to find a lake of red liquid with a massive grasshoppers in the center. Apparently, these creature was an icky that was tainting and guarding the fae's water supply. While others were coming up with a plan to defeat this monster of bugs Cullan threw a rock in the water in attempts to distract the bug. This didn't work out the way he planned as the grasshopper then attacked. No one got hurt at this time thanks to a giant blade of grass Sir Bayard impaled it with. The group decided that the best plan was to get to the center only to find a pool of grasshopper eggs guarded by the second grasshopper. While trying to get back to the shore Miss Lidia fell into the lake dropping her torch which set the whole lake on fire. She got away safely, unfortunately the fire caused the grasshopper eggs to explode with Kaine nearby. The explosions plus the startled grasshopper still nearby was more then our brave Kaine could dodge and was mercilessly and unfortunately killed. <br></br><br></br>From here the group decides to go back and take the left path if only they had to find their way through the tunnel of thorns. The thorns were magical in nature and tried to attack but the quick thinking of the group saved the day by making a barrier of shields to let the group by. After coming out of the tunnel none the worst for the wear the group found a pit and a rock. It's unassuming nature put the group on high alert, looking for the danger to come. Many people came up with ideas but  while arguing Kruix and Sir Bayard jumped into the pit hoping to find the danger. Find it they did, the rock was a curled up massive centiped that stretched far above the pit. Feeling of dread filled the group and they attacked the best they could, only to be thwarted at every turn. After a while water was accidentally splashed on the creature making it shrink. Seeing a plan after such a long battle; the whole group started splashing it with liquid until it was no bigger than a pea.  With a might stomp Sir Bayard ended the tiny bug's life, with much gusto. <br></br><br></br>This left only the center path for the group to explore but they first had to find a way around a blocked entrance. This was done with the help of Koz and Hanneman who disabled the trap and moved the huge rock. After passing this small obstacle the group was faced with a maze with no clear direction, which is when Kruix used his magic match for no apparent reason. With a few wrong turns and a trail of twine behind them our group finds a wall with writing on it that no one can decipher. Reports say that Miss Una used music to call a fae to help read the message which said: "Whisper to me your fears to pass onto the bridge of judgment." The wall lifted to reveal a bridge that literally judged all who passed and no one came out perfect. The result of the judgement left everyone with an impairment; some went deaf, others got their hands stuck together, some got brick feet, and strangely some got feathers ontop their heads. The group somehow made it to another fork in the road, up a bloody staircase or into a dark room; choosing the dark room the group hesitantly entered. Reports claim that the darkness in the room was so thick and complete it had to be magic in nature, even if you had a light source the darkness was overwhelming. They would have fled had they not been stuck in their own minds. Apparently, everyone who touched the dark had to live out their greatest fear, no one was willing to share their fear but reports say that Sir Bayard almost cut down the whole group while Cullan earned his burn scars from this room by setting himself on fire then tearing off his flaming skin. Coming to his senses Hanneman eventually overcame his fears and broke through the darkness by smashing a crystal eye set in the wall. Shaken and weary our heros pass the dark room in which they find a big lake and a praying mantis. Trying to be tactful the group surrounded the beast right away. The bug was focused on Miss Lidia who had a feather on her head which apparently drew the creature's attention for mating much to her cringe. Not having any of that the group attacked it from the left and right, making sure it didn't mate. Hanneman found a fire behind the creature and with the help of others in the group decided that the fire had to be put out. Having to run across the area was the only difficulty Hanneman faced and quickly put the fire out. This caused the bug to become weakened and easily killed. <br></br><br></br>Having defeated the ickies the group was showered with gratitude from the fae village and returned to their normal size at the fae circle with one warning. The fae would call again when the source of such evil was found.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i811.photobucket.com/albums/zz33/lidiaveressen/Brokenpier-crash-126_zps91708d4a.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is about the shipwrecked docks. Art done by Esquire Gabrielle.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Ship of questions~<br></br><br></br>Everyone's seen it, the massive cargo ship crashed into the docks by the sailor's guild. Many question arise from this ship: 'Where did it come from? When did it crash? Why hasn't it been moved?' Well, this reporter has tried to answer these questions. <br></br><br></br>~Where did it come from?~ This ship was captained by the one and only Captain Hooked who is widely known to have worked with the foreigners to do harm to Triskellian. Many may remember he is the one that brought snowbeasts and spiders to our world via the crates and cages still on the ship. He reportedly jumped ship after it crashed to make his escape.<br></br><br></br>~When did it crash?~ The answer to this is 6 months ago when the attacks to Triskellian first started to happen. You may remember that the sewer's where infested with all sorts of danger including many different gangs going by the name of Triskellian's thieve's guild. The ship crashed around the time when that guild was the most active, it's claimed that they were the ones to hire Captain Hooked in the first place. The good news is the sewers are relatively safe, save for alligators but the bad news is Captain Hooked is still at large.<br></br><br></br>~Why hasn't the ship been moved?~ The surrounding areas around the ship are severely damaged and if the ship were to be moved the buildings, docks, and walkways would collapse. Rumors have it you can still get in the sewers by the docks you just have to go through the ship to get there. This reporter has yet to find the way into the sewers via the crashed ship.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~~Zaria, the constable with the biggest stick~~<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: First I want to take the time to thank you for taking the time to answer my questions.<br></br><br></br>zaria: It's no problem, really. I actually have time to spare, which is fantastic.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Lets start with your childhood. Where did you grow up and who are the members of your family.<br></br><br></br>zaria: I grew up in the forests of the Bisclavret with only my mother for company. She was a member of clan Rhashak, which I didn't learn about until I came to Triskellian. A tiger from Akoma had caught her interest, and the tribe hadn't approved, so she ran off with him. Alas, when she became pregnant he all but vanished. So she raised me in the west while trying to find work as a mercenary, which is what I was when I came to the city. She had become sick and I needed to find a better way of raising money for her medical expenses.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: What was your mother sick with?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I couldn't tell you. It made her very weak, her fur fell out in patches... some disease, probably. I mean, she had to take work wherever she could so she could scratch a living for us, and I'd only just started to help, so she could have caught it anywhere.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Is your mother still alive?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: No. She died almost a year after I became a Constable. I thought a job like that would be well paying, since they had to take so much flak from everyone. And I mean -everyone-. But, despite how much I protested, I didn't earn enough for the treatment she needed, so she passed away.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Did you ever know who your father was and have you ever met him?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: If he didn't stick around for my mother when she got pregnant then he's not the type of person I want to get to know. Doubt I'd recognize him if we crossed paths anyway.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: What brought you to the city?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I came to the city so I could earn money TO take care of my mother. The healers won't treat her for free, and I certainly couldn't do it myself.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Have you ever been in trouble with taking on so much responsiblity even as a young one?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I might have got into a little bit of trouble with a boar.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: We'll keep names out of it but an you describe the 'little bit of trouble' for me?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: This was well before I ever had notions of joining the Constabulary, and before I even understood the law to it's fullest extent, but there was this boar knight and he was acting like he owned the entire commons, peering down his tusked nose as us. So I thought, "This would be the perfect opportunity to throw one of those eggs I found at him to imply that DockTown isn't for those who think they're better than everyone else.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: What was the result of this confrontation?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: He raged. You could practically see the steam billowing from his ears. It resulted in two broken legs for me, but I was pleased about it.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Have you ever done anything other then be a constable?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I've tried my hand at being a bodyguard for the investments of an Esquire Celia, but she didn't stick around very long and there was never an opportunity to actively carry out my job. I also joined the Sailors Guild for a time when Xena was leading alongside Fyros, but they didn't pay me much attention until I became Sheriff. Missed opportunity, huh? I was also a guard of the Bisclavret under the guidance of Kaine, he let me go so I could pursue a job with the Constabulary.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Do you ever regret joining the constables?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: The Constabulary has given me more abuse than it has in the way of benefits, in my opinion. But the city needs the law and the law needs a Sheriff, so that's me. Someone has to do it because no one really wants to.<br></br><br></br>gabrelle: Tell me about the different jobs within the constabulary you've done?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Where do I begin? Initially, when I first joined the Constabulary, it was fighting for the rights of a Constable, fighting for what any Deputy needed to do their job properly; this included a proper uniform, pay, guidance and much else besides. Then, when Kegan joined, it was fighting to allow an internal vote within the Constabulary itself, because the Sheriff at the time just wasn't cutting it. We couldn't get anything done in the way of administration which would better the Constabulary as a whole. Not to mention all the cases on the crimeboard were outdated and needed to be refilled into case closed, case closed unresolved, no suspects and open. To which I started that notice revealing those who were wanted. Everything was so disorganized. It took half a year before voting could be implemented, and I achieved the status of Sheriff before the day ended.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Before you, who ran the constables?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Sergeant Biggs. To be fair, though, when Mister Joshua left the city Biggs was the best candidate for the job and was appointed it by the magistrate. He's only ever said he just wanted to be a normal Constable so he could enforce the law, rather than lead things.<br></br><br></br>gabrille: Who has been your biggest thorn in the side in regards to criminals?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I don't know, being the Sheriff means dealing with several unwanted pricks. Luciano was the worst for a while, but I think the biggest thorns are those who can't even be caught by the law. I won't mention who I think those are.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Is there anyone who you've actually appreciated for the cooperation?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Not really. There are few who go willingly, and they often only go willingly because they want to seem like the better person. I won't give them a medal for pretending to be a good person when tonnes of people in the city manage to avoid breaking the law in the first place like normal people.<br></br><br></br>Zaria: What is the best and worst thing about being a constable?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I'd like to say the good thing is respect, but there's more disrespect to deal with, which is the bad thing.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: How hard is it now a days to join the constabulary?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Not hard... if you have a brain.<br></br><br></br>Zaria: You need to be able to follow orders, stick to the law yourself while knowing the law and be able to judge when it's right to act.<br></br><br></br>gabriele: Alright now lets get to the personal questions. Are you seeing anyone right now?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I don't know. I haven't seen Sanu in several months, and he hasn't contacted me whatsoever.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Where did you and Sanu meet and what does Sanu do?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: In the Tail, probably. We both have a thing for steak. He's an armorsmith and tailor.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: There is a rumor going on about you and Fyros. Can you tell me your side of the story?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Eh. He first showed interest in me when I became a Constable, suppose I wasn't all that interesting beforehand. We got into a relationship later on, but it was clear he was in love with someone who refused it. The break up wasn't fun, what with others trying to stick their noses where they don't belong during. I mean, being Sheriff had people wanting to see if they could use it to their advantage. I think it's only made me more mistrusting and suspicious.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Can you paraphrase the rumor you are defending yourself against?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: That Fyros has some kind of hold over me and someone he's been feuding with tried to stir things up? Yeah, no. As the Sheriff I am obligated to be unbiased, and that's what I will continue to do.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: How many relationships have you had?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I was in a relationship with Leoric once... I wouldn't really consider the rest proper relationships before Fyros and Sanu now.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: With the threat from the foreigners and the regular bustle of the city do you see any big changes coming for the constabulary?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: I don't think so. Though I try to set a good example for the Constabulary and teach my Deputies so that we have a good reputation and are regarded with respect for the deeds that we do, there will always be unrest and those who wish to mock us. Being a Constable is an ongoing battle, a fight between what's right and what's wrong. It will never change.<br></br><br></br>gabrielle: Thank you again for taking the time to answer my questions. Do you have any parting kernels of wisdom to share?<br></br><br></br>Zaria: Be the best person you can be, no matter what obstacles stand in your way.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             sixth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the constable page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             <br></br><br></br><br></br><br></br>***UPDATED LAWS***<br></br><br></br><br></br><br></br>*Assault- Intentionally and voluntarily causing immediate harmful or offensive contact.<br></br><br></br>* Assisting a Criminal- Assisting a Criminal is acting with foresight and intent to aid any person in carrying out a crime or escape justice.<br></br><br></br>* Disrespecting Constabulary- Any remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Constabulary or any on-duty member shall constitute Disrespecting Constabulary.<br></br><br></br>* Disrespecting Higher Stations- Any remark or action that shows an overt lack of respect to one's rank and title. This only applies to gentry and above. Drawing weapons against a Noble is a greater offense and shall be counted as Assault.<br></br><br></br>* Disturbing the peace- Any lewd or inflammatory act committed in a public place to either incite peaceful citizenry, to display blatant disregard for public decency, or unsettle public order.<br></br><br></br>* Illegal detainment- Illegal detainment is arresting suspects or criminals and detaining them without a legal warrant of arrest issued by a magistrate or by disallowed 24 detainment.<br></br><br></br>*24 Hour Detainment-If a constable witnesses a crime they may stop the crime and detain the suspect for 24 hours. This may only be done once per crime and only with probably cause. If a constable does this more than once per crime or without probably cause they may be charged with illegal detainment.<br></br><br></br>* Kidnapping- Kidnapping is the taking away of a person by force, threat, or deceit, with intent to cause them to be detained against their will. Further charges of assault may be applied to cases where the kidnapping was violent.<br></br><br></br>* Murder- The willful (non-negligent) killing of one person by another. In incidents that lead to a death as a result of self-defense or defense of another, a charge of murder can be applied.(ooc: Only deaths committed by the "kill" command are considered "willful" deaths IE, the person who uses the "kill" command on another person is the one legally responsible for their death, even if a third person gave all the injuries).<br></br><br></br>* Property damage- Damage or destruction done to public or private property, caused by a person who is not its owner. (in cases of slaves and serfs, the slave is an extension of their owner and may not be charged with any crime. Their owners take full and total responsibility of their actions and are thus liable for all and any crime committed by their slave/serf)<br></br><br></br>*Resisting a Constable- Any attempt to evade or assault a Constable performing a dutiful arrest or ignoring an official summons.<br></br><br></br>* Theft- The taking and removing of personal property with intent to deprive the rightful owner of it. If goods are returned, the severity of the charge may be reduced. In cases of robbery where force is used or damage to the stolen property, additional charges may be included.<br></br><br></br>*Debt-refusing to pay a bill means you are in debt. This applies to any services rendered that go unpaid. If you are charged with this crime you do not have to pay your bill because your punishment will serve as payment rendered.<br></br><br></br>*Treason- Plotting or taking action against the Don while a citizen or guest in his city.<br></br><br></br>* Acting against the Church- Any remark or action that insults or undermines the authority of the Church of S'allumer.<br></br><br></br>* Apostasy- Leaving a religion after making it a profession and swearing solemn vows. This does not apply to someone who moves from one order to another, or retires legitimately.<br></br><br></br>* Heresy- The worship or preaching of a forbidden heresy. This specifically means the 'Old Faith' of Lutara, explicitly denying the tenants of S'allumer, and practicing black magic.<br></br><br></br>*Possession of forbidden items or substance-possession or consumption of any substance or item deemed illegal by the guild council. The selling/buying of any such item fulls under this crime.<br></br><br></br>*Trespassing-entering any private or restricted areas without permission.<br></br><br></br>*Littering-This is the act of dropping unwanted items on the ground instead of in the trash can and walking away.<br></br><br></br>*Public Prostitution-The act or advertising of prostitution in public areas fulls under this law. (ooc this means that the cathouse and private rooms are fine for such rp)<br></br><br></br>---Deaths---<br></br><br></br>Kaine<br></br><br></br>---Arrest warrant:<br></br>Luciano for disprecting constables and nobles.<br></br><br></br>Virendra disrespecting constabulary. <br></br>Damien for assault in the Inn. <br></br> Kakfa for disturbing the peace, theft, and two counts of assault.<br></br><br></br>Gren for assault of Valdus. <br></br>Open Cases:<br></br><br></br>Kruix and Valdus for assault in the severed tail inn.<br></br><br></br>~Militia~<br></br><br></br>The militia was formed as a means of upstanding citizens of the city with martial experience to gain the ability to bring in particularly unruly criminals and aid in exceptional circumstances. It is an honor to be a part of so that the innocent people of Triskellian may rest well at night and be proud of their kin, or their family, or their friends who might be a member.<br></br> Members of the milita are: Mister Bayard of the Avoirdupois; Mister Hanneman of the Avoirdupois; Mister Cullan of the Bisclavret; Mister Kaine of the Bisclavret; Miss Althea of the Doloreaux; Mister Ford, unaffiliated; Mister Jardskjalfti, unaffiliated. To be a member simply have a clean criminal record and, at the very least, 10 lessons in any given combat profession. Then write to Acting Sheriff Zaria for more info. <br></br><br></br>It is of the utmost importance that when a crime is committed any and all that witness it, report it. Do not rely on others to do so because you can't be certain they will. Should you not wish to contact a Constable directly or you don't know any by name then there is another way. Outside the gaol is a carving of a fox head. You can put what you saw on a scroll and then deposit it into the fox head. Only Constables can retrieve it once it's put in there and it is checked daily by myself.<br></br>If you don't know where the gaol is you head west from the west commons onto Market Street. From there, head north through the market place and into Newtown. The gaol is just north of the cafe and to the west. The fox head is outside the gaol on the street.<br></br><br></br>Thank you for you continued support and cooperation.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ On Behalf of All Clothiers of Triskellian ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~\{0\}~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ We offer here a list of what each established clothier in the city is skilled in. A directory of sorts, if you will. WHEN MAKING AN ORDER PLEASE SEND AS MUCH INFORMATION AS YOU CAN. IT MUST INCLUDE: COLOR, MATERIAL, AND GENERAL TYPE. Example: Blue suede  Shoes Belt  Hat Gloves Bag <br></br><br></br>~ Rainbow Rags ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Una -Master of needleworking \& seamstressing.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Brie- Master Dyer\& tailoring.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>= Other Clothiers withing the City walls =<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Esquire Meepers, of Sew you Can Sew - Master Seamstress and Dyer.<br></br><br></br>+List of Terminologies+<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Dyer - Mixer of dyes<br></br>- Seamstress - Creator of feminine garments<br></br>- Tailor - Creator of masculine garments<br></br>- Needleworker - Creator of accessories with skills of embroidering<br></br><br></br>~\{0\}~ Favorable Colors this Season ~\{0\}~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br> ~*~ Colors of the Season ~*~<br></br><br></br>Raven, this black shade of the mysterious raven birds.<br></br><br></br> Fern Green, the darker green of the autumn time plant.<br></br><br></br>Falu Red, cottage colored.<br></br><br></br> Rust Red, the autumn leaves of red.<br></br><br></br>Storm Grey, brooding and dark this is the color of no sunshine. <br></br><br></br>Mauve, the autumnish pink dye.<br></br><br></br> Pale Amber, tree sap in a bottle.<br></br><br></br> copper-colored, harvesting copper for your dying delight.<br></br><br></br> Plum-colored, the harvest season of plums on thumbs.<br></br><br></br> ~ Warm Autumn, to you from me ~<br></br><br></br>Garment of the month<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-<br></br><br></br>~*~Womens~*~<br></br><br></br>~ Hanging sleeved gown.  This is an ankle-length gown uniquely-cut to produce fine draping on the body. The wrist-length sleeves are stitched to the back of the armholes only, enabling the wearer to pull them onto the arm or allow them to hang free from the shoulders.<br></br><br></br>~*~Mens~*~<br></br><br></br>Gentlemen's coat.  It boasts neck and shoulder frills which trail into slightly puffed sleeves until just above the elbow where they give way to a series of three decorative buckles which reach to just above the wrists of the wearer. Five matching buttons grace the front with which the garment can be closed.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eighth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eighth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the crafter directory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^Crafter Directory*^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Una - Master knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Mister Fred<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Tark-armor smith~<br></br>~Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Claton-armor smith<br></br>~Bruno-armor smith<br></br>~Natalie-weapon smith<br></br>~Claton-weapon smith<br></br>~Bruno-weapon smith<br></br>~Tark-weapon smith<br></br>~Natalie-Black smith<br></br>~Zrgt-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Lady Anelie~<br></br>~Caitriona~<br></br><br></br>~Merchants~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Rem~<br></br>~Fips~<br></br>~Aluine~<br></br><br></br>~Healers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Dr. Hush~<br></br>~Physician Suavis~<br></br>~Nurse Sable~<br></br>~Achlys~
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ninth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ninth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of funnies drawn by Sang
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             http://www.tigerknight.com/ss/ss6-4.jpg<br></br>http://www.kizandjenn.com/sean2/031.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_10" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="tenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pages"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             tenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the social life of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             %*%*%*%*%*Esquire Noelane Social Etiquette Corner%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br> As has been issue frequently of those ignorant of the etiquette relating to NewTown and its inhabitants, I have decided to summarise here a list of rules that will allow one to pass through or linger without calling too much unwanted disdain and ill-favoured attention to oneself. NewTown is a place of social rank, so if you do not agree with the customs then simply avoid crossing their land lest there be issue. You will enter NewTown immediately north and through the gate of the market place.<br></br><br></br> #1 - Bow/Curtsy<br></br><br></br> For some of you, this will be an obvious thing to abide by. Bowing and curtsying to those higher ranking or of social station is considered an appropriate greeting/parting as a means of showing respect. A bow/curtsy must also be displayed to those of equal ranking, as you are neither above or below them in station. Higher ranking officials may either reciprocate the gesture, or offer a nod or bow of the head in your direction. If in doubt, or you are unfamiliar with those present, bowing/curtsying is a safe bet to fall back on just in case.<br></br><br></br> #2 - Introduction<br></br><br></br> Upon meeting someone you are unfamiliar with and you are undoubtedly of lower rank it is usually best to wait until the higher ranking vocally acknowledges you. You may then introduce yourself if another third party is not present to introduce the both of you to one another. To be safe, a bow/curtsy to the higher ranking official is appropriate after introductions have been made as a show of deference.<br></br><br></br> #3 - Seating<br></br><br></br> Those of highest rank has first choice of where they sit, and the next highest following that until there are either no seats or everyone has sat. If those of higher rank do not wish to sit you may then seek permission from them to sit. If the higher ranking official rises from a seat and intends on departure then you must rise also until they have taken their leave. Likewise, you must also seek their permission for leave before rising and showing them the proper bow/curtsy upon departure.<br></br><br></br> #4 - Departure<br></br><br></br> Always request those of the highest rank for leave, as well as your highest superior if the highest ranking is of another affiliation and one of similar affiliation as yourself is present. If those mentioned are in deep discussion, do not interrupt them and simply bow/curtsy, bidding them a good day (or blessings, etc, whatever your custom) before leaving.<br></br><br></br> #5 - Language<br></br><br></br> As is usual in proper society, foul language is not tolerated, so attempt to avoid using curse words or entering a conversation that is lewd of offensive to the senses. In addition, it is never appropriate to greet gentry/nobility by their forename, regardless of whether or not their title is included. If you are unaware of their surname then simply use their social rank, i.e. Dame, my Lady, my Lord, Sir, Miss, Mister, Mrs, etc. If you do not know their rank then introductions are in order. In special cases, those of higher rank may allow you usage of their forename, but etiquette must always be adhered to in public lest it be considered a social offense.<br></br><br></br> #6 - Food/Drink<br></br><br></br> If you wish to retrieve or give food/drink to those present then it is always appropriate to defer to the highest ranking, then second highest, until you reach the lowest. If you are unaware, ignorance is no excuse, make sure introductions have been made. It is usually considered proper for the lowest ranking to ensure that those of higher standing have either a beverage in their hand or do not require one. If they are deep in discussion and they have recently finished a beverage you may discreetly indicate that they have done so. They may accept, decline or ignore you. Do not take it personally if the latter is correct, and refrain from pestering them further until their conversation has concluded.<br></br><br></br> These are but a brief summary of the key points regarding etiquette in NewTown. I pray that reading this has been useful. ~Written by columnist Esquire Noelane.<br></br><br></br>%*%*%*%*%*-Poetry Corner-%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Please send in your submissions of poetry to Tammary of the Avoirdupois if you would like your poem printed. <br></br><br></br>An Ode to the Sea<br></br> A Poem by Tammary<br></br><br></br> As tempest-torn tides twist,<br></br> the ripe scent of salt flies high,<br></br> and heralds the coming of deafening clashes,<br></br> were the lightning tongue of a mighty cloud serpent trashes,<br></br> the creaking of wood and masts with sodden sails,<br></br> amidst the bellows of sailors and their shrill wails.<br></br><br></br> The screaming wind of furious force,<br></br> the harrowing breath of the stormy sky,<br></br> breathing down upon the surface of a raging beast.<br></br><br></br> But like a tiger,<br></br> graceful yet deadly,<br></br> it's rage subsides,<br></br> and heckles fall.<br></br><br></br> As the shining eye of the sky,<br></br> bathes it with incandescent rays,<br></br> it naps silently,<br></br> and gentle silence falls fervently.<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_11" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eleventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eleventh"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eleventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the social life of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             %*%*%*%*%*Summer Fever%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Summer's upon us once more! The sun is shining , the trees are as green as can be and love is in the air! Citizens are encouraged to catch the spring fever and spread it to everyone you know. Spring is the best time for merriment and joy, for parties and passion. So grab a stool, pick up your mug and hold your lover close. Chocolate is usually in healthy supply around this time of year, so buy plenty of it if you can afford it! Otherwise a good bouquet of flowers should be the perfect gift from you suave gentlemen, and a fancy hat (or a kiss on the cheek!) from the girls. Citizens are also encouraged to clean, clean and clean! It gets very dirty this time of the year, sweep the house, sweep the room and sweep the streets if you have to. Spring's no fun if you get a literal spring fever. For all of you clothing savvy out there, now's the best time to start stocking up something nice and light for the summer and the best time to buy the best looking dresses, suits and cloaks.~ Written by columnist and social page editor Tammary.<br></br><br></br>%*%*%*%*%*Dressed for the Occasion%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Summer is the season of bright colours and wearing something to reflect that is always good for your image. Leafy greens, whites , yellows , sandy browns and ruby reds are always the best colours for this season. Flowing garments are always fun to wear, women are encouraged to wear long dresses with plenty of bright patterns and a good mixture of colours. Bright reds and whites are always a good combination, and a seasonal bonnet is always fetching and adorable. Now is the time to wear your hair long, curls are always a fun way to style your hair, especially near the late spring season. For all you men out there, dress handsomely. Casual attire for the late spring season's always a muddle, but don't feel shy about showing a bit of arm! Always more for the women to admire. For the mid spring season, it's always fun to keep your hair short and wear a nice comfortable tunic and a colourful jacket.~ Written by columnist and social page editor Tammary.<br></br><br></br>%*%*%*%*%*-Tensions Rising Amongst Citizens-%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Triskellian, being a city, is a melting pot where all walks of life congregate and meet. With that comes plenty of conflict and plenty of trouble. But recently there's been a particular amount of violence and animosity between citizens, in every quarter. Tension between the nobles has been rising as things get more and more competitive, animosity between the local houses is on the rise and crime appears to be at an all time high. With brigands and murderers stalking the streets, giving us reason to feel more and more unsafe. In light of this situation, I encourage everyone to try to mend the growing rift between Triskellian's people by doing their duty and lending each other a helping hand. If your fellow citizen has been robbed, aid them in informing the local constabulary. See someone being mugged? Be consider before jumping to their aid. A coin purse is worth less then one's life. See that poor beggar in the street? Be charitable, give him a denarii or two for his troubles. Tip your local blacksmiths, waiters and tailors. Even a passing compliment or words of encouragement can be worth more then a thousand denarii. Join the local guard and keep the streets safe. Join a local charity and do the downtrodden some good. Because we may have our differences, but in this city we are all family.`Edited by Tammary.<br></br><br></br>%*%*%*%*%*-Amuse and Muse with Musical Use!-%*%*%*%*%*<br></br><br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Looking for a way to brighten your day and expand your mind? Then why not visit the local university, or barring that ask a friend , and learn to play an instrument. The hustle and bustle of the city tends to bother one less when it's replaced with the sweet, smooth melody of a flute, or the strumming of a lute. There is a high demand for bards and musicians lately, especially at popular restaurants and taverns. With that in mind, if you're considering a career in performing arts, singing, dancing and so on - then by all means, go for it. It can be an enlightening experience that strengthens the body, mind and soul. It spreads happiness amongst your friends and anyone lucky enough to catch an earful of your joyous melody. Even those who aren't trained in playing any instruments can do their part. Singing brightens anyone's day, so if you're at the local tavern drinking with the lads or scrubbing the dirt out of your clothing - sing a jaunty tune and let your voice be heard.~Written by Tammary.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_12" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="twelfth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="twelfth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             twelfth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the political page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^Current Ambassadors*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"Rinaldi Ambassador Adon"<br></br><br></br>"Bisclavret Ambassador Sir Twyrch"<br></br><br></br> "Avoirdupois Ambassador Sir Bayard"<br></br><br></br>"Doloreaux Ambassador Lady Anelie"<br></br><br></br> *^*^*^*^*^*^Current Affairs*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Seige at West Triskellian.<br></br><br></br>People in attendance. Chesh - Hanneman - Physician Suavis - Zanthia - Zaria - Logan - Koz - Jasper - corpse of Virendra - <br></br><br></br>Some time ago, information was uncovered that indicated a foreign force had overrun a town west of Triskellian named simply West Triskellian. It was learned that the foreigners had hired an army of mercenary troops to bolster the ranks of the army they had brought from overseas.  An overwhelmming combined army of nearly 7000 troops was assembled from the standing forces of all of the Great Houses, as well as the Constabulary, and sent to meet this threat.  An advance party consisting of Sheriff Zaria, Reeve Zanthia, Physician Suavis, Captain Hanneman, Misters Logan, Jasper and Virendra, as well as the serf Chesh and Koz the slave.  The group managed to infiltrate the city ahead of the akkied army, though not without loss.  During the infiltration, Virendra lost his life due to his own reckless behaviour.  Once arrived at the rather unusual informant's house, the group learned some critical information about the invaders, and departed the next day to meet the army from the capital in the field.  With Captain Hanneman taking command of the disposition of the troops, Reeve Zanthia organizing the logistics of relaying orders and materials, Sheriff Zaria leading the Constabulary's contingent, Physician Suavis understandably taking the rear in anticipation of casualties, and Chesh, Logan, Koz, Jasper and the corpse of Virendra (who proved more useful in death than he was in life, being used once during the ensuing battle as a diversionary tactic),  the allied army took position outside the town in preparation for the attack.  Such a large army does not go unnoticed, however, and the besieged foreigners and mercenaries arrayed themselves in defence, bringing to bear on our forces not only troops, but strange artillery and wizardry.  The initial barrage from the defenders took the heaviest toll, but the allied counteratteck was swift and decisive.  The wizards and artillery were quickly brought down with snipers and scouts, while the bulk of the soldiers and mercenaries from Triskellian engaged the defenders and overwhelmed them.  At one point, a group of several skilled fighters broke through the lines and engaged the leaders of the expedition, but they were beaten back with minimal casualties.  In the end, with a casualty count of just over six hundred allied troops to the foreigners' reported loss of well over a thousand, the combined Calabrese army easily won the day and liberated the town of West Triskellian, and the prisoners and materials captured in the battle have proven invaluable to the investigation of the size and intent of this foreign threat.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_13" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thirteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="thirteenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             thirteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is an ongoing moral story written by a citizen of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *~*~Of Rhiem and Reson*~*~<br></br>-----------------------------------<br></br><br></br>Part Two- Sundered Sight and a Sodden Swordsmith<br></br><br></br>The sky was clear, the weather fair as the pair of intrepid adventurers made their way across the countryside.  The noble Sir Rhiem led the way, of course, atop a stalwart war-mount, his armour gleaming in the afternoon sun despite the wear it had seen throughout his travels.  Loyal Reson, his squire, followed behind in a small cart.<br></br><br></br>   "And that,"  Sir Rhiem was explaining to Reson, as he had all afternoon, "Is the cause of it, for no matter the intent, one always seems to find it difficult to trust a man with an eyepatch."<br></br><br></br>   "Yes, sire." Reson agreed, as he always did, "They do indeed appear suspicious."<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem replied, "Yes, exactly so.  Now, I have known a guardsman once that had the misfortune of losing an eye, but he did not choose to don one; instead he..."<br></br><br></br>   At that moment, a scream was heard in the direction of the woods to the east of the path.  Sir Rhiem immediately spurred his jennet toward the treeline without another word.  Reson hastily gathered a few things from the cart and followed.<br></br><br></br>   As he was charging through the woods, another scream was heard, at which Sir Rhiem corrected his course, shouting ahead.  Reson ran behind him as best he could, but could not keep up.<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem found shortly a small brook, beside which the reason for the screams was apparent.  A woman who had been out gathering herbs was set upon by two men of an evil mein, and had been beaten.  Both men had weapons, and seemed intent to use them.  With a start, they looked up at Sir Rhiem, who slacked in his charge not at all, and ran one of the rogues through with his lance.  The other stood fixed by surprise and terror as the knight dismounted and approached him, drawing his blade.   "Pray S'allumer has mercy upon you, brigand, for your actions have earned you a swift death," Sir Rhiem growled as he bore down on him, raising his sword for a killing strike.<br></br><br></br>   The thug quickly found his senses again, however, and threw a handful of sand into the noble's eyes, then fled stumbling into the woods again.  In his haste he ran directly into Reson, who was ready for him, and ended him with a dagger-thrust.<br></br><br></br>   Reson came upon the brook then, to find Sir Rhiem bellowing in rage, blindly attacking a hapless, unfortunate bush.<br></br><br></br>   "Coward!"  The knight shouted furiously, "Face me!  You are a fool to think that a knight can be defeated with sand!  Addle-pated blackguard!"<br></br><br></br>   Reson explained quickly 'Sire, he cannot.  He has been slain already."<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem turned in the direction of his squire's voice, lowering his blade, 'Oh, has he?  Pitiful cretin.  Brave enough to attack a lone woman, but cannot even face a just death with anything but cowardice.  Good squire, clean the wretch's blood from my sword; I cannot see to do it myself, and I would not have it stained so."   "At once, sire." Reson replied, taking a cloth and wiping sap from his lord's weapon, "Your eyes, sire, are you well?"<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem waved dismissively 'It is nothing, I shall wash them out; they shall be good as new."  He turned then, in the direction of the brook and began to do so.   The woman, who was in a stunned silence until then, interjected, 'I cannot thank you enough, good Sir Knight.  I may have been slain but for your intervention, and certainly worse.  If you will, my lord, my township has a good healer; please allow me to pay for the treatment of the wounds you recieved in my defence."<br></br><br></br>   After a short arguement and the persuasion of both the woman and his squire, Sir Rhiem accepted, for his eyes did pain him greatly.  The three made their way into town, which was of a modest size and seemed rather clean and prosperous.  People wandered the streets they travelled, attending their tasks and businesses.  The place had a quiet and peaceful atmosphere, and the people seemed content, thought Reson.  Sir Rhiem saw none of this, of course.<br></br><br></br>   At the infirmary, the knight was quickly seen to, despite his protestations.  The healer was indeed skilled, and cleaned the sand from his eyes well, and applied a poultice, padding his eyes with bandages to contain it.<br></br><br></br>   "You shall have to wear these eyepatches for no less than a week's time, my lord," the doctor explained, at which the knight grumbled to himself.  The doctor said then, "I shall change them daily, so you will have to stay here, if you will."<br></br><br></br>   Over the next few days, the woman and her husband came to see them often.  They would converse with the knight and his squire, telling them about local legends and stories, which the adventurers listened to eagerly.  The husband, who was a local smith, took Reson aside one day as his wife was regaling the noble knight with a legend of a priestess who had lived near the lake outside town and watched over the townsfolk.<br></br><br></br>   "I would like to thank your lord properly for saving my wife," said the smith to Reson, "I have been saving a bit of rare steel, and I would craft a blade worthy of one of such noble intent, one that would well serve his desire to aid others."<br></br><br></br>   Reson replied to him, "He would be deeply honoured, good smith.  I can assure you that he..."<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem strode in then, after having nearly completely misinterpreted the local legend, shouting, "Squire!  Come, we have a journey we must undertake!  It shan't take long."<br></br><br></br>   Reson asked the knight, "Sire?  I am here; what is it?"   Sir Rhiem grinned in his squire's general direction, "It is no less than the Lady of the Lake herself.  That lake is here, and we must go, immediately!  You must guide me there."  His eyes would likely have been shining eagerly, were they not thoroughly swathed and covered.<br></br><br></br>   Reson knew better than to argue with his lord, of course, and so they set out, reaching the shore of the lake without incident, where they found a sole person, a washer-woman.  Before Reson could greet her, his lord called out, "Hail, good Lady!  We have come hither to see you!  Please, if I am worthy, answer me!"<br></br><br></br>   The poor woman was startled, of course, but Reson smiled and gestured to her reassuringly, so she replied, 'Yes, I know you, good Sir Rhiem.  All have heard of your deeds by now.  I would say you are a worthy knight, indeed."<br></br><br></br>   The knight positively beamed at this, and said further, 'Your words are too kind, Lady.  I bid you, if you will, set a task before me, some noble quest to undertake!"<br></br><br></br>   The washer-woman, amused by the scene before her, told him, 'You have done quite enough for now, I should say, and gotten yourself hurt, too.  You should rest, good knight, you have earned it, and you can't very well quest in that condition."  She indicated her basket of laundry then, "If you like, I have a few things you could do, once you can see again."<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem bowed to the lake respectfully, "I shall do as you bid."<br></br><br></br>   Once back in the infirmary, Sir Rhiem no longer grumbled at the doctor's orders, but rested as well as he was able.  Reson went then to seek the smith and his wife that had visited them before, and explained the situation, making a request.<br></br><br></br>   The days passed quickly, and several people came to visit them, among which was the chief of the local constabulary, who told them that the men they had dispatched were the leaders of a local gang of thugs, and that, leaderless, the rest had been rounded up and arrested easily.<br></br><br></br>   Soon Sir Rhiem's eyes had been restored.  They took their leave, thanking the doctor and the others for their kindness, and headed immediately for the lake they had visited before.  However, instead of the washer-woman, they found upon the shore a box, as Reson had requested of the grateful smith.<br></br><br></br>   Sir Rhiem, after hearing no answer from calling out to the lake, took the box and withdrew from it a note and a magnificent sword of the brightest steel, wrought with fine filigree and sheathed in a scabbard of equal quality.  Admiringly, he drew the sword as he recited from the note.<br></br><br></br>   "This blade is bestowed in gratitude of all you have done, and all you shall do in the future.  May it serve you well as you in turn serve Honour and Justice, and may it be the bane of all those that would harm the innocent."  Sir Rhiem's newly healed eyes misted slightly as he read, "May your path guide you always to where you are needed most."<br></br><br></br>   The knight turned to his squire, 'Well, then.  We have been given a great gift and a noble quest.  We must depart.  See to our preparations."<br></br><br></br>   "At once, sire", replied Reson, and the two heroes set out once again, seeking whatever adventure awaited them.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_14" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="fourteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourteenth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of gossips all submitted by anonymous sources.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^Rumors and Gossips*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"A certain knight, had the balls to not only speak the language of the street rats in the commons but also took it upon herself to teach others the bad habit too. Why would a knight show off such a skill?"<br></br><br></br>"The avoirdupois was invaluable during the siege on West Triskellian and the invading Jadelanders. They helped solve the puzzles at the old tiger's crooked house, scouted out much-needed information, and directed troops efficiently against the magic and numbers of the foreign enemies so that losses were minimal despite the lack of healers. Fantastic!"<br></br><br></br> "Usually shy, Rylen did fantastic playing a feminine flower in Nan's play, Pink! He was a good sport wearing a dress which couldn't have been more fluttery and girlish if it tried.. Personally, I don't think I could have let loose as many tears on the stage in front of so many people if I tried! Good going, skunk boy."<br></br><br></br>"The Doloreaux takes care of house members. They not only paid for the outfit of a house member but tipped the seamstress who made it to make it extra special."<br></br><br></br>"If you dream of paradise, white beaches and palm trees, hospitable people and a good trade, then you should take a look at the Corsair Islands, though I've heard there's a pirate city out there somewhere, so beware how you flaunt your gold."<br></br><br></br>"The Paludestris is a huge morose swap which has many legends surrounding it. It's said to be inhabited by dangerous monsters, the undead, giant lizards, dragons and ghosts! Some of course say it's just bandits and outlaws who fuel the legends to keep bounty hunters away. Others say there's a fox family living in the dangerous Paludestris swamps, a family of grey foxes who fell into disgrace. Their name is Jakoba, the same as our Queen."<br></br><br></br>"Even though it's not his job, a local badger took a personal interest in the murders Razeer and Samuel were accused of, and, despite not being literate, found someone to translate and came up with several solutions and answers to the conundrum."<br></br><br></br>"For a Paladin representing the Church they don't do a good job. Apparenlty, they arrived two hours late to Presbyter Ximen's trial and even spoke out of turn demanding his voice be heard even after the Metropolitans demanded he sit down and be quiet. I'm surprised he wasn't arrested on the spot!"<br></br><br></br>"Despite his idiosyncrasies and social incompetency, mister Iain proved himself exceptionally useful during the merpeople expedition, combining his observance of the surrounding environment with his book smarts he was easily able to figure out most problems people were faced with quickly and efficiently."<br></br><br></br> "Mister Ramsford is very inclusive with people, even if they've take offense to something he's said in the past."<br></br><br></br>"Valentin sent a signed scroll to a noble in which said noble recited it in the commons. It said "Kiss my ass you smug bastard. Your arrogance reflects that of a commoner, not a knight."<br></br><br></br>"In need of licks and tuggings? Find this esquire in any public location and collect your share today! For being an armigerous gentry, she sure is awful friendly. It must be that whole cat thing."<br></br><br></br>"It's really good luck to kiss Brie the seamstress' cheek. The bigger tantrum she throws, the more luck you'll get!"<br></br><br></br>"Did you know that the Chapel in Docktown was burnt down some years ago, but they never found out who did it. The brave whisper it was a masked rat, but no one dares put name to the culprit. Some say it was the necromancers who burnt down the chapel for their own uses. I've heard whispered that they helped rebuild it too."<br></br><br></br>"Did you hear? Apparently Clover was being a downer. What next? Is it going to start raining frogs again?"<br></br><br></br>"Mister Cullan shouldn't speak ill of the Knights of his household, especially to aspirant squires of the Bisclavret, and certainly not int he commons in front of others."<br></br><br></br> "Kahiva should feel embarrassed. She let Tucka kiss her ear, right in the middle of the commons. They aren't even courting."<br></br><br></br>"Doloreaux Master Smith Agriphina has definately got a lot of love for that smithing hammer of hers. Strange, considering it hardly has a dent in it."<br></br><br></br>"Local Avoirdupois scout and writer Tammary is working on a new collection of short stories that is supposed to be a daring tale filled with  'Adventure, romance, action and a lot of carrots'. Local lapines are already estatic"<br></br><br></br>"Despite being a useless drunk most of the time, Ilo surprised us all by diving into a burning, upturned cart and saving an entire family from the flames and potential death. Good work!"<br></br><br></br>"Leave it to Sang to play paid piper and sooth those mourning their fallen companions at the swamp campsite. Music does sooth the soul."<br></br><br></br>" Kegan just learned that Zaria and Fyros have been secretly dating and that Fyros has been lying to Zaria for a while. Turns out he was only with Zaria to influence the constabulary. The cherry on top is that Fyros talks badly about Zaria to the love of his life Dame Xena to make himself look better. Oouch does this make your head hurt as much as mine?"<br></br><br></br>"That bat sure can keep a cool head. She even managed to patch up Deacon Ximen -while- he was burning a heretic! Talk about skill .. woh."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K", 1354853763, "meandmine", "K", 1354942697, "meandmine", "K", 1354945930, "meandmine", "K", 1354949099, "meandmine", "K", 1354949332, "meandmine", "E", 1354949364, "meandmine", "K", 1354949373, "meandmine", "E", 1355259036, "meandmine", "K", 1355259762, "meandmine", "K", 1355259767, "meandmine", "E", 1355259860, "meandmine", "K", 1355260025, "meandmine", "K", 1355260127, "meandmine", "K", 1355267403, "meandmine", "K", 1355281790, "meandmine", "K", 1357690626, "meandmine", "K", 1357692638, "meandmine", "K", 1357692747, "meandmine", "K", 1358310543, "meandmine", "K", 1358312544, "meandmine", "K", 1358320455, "meandmine", "K", 1358321566, "meandmine", "K", 1358325444, "meandmine", "K", 1358328295, "meandmine", "K", 1358331132, "meandmine", "K", 1358331762, "meandmine", "K", 1358332027, "meandmine", "K", 1358332059, "meandmine", "K", 1358332124, "meandmine", "K", 1358332578, "meandmine", "K", 1358332592, "meandmine", "E", 1358332619, "meandmine", "K", 1358908973, "meandmine", "K", 1360909601, "meandmine", "K", 1362049202, "meandmine", "K", 1362103954, "meandmine", "K", 1362872017, "meandmine", "K", 1362875584, "meandmine", "K", 1362876726, "meandmine", "K", 1363927594, "meandmine", "K", 1366999186, "meandmine", "K", 1366999373, "meandmine", "K", 1367000338, "meandmine", "K", 1372307148, "meandmine", "K", 1375138082, "meandmine", "K", 1375316390, "meandmine", "K", 1375342501, "meandmine", "K", 1375413390, "meandmine", "K", 1375414616, "meandmine", "K", 1375415176, "meandmine", "K", 1375415260, "meandmine", "K", 1375415358, "meandmine", "K", 1375415385, "meandmine", "K", 1375416474, "meandmine", "K", 1375416570, "meandmine", "K", 1375417747, "meandmine", "K", 1375420249, "meandmine", "K", 1375420384, "meandmine", "K", 1375422567, "meandmine", "K", 1375422727, "meandmine", "K", 1375423034, "meandmine", "K", 1375424809, "meandmine", "K", 1375424875, "meandmine", "K", 1375424914, "meandmine", "K", 1375425036, "meandmine", "K", 1375425634, "meandmine", "K", 1375427129, "meandmine", "K", 1375427287, "meandmine", "K", 1375427359, "meandmine", "K", 1375427401, "meandmine", "K", 1375427447, "meandmine", "K", 1375427522, "meandmine", "K", 1375427869, "meandmine", "K", 1375427975, "meandmine", "K", 1375428042, "meandmine", "K", 1375428212, "meandmine", "K", 1375428528, "meandmine", "K", 1375430843, "meandmine", "K", 1375431324, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
