<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The first page is the table of content, the second page is the story on the assassins, the third page is the story on the sewer raid, the fourth page is the interview with lePlow, the fifth page is the fashion season, the sixth page is the crafting directory, the seventh page is gossipmonger.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about the assassins.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ASSASSINATION OF THE UPPER CRUST~<br></br><br></br>On Harvest 30th on the closing day of the Harvest Festival, the first of the assassinations happened with Dame Xena being shot through the heart, killing her instantly.  In the days that followed chaos erupted when the assassination attempts did not stop. It was found out that there was a hit list containing the following names:  Esquire Clover, Esquire Lianaar, mister Virendra, Sir Bayard, Esquire Fips, Doctor Hush, Esquire Meepers and Lord Twyrch.   After mister Gus was shot and killed, another list was found and was thought to be more complete: Xena with a line through it - Fips with a line through it - Clover with two x's next to it - Hush with an x next to it - Bayard with two x's next to it - Gus with a line through it - Marcus - Twyrch - Meepers - Virendra - Linaar – Senora. Why there are two lists is unknown but the initial reason for the hit list was to exterminate all gentry and above that had earned their ranks. Speculation says that those sponsored for promotion by Rinaldi are targeted. <br></br><br></br>The victims of the assaults are Dr. Hush shot through the shoulder, Lady Antonia shot in the stomach, Deputy Carrot shot in the shoulder and stomach, Mister Hanneman, Mister Clover, and Miss Dasha all receive minor injuries. Mister Fips, Mister Gus, and Dame Xena were all killed. Our thoughts are with the victims. <br></br><br></br>The villains behind the attacks were not known at the time and their numbers were impressive. When asked about the assassins Sir Bayard quotes 'They call themselves the "Reformed Thief's Guild", and are a combination of four major criminal syndicates in each capital city. The original Thief's Guild in Triskellian, The Old Blood Purge which is based in Chalon sur Sauldre, the Assassin's Blade from Bruges and the Minkers which are located in Phelan lands.'  When acting sheriff Zaria was asked about the assassins she was thoroughly informative quoting 'The Old Blood Purge want to purge those who have risen in rank from commoner to gentry and higher. The Assassin's Blade are comprised of children who had been stolen in Doloreaux lands and raised to become Assassins. The Minkers are a group of faux druids who initially came to Triskellian to steal knowledge on the elementals, as we have information from when they flooded Triskellian.' This information was earned through hard work, high risk, and dedication to keep the city streets safe.  To those who sacrificed to help the city, you are our unsung heroes and you have our thanks.   <br></br><br></br>As you can see there is ample knowledge on each of the criminal syndicates, but the reasoning behind the assaults are still up for debate.  Mister Fyros speculates, 'Xena has a history with the thieves’ guild, from when she ran the sailors guild. That happened shortly after I first arrived in Triskellian. They probably remembered her from then, and wanted to settle a score with her first.' Others like Mister lePlow have a far different idea, 'Crime is sort of like nature right? Criminals, some are hunters, some sort of feed on carrion and whatever they can find, but a city can only handle so many thieves before people start reacting.  Here in a port city there's maybe more opportunity with the sailors and caravans, but still it’s never going to be many. The less fuss they make, the quieter they go about earning their coin the less likely to rile folks. It is possible this were an attack where the thieves were just dupes, but I still don't know why they agreed to it. Was a call to war, not a way to have a business.' <br></br><br></br>Whatever their reasons, the groups banded together and assaulted the city to its core. Their crimes stirred many local citizens to action and brought foe and friends together to stop the random killings and senseless fear.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the follow up story about the sewer raid.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~RAID IN THE SEWER~<br></br><br></br>Throughout the assassinations, the killers had multiple meetings with people from town. The first meeting was with Clover lePlow, Chesh, and Sable. They walked into a hidden room full of thieves and cutthroats. The lead thief invited Clover to join him if only he would give back his lands.  Naturally, Clover declined and since the odds were 9:1 the small party left, relatively unharmed.  The next meeting was between acting sheriff Zaria, Sir Bayard, Kaine who met the lead thief in the swing park on Dock Street.  The meeting was to make a deal, stop hunting them and they would stop killing people. Zaria is quoted with, ‘I don’t make deals with criminals.’  At the conclusion of this meeting, the three in attendance were promised a safe return to the commons. <br></br><br></br>The next meeting would be on the local citizen’s terms and would turn out to be far more lethal and dangerous than anyone could have imagined.  The plan was to block all exits and then set a wagon on fire as it is pushed into the thieves’ hideout. The plan was simple enough and there was a small army to complete this task. In attendance was Clover and his many employees, Fyros and his well trained employees, Sir Bayard and a small troop of Avoirdupois soldiers, a small troop of Doloreaux soldiers, Kaine and a small troop of Bisclavret soldiers, and a handful of medics supplied by Dr Hush. This large group was split into two teams, one stationed at the front entrance to the hideout and one at the rear.<br></br><br></br>When all the men were stationed, the front door group comprised of mostly Clover’s men tried to open the front door. However, it was trapped and after multiple failed attempts Clover himself opened the door, poisoning himself by doing so. The wagon was pushed into the front door and it didn’t take long for both doors to the hideout to become an evacuation route for the killers. What awaited them was death as our small army shot them down as they fled. <br></br><br></br>How I wish I could end the story there but here is where the tail takes a nose dive. It took our side a while to figure it out but they soon realized that the thieves and assassins weren’t even trying to fight or protect themselves. It dawned on many of them that the thieves were running from the hidden room like pests in a sinking ship.  No one had taken into account the sheer mass of gunpowder and poison the thieves had stockpiled.  When flaming wagon meets unknown amounts of explosives bad things happen. According to reports explosions knocked many down and out while some of the sewer itself crumbled around them. If the explosion didn’t get them the cloud of fake death poison in the air did. <br></br><br></br>While I would call the raid a total success with many of the criminals dead or wounded, it was at a high cost. Though none on our side were lethally injured or killed, the sewer itself is severely damaged and it scares this reporter to realize how much gunpowder and poison they had. That they almost succeed in whatever their dastardly plans were should be a loud warning to us all.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~~Clover, the man behind lePlow~~<br></br><br></br> Me: "Your room is lovely; can you point out objects that represent you?<br></br><br></br>Clover:  Clover firstly directs your gaze to two dark blue marble dragon statues, "Since yer an Avoir, can start thar. Years an years back, I mebbe wur still jes gettin inta th' jew'lry bus'ness? Thar wur an auction held at th' cafe by th' Ouses. Each of them brought special items fer one nuther an others t' bid on. So, th' Avoirdupois.. an I thenk this mebbe wur while Lady Calandre wur still in town? They brought those two statues an thas et, an fer whate'er reason nay'un bid. There were tensions I suppose at the time as some of the House seemed to think it odd that a Horse wouldn't just want to join and when I started to become successful they saw me as an up starter. I had no ill will to the Avoirdupois but I'd actually sort of held off bidding on things because I wasn't sure if it was alright for me to. I had the coin, but I didn't want to upset any folk of breeding by bidding against them. Still I didn't want to see the Avoirdupois shamed with their one item at the auction not getting any interest. So I sort of jumped in and made a high bid, at least high at the time. I think I paid something like 250 denarii for those even though the only bidder since I wanted the House to be able to keep its head up that their contribution went for a good amount. The main point I’m trying to make is : I stayed independent, but those statues were sort of my first feeling out of getting involved in society I guess and trying to help out the Embassy on the sly."<br></br><br></br>Me:  Can you tell me about your childhood?<br></br><br></br>Clover: I was born on a farm; my family was freeborn as the Avoirdupois freed most of their serfs... at least legally right? But pretty much things were as they'd been for generations. The land we worked was owned by a not well to do country gentry, more clay and rock than good soil it seemed, and anyone going even so far as the nearest village was a big deal.  I guess we were happy. It was a hard life, never enough food, and the labor was backbreaking. By the time my dad was my age or just a big more he was a broke backed nag from hauling rocks, and trying to help pull a plow through that soil. And if the heavy labor didn't do it, harvesting, especially the cotton, that was bad stuff. You've probably only seen it in fabric but cotton, it burns you, you're hunched over picking it for hours in the sun, and the bones themselves in your hands start to twist. We were happy because we were with herd, and we sang together and we took care of each other, but it was a hard short life, and I coudn't see myself just dying on that land without seeing what was past it."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "What was the size of your herd, and then tell me about your close family. Are your parents still alive?<br></br><br></br> Clover : "With cousins and so forth, the herd I grew up in were about thirty strong. For my immediately family, my sire died nay much older than I am, well before he'd seen thirty winters. My dame died about half a year back, though she got to be taken care of her last couple years which were a joy to be able to do. I've two older sisters that are married, both with young. A younger sister who is near to it, and a younger brother."<br></br><br></br>Me:  How did you start lePlow?<br></br><br></br>Clover:  lePlow was a joke.<br></br><br></br>Me:  In what way?<br></br><br></br> Clover: "So, back where I was brought up it isn't like peasants have fancy last names, but I got to the city and all these folk went around with fancy names. So I thought that was funny and so I figured I'd poke fun at it, and figured well I was a draft horse and pulled a plow.. and added in the 'le' just because it sounded funny. So Clover lePlow. Just a bit of humor."<br></br><br></br>Me:  So the name was a joke but I bet the company is not, how did the company of lePlow get it’s roots?<br></br><br></br>Clover: "I was betrothed to a wolf named Becky. She'd been part of the Bisclavret but wasn't able to get access to jewelry supplies, so I figured what else did I have to do with the coin I'd been making fishing, so won a few contracts. An not long after the lad she'd been with four years earlier showed up while I was out of town for a couple weeks and by the time I came back, they'd got back together, she quit the guild and they both left the city not long after leaving me sitting on contracts costing me thousands of denarii a week. Huge contracts for supplies to the Doloreaux and no jewelers and no idea what I was going to do."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "So it started because you were spoiling a bethrothed who left you?"<br></br><br></br>Clover : "Pretty much. The way I was raised, you take care of your own. So she wanted to be a jeweler, what other use did I have for coin? Anyway, that was the change from lePlow just being me amusing myself with a bit of a joke to poke fun at folk making much of themselves to having to be a real guild. I started hiring people with an interest in jewelry, and when we built that up we went into other businesses banking the biggest of them, since the stocks of gold and precious metals and gems helps to provide confidence in banking."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "What other businesses does lePlow do?"<br></br><br></br>Clover: "We invest in a lot of Docktown businesses, sometimes just providing support to crafting guilds and businesses providing services to visiting sailors and caravans and of course locals, sometimes actually taking a stake in them. lePlow has also developed a large group of guards as our trade activities grew, and we've put those guards to use dealing with trade problems, like some groups of pirates interfering with shipments coming to this city, and we managed to capture prizes when doing so, and while it was expensive we refitted some of those ships and repaired them and have a modest sized merchant marine fleet now to carry our goods and those of others. A lot of our growth in the last couple years has been in that area."<br></br><br></br>Me: Why do people call you the boss of docktown?<br></br><br></br>Clover:  "Because lePlow's the largest guild presence in Docktown and in many ways helps keep things moving smoothly in it. It used to be the Sailors guild had a strong presence and if folk were acting to upset the flow of trade or got too far out of hand the Sailors would try and help. For a good long time Docktown was a lot rougher, and lot of blood would get shed right in the commons upsetting the nobles and folk of station. We had pirates and raiders, swamp dwellers and all sorts of problem types causing problems in Docktown. So lePlow tries to help keep things calmer, keep crime down, even hiring folk that used to be some of the bigger trouble makers and giving them direction and helping them take some pride in doing better."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "How would you keep crime down? Isn't that the job of the constables?"<br></br><br></br>Clover: "Sometimes its easier for someone who is close to just say 'Cut it out.' It isn't like I arrest people or put them in jail. If they commit crimes, that's up to the constables to deal with. But I can encourage folk to change their ways for the future."<br></br><br></br>Me:  What goals do you have personally and business-wise?<br></br><br></br>Clover: "So, what are my plans? I don't know but I ask myself that a lot. I plan to talk to others and figure out what might be appreciated more because it is tiring. Its not that I'm always love and honey. There's some in this city that just want to hug anythting and everything. We've had folk make pets of slugs for S'Allumer's sake. Everyone just wants to be friends even with bad folk. I tend to take people to task, and I'm opinionated and stubborn. But I think on the balance I've done a lot of good for the city and those in it, and I've gone out of my way to send resources to help each of the Great Houses too. The city's been good to me over the years. I got here with nothing, and look at me. I try to give back whether its just helping those new to the city or helping during disasters... but yep, I am tired of being painted as a danger usually by folk that just wish I wasn't around so they could be bigger bullies."<br></br><br></br>Me: "Now lets get to the good stuff. I've heard the name Linaar connected with your name from the gossipmongers. Who is she to you?"<br></br><br></br>Clover: "Lianaar was my betrothed, though as I said about people leaving the city, she's been gone from Triskellian the last two years, really mostly gone for three years alas."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "Are you still bethrothed, being apart so long?"<br></br><br></br>Clover:  "Since I hadn't seen nor heard from her for so long I ended it also about half a year gone."<br></br><br></br>Me: Do you have any love interests now?"<br></br><br></br>Clover:  "I was pressing suit with a Bisclavret guard named Ammy, but we parted ways. At the moment so, no."<br></br><br></br>Me:  "Do you have any words of wisdom or comments you would like to add to your interview?"<br></br><br></br>Clover: " I don't pretend to be a saint, but having risen to where I am I've kept my values as best I could. I try to give back what I get. I take care of others, particularly those that show they deserve it, and you know when you start with nothing all you have is your word. I believe that, and whether friends or foes, people know my word is as pure as my gold.. as for words of wisdom, I don't know. The Don has shown a lot of wisdom in trying to support the independent guilders. He's put a lot of trust in us, and what we're building here is something new. At the same time tradition is important too. Its important to show respect to the Houses and the nobility and that's something I try and teach my employees, but what the Don's done is said a lass or lad if they work hard, if they treat people well and fair, they can improve themselves, and it isn't just me and that's a big part of what brings people to this city and'll drive wealth for those that embrace it in the Houses and out."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ On Behalf of All Clothiers of Triskellian ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~\{0\}~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ We offer here a list of what each established clothier in the city is skilled in. A directory of sorts, if you will.<br></br><br></br>~ Rainbow Rags ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Brie - Master Dyer and Master Tailor.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>= Other Clothiers withing the City walls =<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Mademoiselle Noe, of the Avoirdupois - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>~ Esquire Meepers, of Sew you Can Sew - Master Seamstress and Dyer.<br></br><br></br>+List of Terminologies+<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Dyer - Mixer of dyes<br></br>- Seamstress - Creator of feminine garments<br></br>- Tailor - Creator of masculine garments<br></br>- Needleworker - Creator of accessories with skills of embroidering<br></br><br></br>~\{0\}~ Favorable Colors this Season ~\{0\}~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Orange Hues -<br></br><br></br>1 denar - Bright orange, dark orange, pumpkin colored<br></br><br></br>5 denarii - Burnt orange, bittersweet orange<br></br><br></br>15 denarii - Sunset orange, dark coral colored, persimmon, caquelicot, vivid persimmon<br></br><br></br>- Yellow Hues -<br></br><br></br>1 denar - Dark yellow, flaxen ywllow, canary yellow<br></br><br></br>5 denarii - Goldenrod, gamboge, ochre<br></br><br></br>10 denarii - Saffron, buff<br></br><br></br>15 denarii - Pale amber, arylid yellow<br></br><br></br>- Brown Hues -<br></br><br></br>1 denar - brown, tan, light brown, brown, russet, dark brown, sable, wheat-colored<br></br><br></br>5 denarii - Sandy brown, sienna, beige, ecru, khaki<br></br><br></br>10 denarii - Cinnamon, rich brown, chocolate<br></br><br></br>15 denarii - Dark chocolate, umber, caramel, creamy chocolate, auburn, golden brown<br></br><br></br>-Purple Hues -<br></br><br></br>1 denarii - Dark purple<br></br><br></br>5 denarii - Lavender, plum-colored, bright purple, indigo<br></br><br></br>10 denarii - Violet, amethyst, imperial purple, vibrant purple, lavender rose, orchid purple, indigo purple<br></br><br></br>15 denarii - Dusky violet, thistle-colored<br></br><br></br>- Red Hues -<br></br><br></br>1 denar - Bright red, light red, dark red, crimson, ruddy red<br></br><br></br>5 denarii - Blood-red, rose red, vibrant red, maroon, rust red, scarlet, strawberry red, dark scarlet, pale rose red<br></br><br></br>10 denarii - Blush-red, ruby red, falu red, holly red, cherry-red, red-violet<br></br><br></br>15 denarii - Cardinal red, carmine red, vermilion, cerise, cranberry-colored, lava-colored, dark wine, garnet-colored, soft wine blush, burgundy, pallid sanguine
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the crafter directory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^Crafter Directory*^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br>~ Miss Brie - Master Dyer and Master Tailor.<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Mademoiselle Noe - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Polgara<br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Mistress Pru<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Polgara~<br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Tark-armor smith~<br></br>~Incudine-armor smith<br></br>~Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Clayton-armor smith<br></br>~Bruno-armor smith<br></br>~Virendra-armor smith<br></br>~Natalie-weapon smith<br></br>~Ekalah-weapon smith<br></br>~Bruno-weapon smith<br></br>~Clayton-weapon smith<br></br>~Tark-weapon smith<br></br>~Natalie-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Lidia<br></br>~Caitriona
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of gossip from random gossipmongers.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^GossipMonger*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"Esquire Clover recently entered and left the commons without showing the proper respects to a person of superior rank, despite being greeted. If you're going to play with the big boys, you have to walk the tight rope."<br></br><br></br>"Mister Chesh was inappropriately suggesting smothering dead skinks in Esquire Noe's face, and refused to stand aside from the exit out of the commons. How dreadful for commoners to behave in such a manner; highly disrespectful."<br></br><br></br>"Sticking your nose where it don't belong is one thing. Telling someone not to compliment someone's perfume is a little odd. But implying the girl is a whore is down right mean. You should know better mister."<br></br><br></br>"*tisk tisk* I hear Fyros got Deputy Zaria high on catnip and impaired her ability whilst on duty. How utterly irresponsible of him."<br></br><br></br>"Miss Sable has gone out of her way to take up studying healing techniques while helping others in town purchase fabric and teaching soldiering lessons to the Constabulary on the side, despite her membership in Clover's guild. She shows great talent and is progressing greatly as a person and productive citizen."<br></br><br></br>"When the gorath as having its tantrums, Caitriona rushed off to get the foods to tempt the beast to the docks, and bravely tried to feed the gorath too."<br></br><br></br>"Licking on Carolyn's ear in public, and inviting himself up to her room when she mentioned she was going to go upstairs and work on clothing for someone. Rude, and oh so naughty! How gosh, I wonder who that describes?"<br></br><br></br>"Ilo was unthinking and used an explosive device to free mister chesh from a fallen mast. Now, mister chesh was saved, however the blast injured several allies as well."<br></br><br></br>"Mister Fips is truly a trustworthy man. When he was accidentally sent 136 denarii for a 36 denarii order, he returned the money without hesitation. Honesty and fair dealing are admirable traits, especially in a trade city!"<br></br><br></br>"Rickter defended Flora's honor after Julien verbally attacked her. Don't know if threatening people is the way to do it but he made it clear Julien should treat people properly."<br></br><br></br>"While some details are vague, confessing that she, Gemma,  sometimes lets men see her breasts the first time they meet her is at the very least inappropriate. Lets hope she meant in the bath house."<br></br><br></br>"Zaria's got a mouth on her! Talking about fornication, ew, and pregnancy, yuck, in mixed company with gentry nearby! Light help me!"<br></br><br></br>"Dahlia gives good lessons, helps finish orders of the lesser skilled needleworkers, and works tirelessly to create items for the upcoming party. She is a needleworker with saint like qualities."<br></br><br></br>"Ximen had Sir Matteo removed from his position due to his rudeness to the Church."<br></br><br></br>"Valdus is great at keeping recruits for the Sinners and Saints on their toes -- just ask Darius who randomly got beaten with a backscratcher in the commons."<br></br><br></br>"I hear Matthias isn't always honest with his customers in his line of merchant work. I hear he takes advantage of the less intelligent ones."<br></br><br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
