<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The first page is the table of content, the second page is the story on the trip to Chalon, the third page is the story on the Father Ximen's trial, the fourth page is the interview with Kaine, the fifth page is the constable report, the sixth page is the fashion corner, the seventh page is the crafting directory, the eighth page is the funnies, the ninth page is the social and political life, the tenth page is ongoing story , eleventh page is the stars of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/forestmonster1.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about trip to Chalon. Art done by Gabrielle.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Chalon's party crashers~<br></br><br></br> The ambassador of the Avoirdupois was sent a missive from Chalon requesting aid with their criminal problem. Those that went on the trip (Hanneman, Zanthia, Kruix, Clover, Sable, Rickter, Khagra, Kesla, Zaria, Sylvia, Ilo, Lysandus, Xena, Fyros, Mattimeo, Kilana, Ammy, Sabastien, Chesh) had one major encounter on the way to Chalon, a massive forest. The forest around them attack them as they passed by and reports say that Ilo saved the day by momentarily scaring the forest off via fire. <br></br><br></br> <br></br><br></br>It took the group of good doers a week to get to Chalon after the stressing forest incident. When they got there they hit the streets looking for info. In the market place they learned about the old blood purge were running free in the slums because people were afraid of them. They blatantly killed, stole, and caused general discontent because they could. Reports say that the group dealt with some of these no good sons of grapes by  convincing them to stop being villains, conduct of violence suspected but unconfirmed. Their next stop was at a warehouse that the old blood purge had according to information our friends stole from a red feathered hat man.<br></br><br></br> Good guys set up a camp around the warehouse, at first to watch for anything suspicious. They found suspicious when a group of people went in and came back out carrying a rolled up rug. Clover, Sable, Chesh, Meepers, and Rickter tried to follow the bad guys carrying a rug but sneaky isn't a trait these few possess. Meepers and Sable provided distraction, Clover and Rickter fought bravely against fighting style that has never been seen before, and Chesh rolled the rug back to the groups campout. The distraction seemed to work for Clover and Rickter won the fight, if only a little ego bruising happened. The rug had a body hidden inside of it, a personal friend of Lord Sabastien. The next part of the plan failed horribly. Scouts were told to get on the roof and spy in the building. Kruix is said to have jumped onto the roof and made it collapse, perhaps being the worst spy ever. The rest of the group made a quick plan, half the group went in front, the rest went in back. The people in the front found two hostages being guarded by thugs who were easily dispatched and the hostages heroically saved. The back door people had a tougher time, they found thugs as well but they were trying to put out crates of fire in a panic, it was discovered that these were special firework powders from a foreign land. After saving the warehouse and most of the crates the group tried to capture Gaston, a leader of the old blood purge, but could not apprehend him at the time.<br></br><br></br>From here the group goes to the library because they found a riddle indicating that Gaston had been poking around the records for historic information. Librarys aren't this groups friends, Ilo and Zaria apparently almost got whole group kicked out by being loud and rowdy. The rest of the group found out that Gaston had been looking up who were old nobles and who were related to the archduke d'Avoirdupois. While leaving Meepers and Ilo were stabbed in the ribs by passerbyer's, obviously even in the good parts of Chalon foul play was something to be weary of.<br></br><br></br>After a nights rest we found out the Gaston would be at a party that Lord Sabastien had an invitation to. The group got ready for a party either as guests or as servants, 'Ilo dressed up like a posh female noble and actually pulled it off, well until his boob fell out.' says Lysandus.  At the party the group was split up into smaller cliches to try and find out where Gaston was. Anxious and bored of waiting Lord Sabastien stood on stage and made his announcment calling out Gaston as a coward and villian. Trying to play the hero Cullan dived at the bad guy behind Lord Sabastien (who was trying to kill Sabastien via shooting in the back,) unfortunately Cullan tripped and fell short but brought attention to the attacker who was quickly caught. <br></br><br></br>The archduke graced the party and listened to the tale the group had to tell. After listening to the whole thing the archdueke thanked the group and declared anyone who was associated with the old blood purge to be enemy of Chalon and would be killed on sight. Many of the party goers tried to flee at this announcement but were easily cut down and their family names degraced.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/gavel31_zps518010c2.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is about the trial of Father Ximen.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Inquisitor's turn to burn~<br></br><br></br>A petition by Dame Xena was started some time ago, and while the petition itself if elusive it is said that a good majority of the town signed it. The claims from the people about Father Ximen was that he took bribes, spook to others about confessions, focused on heretics, shunned believers, ect. <br></br><br></br>The higher ups of the church held a trial for the good father, giving him a fair chance to prove his innocence. He came prepared, not with witness but with what he sees of the truth. <br></br>Those present at the trial including, Dame Xena, Esquire Lianaar, Lord Marcus, Esquire Meepers, and even Paladin Khagra spook up against Ximen. The decision came swift and harsh, perhaps not as harsh as some would have liked. Ximen was told that he would get one rank demotion until he proves he can handle the stress. To prove himself he has to rearrange the paladins (probably due to Khagra's outburst in the court) and seek guidance in balance.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~~Kaine, the cat in the wolf den~~<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "First I want to thank you for taking the time to do this interview"<br></br><br></br>Kaine says to Esquire Gabrielle, "You are quite welcome."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle asks Kaine, "First, can you tell me about your childhood?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine , "I don't have any recollection of my childhood. I only have memory from when I first arrived in this city."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Why don't you remember?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "Well I was found out in the woods with a rather serious head injury. I woke in a room in the severed tail and that is how I ended up here. I never regained memory of my life prior to this city."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "What clues did you have on you, of your past?" Kaine says, "I recalled my first name. The last name that I use now is one that I claimed for myself eventually."<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "I believe I also had a club of some sort but I abandoned that long ago."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "What is your last name and what inspired it?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Blackedge. It was rather uninspired...I wield a blade and my fur was black...so, Blackedge."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Have you always been a bisclavret?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Well aside from my first few hours in the city, yes. I was taken into the house my first day in the city, by Lady Georgianna."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "Who were some of the first people you meet in town?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Well, as I just mentioned. Lady Georgianna was the first. I then met several of the Bisclavret members, Sir Twyrch, Lady Kannina, Mister Cullan. I later met others like Mister Sang, Mister Abel. But I wasn't the most social person."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "What positions in your house have you held?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "Well for the longest time I was just a recruit. Eventually I was made Leiutenant and quickly promoted to Captain. Currently, i am Ambassador of the Bisclavret. A Thane. I was Squire to Lord Adrien. You can become anything if you put your mind to it. I do hope to one day reach the rank of Knight."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "What combat skills do you possess?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "Well my primary weapon is my rapier, secondary a pistol. I'm skilled with both, and evasion is one of my primary defensive skills."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "Whom have you learned these skills from?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "I am primarily self taught. Though I did learn some of my early fencing from Mister Abel. I learned a bit from Sir Twyrch and Lord Adrien as well."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "What non combat skills do you have?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Well I am able to ride, and sabering is one of my least used skills. I had a brief stint with being a field medic. But gradually I lost that knowledge to more martial persuits."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Now for the more personal questions. How many relationships of you had?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Well...One. Though I am currently suiting someone."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Who?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Um..Miss Polgara, actually."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "I've heard you name in connection to...a rug. Can you explain."<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "I own one. But I would assume many do."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "Let me explain better, snuggle with rug. Does that ring a bell?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "No I'm afraid it does not."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle asks Kaine, "What is the most heroic thing you've accomplished?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "That is a rather difficult question to answer." Kaine supposes, "The most recent I suppose would be my role in the harrowgate mission."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "What is the most, not so heroic thing, you've ever done?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "I suppose...getting an overly large dose of paralyzing powder and having to be carried to the infirmary like a sack of potatoes.."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "Is there anyone you consider your best friend in town?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "I suppose that Sir Twyrch is one of my oldest friends."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Who would you consider your nemesis?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine  "Well I only have one person that actively wants to kill me. Mister Kafka."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle  "What goals and responsibilities do you have as ambassador?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "Well I do hope to increase the prosperity of the Bisclavret. I have been working very hard to get things running smoothly. It is a challenge but it is attainable goal."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "What's the proudest moment of your life?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "I suppose that would be the day that I was made Captain."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "And your most embarrassing moment?"Kaine "There was an instance where I had been convinced to drink and shortly there after someone put a sprig of catnip up my nose...the result was rather embarrassing."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "How are your houses relation with the other three houses?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "I would like to think we have a strong relationship with the Avoirdupois and our relationship with the Rinaldi is on the mend after a bit of an incident. Our relationship with the Doloreaux is good if a bit distant."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "And your relationship with the other ambassadors?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "I believe that I am on good terms with them."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle "Please give your parting words of wisedom?"<br></br><br></br>Kaine "The sword should always be a last resort. Even your enemy deserves some level of respect."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the constable report page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ---Deaths---<br></br><br></br><br></br>nan<br></br>gren<br></br>rune<br></br>pepper<br></br>oaeo<br></br>zrgt<br></br>shush<br></br><br></br>---Arrest warrant:<br></br>Sir Matteo for the murder of Raz<br></br><br></br>Kruix for the murders of Nan, Shush, Maho, Raz and assault on Razeer<br></br>Damien for assault in the Inn. <br></br> Kakfa for disturbing the peace, theft, and two counts of assault.<br></br>Open Cases:<br></br><br></br>Resisting Arrest, Disrespecting the Constabulary - Case Open - Virendra<br></br>Murder of Nan, Gren and Rune - Case Open - Valdus<br></br>Assisting a Criminal - Case Open - Patrick<br></br>Attempted Murder of Valdus - Case Open - Nan, Rune, Gren<br></br>Murder of Scott and Gwydion - Case Open - Razeer, Patrick<br></br>Murder of Chesh - Case Open - Valdus, Razeer<br></br><br></br>~Militia~<br></br><br></br>The milita bring in wanted criminals and act in the defence of others without having charges filed against them fer their involvement. They must abide by the law and do their guard duties.<br></br> Members of the milita are: Bayard, Hanneman, Kaine, Cullan, Aneira.<br></br><br></br>It is of the utmost importance that when a crime is committed any and all that witness it, report it. Do not rely on others to do so because you can't be certain they will. Should you not wish to contact a Constable directly or you don't know any by name then there is another way. Outside the gaol is a carving of a fox head. You can put what you saw on a scroll and then deposit it into the fox head. Only Constables can retrieve it once it's put in there and it is checked daily by myself.<br></br>If you don't know where the gaol is you head west from the west commons onto Market Street. From there, head north through the market place and into Newtown. The gaol is just north of the cafe and to the west. The fox head is outside the gaol on the street.<br></br><br></br>Thank you for you continued support and cooperation.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             sixth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ On Behalf of All Clothiers of Triskellian ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~\{0\}~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ We offer here a list of what each established clothier in the city is skilled in. A directory of sorts, if you will. WHEN MAKING AN ORDER PLEASE SEND AS MUCH INFORMATION AS YOU CAN. IT MUST INCLUDE: COLOR, MATERIAL, AND GENERAL TYPE. Example: Blue suede  Shoes Belt  Hat Gloves Bag <br></br><br></br>~ Rainbow Rags ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>= Other Clothiers withing the City walls =<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Esquire Meepers, of Sew you Can Sew - Master Seamstress and Dyer.<br></br><br></br>+List of Terminologies+<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Dyer - Mixer of dyes<br></br>- Seamstress - Creator of feminine garments<br></br>- Tailor - Creator of masculine garments<br></br>- Needleworker - Creator of accessories with skills of embroidering<br></br><br></br>~\{0\}~ Favorable Colors this Season ~\{0\}~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br> ~*~ Colors of the Season ~*~<br></br><br></br>cherry blossom pink, the gentle and feminine shade of pink to appease the girl in you.<br></br><br></br> Lavender rose, spring time flowers unite.<br></br><br></br>Canary yellow, happy little birds in a bottle of dye.<br></br><br></br> Strawberry red, who can resist a bright and cherry red?<br></br><br></br>Dark wine-colored,for those who don't like bright and happy reds.<br></br><br></br> Spring Green, how can you have the spring season without spring green?<br></br><br></br> Hunter Green, the masculine version of spring green.<br></br><br></br>Aquamarine, warm weather means it's time to play in the water.<br></br><br></br>Sky blue, when the sky is blue you know it's a good day.<br></br><br></br> bronzed-colored, it's time to tan up in the spring time sun.<br></br><br></br> ~ Happy Springtime, to you from me ~<br></br><br></br>Garment of the month<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-<br></br><br></br>~*~Womens~*~<br></br><br></br>~ Underbust corset.  A decorative corset variation that begins at the bust and extends down to the hips. It is generally worn over blouses or shirts to lend a more attractive shape to the female form.<br></br><br></br>~*~Mens~*~<br></br><br></br>Swordsman pants. Legwear featuring drawstrings at the ankles, as well as right above the knees which can be tightened to lend a puffy and swashbuckling appearance to the wearer, or loosened for a more casual and comfortable look.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the crafter directory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^Crafter Directory*^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Raz~<br></br>~Miss Suchin~<br></br>~Miss Polgara<br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Mistress Pru<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Polgara~<br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Tark-armor smith~<br></br>~Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Clayton-armor smith<br></br>~Natalie-~Clayton-weapon smith<br></br>~Tark-weapon smith<br></br>Black smith~<br></br>~Natalie-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Lady Anelie~<br></br>~Lidia<br></br>~Seened~<br></br><br></br>~Merchants~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Rem~<br></br>~Fips~<br></br>~Aluine~<br></br><br></br>~Healers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Dr. Hush~<br></br>~Physician Suavis~<br></br>~Mattimeo~<br></br>~Nurse Sable~<br></br>~Achyls~<br></br>~Zanthia~
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eighth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eighth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of funnies drawn by Sang
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             http://www.tigerknight.com/ss/ss6-4.jpg<br></br>http://www.kizandjenn.com/sean2/031.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ninth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ninth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the social and political life of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~*~*~*~*~**~*~*Socialites*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*<br></br> The Rinaldi are the most social house with the masquerade ball in a time to be announced and a tea socials on the 28th. The falconry club meetings and hunts for those of rank will be posted when available, reminder that the falconer will sell birds if enough interest in the club is noticed. The Dolreaux will be hosting a single's ball sometime next month too. <br></br><br></br>~*~*~*~*~*~*~*Political~*~*~*~*~*~*~*<br></br>Many of us have noticed a few things going on, like all the manors are finally open. Rejoice. However, though they just opened, the Rinaldi already had a petty theft of silverware. Luckily because of good doers the eating utensils are returned safely. A huge observation hard to miss is the massive ship wrecked into the docks. They have been there for some time, this is the wreck from when the infamous Captain Hooked crashed into Triskellian as a distraction so he could get away.  He did it on purpose, or so we think because of all the spiders onboard. These spiders are massive and mutated and they have spread their nests all over town.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_10" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="tenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             tenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is an ongoing moral story written by a citizen of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *~*~Of Rhiem and Reson*~*~<br></br>-----------------------------------<br></br><br></br>Part One - The Quest for Breakfast<br></br><br></br>The morning sun broke upon a distant hilltop, illuminating the path for a pair of travelers. The first rode a fearsome war-mount and was adorned in gleaming armour, a noble crest proudly displayed upon his shield and banner. The second rode behind him in a small cart pulled behind a pomfrey, clad in drab and simple garments. "Knight-errantry," Sir Rhiem spoke into the clear morning air, "Is a noble occupation, with a long and glorious tradition." "Yes, sire." replied his squire, Reson, "You have mentioned that often." Sir Rhiem continued, "That is because it bears repeating, squire. Consider all the good we have done in the world these past few months." "Yes, sire. I am glad to accompany you. I can think of no better vocation." Sir Rhiem turned and fixed his gaze upon Reson seriously, 'This is no vacation, squire. This is serious business. We are heroes." Reson bowed his head respectfully, "Yes, sire. I shall not forget." Nodding approval, Sir Rhiem replied, 'Very good. How are we set for rations?" "We have enough for several days more, sire." "Pass me a hard roll, then. That breakfast we just partook of was rather unsatisfying." Sir Rhiem accepted the proffered roll, and proceeded to chew on it pensively, apparently lost in thought. "Strange," he mentioned at length, "considering I did not eat less than what my breakfasts normally consist of." "We have been traveling hard this past week, sire. I am sure it has taken its toll. I myself am also still a bit hungry." "Are you? Well, that may be so, then." Sir Rhiem paused for a moment, still in thought. "Probably. We shall see to getting a proper meal at that town just ahead."<br></br><br></br>The town was not large, but did have a modest inn just off the main street, and the Knight and his squire found it easily. As they approached, a group of beggars caught their attention, asking for food. Sir Rhiem peered narrowly at the group, asking, "You are hungry, are you? Your breakfasts were unsatisfying as well?" The eldest beggar, who had not had a breakfast at all in recent memory, replied to him ironically, "No, m'lord, not satisfying at all. I can't remember last time I had one that was." The rest of the beggars nodded in humorous agreement. Sir Rhiem nodded sagely, then contemplated the beggar's words for a time before saying to Reson, "Squire, distribute our rations to these people, we shall fetch some more later." He then turned and proceeded into the inn. Reson did as he was told, passing out the remainder of their food to the grateful group before following his Knight inside. Sir Rhiem stood before a repetitiously bowing inkeeper, giving orders for the care and stabling of their tired mounts, and ordering a moderate meal, which the inkeeper quickly departed to see to.<br></br><br></br> After he left, Sir Rhiem turned again to Reson. "I have a suspicion, squire. Our uncommon hunger is mirrored and apparently long endured by those in this town. It is a coincidence too strange, I think. I suspect some foul sorcery. An evil wizard must have cast an enchantment upon this peaceful village, and cursed its inhabitants, I am sure of it." "Surely there must be some other explanation, sire..." Sir Rhiem nodded gravely, "One would think so, but wizards are subtle. I do not wonder that his ploy has gone unnoticed until now, as everyone always assumes there must be some other explanation." Reson peered incredulously at the Knight, but knew better than to question him after his mind had been decided. At that moment, the inkeeper returned and ushered them toward a table, where their places had already been set. The two sat and enjoyed the meal, conversing sparsely. As the inkeeper was clearing the dishes afterward, Sir Rhiem asked him, "Why was there no bread with the meal?" The inkeeper apologized profusely, explaining, "We have not had bread for some time, good Sir Knight, for our grain is always stolen before it arrives here." <br></br><br></br>At this, Sir Rhiem stood quickly, shouting 'Hunger AND famine?! By S'allumer's beard, this will not stand! That sorcerer will pay, and pay dearly! Settle our bill, squire, then follow. We have a duty to perform." He then proceeds to storm loudly out of the inn, slamming the door behind him. Reson waited for a moment before asking the inkeeper, "Who is stealing the grain?" The inkeeper replied, "The miller lives away on a hill south of town, and we haven't heard from him in a month. One merchant who went out to buy his grain returned nearly dead, warning everyone about a band of rogues out that way. Our Lord's guardsmen have searched for them, but in vain, since the bandits are nowhere to be found when they arrive." Reson considered for a moment, then said to the inkeeper, "I must ask you a favour. I will need a large cloak, old and tattered." The inkeeper looked confused, but complied, providing a dusty old cloak that has obviously seen better days. After paying the inkeeper, Reson followed Sir Rhiem outside, finding him unsuccessfully interrogating several of the beggars. Upon seeing his squire, the Knight turned to him, "It is as I thought. Noone suspects or knows anything about a sorcerer in these parts. Did you discover anything from the inkeeper?" Reson replied tactfully, "Yes, sire. He recommended looking around the hill south of town." "Very well. Good work, squire. Fetch our mounts, then, and we shall be on our way." Reson bowed his head humbly, "If I may say, sire, our mounts have been sorely taxed by our journey, and need rest." Sir Rhiem frowned for a moment, then agreed, "You are right. I do not like the idea of going into a fight without my able war-mount, but he is likely too tired to fight well, anyway. We shall proceed on foot." <br></br><br></br>As they left the town, Sir Rhiem talked occasionally about the dangers of battling wizards, mentioning, "We must be cautious as we approach, squire. An errant thunderbolt or some such danger may find the unwary." Reson spoke opportunely, asking, "Would you not make a chief target if you are seen, clad in armour as you are? You are quite imposing, sire." Sir Rhiem admitted with some alarm, "You are entirely correct. Were I a sorcerer, I would not let myself approach at all. And my armour can do little to ward spells." At this, Reson offered the tattered old cloak to the Knight, saying, "If I may suggest then, sire, you should conceal yourself. This old cloak should cover your armour well." Sir Rhiem glared distainfully at the cloak for a moment before donning it, entirely concealing his knightly armament. He replied, "I do not favour subtle methods, squire, but in this case it may be necessary." They walked southward for some time before Reson pointed out a large windmill atop a hill, "There, sir, do you see it? Do you suppose the conjurer is there? I recall they are often fond of such solitary locations."<br></br><br></br> Peering toward the windmill, Sir Rhiem informed his squire, "No, it is only a windmill. No self-respecting evil wizard would cower in a windmill, they usually have grand towers or some similar lair." "Exactly, sire. Noone would expect a sorcerer in a windmill, and I see no wizard's towers." Suddenly struck with realization, Sir Rhiem exclaimed, "Indeed! A clever guise wrought with conjured illusions, then! Oh, this wizard is a crafty one, to be sure. I nearly fell for it." He stormed off immediately in the direction of the mill, with Reson following behind. Before they got even halfway there, however, they were ambushed and surrounded by a half-dozen ill-intentioned miscreants, the largest one approached them with a swagger. Before he could speak, Sir Rhiem threatened him preemptively, "I am Sir Rhiem, Knight-Errant. Stand aside, and I shall spare you." The bandit leader, seeing only Sir Rhiem's tattered cloak, disbelieved him. He glanced amusedly at his fellows, then laughed loudly at the Knight, "You are naught but a pair of penniless vagrants!" Sir Rhiem, barely containing his rage, snarled, "You will not stop us from reaching the sorcerer, fool. You are outmatched. He should have sent an army, not a petty band of henchmen." The bandit leader's expression quickly alternated between insult and utter bewilderment, then brief fear as Sir Rhiem threw open his cloak, drew his sword and slew him with a single thrust. The brigand immediately to the Knight's left tried to attack him unawares, and was also cut down instantly. The rest fled, then, as quickly as they could. Sir Rhiem, unperturbedly wiping blood from his blade, said, "Cowards, the lot of them. That spell-mumbler was foolish to rely on such mercenaries." <br></br><br></br>Shortly thereafter they reached the mill, and the Knight kicked the door open wide, rushing in, sword drawn, to confront a very surprised miller. The miller opened his mouth to say something, but Sir Rhiem quickly interrupted him, shouting, "Silence, conjurer! You'll cast no devious magicks at me!" The miller remained silent and wore a terrified and terribly confused expression. Sir Rhiem spoke again, "Your reign of fear has come to an end, wizard. You will no longer afflict these good people with your foul enchantments." The miller stammered, "I..I.. am j..just a miller..." Sir Rhiem sneered at him, "A clever ploy, but your illusions do not fool me. Cease your spells or I will end you." The miller, utterly confused, muttered earnestly, "I.. I'm sorry..." Reson then spoke up, suggesting politely to Sir Rhiem, "Sire, he seems quite contrite. Perhaps it is not necessary to kill him." At this, the miller nodded emphatically. Reson continued, "Imagine, sire, the good he could do if he applied his skills and knowledge to helping the townsfolk. I am sure he could be persuaded to do so." Sir Rhiem considered this carefully, never taking his eyes from the miller, who looked confused, frightened and hopeful at once. Eventally he addressed the miller, "So be it. Your guise, then, shall be your punishment, conjurer. You shall stay as a miller, and bend your sorceries to such work. As you caused hunger, so shall you abate it." The miller nodded eager agreement, "As you say, my Lord. I shall diligently work my craft to feed the village." Sir Rhiem nodded also, "Good. Start immediately. And If I hear word of you doing otherwise, I shall return, and I shall not be so merciful." With one last glare of warning, he walked out. <br></br><br></br>Reson followed his Knight back to town, where they fetched their gear and mounts, bought provisions, and prepared to continue thier journey. Sir Rhiem sought out the lieutenant of the guardsmen and explained what transpired, warning him to keep an eye on the miller, in case he should try such malevolent sorceries again. The lieutenant looked askance at the Knight, but thanked him respectfully, saying, "Yes, those ...henchmen of his have been causing trouble for some time. On behalf of the townspeople, and the Lord of this village, I thank you for your service." Reson remained silent throughout.<br></br><br></br>And so Rhiem and Reson departed, off to find another quest somewhere along the road ahead...
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_11" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eleventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eleventh"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             tenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of gossips about the good Samaritans of the city.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^Good Samaritans*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"Sable risked her own life in order to obtain the spider silk needed for the sylphs. Brave and heroic deed of her."<br></br><br></br>"Mister Hanneman managed to keep a level head during an expedition to the swamp to get several ingredients for the cure of the unwanted spirits in two Avoirdupois members, despite there being several disfavourable influences on the trip; such as Ilo taunting Noe and the Avoirdupois. He came up with several ideas to get by the obstacles, such as scouting for more information and creating a phalanx to get through the vines into the swamp in the first place! Good work, guardsman."<br></br><br></br> "Poor guy seemed to have extremely bad luck when it came to keeping a hold of his shoes in Harrowgate, but that didn't deter Lysandus from being good support to the group as a whole when it came to fighting the Minkers and their elementals. He cheered us on with ample spirit, came up with brilliant ideas (such as digging under the giant blue wall of fire and creating the net to catch would-be victims of the wind tunnel with Gemma) and dispatched the foes in our way with the use of his sword arm. Such a good bloke!"<br></br><br></br>"Stacy went to fight those nasty blood sucking vampires and did a good job. Or so they say."<br></br><br></br>"Valdus fought gamely, leaping onto a sea serpent's back. Not smart, definitely not smart, but brave."<br></br><br></br>"Miss Lys was ever brave and helpful on the swamp expedition, her healing was a viatal part of why as many people made it back alive as they did."<br></br><br></br>"Miss Gemma was a calming presence and surprisingly a knowledgable support on calling the spirits. She accompanied Dean Dylan to the docks to summon the air sylphs. It's too bad she's stuck in a dead-end job, or she could have a real future as a summoner and elemental scholar."<br></br><br></br>"Brie gives free pie! Need I clarify?"<br></br><br></br>"Miss Polgara saw someone was obviously distressed and stepped in to attempt to help. Her efforts proved to unveil that the young man was being pressed into virtual slavery by another individual due to a minor incident. Polgara offered him compensation and said she would inform the local Constabulary of the issue. Her good deeds and willingness to step in when she sees a wrong are something which all should aspire towards."<br></br><br></br>"Even though it's her job, miss Natalie took on a very large order for twenty trophies, each with individualized engravings! It's good to know that crafters don't just do the work, but sometimes enjoy it too!"<br></br><br></br> "Khagra is an apt warrior, he proved both skill and bravery during the expedition for the spider egg to stop the spider itch epidemic."<br></br><br></br>"Kaine, Ambassador of the Bisclavret, was kind enough to arrange carpenters for the rebuilding of the swamp people's home and even worked alongside them to make sure they were doing their job properly while neglecting his own rest."<br></br><br></br>"Sir Bayard reportedly protected Doctor Hush on her way to healing the injured during the bandit attack. His strength and martial abilities ensured the survival of many allies!"<br></br><br></br>"Dame Xena really put herself at risk, offering to be kidnapped by bandits and managing to pull it off without the death of herself or anyone of importance."<br></br><br></br>"Sir Alvaro is a true Knight. His bravery when facing the two-headed alligator was commendable, and he didn't hesitate one moment when Esquire Noe was severely hurt by the beast, jumping in between her and the alligator as it turned to attack her, protecting her from further injury and harm. The Avoirdupois are fortunate to have him among their numbers."<br></br><br></br>"Though mister Rune comes across as cowardly in the face of ship travel, he persevered and even fought pirates at the risk of his own life to return the stolen item that, in its absence, caused the vines to begin destroying the docks."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K", 1354853763, "meandmine", "K", 1354942697, "meandmine", "K", 1354945930, "meandmine", "K", 1354949099, "meandmine", "K", 1354949332, "meandmine", "E", 1354949364, "meandmine", "K", 1354949373, "meandmine", "E", 1355259036, "meandmine", "K", 1355259762, "meandmine", "K", 1355259767, "meandmine", "E", 1355259860, "meandmine", "K", 1355260025, "meandmine", "K", 1355260127, "meandmine", "K", 1355267403, "meandmine", "K", 1355281790, "meandmine", "K", 1357690626, "meandmine", "K", 1357692638, "meandmine", "K", 1357692747, "meandmine", "K", 1358310543, "meandmine", "K", 1358312544, "meandmine", "K", 1358320455, "meandmine", "K", 1358321566, "meandmine", "K", 1358325444, "meandmine", "K", 1358328295, "meandmine", "K", 1358331132, "meandmine", "K", 1358331762, "meandmine", "K", 1358332027, "meandmine", "K", 1358332059, "meandmine", "K", 1358332124, "meandmine", "K", 1358332578, "meandmine", "K", 1358332592, "meandmine", "E", 1358332619, "meandmine", "K", 1358908973, "meandmine", "K", 1360909601, "meandmine", "K", 1362049202, "meandmine", "K", 1362103954, "meandmine", "K", 1362872017, "meandmine", "K", 1362875584, "meandmine", "K", 1362876726, "meandmine", "K", 1363927594, "meandmine", "K", 1366999186, "meandmine", "K", 1366999373, "meandmine", "K", 1367000338, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
