<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The first page is the table of content, the second page is the story on the trip to Bruges, the third page is the giant spider autopsy, the fourth page is the interview with Ximen, the fifth page is the constable report, the sixth page is the fashion corner, the seventh page is the crafting directory, the eighth page is the funnies, the ninth page is the gossipermonger.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/monster_artwork_3.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about trip to Bruges. Art done by Sang.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Kids in Cages~<br></br><br></br> The ambassador of the Doloreaux received a note asking for help in Bruges the capital city of the Doloreaux. The people in Bruges are currently dealing with the same demons that those in Triskellian just defeated.  The brave heroes, Sir Bayard, Clover lePlow, Acting Sheriff Zaria, Fyros Fulke of the Sinners and Saints, Dasha di Silvi, Rickter Doloreaux Triskellian Ambassador, Paladin Nuiros, Sang of the Triskellian University, Ilo, Prion, Chesh (serf of Doctor Hush and Fips) left on a five day trip that would prove to be a challenge to their resolve and their health.<br></br><br></br>On the way up there our heroes met a strange beast. This beast was named 'the leech monster' (as shown in the popup picture) and was described as a massive leech walking on small feet. Sir Bayard further describes the beast, "I think the strangest thing was that it seemed to emit this strange gas that caused certainly individuals to be drawn to it obsessively. They would walk toward it, try to touch it and things. They continued to be drawn to it, even as it attacked them and burnt them with it's acidic flesh." Reports say that they group eventually defeated this beast after several injuries to the party.<br></br><br></br>The group finally makes it the gates of Bruges where they find a full days rest due to a long waiting time to check in at the gates.  While they waited the group encountered another new monster, "the snowbeast". It's described as a large furry ball of fury with teeth. According to Fyros, he had come across a hut with a man inside manipulating a globe, it apparently created the snowbeast that attacked us and the ones we learned later on that were inside the city. It was large and vicious, covered in fur as white as snow. When asked how to defeat a snow beast the general answer was brute force. <br></br><br></br>According to Zaria, "We had a hard time getting through the gates because Clover tried to assert his dominance and speak to the person in charge. It didn't make a difference, except for the fact we wasted nine hours for nothing." After said nine hours the group made it into the city where they broke up and looked for information. The following is what the group learned, "The Thieves guild, men wearing black and red feathered hats, were stealing children from their beds and smuggling them away to be turned into assassins. When the children were seen again they attempted in turn to kill you. Nobles had been randomly killed as well. Things got worse when they refused to give the thieves the land and rights they were demanding and it was the night we arrived that the ice monsters were set loose inside the city."  Sang and Ilo went undercover as a thief guild member displaced from Triskellian. After proving their worth with a local watermelon sales man, the two were able to find out where the thieves guild was and leaked info to the group by pretending to pick pocket the group.<br></br><br></br>Sang details what happened, "Well, we learned that the entrance to the thieves hideout was in a crypt in the graveyard. We went down there and discovered all the children they'd kidnapped kept in cages. We realized we had the choice, we could either kill leaders or save the children. I might have upset a few by not even talking the idea over and just going and saving the children." So our heroes save the day and children and make their way home.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/step10.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the follow up story about the giant spiders. Art drawn by Esquire Gabrielle.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Larger than life Spiders~<br></br><br></br>Many of you may have noticed large blue, green, and red spiders around town. These spiders are around 9 feet tall and appear aggressive. According to Nurse Sable these spiders attack the upper body because it is all they can reach. When asked how the spiders get so big she replied with, 'It's their nature, these specific spiders get large because it's how they breed.'<br></br><br></br> Sable also mentioned she dissected one of these large spiders and described the autopsy for me. (the popup is Gabrielle's take on said description). The spider has clear blood with strings of tissue connecting the inside of the spider. There is also an sac of unknown purpose alongside the poison sac. It is inconclusive if the spider is poisonous to people but it is likely not.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~~Ximen-The man behind the cloth~~<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "First I want to thank you for taking the time to do this interview"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "I will admit. I find it unusual to be the one answering questions. It is usually my position to get the answers."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "And what is your position within the church?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "As you know I am a Presbyter, which in the terms of the church puts me at the equivalent position of armigerous gentry. I am also the representative of the church here in Triskellian, which would be the same as an ambassador from any of the Houses. On top of this I am High Inquisitor of the Holy S'allumarian Inquisition.<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "I see. Can you tell me who else are officials of the church here in Triskellian?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "We have many officials coming through various parishes. Currently you may meet with Bishop Yarwoodle or Father Obano. Of course Triskellian is the home of the Holy See, the highest of our officials, and a great number of our upper echelons, but it is very unlikely that you will be able to meet them."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Lets get some background on you. Can you tell me about your child hood."<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "I was raised in a monastery quite far from here. I was there for a great many years until I decided to become a priest rather than a monk so I came to Triskellian to join the seminary here."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "What of your birth parents?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "Quiet and strict. As well taking a as vow of silence many of the brothers also followed the way of Haimorr. Misbehavior was not tolerated and I was taught the virtues of complete devotion to the Light."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Do you convey the lessons you were taught to those seeking spiritual aid?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "I believe we all have our skills and talents, and an intended duty to perform for S'allumer. It became quite obvious that my talents are best suited to stamping out evil where I find it and bringing the Light to the darkness by any means necessary. Some lack the means to able to do as I do. They are of no less value, they simply have a different duty to fulfill. Not many other priests have the ability to make the walls have ears and have eyes everywhere. Even fewer have the heart to do what must be done with the heretic. I forgot to mention, with my duties I have assumed a new role. I can perform resurrections and cleansing rituals as I have followed the meditations of the white mages. You should note that I do not only take life away, but I can return it to those worthy."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Oh And how do you gauge the worthiness of the deceased?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "I don't. S'allumer does. We perform the ritual, but He chooses who shall be returned and who shall not. Some are cast out of His Light, some achieve ascension and those that remain are returned to the mortal realm to complete their duty."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Can you tell me the most inspirational experience you've had in the church?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "I have been killed twice in my service to S'allumer. Once by the heretic Xavios and once by the lunatic Kafka, both times I was returned. Especially with my last resurrection I felt that I had been returned specifically to do my duty as Inquisitor. And I shall not stop until the last breath is dragged from my body and S'allumer in His infinite wisdom chooses to not return me. Being returned to life; that is my most inspirational experience."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "What is the most horrific story you can tell me?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "Many years ago there was a man by the name of Dio Goldengate. He was a terrible man, a monster by any standards. He once killed a child and scattered her remains over the city. He died. Then he came back, but he was not brought back by the white mages. No, he was returned by a Necromancer as a hideous and twisted mockery of life. His heart had been torn from his chest, leaving a gaping chasm and malformed wings had sprouted from his back. He was truly a horror to behold. I performed that exorcism, banishing him from the mortal realms."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Lets get some statics, in your service how many exorcisms, confessionals, burning of heretics, and blessings have you done?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "In my duties across the continent I have performed more than can be counted. I have set entire villages to the torch and flame because of their evil corruption. I have hunted down demons and stamped out blasphemy across the lands. After a year of this the Holy See saw fit to call me back to Triskellian so that I might apply my methods here."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "I have hard from gossip your name linked with Adriana. Whom is she to you?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "She was a Prelate here when I first came to seminary, when I was young and hot-headed. I too have heard that gossip, there is some kernel of truth there, but most of it has been greatly exaggerated. When she left here we were once again on more amicable terms."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "I was asked to ask you this. What is your favorite wood to burn heretics with?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "Birch, it burns the hottest."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "In your words can you explain how the gossip and the truth differ? And for the readers do you mind stating what the rumor is?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "The rumor is that I did her some great harm. This is not true. What I did do was allow for a man not of sound mind to believe that he must do her a harm. This I freely admit, and have confessed to my superiors. I was, of course, duly punished. Even then I do not believe I was punished enough. I follow the way of Haimorr myself."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Do you have any words of wisdom or advice for the readers?"<br></br><br></br>Presbyter Ximen: "Be faithful, be obedient, confess your sins. S'allumer is always watching. The Inquisition is watching too."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the constable report page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ---Deaths---<br></br><br></br>Dame Valara d'Avoirdupois<br></br>Clover lePlow<br></br>Milli<br></br>Iain<br></br>Maho<br></br>Raz<br></br><br></br>---Arrest warrant:<br></br>Luciano, closed case, warrant issued<br></br><br></br>Open Cases:<br></br><br></br>maho and iain open murder cases- no known suspects<br></br>fishermiggers open cases  disturbing the peace, assault and kidnapping<br></br>Raz open murder case- Sir Matteo suspect
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             sixth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ On Behalf of All Clothiers of Triskellian ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~\{0\}~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ We offer here a list of what each established clothier in the city is skilled in. A directory of sorts, if you will. WHEN MAKING AN ORDER PLEASE SEND AS MUCH INFORMATION AS YOU CAN. IT MUST INCLUDE: COLOR, MATERIAL, AND GENERAL TYPE. Example: Blue suede  Shoes Belt  Hat Gloves Bag <br></br><br></br>~ Rainbow Rags ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>= Other Clothiers withing the City walls =<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Esquire Meepers, of Sew you Can Sew - Master Seamstress and Dyer.<br></br><br></br>+List of Terminologies+<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Dyer - Mixer of dyes<br></br>- Seamstress - Creator of feminine garments<br></br>- Tailor - Creator of masculine garments<br></br>- Needleworker - Creator of accessories with skills of embroidering<br></br><br></br>~\{0\}~ Favorable Colors this Season ~\{0\}~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br> ~*~ Colors of the Season ~*~<br></br><br></br>Azure mist, a lovely light shade of blue.<br></br><br></br> Cornflower blue, wintry, yet vibrant.<br></br><br></br>Holly red, reminscent of mistletoe, naturally.<br></br><br></br> Garnet-Colored, for the sultry who like the less perky red.<br></br><br></br>Pine green, makes one think of the scent of tall fir trees.<br></br><br></br> Dark feldgrau, muddy green for the little boy that resides in every man's heart.<br></br><br></br> Plum-Colored, that's right. For the visions of sugarplums, dancing in their heads.<br></br><br></br>Dark chocolate, mmmm.... Chocolate.<br></br><br></br>Snow white, that damnable fluff from the clouds.<br></br><br></br> Metallic-gold, for the pretties on your tree.<br></br><br></br> ~ A merry Yuletide, to you from me ~<br></br><br></br>Garment of the month<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-<br></br><br></br>~*~Womens~*~<br></br><br></br> Under loved petal gown. Feminine yet elegant, this gown is largely overlooked in its fanciness, for either more revealing gowns, or for a more serious look. This gown is perfect for any sort of winter social.<br></br>Petal gown (6 yards) - A sleeveless gown bearing eight large, overlapping, triangular petals which fall from the low waistline to the feet. The bodice is princess cut to accommodate the curviest of figures, while the deep v-shaped back can be left open or trimmed with decorative lacing for a more interesting look.<br></br><br></br>~*~Mens~*~<br></br><br></br>Comfortable, yet dressy enough to impress that special someone, the peascot doublet is the perfect men's coat for the winter season.<br></br>A  peascod doublet (4 yards). A traditional doublet bearing the characteristic shape of a pot belly. It features a stiff, tight underlining, buckram to make the protruding shape, and padding to hold it out. A peplum decorates the lower portion of the garment with small wings surrounding the armholes and hiding the points that are used to tie on the sleeves.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the crafter directory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^Crafter Directory*^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Raz~<br></br>~Miss Suchin~<br></br>~Miss Polgara<br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Mistress Pru<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Polgara~<br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Tark-armor smith~<br></br>~Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Clayton-armor smith<br></br>~Mercy-armor smith<br></br>~Natalie-weapon smith<br></br>~Clayton-weapon smith<br></br>~Tark-weapon smith<br></br>~Mercy-Black smith~<br></br>~Natalie-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Lady Anelie~<br></br>~Lidia<br></br>~Seened~<br></br><br></br>~Merchants~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Rem~<br></br>~Fips~<br></br>~Aluine~<br></br>~Sable~<br></br><br></br>~Healers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Dr. Hush~<br></br>~Physician Suavis~<br></br>~Mattimeo~<br></br>~Nurse Sable~<br></br>~Achyls~<br></br>~Zanthia~
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eighth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eighth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of funnies drawn by Sang
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             http://www.tigerknight.com/ss/ss5-24.jpg<br></br>http://www.tigerknight.com/ss/ss6-1.jpg<br></br>http://www.kizandjenn.com/sean2/002.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ninth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ninth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of gossip from Suchin.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^GossipMonger*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"It is rumored that a certain snow leopard that is engaged to a certain ambassador was heard talking about the wild escapades she shared with a limp eared rabbit in her bedroom. Why would anyone want to talk about that in public, if I was her housemates I would be ashamed."<br></br><br></br>"Leave it to that perverted wolf to go around grabbing on women in public. And not in a good way, I'm told."<br></br><br></br>"The heavy accented weasel that we all know engaged in indecent acts with mister a certain Dean in the boarding house, licking the chest of mister the Dean and eying his private regions. When asked to stop, and asked twice, they didn't stop, but just laughed."<br></br><br></br>"The women have started to complain about a certain feline jeweler, insisting that she latches onto any man that appears to garner any interest from another female. It's no wonder people have difficulty keeping relationships intact with her dirty paws always in the way."<br></br><br></br>"Coming out of a private room with with that lecherous Rinaldi Knight? Alone? How low a certain ship  captain must have fallen to spend private time alone with a Knight of such ill repute."<br></br><br></br>"A whole hour late, the carrot munching constable managed to make it to the meeting for his promotion to Deputy in the Constabulary. Better to make it than not make it all, I suppose. Lets hope this promotion brings with it some better time-keeping."<br></br><br></br>"I heard some folks talking about that snow leopard Doloreaux guard and the one eared Doctor... apparently, the two of them were acting -very- suspicious in the commons earlier, and he had his hand where it shouldn't be. That's just not proper behavior for a public area! A member of House Doloreaux ought to know better than that, as should a Doctor of the city. What were they thinking?"<br></br><br></br>"That wolf lass that was a recent girlfriend of the self professed lord of Docktown? If you feel you need a lap warmer, she might be the one to ask. I heard she is free to sit on men's laps in the commons. Though you might get slapped if you try. Lasses are fickle things."<br></br><br></br>"A Noble invests in the Sailors Guild - that, at least, would be somewhat reasonable, but to actually take over the guild directly? The guild of sometimes honest (usually not) sailors, smugglers, dockside petty criminals -- the home of the basest born? It's disgraceful for a Noble to publicly and officially run such a guild, as it's such roles that differentiate common born and Noble born."<br></br><br></br>"The Knight and past Ambassador of the Doloreeaux was overheard talking poorly about the Rinaldi to mister a certain panther serf, shortly after a Rinaldi Baron was telling of the embassy working on repairing the damage to Docktown. To say the Rinaldi don't care about their city when they're obviously working on fixing it is hardly appropriate, nor is it befitting of a Noble to gossip thusly with commoners."<br></br><br></br>"S'allumer is the most important, right? Right! But some do not wish to learn of him! A certain womanizing dingo picked whispering to a whore instead of learning of the light. Doesn't he know, S'allumer sees all?"<br></br><br></br>"Did you see the clothing a certain scantily clad bunny was wearing at the Bisclavret banquet? Sharing your culture is one thing, but dressing like a Maison worker is another."<br></br><br></br>"For a Knight, a certain lecherous Rinaldi of said rank sure isn't acting like one. Apparently he rather obviously suggested to bed a certain dashing fox not long ago, and, despite her telling him off and saying she'd not do that, he made a comment about being allowed to dream. She's gentry, so any kind of relationship like that outside of wedlock is most inappropriate. I wonder what the Rinaldi think about all this?!"<br></br><br></br>"The local panther Ambassador was mean when he unnecessarily told Natalie that the doctors had to preform surgery to feed her and making it sound horrific when it was just a little hole and tube used that caused her little pain."<br></br><br></br>"The wife of a certain panther serf was inappropriately suggesting smothering dead skinks in a certain Avoirdupois Gentry's face, and refused to stand aside from the exit out of the commons. How dreadful for commoners to behave in such a manner; highly disrespectful."<br></br><br></br>"A certain limp eared rabbit refused to let a certain Rags dealer heal him, despite a wound to his face, because it wasn't the local mercenary guild leader. When you're hurt don't insult someone who is trying to save your life, next time they might not."<br></br><br></br>"Detestable! The Lieutenant of the Bisclavret was heard leading a conversation on cannibalism in public. What an offensive subject, and to go as far as discussing the actual consumption of people and the possibility of using their skins for leather? Better keep an eye on this one."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K", 1354853763, "meandmine", "K", 1354942697, "meandmine", "K", 1354945930, "meandmine", "K", 1354949099, "meandmine", "K", 1354949332, "meandmine", "E", 1354949364, "meandmine", "K", 1354949373, "meandmine", "E", 1355259036, "meandmine", "K", 1355259762, "meandmine", "K", 1355259767, "meandmine", "E", 1355259860, "meandmine", "K", 1355260025, "meandmine", "K", 1355260127, "meandmine", "K", 1355267403, "meandmine", "K", 1355281790, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
