<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="killandra">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             First page is the table of content<br></br>Second page is crafter directory <br></br>Third page is the story of the Cannibal Goat<br></br>Fourth page is the story on the Rinaldi Formal Hunt<br></br>Fifth page is the interview with Baron Azru<br></br>Sixth page is the constable report<br></br>Seventh page is the fashion corner<br></br>Eight page is the Life page<br></br>Ninth page is the funnies<br></br>Tenth page is the Guild page<br></br>Eleventh page is the Bisclavret page<br></br>Twelfth page is the Avoirdupois page<br></br>Thirteenth page is the Rinaldi page<br></br>Fourteenth page is the Doloreaux page<br></br>Fifteenth page is the stars of Triskellian.<br></br><br></br>Editor and compiler is Gabrielle vits Chantal, esquire d'Avoirdupois.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/directory.png
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is a crafter directory (examine to see pop-up).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^CrafterDirectory *^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Flora - Master Needleworker and Tailor<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br>~ Miss Landa -Master Seamstress<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Miss Kyla<br></br>~Miss Pru<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br>~Miss Kyla<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Mister Claton-armor smith<br></br>~Mister Ekalah-armor smith<br></br>~Miss Natalie-weapon smith<br></br>~Mister Claton-weapon smith<br></br>~Mister Ekalah-weapon smith<br></br>~Miss Natalie-Black smith<br></br>~Miss Odela-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Caitriona<br></br>~Mister Elvin<br></br>~Miss Kievas<br></br><br></br>~Merchants~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Rem<br></br>~Mister Fips<br></br>~Miss Alana<br></br>~Miss Aiko<br></br><br></br>~Gardening~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Mister Fips<br></br>~Mister Jorgen<br></br>~Miss Lexie<br></br>~Miss Trinity<br></br>~Miss Shade<br></br><br></br>~Hairstyling~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Landa<br></br>~Miss Nan<br></br>~Miss Electris<br></br>~Miss Elizabeth<br></br><br></br>~Tattooist~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Kyla<br></br>~Miss Shahir<br></br><br></br>~Healers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Dr. Hush<br></br>~Physician Suavis<br></br>~Nurse Sable<br></br>~Miss Trinity<br></br>~Mister Mattimeo<br></br>~Mister Legion<br></br>~Mister Fyros<br></br>~Mister Nyko<br></br>Mister Cullan
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/goat_on_fire_small.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about a cannibal goat.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *~*~*~*~* Cannibal Goat *~*~*~*~*~*~*~<br></br><br></br>On Snow 7th a horrific crime came to a sad ending. It is long standing knowledge that a goat by the name of Patrick is both a criminal and cannibal and thus became known as the cannibal goat. His arrest record is long and includes at least three murders, assault with intent to murder, and disturbing the peace.<br></br>Knowing his background doesn't make his latest crime any easier to understand. He kidnapped and tortured two young woman by the names of Anastasyia and Nan claiming they were to pay for the sins of the city, that everyone must witness their suffering to understand their own wrong doings.<br></br>He kept the girls at least three days and caused a wide-spread panic through the city via the couriers. He sent two infamous 'horror packages' that contained proof that he was torturing the girls and that they were still alive. He sent on package to Mersai and the other to Kilana, both of which were close friends to Anastasyia.<br></br> For three days, search parties flooded the city in hopes of finding signs of Patrick and his victims. It wasn't until the 7th that Mersai was walking in the seedy part of docktown when he heard screaming. He immediately went for help, gathering as many people as possible to help with the danger he assumed to be Patrick. His assumption was right for the rescue party found an out of the way boarding house where Patrick was staying, the screaming was coming from the room he was renting. Knocking on the door provided to be both wise and dangerous because the pressure of being found provoked his next action.<br></br>He set Ana and Nan on fire and threw them out his door before stepping through the flames and smoke wielding an axe like some monstrous nightmare. While Kilana and others subdued and eventually killed the cannibal goat others put out the flames raging on the girls. Both girls are in critical health in the infirmary with a very long recovery in front of them. It is suspected that the horrors of the cannibal goat are over, for now.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/DVSeonaSpiderForest.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is about the Rinaldi Hunt. Art done by Esquire Gabrielle.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ^^^^^ Rinaldi's Formal Hunt ^^^^^^<br></br>On Yule 31 Lady Antonia, the Rinaldi's Dame, hosted a formal hunt. She graciously invited all inside the city to attend. In attendance were some prominent members of high soceity including Lady Antonia herself, the new lady of the Rinaldi Dame Ravenna, as well as the knight Sir Matteo. Many people gathered to relish in the event which was held just outside the city walls in the nearby forest.<br></br>After embarking into the forest the large group split into skilled hunters and casual hunters. The idea was to keep the more dangerous animals to the more experienced of the group. The casual group included the dames, their servants, and non violent commoners. Without a wealth of seasoned fighters they faced a wild dray that would not be killed. The group triumphantly killed birds and would be bandits that populate the forest. After ruthlessly dispatching the bandits a witch hut was found. She is described as mysterious yet normal and best if left alone. <br></br>The seasoned fighters fought a wild dray as well and were able to put the beast down so that it's meat and skin could be used. Then Mister Fyros scouted out in the wild fields to search out a spider infestation. Fyros was able to lead the group to a cave where swarms of ghost spiders resided. These spiders were slain so that their leader the matriarch ghost spider could be killed to stop the infestation. <br></br>Sir Matteo was able to be the bait needed so the rest of the group could hack and slash the queen to death. Mister Brenenr and Miss Trinity are given special thanks for saving Sir Matteo's life. Mister Brenner pulled the good knight to safety and Trinity took Matteo's place and ended up getting poisoned. <br></br>All in all the hunt was a blast and provided chances for hunters to bond and get out of the city for a brief time.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             @#@#@#@#@#@#@#@#@ Bloody Business and Apologies: The story of Baron Azru MacMagnus de Bisclavret @#@#@#@#@#@@#@#@#@##@#<br></br><br></br>Gabrielle: I want to thank you for taking this time to tell me about yourself. I'm sure my reader will enjoy learning about you.<br></br>Baron Azru: Perhaps.<br></br>Gabrielle: I'm sure of it. These questions should explain some of the reasons you are who you are. I’d like you to state your full name and title for my readers.<br></br>Baron Azru: Baron Azru MacMagnus de Bisclavret.<br></br>Gabrielle: Can you tell me who your immediate family is?<br></br>Baron Azru: Just my mother Baroness Nara MacMagnus de Bisclavret.<br></br>Gabrielle: You don't know who your father was? No siblings?<br></br>Baron Azru: My father Baron Darroch MacMagnus de Bisclavret, is deceased, has been for nearly 8 years now.<br></br>Gabrielle: I'm sorry for your loss. How did he die?<br></br>Baron Azru: He was on a peace mission in the Phelan lands and was invited into a trap and killed along with most of his guardsmen.<br></br>Gabrielle: Is that a common occurrence?<br></br>Baron Azru: Killing Bisclavret? Yes, that is pretty common for the Phelan.<br></br>Gabrielle: How old are you by the way?<br></br>Baron Azru: Early thirties.<br></br>Gabrielle: So he died in your mid-twenties?<br></br>Baron Azru: Yes.<br></br>Gabrielle: What is your earliest memory?<br></br>Baron Azru: I guess it would probably be playing with children in the city.<br></br>Gabrielle: How old were you and what were you playing?<br></br>Baron Azru: It was probably some game of tag or hide and seek, as for my age I could not venture to guess.<br></br>Gabrielle: I'm guessing you had a good education?<br></br>Baron Azru: I believe some would debate the merits of military schooling versus traditional education, but yes, I am educated.<br></br>Gabrielle: Which military school did you attend and how long where you in school?<br></br>Baron Azru: The Harrowsgate school of Military Tactics and Strategy from the age of 6 till 16.<br></br>Gabrielle: Can you tell us about your favorite mischief you had at school?<br></br>Baron Azru: That would be the meat pie on the instructor's seat. I got in so much trouble.<br></br>Gabrielle: What did you do after school?<br></br>Baron Azru: War games.<br></br>Gabrielle: What was your favorite game?<br></br>Baron Azru: capture the flag.<br></br>Gabrielle:  Did you get any honors in school?<br></br>Baron Azru: Hmm there weren't actual honors per say but I was chosen to lead one of the military enactments once.<br></br>Gabrielle: Once you left school at the age of 16 what did you do?<br></br>Baron Azru: Started learning how to run a city with my Father.<br></br>Gabrielle: In which city?<br></br>Baron Azru: My family runs the city of Merza.<br></br>Gabrielle: What did your father have you doing to help him?<br></br>Baron Azru: Everything, taxes, imports, military, gatherings.<br></br>Gabrielle: In the time you served under your father did you have hobbies or a love life?<br></br>Baron Azru: I became a guardian of the Granvert.<br></br>Gabrielle: Can you describe what the purpose of guarding the Granvert is for those who may not know?<br></br>Baron Azru: We keep the peace between the Bisclavret and the Phelan around the Granvert forest and the Lochlan mountains. Gabrielle: What is it like to guard the Granvert?<br></br>Baron Azru: Well just like any military position it is all of those things. Most of the time the Phelan behave themselves and we don't need to interact, but there are occasions when they feel the need to break our arrangements.<br></br>Gabrielle: Is it one of these broken arrangements that your father died?<br></br>Baron Azru: He was lured into of the their encampments under the pretense of peace talks.<br></br>Gabrielle: When did you learn of his untimely death?<br></br>Baron Azru: When one of his guards came running back bloody and injured to inform us.<br></br>Gabrielle: What happened next?<br></br>Baron Azru: Something I am not very proud of. I took revenge for my father's murder.<br></br>Gabrielle: How did you take revenge?<br></br>Baron Azru: With blood.<br></br>Gabrielle: And pelts?<br></br>Baron Azru: That was not from that moment.<br></br>Gabrielle: Where did you get the cloak made of wolf hide?<br></br>Baron Azru: From a tribal leader who thought it a smart idea to attack my city and murder innocent people.<br></br>Gabrielle: So after your father's death did the peace between your city and the phelan tribe degenerate?<br></br>Baron Azru: We made peace again, it was a single leader who came up with the plot. It was not consulted with all of the tribes.<br></br>Gabrielle:  Was this the first conflict you had to deal with as leader of the city?<br></br>Baron Azru: No, the first one would be just after the death of my father when I became the leader at the point.<br></br>Gabrielle: Is there any other unfortunate decisions you had to make as leader of your city?<br></br>Baron Azru: Things were relatively peaceful.<br></br>Gabrielle: And how did you go from being a leader of a city to an ambassador of the Bisclavret in Triskellian?<br></br>Baron Azru:  I came to the city and they needed an Ambassador.<br></br>Gabrielle: Who is leading Merza in your absence?<br></br>Baron Azru: My council of advisors and my Mother.<br></br>Gabrielle: Lets talk about your time here in Triskellian? What did you think of the city when you first arrived.<br></br>Baron Azru: It is very odd.<br></br>Gabrielle: How so?<br></br>Baron Azru: Wolves leading Boars, Cats as Captains for the Boars, Cats leading the Wolves, rudeness rampant in the streets, and just plain odd people in general.<br></br>Gabrielle: Has your opinion of the city now changed?<br></br>Baron Azru: Has the oddness changed? No.<br></br>Gabrielle: Who was the first memorable person you recall.<br></br>Baron Azru: Dasha.<br></br>Gabrielle: You seem to disapprove of inter-species mingling in the house. Do you find it offensive that the house's employee different species?<br></br>Baron Azru: Not offensive, just odd.<br></br>Gabrielle: How long did you serve the embassy before being made an ambassador.<br></br>Baron Azru: Just a month or so. Their prior Ambassador, Donatella, had been absent for quite some time.<br></br>Gabrielle: Did you change anything since you've been promoted to ambassador?<br></br>Baron Azru: I made Captain Ammy the Captain. I've also started the imports again.<br></br>Gabrielle: Do you believe you've made a positive impact on your house?<br></br>Baron Azru: Well I know what is being said and I am now working on mending some of the bridges I have broken. I may have been too brash and direct with my methods.<br></br>Gabrielle: Is what is being said about you true?<br></br>Baron Azru: Parts of it. I was brash and direct and at times rude.<br></br>Gabrielle: How are you working on those broken bridges?<br></br>Baron Azru: Diligently.<br></br>Gabrielle: Do you have any help in your diligent work?<br></br>Baron Azru: I have sought the help of my House and they have been generous and understanding.<br></br>Gabrielle: Would you like to talk about your constable report?<br></br>Baron Azru: What about it?<br></br>Gabrielle: The public board has quite a few testimonies but not your own.<br></br>Baron Azru: That is does.<br></br>Gabrielle: Can you give me your side of the story?<br></br>Baron Azru: It is simply one of those times I was too brash and direct, one of the bridges if you shall.<br></br>Gabrielle: Are you planning on accepting the charges?<br></br>Baron Azru: I guess you'll just have to see when the time comes.<br></br>Gabrielle: I've read on the boards that there is a house meeting tomorrow. Your house members seem gloomy and on edge lately and I'm guessing it has to do with the meeting. Care to enlighten us on the purpose of the meeting?<br></br>Baron Azru: I will be addressing their concerns.<br></br>Gabrielle: Do you believe this meeting will help with the seemingly unease of your house?<br></br>Baron Azru: Yes.<br></br>Gabrielle: Let’s move onto my favorite topic. Love lives. It's no secret that you and Dame Cora are courting correct?<br></br>Baron Azru: This will be a good one to engage your readers, but no, we are no longer courting.<br></br>Gabrielle: Do you and she remain friends?<br></br>Baron Azru: That remains to be seen.<br></br>Gabrielle: Do you have parting words for my readers?<br></br>Baron Azru: I apologize to them for being the big bad wolf and I am hoping to return to the once well known and loved Baron that could chat with the common man and not cause fear or anger.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             sixth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the constable page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~`~`~`~ Constables Report ~`~`~`~`~<br></br><br></br>open cases<br></br><br></br>~kidnapping and assault<br></br> Patrick allegedly kidnapped Anastasiya and Nan, who he bound, burned and tortured.<br></br><br></br>~disrespecting a noble<br></br>Baron Azru of the House Bisclavret has allegedly disrespected Dame Ravenna of the House Rinaldi.<br></br><br></br>~murder of mersai<br></br>The corpse of Mersai was found by Lexie. Injuries to the head, jaw and left cheek were reported by Lexie, though no report from the healers were filed. Lexie reportedly put him on the altar for resurrection.<br></br><br></br>current warrants<br></br><br></br>~kafka<br></br>~zanthia<br></br><br></br>closed cases<br></br><br></br>~Dolf-serving 1002 hours in prison for assault.<br></br>~Virendra-found guilty, charged closed, no punishment.<br></br>~Donatella- paid 10 fines for murder<br></br>~Rune- banned from docktown for five weeks for assault<br></br>~Rune- 1002 hours in prison for murder of Gado<br></br>~Dame Xena- write an apology, pay 5 fines, restrickted to docktown for  a month, 24 hour in prison for murder of seened and shamary.<br></br>~Patrick- 1002 hours in prison for murder of Luciano<br></br>~Seened- paid 6 fines for the arson in the commons<br></br>~Patrick- 1002 hours in prison for murder of Aiko<br></br><br></br>Militia~<br></br><br></br>The militia was formed as a means of upstanding citizens of the city with martial experience to gain the ability to bring in particularly unruly criminals and aid in exceptional circumstances. It is an honor to be a part of so that the innocent people of Triskellian may rest well at night and be proud of their kin, or their family, or their friends who might be a member.<br></br>Members of the milita are: Mister Cullan, Mister Fyros, Lord Marcus, Esquire Dasha, Mister Jeager, Miss Althea, Mister Valentin, Esquire Kaine, Mister Drosnan, Mister Brenner, and Esquire Gabrielle. To be a member simply have a clean criminal record and, at the very least, 10 lessons in any given combat profession. Then write to Acting Sheriff Zaria for more info.<br></br>It is of the utmost importance that when a crime is committed any and all that witness it, report it. Do not rely on others to do so because you can't be certain they will. Should you not wish to contact a Constable directly or you don't know any by name then there is another way. Outside the gaol is a carving of a fox head. You can put what you saw on a scroll and then deposit it into the fox head. Only Constables can retrieve it once it's put in there and it is checked daily by myself.<br></br>If you don't know where the gaol is you head west from the west commons onto Market Street. From there, head north through the market place and into Newtown. The gaol is just north of the cafe and to the west. The fox head is outside the gaol on the street.<br></br>Thank you for you continued support and cooperation.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~-~0~-~ FASHION CONER ~-~0~-~-.<br></br><br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~*~ Colors of Spring ~*~<br></br><br></br>twilight black, this is a romantic shade of black.<br></br>peach, just like the fruit this color is soft and cheerful.<br></br>dusky grey, as refreshing and mysterious as a midafternoon rainstorm.<br></br>light yellow, after months of grey this color is as welcomed as sunshine.<br></br>cherry blossom pink, sweet and gentle this color floats on the wind.<br></br>cardinal red, like its name sake this color of bird can't be missed.<br></br>dark spring green, spring is in the air and this shade of green.<br></br>shimmering blue-green, when the ice melts the water sparkles this shade.<br></br>iridescent moonglow, only in spring does the moon shine this bright.<br></br><br></br>~ MERRY SPRING FEVER, FROM ME TO YOU ~<br></br><br></br>Garment of the month<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-<br></br><br></br>~*~Womens~*~<br></br><br></br>Mermaid Gown. This is a sleek, floor-length gown that hugs the torso, hips and legs before flaring out at the knees and cascading to the floor in voluminous, elegant folds that trail slightly behind the wearer. A sweetheart neckline offers a small glimpse of cleavage with a lack of straps or sleeves to lend coverage to the shoulders and arms.<br></br>~*~Mens~*~<br></br><br></br>Open-Neck Vest. This is a sleeveless vest secured at the front via a series of loops and laces. The collar of the garment opens at the neck and extends down just past the ribcage, exposing a fair bit of chest underneath.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eighth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eighth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is Life As We Know It.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ===== Life As We Know It =====<br></br><br></br>---Engagments---<br></br><br></br>Aiko and Aramil, engaged Yule 17, 896.<br></br>Bigby and Landa, engaged Yule 25 896.<br></br>Virendra and Elizabeth, engaged Snow 15 896.<br></br><br></br>---Marriages---<br></br><br></br>Chesh and Alana Veressen<br></br>Joined in the chapel, Yule 9 896.<br></br><br></br>Matthew and Trinity Farrel<br></br>Joined in the cathederal, Snow 9 896.<br></br><br></br>Brennus and Tomoe MacLeoid<br></br>Joined in the chapel,  Snow 5 896.<br></br><br></br>---Children---<br></br><br></br>Ember Darya d'Rinaldi born Yule 6 896<br></br>Daughter of Dame Xena and Lord Marcs d'Rinaldi.<br></br><br></br>Olbos d'Rinaldi <br></br>Adopted by Sir Matteo and Lady Tara d'Rinaldi<br></br><br></br><br></br>---Deaths---<br></br><br></br>Patrick, excuated by Captain Kilana of the Rinaldi.<br></br>Mersai, found dead with no suspects. Returned by the light.<br></br>Unknown mother and daughter, died of unknown illness.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ninth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ninth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of funnies drawn by Sang
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/DR0003-Manage-knotty-problems.png<br></br>http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/buni1.jpg<br></br>http://i976.photobucket.com/albums/ae250/jsd1985/2014-02-02-109_yesfunny.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_10" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="tenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="pages"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             tenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to Houses.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             _-_-_-_-Guild page-_-_-_-_-_<br></br>Come to So you can sew for all your sewing needs, we specialize in (ooc http://forum.skotos.net/showthread.php?p=1037777#post1037777) just speak to our staff who will help you with a friendly smile. Our staff members are:<br></br>Miss Flora for tailoring and needleworking, Miss Nan for Seamstressing Hairdressing, Miss Electris for Hairdressing, Lady Meepers for Seamstressing and Dye.<br></br><br></br>We can provide you with the following lists:<br></br>(ooc http://forum.skotos.net/showpost.php?p=1041449\&postcount;=23)<br></br>(ooc http://forum.skotos.net/showpost.php?p=1041363\&postcount;=40)<br></br><br></br>---@ Triskellian Gardening Guild---@<br></br><br></br>We don’t just do cigars, tobacco pouches, fruits, veg, teas, herbs, perfumes, medical supplies and soaps!<br></br><br></br>Our specialties include:<br></br><br></br>- Bottles of pungent oil, perfect for repelling your ex (or vampires)!<br></br>- Unique bottles of Strawberry wine, perfect for the up and coming warm months<br></br>We also boast two of the cities most trusted merchants. Contact Fips or Rem for details and all things merchant related.<br></br>:::: The Pink Roses ::::<br></br><br></br>The Pink Roses is a new guild created by Trinity Taki. The guild itself focuses on healing and gardening but they have other members that focus in medic and translating.<br></br><br></br>They can be recognized by their pink guild rings or pink healer bags. They're always seeking new members. To join write Miss Trinity Taki.<br></br><br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_11" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eleventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eleventh"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eleventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the House Bisclavret.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             _-_-_-_Bisclavret_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>Three hundred years ago, on the night of the Seiscethir, the Bisclavret proclaimed themselves a separate nation from the Phelan. They threw off the trappings of their old ways and embraced the progressive modernism of the Church of S'allumer, of kings and vassals, of commerce and technology. Today they are a formidable Noble House in their own right, one of the four Great Houses of Triskellian.<br></br><br></br>Their control over the northwestern forests of Calabria has given them the economic power to build an army, rumoured to rival that of the Avoirdupois. The might of their mercenaries and the quality of their troops should not be doubted, before the dawn of a battle, their troops have been known to don fierce some war pant about their body in order to further intimidate the opposing ranks. Their naval prowess and shipping industry has been a priority of late and is growing, spurred on in no small part by their monopoly and endless supply of lumber. This is further increased by establishing a firm foothold in Triskellian waters and offering low taxation and docking fees in their home ports.<br></br><br></br>A proud and noble House, loyal to a fault and fierce in defence of one of their own ranks, no wonder their motto is ?Strength and Honor?.<br></br><br></br>- People of note<br></br>Best way to contact each member of the Great House Bisclavret is to either send them a missive directly using the city?s courier service or to stop by the Embassy building and use the bell to draw attention of your presence.<br></br><br></br>Esquire Kaine Blackedge - Ambassador<br></br>Dame Cora MacUilleam -Triskellian shipping director<br></br>Lord Ralston Beuchanon - Envoy<br></br>Cullan - Reeve<br></br>Ammy -Captain of the Guard<br></br><br></br>- Trade and import<br></br>Auction house imports- All lumber, all pistols, certain mechanical gadgets, tartans, sporrans, whiskey, rum, woollen cloths (cashmere/angora), bagpipes, furnitures.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports- <br></br><br></br>~*Cross Breasted Jerkin*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cross-breasted jerkin. This close-fitting jacket features a cross-breasted design meant for swordplay and style. It exhibits a fashionable merger of fine lines and functionability allowing for movement and grace. It comes complete with (metal) hardware and matching button closures.<br></br>**takes 1 gram of metal and 5 yards of dyed fabric AND Cost 60 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Glengarry Hat*~<br></br>A (color) (material) glengarry hat. The glengarry bonnet is a traditional boat-shaped hat without a peak made of thick-milled (material) material with a toorie on top, a rosette cockade on the left, and ribbons hanging down behind.<br></br>**takes 3 yards of dyed fabric AND Cost is 36 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Waist Coat*~<br></br>A (color) (material) waist coat with full cuffs. This long-sleeved jacket features a series of stylish, (shape) (metal) buttons that run down the center to aid in opening and closing the garment. It stops just at the waist, and is traditionally worn with kilts or pants.<br></br>** takes 1 shaped button and 5 yards of dyed fabric AND Cost 56 papers<br></br><br></br>~*V Cut Bodice*~<br></br>A (color) (material) V-cut bodice. A definite must for any fencer or swordswoman, this garment boasts a V-cut on the front which rolls smoothly down to the rear and high sides to allow for maximum comfort and movement. The supple (color) (material) bodice fit is accentuated by a button-up flap that covers the normal front lacing making for a double-layered effect. It bears (variation) silken laces along the sides along with shiny (metal) grommets.<br></br>**takes 1 use of dye, 1 gram of metal, and 3 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 68 papers.<br></br><br></br>All trade requests are to be directed to Cullan<br></br><br></br>- List of future House events \& dates<br></br>Azru event - celebration of the New Year ? Before end of Snow (Feb)<br></br>Ralston/Emmaline Event ? Nobility Social drinks, Not yet set<br></br>Gabrielle/Kaine event - ranged relay competition, Not yet set<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_12" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thirteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="thirteenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             twelfth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the House Avoirdupois.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             _-_-_-_Avoirdupois_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>~NEWS~<br></br><br></br>Caliste earned her freedom on Yule 10 896 after several years of slavery thanks to the efforts of the Avoirdupois and Rinaldi sponsorships.<br></br>Mattimeo du Pont has taken leadership of the guard and because of him the guard's skills and pride have improved greatly.<br></br><br></br>~UPCOMING EVENTS~<br></br><br></br>Gabrielle/Kaine- ranged competition (no date set)<br></br>Emmaline/Ralston- ball (no date set)<br></br>Emmaline- secret garden party (no date set)<br></br>Gabrielle- shooting practice (every sunday)<br></br>Brigiette- church party (no date set)<br></br><br></br>~MEMBERS~<br></br><br></br>Ambassador:<br></br>Esquire Renaud<br></br><br></br>Reeve:<br></br>Caliste<br></br><br></br>Captain of the Guard:<br></br>Mattimeo<br></br><br></br>Nobility:<br></br>Lord Sabastien<br></br>Lady Emmaline<br></br><br></br>Gentry:<br></br>Esquire Louis<br></br>Esquire Brigiette<br></br> Esquire Gabrielle<br></br><br></br>Bard:<br></br>Thukal<br></br><br></br>Guard Recruits:<br></br>Axeumit<br></br>Brenner<br></br>Martin<br></br>Weeble<br></br><br></br>~IMPORTS~<br></br><br></br>For all import requests speak to Ambbasador Esquire Renaud du Harmonieux.<br></br><br></br>~Auction house imports: All wine, steel, fancy fabrics, cognac, all perfumes/colognes, face powder, high fashion garments, wigs.<br></br><br></br>~Direct Imports~<br></br><br></br>~*Malliot Pantaloons*~<br></br>The maillot pantaloon is a one-piece, fitted sleeveless garment with a scooped-neck and tight legline that ends at mid-thigh. It is constructed out of (color) (material) and is traditionally worn during exercise and spars.<br></br>**takes 5 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 52 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric And cost 52 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Sheath Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) one-piece, strapless, sheath silhouette gown with (metal) back closures. This slinky garment features an inventive, pin-tucked bodice highlighted with sparkling embellishments and scrolling embroidery. The skirt itself is a full a-line and boasts box pleated ruffles which flow into a decorated semi-cathedral train.<br></br>**takes 1 gram of metal and 6 yards of fabric AND cost 68 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Waterproof Bag*~<br></br>A (color) (material) waterproof messenger bag. A satchel that is made of $(this.trait:color) (material) that has been treated to repel water. This bag has a strap that can wrap around the shoulder and closes via a (metal) horse-shaped clasp.<br></br>**takes 1 gram of metal and 2 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 96 paper
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing:_-_-_-_avoirdupois_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>~news~<br></br><br></br>caliste earned her freedom on yule 10 896 after several years of slavery thanks to the efforts of the avoirdupois and rinaldi sponsorships.<br></br>mattimeo du pont has taken leadership of the guard and because of him the guard's skills and pride have improved greatly.<br></br><br></br>~upcoming events~<br></br><br></br>gabrielle/kaine- ranged competition (no date set)<br></br>emmaline/ralston- ball (no date set)<br></br>emmaline- secret garden party (no date set)<br></br>gabrielle- shooting practice (every sunday)<br></br>brigiette- church party (no date set)<br></br><br></br>~members~<br></br><br></br>ambassador:<br></br>esquire renaud<br></br><br></br>reeve:<br></br>caliste<br></br><br></br>captain of the guard:<br></br>mattimeo<br></br><br></br>nobility:<br></br>lord sabastien<br></br>lady emmaline<br></br><br></br>gentry:<br></br>esquire louis<br></br>esquire brigiette<br></br> esquire gabrielle<br></br><br></br>bard:<br></br>thukal<br></br><br></br>guard recruits:<br></br>axeumit<br></br>brenner<br></br>martin<br></br>weeble<br></br><br></br>~imports~<br></br><br></br>for all import requests speak to ambbasador esquire renaud du harmonieux.<br></br><br></br>~auction house imports">
             All wine, steel, fancy fabrics, cognac, all perfumes/colognes, face powder, high fashion garments, wigs.<br></br><br></br>~Direct Imports~<br></br><br></br>~*Malliot Pantaloons*~<br></br>The maillot pantaloon is a one-piece, fitted sleeveless garment with a scooped-neck and tight legline that ends at mid-thigh. It is constructed out of (color) (material) and is traditionally worn during exercise and spars.<br></br>**takes 5 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 52 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric And cost 52 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Sheath Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) one-piece, strapless, sheath silhouette gown with (metal) back closures. This slinky garment features an inventive, pin-tucked bodice highlighted with sparkling embellishments and scrolling embroidery. The skirt itself is a full a-line and boasts box pleated ruffles which flow into a decorated semi-cathedral train.<br></br>**takes 1 gram of metal and 6 yards of fabric AND cost 68 paper<br></br><br></br>~*Waterproof Bag*~<br></br>A (color) (material) waterproof messenger bag. A satchel that is made of $(this.trait:color) (material) that has been treated to repel water. This bag has a strap that can wrap around the shoulder and closes via a (metal) horse-shaped clasp.<br></br>**takes 1 gram of metal and 2 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 96 paper
SName: page
SName: twelfth
PName: pages
Adjective: page
Adjective: twelfth
----------------------------------------------------------------------
DETAIL [page_13]
Brief: thirteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
Look: This page is dedicated to the House Rinaldi.
Writing: [*
  _-_-_-_Rinaldi_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>imports: [*   Contact Lady Antonia or Dame Ravenna<br></br><br></br>Auction house imports- Musical instruments (except bagpipes), apple brandy, hypocras, framboise, cartouches, gunpowder, rejuvenation jars, draughts, make-up (except face powder), spices, dyes, nectar, glass objects, crossbows.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports-<br></br><br></br>~*Banded Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) floor-length gown banded with (variation) and gold metallic trim. It features a split-front chiffon overlay, and extravagant two-piece gauntlet style sleeves which have been trimmed to match. These sleeves tie on with alget-ended gold lacing, to allow the chemise to puff through to the surface.<br></br>**takes 1 dye use and 5 yards of dyed fabric and cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Justacorps Jacket*~<br></br>A (color) (material) justacorps jacket. This is a knee-length coat, fitted to the waist and flared below, without a mid-seam. It features deep, turn-back cuffs, and is generally worn over a long vest or waistcoat and breeches.<br></br>**takes four yards of dyed fabric And cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric and cost 52 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Slashed Sleeved Gown*~<br></br>A patterned (color) (material) ankle-length gown trimmed with small (metal) beads and (gem) gemstones. The slashed sleeves reach just below the elbow and attach to the gown with satin shoulder rolls bearing matching trim.<br></br>**takes 1 bead, 1 carat gem, 6 yards dyed fabric and cost 84 papers.<br></br><br></br>PEOPLE OF IMPORT:<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia di Rinaldi, Baronessa LiguriaAzzurra al Mare<br></br>(Write to Captain Kilana if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Dame Ravenna il Legno d'Avorio<br></br>(write to Miss Ismae if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Sir Matteo<br></br>(Can be contacted directly)<br></br>Captain Kilana, leader of the guard.<br></br><br></br>UPCOMING EVENTS:<br></br><br></br>Spring Equinox Ball - The Ballroom in Oldtown<br></br>[ooc: Saturday 21st March at 3 pm EST]<br></br>Hosted by the Rinaldi<br></br><br></br>In Planning:<br></br>Formal Dinner (late Feb potentially)<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing:_-_-_-_rinaldi_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>imports">
             Contact Lady Antonia or Dame Ravenna<br></br><br></br>Auction house imports- Musical instruments (except bagpipes), apple brandy, hypocras, framboise, cartouches, gunpowder, rejuvenation jars, draughts, make-up (except face powder), spices, dyes, nectar, glass objects, crossbows.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports-<br></br><br></br>~*Banded Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) floor-length gown banded with (variation) and gold metallic trim. It features a split-front chiffon overlay, and extravagant two-piece gauntlet style sleeves which have been trimmed to match. These sleeves tie on with alget-ended gold lacing, to allow the chemise to puff through to the surface.<br></br>**takes 1 dye use and 5 yards of dyed fabric and cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Justacorps Jacket*~<br></br>A (color) (material) justacorps jacket. This is a knee-length coat, fitted to the waist and flared below, without a mid-seam. It features deep, turn-back cuffs, and is generally worn over a long vest or waistcoat and breeches.<br></br>**takes four yards of dyed fabric And cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric and cost 52 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Slashed Sleeved Gown*~<br></br>A patterned (color) (material) ankle-length gown trimmed with small (metal) beads and (gem) gemstones. The slashed sleeves reach just below the elbow and attach to the gown with satin shoulder rolls bearing matching trim.<br></br>**takes 1 bead, 1 carat gem, 6 yards dyed fabric and cost 84 papers.<br></br><br></br>PEOPLE OF IMPORT:<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia di Rinaldi, Baronessa LiguriaAzzurra al Mare<br></br>(Write to Captain Kilana if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Dame Ravenna il Legno d'Avorio<br></br>(write to Miss Ismae if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Sir Matteo<br></br>(Can be contacted directly)<br></br>Captain Kilana, leader of the guard.<br></br><br></br>UPCOMING EVENTS:<br></br><br></br>Spring Equinox Ball - The Ballroom in Oldtown<br></br>[ooc: Saturday 21st March at 3 pm EST]<br></br>Hosted by the Rinaldi<br></br><br></br>In Planning:<br></br>Formal Dinner (late Feb potentially)<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_13" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thirteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="thirteenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             thirteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the House Rinaldi.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             _-_-_-_Rinaldi_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>imports: [*   Contact Lady Antonia or Dame Ravenna<br></br><br></br>Auction house imports- Musical instruments (except bagpipes), apple brandy, hypocras, framboise, cartouches, gunpowder, rejuvenation jars, draughts, make-up (except face powder), spices, dyes, nectar, glass objects, crossbows.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports-<br></br><br></br>~*Banded Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) floor-length gown banded with (variation) and gold metallic trim. It features a split-front chiffon overlay, and extravagant two-piece gauntlet style sleeves which have been trimmed to match. These sleeves tie on with alget-ended gold lacing, to allow the chemise to puff through to the surface.<br></br>**takes 1 dye use and 5 yards of dyed fabric and cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Justacorps Jacket*~<br></br>A (color) (material) justacorps jacket. This is a knee-length coat, fitted to the waist and flared below, without a mid-seam. It features deep, turn-back cuffs, and is generally worn over a long vest or waistcoat and breeches.<br></br>**takes four yards of dyed fabric And cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric and cost 52 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Slashed Sleeved Gown*~<br></br>A patterned (color) (material) ankle-length gown trimmed with small (metal) beads and (gem) gemstones. The slashed sleeves reach just below the elbow and attach to the gown with satin shoulder rolls bearing matching trim.<br></br>**takes 1 bead, 1 carat gem, 6 yards dyed fabric and cost 84 papers.<br></br><br></br>PEOPLE OF IMPORT:<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia di Rinaldi, Baronessa LiguriaAzzurra al Mare<br></br>(Write to Captain Kilana if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Dame Ravenna il Legno d'Avorio<br></br>(write to Miss Ismae if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Sir Matteo<br></br>(Can be contacted directly)<br></br>Captain Kilana, leader of the guard.<br></br><br></br>UPCOMING EVENTS:<br></br><br></br>Spring Equinox Ball - The Ballroom in Oldtown<br></br>[ooc: Saturday 21st March at 3 pm EST]<br></br>Hosted by the Rinaldi<br></br><br></br>In Planning:<br></br>Formal Dinner (late Feb potentially)<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing:_-_-_-_rinaldi_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>imports">
             Contact Lady Antonia or Dame Ravenna<br></br><br></br>Auction house imports- Musical instruments (except bagpipes), apple brandy, hypocras, framboise, cartouches, gunpowder, rejuvenation jars, draughts, make-up (except face powder), spices, dyes, nectar, glass objects, crossbows.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports-<br></br><br></br>~*Banded Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) floor-length gown banded with (variation) and gold metallic trim. It features a split-front chiffon overlay, and extravagant two-piece gauntlet style sleeves which have been trimmed to match. These sleeves tie on with alget-ended gold lacing, to allow the chemise to puff through to the surface.<br></br>**takes 1 dye use and 5 yards of dyed fabric and cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Justacorps Jacket*~<br></br>A (color) (material) justacorps jacket. This is a knee-length coat, fitted to the waist and flared below, without a mid-seam. It features deep, turn-back cuffs, and is generally worn over a long vest or waistcoat and breeches.<br></br>**takes four yards of dyed fabric And cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Reversible Cloak*~<br></br>A (color) (material) cloak edged and lined in (lining) and bearing the symbol of the (symbol).<br></br>**takes 1 spool dyed thread, 1 dyed lining, 2 yards of dyed fabric and cost 52 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Slashed Sleeved Gown*~<br></br>A patterned (color) (material) ankle-length gown trimmed with small (metal) beads and (gem) gemstones. The slashed sleeves reach just below the elbow and attach to the gown with satin shoulder rolls bearing matching trim.<br></br>**takes 1 bead, 1 carat gem, 6 yards dyed fabric and cost 84 papers.<br></br><br></br>PEOPLE OF IMPORT:<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia di Rinaldi, Baronessa LiguriaAzzurra al Mare<br></br>(Write to Captain Kilana if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Dame Ravenna il Legno d'Avorio<br></br>(write to Miss Ismae if you wish to contact her.)<br></br>Sir Matteo<br></br>(Can be contacted directly)<br></br>Captain Kilana, leader of the guard.<br></br><br></br>UPCOMING EVENTS:<br></br><br></br>Spring Equinox Ball - The Ballroom in Oldtown<br></br>[ooc: Saturday 21st March at 3 pm EST]<br></br>Hosted by the Rinaldi<br></br><br></br>In Planning:<br></br>Formal Dinner (late Feb potentially)<br></br>
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_14" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="fourteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourteenth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the House Doloreaux.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             _-_-_-_Doloreaux_-_-_-_<br></br><br></br>Ambassador is Shade<br></br><br></br>Auction house imports:All gems, all metals (except steel), plants, herbal and fruit teas, beers/ales.<br></br><br></br>Direct imports:<br></br>~*Bucket back*~<br></br>A (color)( material) bucket bag. A roomy bag shaped like a bucket with an open top and thick shoulder strap.<br></br>**takes 3 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 64 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Cranach Gown*~<br></br>A (color) (material) floor-length and full-skirted cranach gown, complete with an elegant pair of segemented sleeves bordered in (gems) and decorated with (variation) lace. The top bears inch and a half wide straps and is comprised of fitted (variation) faille embroidered with (pattern). Thick (color) cords have been horizontally strung against the abdomen of the garment, revealing the color and fabric of the chemise beneath.<br></br>**takes 2 uses of dye, 1 carat gem, 1 spool of dyed thread, 5 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 100 papers<br></br><br></br>~*Scented Gloves*~<br></br>A pair of thick, wrist-length (color) (material) gloves which give off the smell of (smell) to passerby.<br></br>**takes 1 use of oil/perfume and 2 yards dyed fabric AND cost 56 papers<br></br><br></br>~*War Coat*~<br></br>A (color) (material) skirted doublet with a side closure and elaborate front placket closures. A garment of decoration, it can be practically worn over a single or double layer of doublets and trews as an added protection against enemy weapons.<br></br>** takes 4 yards of dyed fabric AND cost 36 papers.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_15" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="fifteenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fifteenth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifteenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the Shining Stars of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             * * * * Shining Stars * * *<br></br><br></br>How generous is Miss Ammy of the Great Bisclavret House. She heard that Lady Antonia of the Great Rinaldi House, was aiding with the orphanage in town and sent the Rinaldi a donation of wonderful toys. They've been graciously accepted by Miss Beatriss and the kids. Miss Ammy is truly a wonderful and kind person.<br></br>Bigby has been naught but proper and helpful to those he mets. He is an example of how to get things done, be involved, propriety and social grace.<br></br> Lord Marcus goes out of his way to welcome everyone into the city, and was constantly giving slaves small tasks to do to keep them busy.<br></br>Esquire Renaud has gone out of his way to ensure the delivery of Caliste's freedom, and even when she was a slave he was remarkably kind and welcoming.<br></br> While inside the swamp Aiko came across snakes that appeared ready to attack. She froze, too shaken to defend herself and nearly got eaten alive. Then Miss Ammy, Captain of the Bisc house put her body in front of Aiko. She defeated two of the snakes and never moved from Aiko's side until the snakes were dead. Mister Trevyn came to her aid as well.<br></br>Bigby has started a new tradition. It's called pay it forward. He helps out others and where he should be paid he asks that you pay it forward by helping someone else for free in the future.<br></br>Chesh, Lucky, and Chinco have been behaving if you are to ask around docktown. Random attacks, murders, and general mischief is at a all time low thanks to these three behaving.<br></br> Electris is friendly and hardworking. She is on a mission to help people look and feel better while being happy and chipper all the while.<br></br>Father Antos made toys for orpahns while sitting in the commons. He makes sure children have what they need and enjoy their lives.<br></br>Weeble maybe new to town but he has marched his way to our hearts. He is quiet, nice, and goes ot of his way to ensure everyone is safe and warm.<br></br>Tomoe is gracious and kind as she is smart. She gives out lessons in langauges like coins to the poor.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K", 1354853763, "meandmine", "K", 1354942697, "meandmine", "K", 1354945930, "meandmine", "K", 1354949099, "meandmine", "K", 1354949332, "meandmine", "E", 1354949364, "meandmine", "K", 1354949373, "meandmine", "E", 1355259036, "meandmine", "K", 1355259762, "meandmine", "K", 1355259767, "meandmine", "E", 1355259860, "meandmine", "K", 1355260025, "meandmine", "K", 1355260127, "meandmine", "K", 1355267403, "meandmine", "K", 1355281790, "meandmine", "K", 1357690626, "meandmine", "K", 1357692638, "meandmine", "K", 1357692747, "meandmine", "K", 1358310543, "meandmine", "K", 1358312544, "meandmine", "K", 1358320455, "meandmine", "K", 1358321566, "meandmine", "K", 1358325444, "meandmine", "K", 1358328295, "meandmine", "K", 1358331132, "meandmine", "K", 1358331762, "meandmine", "K", 1358332027, "meandmine", "K", 1358332059, "meandmine", "K", 1358332124, "meandmine", "K", 1358332578, "meandmine", "K", 1358332592, "meandmine", "E", 1358332619, "meandmine", "K", 1358908973, "meandmine", "K", 1360909601, "meandmine", "K", 1362049202, "meandmine", "K", 1362103954, "meandmine", "K", 1362872017, "meandmine", "K", 1362875584, "meandmine", "K", 1362876726, "meandmine", "K", 1363927594, "meandmine", "K", 1366999186, "meandmine", "K", 1366999373, "meandmine", "K", 1367000338, "meandmine", "K", 1372307148, "meandmine", "K", 1375138082, "meandmine", "K", 1375316390, "meandmine", "K", 1375342501, "meandmine", "K", 1375413390, "meandmine", "K", 1375414616, "meandmine", "K", 1375415176, "meandmine", "K", 1375415260, "meandmine", "K", 1375415358, "meandmine", "K", 1375415385, "meandmine", "K", 1375416474, "meandmine", "K", 1375416570, "meandmine", "K", 1375417747, "meandmine", "K", 1375420249, "meandmine", "K", 1375420384, "meandmine", "K", 1375422567, "meandmine", "K", 1375422727, "meandmine", "K", 1375423034, "meandmine", "K", 1375424809, "meandmine", "K", 1375424875, "meandmine", "K", 1375424914, "meandmine", "K", 1375425036, "meandmine", "K", 1375425634, "meandmine", "K", 1375427129, "meandmine", "K", 1375427287, "meandmine", "K", 1375427359, "meandmine", "K", 1375427401, "meandmine", "K", 1375427447, "meandmine", "K", 1375427522, "meandmine", "K", 1375427869, "meandmine", "K", 1375427975, "meandmine", "K", 1375428042, "meandmine", "K", 1375428212, "meandmine", "K", 1375428528, "meandmine", "K", 1375430843, "meandmine", "K", 1375431324, "meandmine", "K", 1424408104, "killandra", "R", 1424409561, "killandra", "E", 1424409666, "killandra", "E", 1424409718, "killandra", "E", 1424409760, "killandra", "E", 1424409857, "killandra", "E", 1424410016, "killandra", "E", 1424410085, "killandra", "E", 1424410132, "killandra", "E", 1424410244, "killandra", "E", 1424410809, "killandra", "E", 1424410849, "killandra", "E", 1424410987, "killandra", "E", 1424411649, "killandra", "E", 1424411703, "killandra", "E", 1424411731, "killandra", "E", 1424411735, "killandra", "E", 1424411740, "killandra", "E", 1424412754, "killandra", "E", 1424443568, "killandra", "K", 1424443953, "killandra", "K", 1424809433, "killandra", "K", 1424809622, "killandra", "K", 1424810107, "killandra", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
