<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="meandmine">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="true" against="false" under="false" on="true" inside="false" near="true" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="true"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="paper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="newspaper"/>
            <Base:SName sname="thing"/>
            <Base:SName sname="object"/>
            <Base:SName sname="item"/>
            <Base:SName sname="everything"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="papers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="items"/>
            <Base:PName pname="objects"/>
            <Base:PName pname="stuff"/>
            <Base:PName pname="things"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapaers"/>
            <Base:PName pname="newspapers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="news"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A collection of large papers, printed on with block letters. This is $(this.trait:brief).
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             Try reading the first page, then second page, and so on.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_01" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="first"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="first"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             first page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the front page containing the table of content.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             The first page is the table of content, the second page is the story on the trip to Harrowgats, the third page is the story on the cursed jars, the fourth page is the interview with Lady Antonia, the fifth page is the constable report, the sixth page is the fashion corner, the seventh page is the crafting directory, the eighth page is the funnies, the ninth page is the social and political life, the tenth page is the gossipmonger.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_02" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="second"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="second"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/snail.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             second page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the leading story about trip to Harrowgates. Art done by Gabrielle.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Elemental trouble in the heart of the wolves~<br></br><br></br> The ambassador of the Bisclavret was sent a missive from Harrowgates requesting aid with their criminal problem. Reports say the trip there was bizarre and that Harrowgate was suffering via the Minkers. Speaking with Zaria, 'The minkers are the group that were in Triskellian a while back. They robbed the library of their elemental artifacts. The group is a faux druid group that steals artifacts to control the elementals.' <br></br><br></br>On the way up there our heroes, (Ammy of the Bisclavret, Aneira of the Bisclavret, Sir Bayard Ambassador of Avoirdupois, Clover of lePlow, Dasha of lePlow, Gemma of the Adominable, Hanneman of the Avoirdupois, Kaine Ambassador of Bisclavret, Kalleah Reeve of Doloreaux, Lysandus of the Doloreaux, Meepers of the So you can sew, Milli of the leplow, Rickter Ambassador of the Doloraux, Sable of leplow, Samstag of the Doloreaux, Suavis of the University, Dame Valara of the Avoirdupois, Zaria acting sheriff and Zuberi of the Bisclavret) met some of the most interesting obstacles. The first was a massive snail who lured people to bite it so that those poor victims become giddy (shown in the picture). The second obstacle was a strange wizard who had claimed a part of the road. This wizard froze wagons to the ground and did cold assaults on his targets. He was defeated with good old fashion fire.  The last obstacle was bandits who puts flying skinks in a hole, then set them lose on traveler. <br></br><br></br>The group took five days to get to Harrowgates and when they did they got a big surprise. They found that there were riots and the weather was funkified, as in there was all sorts of weather in defined circles in the same area. According to Sir Bayard, 'There was sunshine here and rain over there, fire sprouting up everywhere, wind howling in that corner. It was crazy.'<br></br><br></br>The first piece of action was to deal with the rioters. Kaine was the head of this action and got people to go to safety with his wise words. After which the group made it into the keep. Within moments they discovered a horrible situation, hundreds of small statues came to life when they entered the main hall. These little monsters were found out to be earth elementals that could control the very ground. Brute force wasn't enough to defeat these little monsters, they found an odd circle of light which people disappeared into. In these light sources was one of the minkers and a huge ball of rock called the earth artifact. After the minker was defeated, Zaria pressed her geode into the earth artifact and destroyed it and all the little monsters. <br></br><br></br>After the earth artifact was found and destroyed, some guards in the prison cells were released (they were put there by the earth monsters) and the group found the duke's councilors. After speaking with them and being told to basically go deal with the problems and leave us alone, the group made their way to the second artifact down by the docks. This is where the group found some living seaweed that pulled people into the water so that the water elementals could attack the victim. The victims where either hit with strong bursts of water or frozen. This is unfortunately, how Clover lePlow ended up dying. Meanwhile, Zaria borrowed a boat and alongside a swimming Bayard made their way to the water artifact which is underwater in a sunken ship. Together Zaria and Sir Baybard blow the conch shell (water artifact) and destroy the artifact and the water elementals. The most notable part of the whole trip according to Hanneman, 'Ambassador Kaine was confident and competent throughout, and commanded every situation well. Also, when the water stone was broken, it likewise released a flood, a massive wave that swept us all away. Except for the Ambassador. He dodged it with ease. It was most impressive. That man could probably walk through the rain and not get wet.'<br></br><br></br>Oddly enough, balls of fire above the group dissipate when the water elementals disappear and a naked man drops from the sky. After securing him and dressing him the group found out he was the previous leader of the Minkers but his group put him in that ball as a way to say 'We disagree with you, go away.' He told the group where to find the next artifact, 'In the underground black market.' It took some time but after securing lines to posts in the tunnel the group was able to make their way up the tunnel in which the black market was held. The lines were needed because high wind swept the group backward. The wind elementals were causing the difficulties in the tunnels and were merely distracted until the air artifact could be destroyed which caused minor damage to the group by throwing everyone against the walls. <br></br><br></br>At this point small salamanders lurked in the shadows, spawning fire whenever the word FIRE was uttered. Our heroes finish off the elementals by going to the courtyard and facing a wall of fire. Yes, you heard me correctly, a wall of fire. According to accounts, the group had to had actually be on fire before passing through the wall. With smoke coming off their newly flame free clothing, they came face to face with a horrific sight: lava flowing from the ground, fire spitting from cracks, small salamanders zooming around catching things on fire and most notably a gigantic fire elemental spewing doom on everyone. Hanneman and Kalleah defeated the last minker and destroyed the last of the elemental artifacts, causing serious damage to everyone and everything while Dame Valara saved the day by opening a cursed jar, making it rain.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_03" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="third"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="third"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="arturl">
             http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/Blue-Roses-flowers-25785535-523-347_zpsc72ee046.jpg
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             third page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is about the cursed jars and a farewell to Dame Valara.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~Soul Leeches~<br></br><br></br>Jardskalfti of the Avoirdupois was the first to experience a soul leeching. He was close to death and was given a rejun jar, that when opened surrounded Jardskalfti in fog and echoed his name throughout the city. It was found out later that another soul entered his body at this time, this other soul eventually took over and behaved unlike Jardskalfti would normal act.  Dame Valara also become a victim of soul leeching when she opened a rejun jar, her's made it rain and ended up saving the day. The soul inside of Dame Valara was a sailor who enjoyed being crude. Both victims were brought before the church who had discovered a way to cure soul leeching. Special ingredients from the swamp were needed: a purple swampweed, a pink love juice, a green myrtle branch, and lily-scented mudball.  These were used in a ceremony to remove the soul leeching that Prebyster Ximen and Bishop Yarwoodle lead. Unfortunately, this lead to the death of Dame Valara.<br></br><br></br>~Farewell, Dame Valara~<br></br> A service will be held in memory of the dearly departed Dame Valara. You will be missed and your passing is a tragic lose to the city and to your house. Those that wish to pay respects will be welcomed to say their good-bye at the service, which will be announced in the future.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_04" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fourth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fourth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the interview of the month.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~~Lady Antonia, the woman behind the shells~~<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "First I want to thank you for taking the time to do this interview"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia bobs her head gently, "It is my pleasure."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "For the record what is your full name?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "I am Lady Antonia di Rinaldi, Baronessa Liguria Azzura al Mare."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "What is your position within the house?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "I am currently the leader of the Rinaldi embassy, overseeing trade and diplomatic relations to the other houses."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Can you name the important people of your house?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "There is Dame Xena and Lord Marcus who have done very well during my absence from the city. Unfortunately, Lord Marcus is away from Triskellian dealing with some personal matters and Dame Xena is still mostly recovering from her assassination. There is of course also Sir Matteo as a knight. Currently, miss Zanthia is serving as Reeve and thereby essential to the house. Captain Sunta is working outside of the city and we are hoping to groom a new Captain for the guard. Most recently I have hired mister Adon as a scribe and assistant. Of the guard there is mister Devon and mister Gwydion, the latter serving as personal guard to Lady Bianca, though both have left the city for the time being. Lastly cousin Lord Valentinus has returned to the city though and it will be interesting to see what he might focus on."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Lets start with your childhood. What can you tell me of your parents and siblings growing up?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: 'I have mostly grown up here in Triskellian, though spent significant time at our estates by the sea. I am a sole child though and stand to inherit when my parents are no more. My parents are Lorenzo and Lucia di Rinaldi, and my father took over the trading empire his father started. We are all merchants. All my father's brothers died before I were born, so the line rests upon myself. As a child I loved going to the beach and explore the cave which was found there, though I must confess most of my time was spent learning and reading, preparing me for my role as the head of my family and the trade. My parents now mostly reside in Triskellian and I am staying with them until the renovation work at the Rinaldi mansion is completed."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: 'What was the best thing you ever found on the beach?'<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "A beautiful piece of driftwood, it appeared as if a face was hidden therein and my imagination went soaring. I even think I for a while had it as a friend. I have not been very old at the time though, perhaps five or six."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Did you go to school or have a tutor?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "Tutors, a house teacher taking care of all the basic education as I was younger, and then later my father would arrange for diplomats or traders to come in and teach me. I of course also learned those basic needlework things and how to host a dinner, how to write an invitation and such, that was mostly my mother teaching me those. She still tend to chide me if I have not written a letter correctly.Ever to be kind, to think before you speak, to learn the truth and not place judgement before you have seen all sides of a story. And then of course, to be screwd in a trade."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Have you ever left the city?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "Yes, quite a few times. Recently I spent some three years at my estates and dealing with matters there. I have also spent half a year in a convent as well as travelled around parts of Calabria, meeting trade contacts, visiting nobles, strengthening diplomatic relations between my family and other families and such things."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Can you list your best and worst qualities?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "I am intelligent that I know, I am kind and perceptive, I understand trade and politics. As for worst quality, perhaps a tendency at times to let my temper get the better of me, or maybe my very wordy missives."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Is there anyone in your house that you have problems with and on the opposite side do you have someone that you would die without?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "That is quite a personal question, is it not?"<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "It is. Do you have a problem answering it?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "Realistically I would probably not die, but if it was not for the Reeve I would be very burdened by tasks, and it appears that mister Adon is lifting another burden of my shoulders. On a personal level, my cousin is a challenge as he stands to inherit my lands and the trade should I not marry or have children."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "You have stipulation on your lands, tell me about that?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "My grandfather and his brother split in disagreement many years ago and the family was parted in two. As my father has no brothers and I no siblings, should I die without an heir, the lands will fall to my cousin Lord Valentinus, as he is next in line to inherit. He is technically my second cousin, the son of my father's cousin."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Do you have revery between you two?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "There are some tensions, but nothing I would elaborate upon in public."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "To change the topic, you said you are good with politics. Does your house have any current political interest or strife?"<br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "Things are rather quiet between the houses these days. There is of course the whole matter of the Jade empire people and those criminal guilds which takes up most of our attention. Though, if we had strife or special interests and plans, I would certainly not reveal such in a newspaper for all to read. It would not do to tip the hand before the cards have been played. I have not heard such rumours myself. I have only met Lady Bianca a couple of times. She had returned to the city after a longer time away and I welcomed her. Perhaps it was because of my open and kind way towards her, showing her trust and not judging her. It is merely the truth. I do tend to give people a chance to show their worth and a chance to shine, by giving them the possibilities to do so, instead of closing the door before it has been walked through."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Do you have any love interests?" <br></br><br></br>Lady Antonia: "Love interests? That is a hard thing to have as a noble. Not only is there the political matters to consider, the potential alliances between families or houses, but also the approval of said families or houses. I do not expect to fall in love and marry for love, for that I am too realistic and know it will not be possible. What I can hope for though is a marriage with someone I respect and like, with whom love might grow over time. There is one knight who might suit for such, though there are the house matters to consider and the political situations. I should likely soon let it be known that I will accept suitors."<br></br><br></br>Esquire Gabrielle: "Last, question, can you give me a parting quote?"<br></br><br></br> Lady Antonia: "Per aspera ad astra. Through hard work to the stars. Dreams can be achieved and goals reached, and for those suitable, I am here to support them in those things."
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_05" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="fifth"/>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="fourth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             fifth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the constable report page.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ---Deaths---<br></br><br></br><br></br>Sir Axel<br></br>Nan<br></br>Raz<br></br>Chesh<br></br>Kilana<br></br>Kafka<br></br><br></br>---Arrest warrant:<br></br>Sir Matteo for the murder of Raz<br></br><br></br>Kruix for the murders of Nan, Shush, Maho, Raz and assault on Razeer<br></br>Damien for assault in the Inn. <br></br> Kakfa for disturbing the peace, theft, and two counts of assault.<br></br>Open Cases:<br></br><br></br>Murder of Sir Axel,suspects Kruix and Razeer<br></br><br></br>~Militia~<br></br><br></br>The milita bring in wanted criminals and act in the defence of others without having charges filed against them fer their involvement. They must abide by the law and do their guard duties.<br></br> Members of the milita are: Bayard, Hanneman, Kaine, Cullan, Aneira.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_06" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="sixth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="sixth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             sixth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is this months fashion tips.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             ~ On Behalf of All Clothiers of Triskellian ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~\{0\}~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ We offer here a list of what each established clothier in the city is skilled in. A directory of sorts, if you will. WHEN MAKING AN ORDER PLEASE SEND AS MUCH INFORMATION AS YOU CAN. IT MUST INCLUDE: COLOR, MATERIAL, AND GENERAL TYPE. Example: Blue suede  Shoes Belt  Hat Gloves Bag <br></br><br></br>~ Rainbow Rags ~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br><br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br><br></br>= Other Clothiers withing the City walls =<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>~ Esquire Meepers, of Sew you Can Sew - Master Seamstress and Dyer.<br></br><br></br>+List of Terminologies+<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br>- Dyer - Mixer of dyes<br></br>- Seamstress - Creator of feminine garments<br></br>- Tailor - Creator of masculine garments<br></br>- Needleworker - Creator of accessories with skills of embroidering<br></br><br></br>~\{0\}~ Favorable Colors this Season ~\{0\}~<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~<br></br><br></br> ~*~ Colors of the Season ~*~<br></br><br></br>Azure mist, a lovely light shade of blue.<br></br><br></br> Cornflower blue, wintry, yet vibrant.<br></br><br></br>Holly red, reminscent of mistletoe, naturally.<br></br><br></br> Garnet-Colored, for the sultry who like the less perky red.<br></br><br></br>Pine green, makes one think of the scent of tall fir trees.<br></br><br></br> Dark feldgrau, muddy green for the little boy that resides in every man's heart.<br></br><br></br> Plum-Colored, that's right. For the visions of sugarplums, dancing in their heads.<br></br><br></br>Dark chocolate, mmmm.... Chocolate.<br></br><br></br>Snow white, that damnable fluff from the clouds.<br></br><br></br> Metallic-gold, for the pretties on your tree.<br></br><br></br> ~ A merry Yuletide, to you from me ~<br></br><br></br>Garment of the month<br></br>~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-~-<br></br><br></br>~*~Womens~*~<br></br><br></br> Under loved petal gown. Feminine yet elegant, this gown is largely overlooked in its fanciness, for either more revealing gowns, or for a more serious look. This gown is perfect for any sort of winter social.<br></br>Petal gown (6 yards) - A sleeveless gown bearing eight large, overlapping, triangular petals which fall from the low waistline to the feet. The bodice is princess cut to accommodate the curviest of figures, while the deep v-shaped back can be left open or trimmed with decorative lacing for a more interesting look.<br></br><br></br>~*~Mens~*~<br></br><br></br>Comfortable, yet dressy enough to impress that special someone, the peascot doublet is the perfect men's coat for the winter season.<br></br>A  peascod doublet (4 yards). A traditional doublet bearing the characteristic shape of a pot belly. It features a stiff, tight underlining, buckram to make the protruding shape, and padding to hold it out. A peplum decorates the lower portion of the garment with small wings surrounding the armholes and hiding the points that are used to tie on the sleeves.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_07" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="seventh"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="seventh"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             seventh page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is the crafter directory.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^Crafter Directory*^*^*^<br></br><br></br>~Clothiers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Una - Proficient knowledge of needlework \& seamstressing.<br></br>~ Miss Dahlia - Master Needleworker \& proficient knowledge of tailoring.<br></br>~ Miss Nan - Master Seamstress.<br></br>~ Esquire Meepers - Master Seamstress and Dyer<br></br><br></br>~Carpenters~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Raz~<br></br>~Miss Suchin~<br></br>~Miss Polgara<br></br>~Mister Jayland<br></br>~Mistress Pru<br></br><br></br>~Stone Masons~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Miss Polgara~<br></br>~Mister Sang<br></br><br></br>~Smiths~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Tark-armor smith~<br></br>~Sanu-armor smith<br></br>~Clayton-armor smith<br></br>~Mercy-armor smith<br></br>~Natalie-weapon smith<br></br>~Clayton-weapon smith<br></br>~Tark-weapon smith<br></br>~Mercy-Black smith~<br></br>~Natalie-Black smith<br></br><br></br>~Jewelers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Lady Anelie~<br></br>~Lidia<br></br>~Seened~<br></br><br></br>~Merchants~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Rem~<br></br>~Fips~<br></br>~Aluine~<br></br>~Sable~<br></br><br></br>~Healers~<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>~Dr. Hush~<br></br>~Physician Suavis~<br></br>~Mattimeo~<br></br>~Nurse Sable~<br></br>~Achyls~<br></br>~Zanthia~
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_08" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="eighth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="eighth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             eighth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of funnies drawn by Sang
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             http://www.tigerknight.com/ss/ss6-3.jpg<br></br>http://www.kizandjenn.com/sean2/019.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_09" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="ninth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="ninth"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             ninth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This page is dedicated to the social and political life of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^Win a Date with an Ambassador*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>Kaine Blackedge the ambassador of the Bisclavret answered these questions. Whoever answers them the best will win a blind date with the ambassador to the masquerade ball. Submissions must be sent to Gabrielle the morning of the ball.<br></br>What is your favorite color?, what is your best and worst qualities?, What would be a perfect date to you?, How would you describe yourself?, What is the best present you ever bought someone else?, What is the most annoying thing someone could do?, What is the most risque thing you've ever done in public?, What do you look for in a mate?, What are your pet peeves?, How many relationships have you had?, What is the worse date you've ever been on?<br></br><br></br>~*~*~*~*~**~*~*Socialites*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*<br></br> The Rinaldi are the most social house with the masquerade ball on the 19th of this month and the promise of tea socials once a month and the falconry club meetings and hunts for those of rank.  Dates will be posted and inventions will be sent to those important enough to get them.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="page_10" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="page"/>
            <Base:SName sname="tenth"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="pages"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="page"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="tenth"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             tenth page of the $(this.trait:brief)
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             This is the page of gossip from random sources.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="writing">
             *^*^*^*^*^*^GossipMonger*^*^*^*^*^*^*<br></br>~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~<br></br><br></br>"Apparently a certain plow horse of rank doesn't have anything better to do with his time than torment commoners. He reportedly incited the wolf cook to emotion in the commons by saying hurtful things to her rather than just walking away and being diplomatic. What a great example of leadership and rank, to act so petty."<br></br><br></br>"Apparently a certain paladin tiger supports knife-wielding mothers who tow their children through thick ash without a care in the world. For shame!"<br></br><br></br>"Not only was a certain tree dwelling panther kissing publicly in the presence of a Lord, but she was even bold enough to think it is her right to do so and no consequences should follow."<br></br><br></br>"Apparently a certain foxy artist decided to force drug the local kidnapper with the aid of the tiger constable and the not-very-Knightly Avoirdupois horse, with swamp pebbles to try and get him to talk about his crime. It sounds like they were all committing crimes themselves to me."<br></br><br></br>"Oh my, an Avoirdupois who publicly makes fun from nobles wearing tutus in private? A certain tail snatching monster should know better to keep certain laundries behind closed doors."<br></br><br></br>"Docktown has a few rugged and crude people around. Some claim the local womanizing dingo is one of the more disrespectful types, but I've never seen the man myself."<br></br><br></br>"It's all swell and dandy to want to do what's best for your House, but when the local Doloreaux rhino (a commoner) usurped the role of Ambassador from the hateful pig (a noble), someone who had been doing a good job of leading beforehand, that's just highly disrespectful and inappropriate. What happened to deferring to your superiors? I guess he has no qualms neglecting social etiquette."<br></br><br></br>"Can you believe that plow horse's panther? Though it might have been loosely based on bravery, I heard that he harassed a child who could create explosions out of thin air, simultaneously risking the Avoirdupois knight's life by surprising him. He got his own hair burnt off completely and still refused to listen to his allies and get away from danger. At that point, it does seem to cease being brave and begins to enter into the hall of fame of stupid."<br></br><br></br>"The local sinner forest cat was being so kind, helping helping the one eared Doctor to get better by massaging her foot and ankle -- that is until he started to massage right up her leg and hint that he could -really- make her feel better. She's married, and healers aren't supposed to be inappropriate with patients!"<br></br><br></br>"Despite the fact that the nail tossing wolf prefers cremation over burial, it wasn't the appropriate comment to make while transferring coffins into a wagon while the people hadn't had a chance to be revived."<br></br><br></br>"Want to hear all about carpenter lemur and the zippy racoon smith's sex life? Apparently you just have to mill about in the west commons and the information will be shared freely by the two, or so witnesses say."<br></br><br></br>"A certain brass collared panther was running his mouth at the local foxy artist, threatening him over a sword said artist was fixing as a favor to him. When asked to calm down, he said he couldn't give a flying fig leaf about the city or his collar. For a serf he sure is mouthy."<br></br><br></br>"Word has it that when someone at the farm was grieving due to personal loss, the local harlequin cat scented herself with an alluring perfume and attempted to be flirtatious with the man despite the fact he was just hoping for a comforting presence. How inappropriate!"<br></br><br></br>"Despite a certain kind Bisclavret panther and less than reputable Lieutenant, well known militia, chasing after a noble masked villain, a well known criminal, a certain snow leopard of rank brought her own child to the shady area of the city to watch the proceedings when it was a great danger to both herself and the kid."<br></br><br></br>"I didn't hear what the topic was about, but a certain uppity equine Esquire corrected a Knight of her embassy in the middle of the commons despite his being of higher stature. How inappropriate!"<br></br><br></br>"A certain equine knight having a snow ball fight is a little below his station but it shows his down to earth attitude.  However, he became inappropriate when he shoved a snowball down noble lioness' shirt. Tisk tisk."<br></br><br></br>"When a certain rabbit constable was upholding the law and requesting the fox guardsman alter a testimony so that it was correct and factual, said reportedly reacted in anger by throwing his scroll in the constables face and disrespecting the Constabulary by stating 'There's no justice in this city'. Don't the Avoirdupois teach manners anymore, or do they leave that to the Doloreaux?"
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:nip:item:cost">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:brief">
         "pony press newspaper"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:papername">
         "the pony press"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:trash">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:act:start">
         X[M] /* Generate the newspaper contents based on the press sheets */  
  
/* set the front page */  
\$page = \$this.mainpage;  
if(\$page) \{  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:look", "The first page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"))+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:writing", Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing")));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:description:brief", \$page."trait:article_title");  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page01:adjective:first", TRUE);  
\}  
  
/* set the other pages */  
\$pages = Arr(\$this.pages);  
\$pages -= (\{ nil \});  
for(\$i=0;\$i\<sizeof(\$pages);\$i++) \{  
  \$page = \$pages[\$i];  
  \$number = Str(\$i+2);  
  if(\$i+2 \< 10) \$number = "0"+\$number;  
  \$writing = "";  
  if(\$page."trait:article_title" \&\& \$page."trait:article_title" != "fill in article title here")  
    \$writing = Str(\$page."trait:article_title")+"\\n";  
  \$writing = Str(UnSAM(\$page."details:objskin:description:writing"));  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:brief", desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:look", "The "+desc_ordinal(\$i+2)+" page of "+Str(\$this."trait:papername")+". It says:\\n\\""+\$writing+"\\"");  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":description:writing", \$writing);  
  /* set names and adjectives */  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":sname:page", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":pname:pages", TRUE);  
  Set(\$this, "details:page"+\$number+":adjective:"+desc_ordinal(\$i+2), TRUE);  
\}  
  
return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1190286276, "tonyd", "X", 1190286282, "tonyd", "P", 1190286317, "tonyd", "X", 1190286370, "tonyd", "E", 1190286718, "tonyd", "P", 1190286822, "tonyd", "P", 1190286884, "tonyd", "E", 1190286914, "tonyd", "P", 1190286936, "tonyd", "E", 1190286962, "tonyd", "P", 1190287005, "tonyd", "P", 1190287270, "tonyd", "P", 1190287378, "tonyd", "E", 1190287498, "tonyd", "P", 1190287598, "tonyd", "E", 1190287641, "tonyd", "E", 1190287775, "tonyd", "P", 1190287829, "tonyd", "P", 1190287854, "tonyd", "P", 1190287924, "tonyd", "P", 1190287971, "tonyd", "P", 1190288229, "tonyd", "P", 1190288323, "tonyd", "P", 1190288498, "tonyd", "P", 1190288743, "tonyd", "P", 1190288932, "tonyd", "E", 1190288953, "tonyd", "E", 1190289239, "tonyd", "P", 1190289255, "tonyd", "P", 1193457108, "tonyd", "E", 1193457156, "tonyd", "E", 1193457248, "tonyd", "P", 1193457277, "tonyd", "P", 1193457303, "tonyd", "P", 1193457337, "tonyd", "P", 1193457406, "tonyd", "P", 1193457428, "tonyd", "P", 1193457616, "tonyd", "P", 1193457639, "tonyd", "P", 1193457667, "tonyd", "P", 1193457681, "tonyd", "P", 1193457716, "tonyd", "P", 1193457747, "tonyd", "P", 1193457814, "tonyd", "P", 1193458056, "tonyd", "P", 1193458079, "tonyd", "P", 1193458119, "tonyd", "P", 1193458305, "tonyd", "P", 1193458776, "tonyd", "P", 1193458867, "tonyd", "P", 1193458924, "tonyd", "P", 1193463878, "tonyd", "E", 1238900072, "tonyd", "E", 1351122400, "meandmine", "R", 1351122479, "meandmine", "X", 1351127435, "meandmine", "K", 1351127487, "meandmine", "X", 1351127575, "meandmine", "K", 1351127622, "meandmine", "K", 1351127803, "meandmine", "K", 1351130840, "meandmine", "K", 1351131036, "meandmine", "K", 1352829477, "meandmine", "K", 1352832416, "meandmine", "K", 1352832650, "meandmine", "K", 1352832941, "meandmine", "K", 1352833139, "meandmine", "K", 1352833251, "meandmine", "K", 1352834286, "meandmine", "K", 1352847766, "meandmine", "K", 1352851359, "meandmine", "K", 1354853763, "meandmine", "K", 1354942697, "meandmine", "K", 1354945930, "meandmine", "K", 1354949099, "meandmine", "K", 1354949332, "meandmine", "E", 1354949364, "meandmine", "K", 1354949373, "meandmine", "E", 1355259036, "meandmine", "K", 1355259762, "meandmine", "K", 1355259767, "meandmine", "E", 1355259860, "meandmine", "K", 1355260025, "meandmine", "K", 1355260127, "meandmine", "K", 1355267403, "meandmine", "K", 1355281790, "meandmine", "K", 1357690626, "meandmine", "K", 1357692638, "meandmine", "K", 1357692747, "meandmine", "K", 1358310543, "meandmine", "K", 1358312544, "meandmine", "K", 1358320455, "meandmine", "K", 1358321566, "meandmine", "K", 1358325444, "meandmine", "K", 1358328295, "meandmine", "K", 1358331132, "meandmine", "K", 1358331762, "meandmine", "K", 1358332027, "meandmine", "K", 1358332059, "meandmine", "K", 1358332124, "meandmine", "K", 1358332578, "meandmine", "K", 1358332592, "meandmine", "E", 1358332619, "meandmine", "K", 1358908973, "meandmine", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="971734080" state="Comment" user="brianm">
           The UrBook.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
