<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="tunk_bodin">
  <Help:Node title="Combat">
    <Log:Description>
       Title: Combat<br/><br/>You must first $(udat.chatchar)WIELD your weapon, regardless of what kind of weapon it is to have it taken into account during combat. If you do not, your attacks will be based off your unarmed skill.<br/><br/>To enter combat, type $(udat.chatchar)FIGHT and the person's name you're wishing to oppose. Eg., FIGHT AZRAEL.<br/><br/>Once the fight begins, you will be assigned actions based on your combat-related skills and careers, or you will see a message that says your opponent has been assigned actions. When you see an action you'd like to use, simply type it verbatim. Eg., $(udat.chatchar)SLIGHTLY HURT AZRAEL. This will give Azrael a wound on a random part of his body. If you want to target a specific body part on your opponent you would just add the body part onto the end of your command. Eg., $(udat.chatchar)SLIGHTLY HURT AZRAEL'S RIGHT EYE.<br/><br/>As a general rule of thumb, sustaining 24 points of combat damage is cause for your character to suffer a permanent injury. 36 points of combat damage is cause for your character to die. You should keep these numbers in mind and RP accordingly.<br/><br/>Combat will continue until one of the parties involved submits or dies. As your wounds stack up, you will receive queues asking if you want to keep fighting or want to concede the fight to your opponent. You simply need to answer yes/no as desired and continue RP based on that decision.<br/><br/>Occasionally, the combat system will bug and no actions will be assigned to any of the fighters. At this point, it's best to $(udat.chatchar)BREAKCOMBAT and re-enter by typing FIGHT AZRAEL again. If combat still does not work for you, you should @assist and report the issue in as much detail as possible.<br/><br/>See Also: <helplink to="consent"/>, <helplink to="death"/>, <helplink to="injury"/><br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="combat"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="duel"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="dueling"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="duelling"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="fight"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="fighting"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1135365937, "-", "SYNC", 1136676400, "rhenn", "E", 1137619932, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1137630916, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1295119988, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1295148569, "jominey", "S", 1295148629, "jominey", "S", 1309488257, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315235047, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315235117, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1315235144, "slurpeeslurp", "E", 1509727438, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
