<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trading:notes">
         (\{ "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained oak desk by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tall dark-stained oak cabinet by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained oak caquetoire chair by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron tower shield by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of strawberry wine by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cedar book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained mahogany book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flowered dark blue silk long-sleeved gown by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey-stained maple book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black granite mortar by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black granite pestle by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze-plated book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black spider embroidered wool robe by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a beribboned dark grey dahlia embroidered muslin long-sleeved gown by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of samite by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut smoky quartz by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of samite by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sharp tooth of an alligator by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a driftwood dragon figurine by a dragon masked white rabbit.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light blue face powder jar by Odhran.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dusty aqua silk purse by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue leather pouch by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ginger teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ginger teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of blackberry silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bar of vanilla sugar soap by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raven faux fur ape doll by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dusty aqua silk purse by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a potted plant with yellow blossoms by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a beaded rose dust leather purse by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raven faux fur kitten doll by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light green wool blanket by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sage teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white leather dagger sheath by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze broad-bladed spear by Bakaal.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slate egg-shaped trinket box by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden yellow dragonfly embroidered velvet purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a storm grey starburst embroidered cotton corsetted hunting frock by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a storm grey smoke embroidered cotton witch doctor mask by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering berry velour purse by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sparkly bronze brocaded silk vixen doll by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blood black knotwork embroidered silk purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay hallowed sphere by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of glossy garnet dye by Penny.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay hallowed sphere by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vibrant-green alligator claw by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of rich umber lacewood lumber by Penny.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sharp tooth of an alligator by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a molten red whipcord purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden jade water-marked moire purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of blackened bronze chainmail by Bakaal.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow wine rack by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered maple rocking chair by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron trident dagger by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze dagger sheath by Bakaal.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an antique brass-colored knotwork embroidered jaconet fan by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay hallowed sphere by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay hallowed sphere by Detective Kegan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron craoiseach spear by Bakaal.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze chainmail cuirass by Bakaal.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron smallsword by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of batiste by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze chainmail shirt by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light umber zangolin scaled lorica squamata by Doctor Hush.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a studded black leather breastplate by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of dioptase green cotton shimmering dragonfly wings by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black leather heavy gorget by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shadowy coral ship embroidered frogskin purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark red satin sleeveless blouse by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of alabaster leather heeled boots by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alabaster leather waist cord by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dioptase green cotton dragonfly mask by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron locket by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden champagne velvet book by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty black leather holster by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flawless sapphire-embellished gold tri-strand necklace by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cone of exotic sandy brown incense by Doctor Hush.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a caramel leather purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a resplendent ruby red leather great bascinet by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a magenta silk purse by Kaylie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearl aqua petal embroidered brocade purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a medium white oak vanity by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white oak wardrobe by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black silk benda by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of shiny pewter chandelier earrings by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gleaming silver double-weave chain bracelet by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a warm mocha faux fur purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze misericorde dagger by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a heavy soft brass chain necklace by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark iron beetle bead by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iridescent moonglow silk choker by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vibrant purple brocade purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a warm peach waffle pique purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bejeweled iron circlet by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a spiked bronze hounskull by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched blackened bronze draping anklet by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clay bottle of freesia perfume by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of iron gauntlets by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glossy chalcedony blue silk choker by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a soft bronze dog charm by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron belly chain by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blueberry teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered alder high-backed chair by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of blushed rose silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blued steel rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper chastity belt by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched alligator tooth and iron cocktail ring by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, alligator tooth-embellished iron armband by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of glossy garnet silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered alder dragon mask by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an umbral purple quartz crystal and polished pewter ring by Esquire Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a scorched pewter-colored oak jewelry box by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of alligator tooth-embellished alligator stud earrings by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of batiste by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mahogany picnic basket by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sharp tooth of a shark by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of star peridot and soft bronze earrings by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flute by Delphine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a phantasmal black satin djinn costume by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black damask corsetted jacket by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black brocade corset by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight blue batiste strapped adventurer's corset by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a violet engraved slate vase by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a picture of an open-top cave by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blood-splotched ebony bluethroat feather bluethroat mask by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black lacquered mahogany clothing rack by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue gift box by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Guardsman Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pearly white supple leather gloves by Srulik.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of champagne shimmer faux fur gloves by Srulik.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sage teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sage teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of cinereous vulture feathers by Kaylie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of stygian vulture feathers by Kaylie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron warhammer by Valklov.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of strawberry wine by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lustrous spider eye by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blueberry teabag by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved lacquered maple surgical kit by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of rose red linen lace by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a face powder jar by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amaranthine lipstick tube by Lexie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of boxelder lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory-lacquered spruce wardrobe by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of sugar maple lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glossy black bottle by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, iron armband by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pearly white brocade gloves by Srulik.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched iron ring by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black gift box by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gray gift box by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black whipcord scarf by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of obsidian black whipcord gloves by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of sparkling pale blue brocade slippers by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a green gift box by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a green gift box by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a satiny blue velvet purse by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an imperial purple damask v-neck overgown by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ginger teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered oak jewelry box by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of slimy green gel by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey-stained oak cargo wagon by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of slimy green gel by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black lacquered mahogany dovetail vanity by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey-stained oak bookshelf by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered oak armoire by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered oak folding screen by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite flower pot by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite flower pot by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered maple cupboard by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay lighthouse decoration by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tan leather pouch by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red gift box by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sapphire silk filigreed slinky gown by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lemon teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sapphire satin mask by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched brass tail ring by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white gift box by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue owl embroidered canvas hammock by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a satiny blue suede poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a leaf-embroidered silvery primrose georgette floor length gown by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sable faux fur shawl by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gray gift box by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of flannel by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a satiny blue suede poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a satiny blue suede book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sunglow cotton camisole by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver velvet purse by Roxann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of rainbow-hued aurora glass-embellished iron drop earrings by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black lacquered mahogany armoire by Tanis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver gift box by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cedar footstool by Tanis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a coffee brown faux fur hooded cloak by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silk-trimmed lapis blue embroidered silk pillow by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silk-trimmed pine green embroidered silk pillow by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a catnip teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst lipstick tube by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut black akoman sapphire by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a snow white silk nightgown by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a satiny blue suede folder by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bag of enriched fertilizer by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pastel pink silk heeled slippers by Kaylie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pastel pink foray embroidered silk corset gown by Kaylie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of iridescent moonglow fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of iridescent moonglow hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white cotton belt pouch by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a licorice teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ginger teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fenugreek teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ginger teabag by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cotton by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a snowdrop white rose embroidered silk handkerchief by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich dun silk choker by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich dun silk ribbon by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a snowdrop white silk choker by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory crate by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory kestrel figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of whipcord by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black-lacquered teak toy top by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a baby blue dragon embroidered cotton washcloth by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fiery nacarat velvet artificial flower by Kierra.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black poplin eye mask by Kierra.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of faux fur by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brandywine broadcloth cloth by Kierra.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue brocade poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue brocade journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of batiste by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of damask by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a guild charter by Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a frosted ube glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amaranthine glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sugarplum glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight violet glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight violet glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark crimson glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering merlot glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amaranthine glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a scintillating green glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid glass bead by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark scarlet suede ankle-length jacket by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jet black suede ankle-length jacket by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of lustrous mocha leather calf-high boots by Edward.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lustrous mocha leather braided belt by Edward.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mulberry lipstick tube by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a frosted ube lipstick tube by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glossy purple lipstick tube by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vivid violet lipstick tube by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vinaceous lipstick tube by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a keg of malt whiskey by Lochlann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Dame Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a strange jar by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden peach silk dressing robe by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an azraq-ahdar kalamkari salwar suit by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of alder lumber by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slate frog-shaped trinket box by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fuschia poppy embroidered canvas sack by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of barras by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of beech lumber by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of teak lumber by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a green eyeshadow jar by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white eyeshadow jar by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white foundation jar by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of golden champagne hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of mahogany hairsticks by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey-stained oak desk by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue brocade journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of ash lumber by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sandstone winged lion statue by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black lacquered maple rosary ring by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a soft bronze chain bracelet by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper armband by Celestine.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of pristine white hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of barras by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of samite by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of barras by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a studded blackened bronze chainmail cuirass by Dame Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a spiked rich dun leather breastplate by Dame Amalasanda.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of poplin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron centurion helm by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite carriage trinket box by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite turtle trinket box by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory crib by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty bouquet by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slate leaf-shaped plate by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of muslin by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of batiste by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bixie statue by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a kitten statue by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut rose quartz by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron stiletto by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red brass-plated journal by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an aurulent honey suede book by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze rapier by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver gift box by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze pair of knuckledusters by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze chainmail brigandine by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of mottled-brown alligator skin bracers by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of bronze rerebraces by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron bascinet by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of bronze poleyns by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze sallet by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of bronze pauldrons by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron lorica by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron barbute by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sandy brown brocade purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shadowy coral ship embroidered frogskin purse by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a carmine red leather sack by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of carmine red leather strapped, knee-high sandals by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron chain whip by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shadowy silver orchid embroidered brocade short coat by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pecan tart teabag by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of satin by Raven.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark iron falcon charm by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, sterling silver handcuff anklet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of sunglow iron chainmail boots by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron chainmail-trimmed emerald iron chainmail hood by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of emerald iron chainmail pants by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark iron keyring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of emerald iron chainmail gauntlets by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glistening cherry-blossom pink silk brocade bliaut by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark iron keyring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched dark iron archaic ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pastel pink silk overlayed tulip dress by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glistening cherry-blosson pink muslin petal gown by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of cherry-blossom pink silk high heels by Adelaide.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark iron horse charm by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched brass rosary ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peach teabag by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sunglow samite cloak by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron chainmail-trimmed emerald iron chainmail riveted tunic by Zaria.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of lacewood lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite wolf statue by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched soft brass ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched brass lace boardered ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched brass ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue canvas hammock by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue brocade poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery grey rosewood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a warm mocha lacewood sketchbook by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered oak soldier figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of suede by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Raven.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of black granite stone by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of silver nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich umber lacewood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of velvet by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of barras by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of woolsey by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of broadcloth by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of samite by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of wysteria nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue canvas hammock by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black-lacquered oak spider mask by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of vodka by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of gin by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cool vanilla leather chain by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of ochre clay dice by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of oak lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of cedar lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich umber lacewood poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of orange clay dice by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden honey-hued ironwood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, soft brass armband by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a painting of a large star field by Aneira.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of cyan silk by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden honey-hued ironwood sketchbook by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of oak lumber by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of oak lumber by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a preserved olive weakfish by Darius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of smoky grey fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted ocean green glass by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted blue violet glass by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of golden champagne fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered beech dragon figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wad of fishing line by Mallory.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of lustrous mocha fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of deep red merlot by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of deep red merlot by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of lapis blue nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of midnight green nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of whiskey by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a half-bouquet of stark-white tulips by a witch doctor masked white rodent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved tin serving tray by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of obsidian black nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of jade nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of rose red nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of cognac by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of plum-colored nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of pastel pink nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of scarlet nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of obsidian black hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of dark scarlet hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light pink barras and teak low-backed bench by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron craoiseach spear by Gunther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of cognac by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of deep red merlot by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze dagger by Gunther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden honey-hued ironwood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered alder scroll case by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained mahogany picnic basket by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of scarlet hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved iron dirk by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved scorched pewter-colored oak fan by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron shortsword by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light blue foundation jar by an armadillo masked white cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sandstone fountain by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite frog-shaped trinket box by Aysel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white face powder jar by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory-lacquered ash angel figurine by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a crescent-shaped silver foil glass bead by a dragon masked blue black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of rum-spiced milk by Dame Eilionoir.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron ash tray by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearlescent black orchid embroidered cotton purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a linen-lined rich brown knotwork embroidered leather purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pure white cloudy mountain embroidered wool beach towel by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a keg of malt whiskey by Dame Eilionoir.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black celestial embroidered muslin sheer ceiling drape by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wheat-colored velvet capelet by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark turquoise sword embroidered cotton sack by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an imperial purple thorn embroidered pashmina purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron fire poker by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black starburst embroidered muslin parasol by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty iron chatelaine by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron arming sword by Gunther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large roll of lilac wool high-pile carpet by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of bronze hedge shears by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze can of water by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of cognac by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of peacock dye by Dame Eilionoir.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of dark-stained maple lumber by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a medium-sized blue-tinted seashell by a dragon masked blue black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of iron-clawed battle gauntlets by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tin can of water by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory-lacquered ash wardrobe by Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raven suede mouse doll by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished pewter spider bead by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished pewter lace and alligator claw gothic choker by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter tea kettle by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of iron scissors by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of honey-hued cocoa fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sugar maple shield by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red brass keyring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter tea kettle by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering merlot lipstick tube by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze spade by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a porcelain bottle of blood red sand by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight violet lipstick tube by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glittery black eyeshadow jar by Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ebony whipcord corsetted overlay dress by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vivid violet lipstick tube by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of shadowy silver hair dye by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black velvet book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted dusky red glass by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted azure glass by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted vivid turquoise glass by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tin bottle of vivid purple sand by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tin bottle of golden sand by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tin bottle of volcanic orange sand by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron lorica by Angel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid purple canvas hammock by Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron harpoon by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, iron chainmail bracelet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, iron hexmaile belt by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ice blue leather tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a royal blue-lacquered myrtle staff by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of midnight black silk by Master Belarius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron mace by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of midnight black samite by Master Belarius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of midnight blue silk by Master Belarius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of midnight black samite by Master Belarius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of midnight blue silk by Master Belarius.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blood-red suede tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a crimson suede and oak couch by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a porcelain bottle of golden sand by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black criss-cross embroidered canvas spider mask by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a viridian autumn leaf embroidered canvas comedy mask by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glass bottle of olive green sand by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a crimson velvet wolf mask by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an arylide yellow claw embroidered canvas gorath mask by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearlescent black damask purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper die by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper die by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron aspergillum mace by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silk-lined umber velvet purse by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron arming sword by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron gauche dagger by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty brilliant silver charm bracelet by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raven brocade sack by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered maple short bow by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered maple longbow by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fern green leather tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst suede tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered oak chair by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron dirk by Colborn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich brown-lacquered maple jewelry box by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wool pouch by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blood-red-lacquered cedar carved puppet doll by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of vanilla shisha oil by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of plum-colored nail polish by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of pastel pink nail polish by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of scarlet nail polish by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brass basin of water by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of golden honey-hued ironwood lumber by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of curly white ash lumber by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a reddish-orange desert clay hookah by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a painting of an undead mermaid by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of steel bracers by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a steel breastplate by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a limestone oval shaped bathing tub by Rion.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of sunset orange nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slate oval shaped bathing tub by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of azure nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of wine nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of obsidian black nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cone of coriander incense by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of blood-red nail polish by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red brass longsword by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glowing meteorite by Pirate Captain Omen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fern green leather large tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dragon embroidered obsidian black brocade and poplar armchair by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a drawing of a fresh aloe plant by Eyriel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of honey-hued cocoa hair dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a drawing of a bright and spacious ballroom by Eyriel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold leather purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grey sandstone lily pad shaped basin by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black sandstone oval shaped bathing tub by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a drawing of a mirror world by Eyriel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blood-red suede large tome by Romain.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak corner cabinet by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered cedar writing table by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak picnic basket by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a string of driftwood prayer beads by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silk by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of brocade by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Antonia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak toy top by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered beech owl figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a scorched pewter-colored-lacquered pristine ebony storage bench by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an a painting of a winding path in a mossy forest by Esquire Gabrielle.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a broadcloth polishing cloth by Andreas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tan suede belt pouch by Andreas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a keg of malt whiskey by Lochlann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peacock suede journal by Dame Lucie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak painter kit by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak painter's palette by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of rum-spiced milk by Lochlann.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden champagne brocade purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alabaster satin purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey-hued cocoa suede cushion by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold leather cushion by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tan hemp and ash button-tufted chair by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black velvet journal by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black velvet tome by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a teak clothing rack by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embroidered gold leather and ironwood armchair by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embroidered ivory velvet and ash cabriole chair by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embroidered honey-hued cocoa suede and mangrove camel-back armchair by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embroidered cream velvet and carob wood button-tufted chair by Tattooist Kyla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper-plated journal by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper-plated book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron shortsword by Keko.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a thorny locust scroll case by Una.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron francisca by Keko.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a suit of black diamond-patterned snakeskin armor by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a suit of black steel chainmail armor by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron frying pan by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron leaf-bladed spear by Keko.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper-plated book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron-plated book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a spiked alligator skull hounskull by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel heaume by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jagged shard of bone by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery-black alligator claw by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of pale-green alligator skin by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of spotted-green alligator skin by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Sturm.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory dinner plate by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Physician Suavis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iridescent moonglow silk purse by Una.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large Myr steak by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brown-streaked black pheasant feather by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brown-streaked black pheasant feather by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brown-streaked black pheasant feather by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bright gold and purple pheasant feather by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron rod by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze cascading necklace by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark grey kohl pencil by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn leaf-bladed spear by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grayish green clay slingshot pellet by Sir Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grayish green clay slingshot pellet by Sir Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grayish green clay slingshot pellet by Sir Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grayish green clay slingshot pellet by Sir Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron buckler by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lustrous damascus steel spear by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grayish green clay hallowed sphere by Sir Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched ivory Myr horn kilt pin by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alligator skull hounskull by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper bumblebee charm by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a steel scimitar by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a smoky grey knit wool scarf by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mangrove lumber by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of herringbone tweed by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of cream white knit wool socks by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bejeweled ivory Myr horn snow flake charm by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a smoky quartz and shadowy silver ring by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a steel rapier by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved cast iron ash tray by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brilliant silver drop necklace by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of silvered-onyx leather laminar boots by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sterling silver keyring by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a homespun earthen brown crocheted hooded shawl by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched blue-tinted seashell and copper ring by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of warm mocha lacewood lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched ivory Myr horn ring by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brilliant silver drop necklace by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery nickel and black glass glass shoulder clasp by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of warm cream angora wool by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fancy, feathered writing quill by Maggie.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight black horned viper skin dagger sheath by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty mottled-brown alligator skin back harness by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty midnight black leather back harness by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved, brilliant silver locket by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze topaz-embellished ivory Myr horn brooch by Drake.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a resplendent ruby red leather back scabbard by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-umber dray-hide open-faced sallet by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of smoke-haze-black leather laminar boots by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery nickel and lichen green glass shoulder clasp by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved steel double-bladed battle axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear blue vial of hot spring water by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of empress green marble stone by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raven silk-covered box of sweet treats by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cartouche by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cartouche by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a purified steel rod by Ilo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery nickel and lichen green glass shoulder clasp by Ilia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered ash hairbrush by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wheat-colored leaf embroidered leather purse by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tan leather pouch by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a velvet sketchbook by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cobalt blue satin ribbon by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by a borage masked white rodent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by a borage masked white rodent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by a borage masked white rodent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron-plated poetry book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tiny sandy brown seashell by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a painting of a ruined wall by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a painting of a snowflake fairy by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cerulean glitter and glass globe by an owl masked white fading to white rodent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden champagne brocade purse by Esquire Faith.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an elegant cherry-red-lacquered mahogany table by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory kite shield by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light purple-lacquered spruce tiki figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mica-freckled copper and prismatic plum-colored glass shoulder clasp by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a translucent gold rosewood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich umber lacewood poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a translucent gold rosewood poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a warm mocha lacewood sketchbook by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden honey-hued ironwood book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tuft of dark yellow moss by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rich umber lacewood journal by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a chocolate velvet belt by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow picnic basket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty oak bucket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty mahogany bucket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black leather belt by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of obsidian black leather gloves by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large roll of ivory velvet upholstery by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-edged tawny Julex fur vest by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid purple damask gambeson by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of starlight white satin streamers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of starlight white satin streamers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue brocade folder by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large roll of ivory velvet upholstery by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of twilled homespun by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of toffee-brown suede laminar boots by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flawless white diamond star pendant by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sterling silver drop necklace by Esquire Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale blue silk tapestry by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small flawless platinum bar by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small flawless platinum bar by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flawless white diamond star pendant by a masked black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver brocade parasol by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden topaz-studded chiffon-trimmed black silk ear-shaped caul by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cream wool unicorn doll by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ocean blue velvet mermaid doll by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark chocolate wool wolf doll by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a warm mocha lacewood tome by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow picnic basket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an umber poplin puppy doll by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron arming sword by Sergeant Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale blue silk tapestry by a masked black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tyrian purple cotton hat by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron arming sword by Sergeant Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a painting of a stormy voyage by Eyriel.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron spear by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a yellowish-green alligator skin skink doll by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue java banana by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iridescent moonglow celestial embroidered silk purse by Una.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a leafy white, daisy-like feverfew flower by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a yellow lemon by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small, stinging nettle by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a quill of cinnamon bark by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a quill of cinnamon bark by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a quill of cinnamon bark by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue java banana by Izzy.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze tea kettle by Ketoro.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze chisel by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Ketoro.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron tower shield by Ketoro.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alabaster flower embroidered cotton handkerchief by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of wrought iron surgical scissors by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raspberry rose damask purse by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery-grey leather pouch by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alabaster wave embroidered cotton handkerchief by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of midnight black leather boots by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearl aqua satin ribbon by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of pale amber silk streamers by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of sunglow satin streamers by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale blue criss-cross embroidered poplin scarf by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a midnight black satin tapestry by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a scarlet leather pouch by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black horned viper skin belt by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron fire poker by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of black leather boots by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst flower embroidered cotton handkerchief by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper clasp by Tomasso.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tan hemp pouch by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a misty rose brocade ribbon by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery-grey suede skink mask by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black faux fur wolf doll by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron longsword by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron arming sword by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory damask lily mask by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst cotton wristlet by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale blue wave embroidered suede wristlet by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hemp pouch by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ash grey suede wolf mask by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory velvet daisy mask by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery-grey brocade fox mask by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black faux fur tail warmer by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an obsidian black smoke embroidered batiste pouch by Alexis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, polished pewter tragus ear cuff by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter rod by Azora.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved dark-stained maple longbow by Christian.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter rod by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a package by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small white gold bar by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of gold satin streamers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of gold satin streamers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alligator claw-embellished bright tin armband by Esquire Tomasso.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a handful of iron nails by Bruno.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow picnic basket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze wildvine tiara by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow picnic basket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lizard egg by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of herringbone tweed by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of some red-stained alder parquet wood flooring by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pine couch frame by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of waterproof canvas by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pine bed by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty oak bucket by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sharp tooth of an alligator by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of some black-lacquered pine flooring by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of twilled homespun by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of earthy brown dye by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of moss green dye by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearlescent purple lipstick tube by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sugarplum lipstick tube by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orchid lipstick tube by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an aubergine lipstick tube by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper hinged bangle by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gleaming steel cocktail ring by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper bangle by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gleaming steel locket ring by Lidia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lustrous damascus steel rod by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black glitter and glass globe by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mahogany coffered ceiling paneling by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rose grey glitter and glass globe by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrinkled morel by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an odd mushroom by Dahlia.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fuschia glitter and glass globe by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched iron ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hickory back scabbard by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vibrant white suede and mahogany chaise by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained hickory tower shield by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a granite flower pot by Troyes.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a violet granite round table by Troyes.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered teak sword by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mahogany wainscot paneling by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mahogany wainscot paneling by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mahogany wainscot paneling by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of mahogany wainscot paneling by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of charcoal black leather gloves by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a charcoal black leather cloak by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished bone book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of midnight black horned viper skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of brown and grey horned viper skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of piebald Myr hide by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of brown and grey horned viper skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, banded jasper and copper arm cuff by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a russet suede satchel by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an etched, frosted glass and bronze luck brooch by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue leather arms pack by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an aurora glass and bronze hair comb by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished bone leaflet by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fresh thick catnip-flavored cigar by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a broken streaked blue seashell by Rik.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sable leather belt pouch by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a violet granite bench by Troyes.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alabaster suede umbrella by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a navy blue leather rucksack by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered polished bone book by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jet black leather umbrella by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an earthy brown leather arms pack by Rhol.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished bone dragon figurine by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an opalescent glass skull bead by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fresh thick catnip-flavored cigar by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red brass misericorde dagger by Gowther.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished bone snake figurine by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue glass beetle bead by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lilac glass oval bead by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a frosted ube glass round bead by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark, dust brown snake embroidered okon skin cloak by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved blackened bronze double-bladed battle axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a keg of Schwarzbier by a masked black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished bone weapon hilt by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mechanical brass scorpion toy by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glass bottle of spring breeze perfume by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of iron-clawed battle gauntlets by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jagged shard of bone by Nix.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a purified steel dirk by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a spotted-green alligator claw by Nix.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an antiquated silver twisted fyrenu necklace by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale aqua batik silk mid-riff bearing choli by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper bottle of woody spice cologne by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of yellowish-green alligator skin by Nix.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of mottled-brown alligator skin by Nix.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper bottle of pink paradise perfume by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of sapphire dye by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a barrel of rum-spiced milk by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of fiery nacarat dye by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery-black alligator claw by Levison.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared Myr hide by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of sapphire dye by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pot of emerald dye by Maddog Madalina.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mahogany writing table by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of deep sienna clay by Frang.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shadowy silver cascading necklace by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of silvery charcoal angora wool by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of soft wine blush satin curtains by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pale brown zangolin scaled pauldrons by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel rod by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rod by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of burnt sienna clay by Staci.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of burnt sienna clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of burnt sienna clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of light brown clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of light brown clay by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered mangrove fishing pole by Arran.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white smoke cotton cavalier shirt by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white smoke cotton gypsy shirt by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark blue Myr hide jacket by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of dark blue Myr hide pants by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a freshly roasted cassia coffee bean by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a freshly roasted coffee bean by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Staci.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of gold-orange clay by Staci.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fresh thick catnip-flavored cigar by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of miry-grey alligator skin bracers by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a miry-grey alligator skin lorica by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of ivory Myr horn chainmail greaves by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn chainmail cuirass by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel moth bead by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered spruce dye cubby by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a teak leg splint by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved oak mop by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oak pegasus button by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered mangrove coat rack by Arran.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a purified steel harpoon by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronze ear dagger by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of starlight white satin streamers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of pearlescent black fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a green gift box by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver gift box by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black leather quiver by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pink linen pants by Lamhirh.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of shadow black fur dye by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron backsword by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a fresh thick catnip-flavored cigar by Sinn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered yew longbow by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of black tweed pants by Lamhirh.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of heavy linen by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold bottle of moon sparkle cologne by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of sheer linen by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of orange daisies by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pearl satin smock by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peacock damask kirtle by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peacock satin choker by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an indigo purple muslin tiered gypsy skirt by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an orange clay soap by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glass bottle of chocolate sin perfume by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-flecked silver tsabit bangle by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a woven sterling silver choker by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved ivory Myr horn candelabra by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a color-change akoman sapphire and pallid leviathan bone eternity ring by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cartouche by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cartouche by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cartouche by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a limestone egg-shaped trinket box by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small silver-white rhodium bar by Trevyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of sapphire cotton gloves by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tuft of faded green moss by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished pewter spider bead by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white-lacquered oak eyeball bead by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black polished silver hookah by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jagged shard of bone by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red clay soap by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn die by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn die by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a circlet of yellow roses by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of red roses by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cast iron frying pan by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black wool scarf by Jayde.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black silk nighty by Jayde.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ceremonial shamshir by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of shadowy jet foulard by Vincent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white grape teabag by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of red-speckled white marigolds by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel sunflower bead by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel windmill bead by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery polished steel daisy bead by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of vermilion batiste by Vincent.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn circular bead by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of stark-white orchids by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of akoman lace by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a circlet of red daisies by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a light brown clay soap by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a translucent gold rosewood journal by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold-orange clay soap by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vibrant gold rose by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a three-drawer mahogany burl dresser by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mahogany rocking chair by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered spruce fabric chest by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lacquered maple nightstand by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered mahogany sling-back chair by Bjorn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of zangolin scale by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of red roses by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small filigreed gold bar by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small old gold bar by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved ivory Myr horn hairbrush by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a slab of orange-yellow clay by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a circlet of stark-white marigolds by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of mottled-green alligator skin by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved red-tinted damascus steel arming sword by Commander Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut cat's eye aquamarine by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small antiquated orichalcum bar by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a crystallized cherry lacquered oak pitcher by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut crystal clear diamond by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sheathed engraved iron shortsword by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a jagged shard of bone by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of dark aubergine watered silk by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of akoman lace by a masked black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bolt of pristine white mohair by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved ivory Myr horn rondel dagger by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron rapier by Claton.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a scarlet-tinted massai sword by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of molten red geometric embroidered silk pajamas by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty crystallized cherry lacquered oak basin by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a creamy chocolate leather arms pack by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a creamy chocolate leather tapestry pouch by Nan.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of spring green lilies by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blueberry teabag by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a circlet of white-tipped pink marigolds by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bright platinum bar by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ash frame loom by Charlotte.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze file by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a honey pot by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pink iron chainmail ailettes by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pink iron chainmail greaves by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of pink iron chainmail bracers by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pink iron chainmail lorica by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pink iron chainmail cuirass by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of silvery grey oak lumber by Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blackened bronze arming sword by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of blackened bronze fire tongs by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron saw by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper fire poker by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron fire shovel by Roofus.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an empty engraved koro horn chalice by Claton.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an uncut jasper by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oval jasper by Rem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a preserved dark blue spearfish by Vane.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue satin scholar robe by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silver-flecked blue satin poetry book by Leliana.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small white gold bar by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small vibrant gold bar by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small vibrant gold bar by Drea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an alligator skull heaume by Claton.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ebony leather dagger sheath by Claton.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unusually striped supple leather back scabbard by Claton.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bouquet of wintery blue roses by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sprig of leafy mistletoe by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sprig of leafy mistletoe by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by a dragon masked blue black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by a dragon masked blue black cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small lap-harp by Decima.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of ash grey Myr hide strapped boots by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of sandy brown waterproof canvas by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of dark, dust brown okon skin by Adon.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of silvery ambrosia dye by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of yellowish-green alligator skin by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a clear vial of white willow bark liquid by Perfect Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a crimson leather lorica by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a roll of leather by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of red leather bracers by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron muscle cuirass by Sanu.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering brass interlocked chain bracelet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering brass hinged bangle by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery grey bottle by Perfect Master Fips.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a silvery grey pine weapon hilt by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a coquina shell-embellished soft bronze medallion belt by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved silvery grey pine fishing pole by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a quartz and polished pewter ferroniere by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a polished pewter handcuff anklet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved starfire emerald and dark iron ring by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a coral-embellished sapphire leather double-weave chain bracelet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved starfire emerald and polished pewter ring by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared horned viper skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved gray topaz and polished pewter armband by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pineapple teabag by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a strawberry teabag by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gold moon charm by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an unprepared okon skin by Gladiator Koz.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a large bouquet of multi-colored roses by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a red coral-studded sunglow satin wristlet by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amaranthine lipstick tube by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper amaryllis link necklace by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black-lacquered mangrove fishing pole by Arran.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper hinged bangle by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper tragus ear cuff by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a raw slab of gator meat by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rotting skink corpse by Vargo.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a myrtle corner cabinet by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow cupboard by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a block of granite stone by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tall willow cabinet by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a myrtle wardrobe by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of gray topaz-embellished copper nipple rings by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flowered cobalt blue silk beribboned garland by Xen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow button-tufted ottoman frame by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow bowl by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a charcoal black leather noble tiara by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a gray topaz-embellished copper chainmail headdress by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved gray topaz and copper ring by Marea.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a solitary engraved polished pewter and starfire emerald star pendant by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a stack of small granite mosaic tiles by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow lotus bead by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vivid celadon kente cloth salwar suit by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow thorn bead by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow platypus button by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow bowl by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow bowl by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a myrtle sling-back chair by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ruby red skull embroidered satin waist sash by Xen.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved blackened bronze single-bladed battle axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a multi-hued anodized steel shillelagh mace by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a multi-hued anodized steel warhammer by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark grey slate jar by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark grey slate whetstone by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark grey slate jar by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark grey slate jar by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron craoiseach spear by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron gae bolga spear by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a lustrous engraved damascus steel lochaber axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron flanged mace by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vibrant white silk vest by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of midnight black Myr hide calf-high boots by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow high-backed chair by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow writing table by Polgara.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of blush-red silk harem pants by Mitena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of silver-flecked blue nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of sapphire nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a white engraved polished steel single-bladed battle axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of ruby red nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of glowing red nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of purple nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mahogany writing table by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of brandywine nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a hemp sling by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of midnight black nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of black-to-grey ombre nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an amethyst glass bead by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a copper-plated book by Miriam.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pewter-plated book by Miriam.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of midnight blue nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a rose red-stained oak crib by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of fiery nacarat nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of midnight blue nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of creamy chocolate nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of raven leather heeled boots by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bronzed hardened steel leaf-bladed spear by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sterling engraved silver tea kettle by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a leather-trimmed dark blue dragon embroidered leather vest by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of black-to-grey ombre nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a flowered raven silk stomacher by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of sapphire nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of light blue nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of white nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wheat-colored seashell embroidered canvas sack by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of six chalky red clay balls by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a porcelain bottle of vivid purple sand by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrinkled morel by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrinkled morel by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tuft of dark black moss by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of golden bronze yew lumber by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a deep sienna clay apothecary jar by Ulliem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a deep sienna clay apothecary jar by Ulliem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a deep sienna clay cistern by Ulliem.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a cherry-red-lacquered poplar fan by a dragon masked copper cat.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a shimmering pink panne folder by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sparkling scarlet moire folder by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a smoky gray soft leather folder by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a dark-stained mahogany book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrought iron-plated book by Preston.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a mechanical brass scorpion toy by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a circlet of spring green lilies by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a perfect large bouquet of multi-colored tulips by Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a misty rose apple blossom embroidered brocade parasol by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a radiant azure organza nebulae headdress by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iridescent moonglow brocade braided hairband by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iridescent moonglow flower embroidered brocade filigreed slinky gown by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a misty rose petal embroidered brocade corset by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a set of leather armor straps by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a misty moss green arabesque embroidered damask tapestry pouch by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a steel hounskull by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a steel lochaber axe by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a twilight black brocade corsetted overlay dress by Carolyn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black leather poetry book by Lotis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a purple-hued iron trident triple-tipped spear by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a sunspray gold ultra-thin cotton shemagh by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a vanilla gold ultra-thin cotton midriff-baring choli by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black leather manual by Lotis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a black leather journal by Lotis.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of smoky grey steel chainmail breast bags by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of smoky grey steel chainmail short bloomers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of snowdrop white silk breast bags by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of snowdrop white silk short bloomers by Orla.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pale silver silk asoke kaftan by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a serpent green glass and antiquated silver chat chat necklace by Heather.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a perfect small bouquet of sun-kissed orange daisies by Nurse Bess.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a poplar cat figurine by Steve.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a ribbon pattern by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a badge design by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a brilliant green emerald and white polished steel ring by Edric.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of silver-flecked blue nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of glowing red nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a maple picnic basket by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of ruby red nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of emerald nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of moss green nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of burnt sienna nail polish by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an engraved golden bronze yew longbow by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a glowing red velvet v-cut bodice by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a pair of brilliant silver chainmail bracers by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wolf embossed burgundy tartan folder by Nisha.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embossed black leather manual by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an embossed black leather manual by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a grey face powder jar by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a king bolete by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a wrinkled morel by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a golden chanterelle by Karacas.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a willow hairbrush by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue-lacquered cedar hairbrush by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a smoky grey-lacquered cedar hairbrush by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a small bottle of nail polish by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a peacock-feather quill by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an eagle-feather quill by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bottle of deep red merlot by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron warhammer by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a piece of sand-blasted goldenrod glass by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron stiletto by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an ivory Myr horn by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an iron sword scabbard by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of an oil painting of a wine arrangement by Goldenfawn.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate jar by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate flower pot by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate mortar by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a blue slate pestle by Carvale.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a tuft of dark red moss by Maena.", "Your guild has successfully earned 1 denarii for the sale of a bright yellow lemon by Maena." \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
