<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="001">
         "Type @compose my scroll to bring up a popup window where you can write your scroll."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="002">
         "Your gardening skill determines how nice the flowers you grow are, as well as what items you can make from the plants."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="003">
         "It is faster and cheaper to learn skills and careers from other player characters."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="004">
         "The clerk in Home Delights can sell you things to decorate your room with."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="005">
         "Typing @hotspots will tell you where other players are hanging out."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="006">
         "If you're an artist you can buy basic equipment at the painters studio."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="007">
         "Duels are illegal by law, but as long as you do them honorably and in the right location, nobody's going to bother."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="008">
         "The laws for the city can be found in the library, post office, and prison."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="009">
         "The punishment of crimes is based on evidence, testimony, and the judgement of the city guard member doing the investigating."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="010">
         "If you need lacquer for your furniture, ask the wheeler at the wood shop."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="011">
         "You can write messages on packages and gift boxes."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="012">
         "When you type @away you set your character away and it shows on the who list."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="013">
         "Typing who allows you to see who is online."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="014">
         "At the time of the last census five years ago, the population of the city of Rinascita was in excess of 55,000 people."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="015">
         "Using @remember and @forget allows you to manage the memories in your character's @recall."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="016">
         "To access the pages and information of your guild, type @guild to display a popup window."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="017">
         "When you type @idle name you can see how long a character has been idle for."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="018">
         "Typing @idle watch name allows you to keep track of when a character becomes active again."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="019">
         "To send a private out of character message to someone, just type @msg name followed by your text in quotes."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="020">
         "Typing @consent allow name you give that character consent to approach you and physically interact with you."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="021">
         "Type @consent allow all to allow all characters to get into your proximity."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="022">
         "Type @recall to see what memories are stored in your character."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="023">
         "@undress and @dress are useful commands to quickly remove all your worn items and clothes, and to wear them again in the same order."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="024">
         "If you regret starting a lesson or other activity which takes time, you can always type @stop to cancel it."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="025">
         "Type @readall to easily your scrolls or books in a popup window."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="026">
         "Lots of information about the game can be found on the forums, which you can access with the command @forum."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="027">
         "Storypoints can be used to get custom items or modifications."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="028">
         "Send an @assist to get in touch with staff if you have questions, complaints or ideas."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="029">
         "With storypoints you can buy a new character that starts with rank and lands."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="030">
         "Typing @help topic will display help files."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="031">
         "You can use the @event system to schedule, host, and announce events in the city."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="032">
         "Make sure to balance your @favor and @disfavor as it makes your opinions more valuable."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="033">
         "Spread out your @favor and @disfavor among many different characters to be properly heard."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="034">
         "To get rid of stuff, toss it in the trash or @discard it."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="035">
         "Food will go stale if you don't eat it."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="036">
         "@toggle linebreaks gives you spaces between text in the client."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="037">
         "@verb and @adverb are helpful commands to see different parser options available to you. For example, @verb a will return all verbs that start with the letter a. @adverb ab will return all adverbs that start with the letters ab."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="038">
         "Clothes can be made from rolls and bolts of fabric, if you have the right tools and skills."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="039">
         "Bars and rods of metal can be turned into weapons and jewelry if you have the skills and tools to do so."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="040">
         "If you want to pickpocket someone, make sure you stand next to them before attempting."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="041">
         "Touching and fighting with another will leave their scent on you."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="042">
         "@victim is a command you can toggle on to allow staff to see whether players consent to injuries during plots and events. Death consent is not given by using the @victim command, only injuries."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="043">
         "If you see a crime, report it to a City Guard member."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="044">
         "When you want to give testimony on a crime, contact a member of the City Guard."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="045">
         "If a consulate leader hasn't been around for a while, the active members of the consulate are given the chance to vote for a new leader."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="046">
         "The more you play, the more learning points you get each day. The maximum amount you can earn is determined by your account tier; free, basic, or premium."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="047">
         "Anyone can mix dye to produce some basic colors, but you need the dyer skill to make the special ones."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="048">
         "Your income can be used to rent boarding rooms, apartments, and even small farms."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="049">
         "To rent a room in the boarding house, ask the concierge for a key."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="050">
         "Only guilds and consulates can bid on items in the auction houses."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="051">
         "Some plants can be poisonous."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="052">
         "You can pick flowers from the plants and bushes you find in the game."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="053">
         "You can hide items everywhere, and others can search to find them."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="054">
         "Broadsheets for public announcements can be obtained from the couriers. You can hang them on walls where people can read them."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="055">
         "You can find both food and drinks in the inn."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="056">
         "Anyone has a chance of catching fish, even without the fishing skill."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="057">
         "Some of the NPCs will have quests for you."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="058">
         "If you want a fancy outfit, contact a tailor or seamstress in game."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="059">
         "One gold lira is the same as twenty-four silver florins."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="060">
         "You can type: withdraw from my money pouch \\"(amount you wish to withdraw)\\" to pull coins from your money pouch. You can also deposit your coins in your money pouch or offer the coins to the NPC in the bank to have it deposited."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="061">
         "The NPC at the bank can give you a promissory note that acts like a check for paying people through the mail."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="062">
         "Piazza Vecchia is at the center of the city. Most roads lead to this area and you can often find people gathered around the fountain there."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="063">
         "There is an emergency bell located near the Piazza Vecchia fountain if you need immediate assistance from a member of the City Guard, Militia, or medical community."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="064">
         "If you become injured, you should seek the attention of a healer as soon as you are able so that your wounds do not become infected."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="065">
         "The wilderness outside the protection of the city walls can be a very dangerous place filled with aggressive animals and shady characters."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="066">
         "Bookbinders can create all sorts of paper products including custom scrolls, books, folders, gift boxes, and invitations, as well as many other items."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="067">
         "Anyone can do some of the most basic hairstyles, but for a fancier style or a proper haircut, you will need to find a hairstylist in the game."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="068">
         "Weavers can spin, weave, and knit different kinds of raw fiber into many different varieties of material that can be used to craft clothing, home goods, books, and more."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="069">
         "Those with the skinning skill can skin animal carcasses to harvest the pelts for use in crafting many different items. The level of this skill determines the quality and amount you are able to harvest."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="070">
         "The cooking skill allows you to create many different kinds of food, from pasta and bread to roasted meats or soups and stews. The higher your skill, the more complex items you can create."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="071">
         "If you have the trapping skill, you can set a number of different kinds of traps to catch wild animals for their pelts and meat."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="072">
         "The lipreading skill allows some people to understand what you whisper to others, so always be careful what you say! It might come back to bite you."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="073">
         "Those people with the eavesdropping skill can pick up on what is being said in the other room. You never know who might be listening!"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="074">
         "A higher animal husbandry skill can make your efforts in tending livestock more fruitful."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="075">
         "Different sorts of livestock provide different resources. Some are available for purchase in the game while others are available through storypoint purchase only."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="076">
         "The City Market, located a little south of the Citadel, is filled with vendors and stalls for people to sell their wares."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="077">
         "There are a number of stables in the city and at the outpost where you can keep your horses safe."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="078">
         "You can use storypoints to purchase horses, ponies, mules, and donkeys to ride around town and through the wilderness."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="079">
         "You will find NPC teachers throughout the world who can teach you all the skills your class or classes allow you to learn as well as all the general skills available to everyone."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="080">
         "You will find workshops for crafters throughout the world, where you can buy materials and tools needed to make items. Specific guild types will allow you to craft without a timer if you are working in the correct workshop for your trade."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="081">
         "You can make copies of your room keys to share with friends and family members. Be sure you don't lose them, though! Anyone with the right key can get into your home or workspace."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="082">
         "@money will tell you how much you have in your bank account. @income will tell you how much you make a day and how much you spend in rent, as well as where."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="083">
         "The pay command allows you to pay people directly from your account. Syntax: pay \<amount\> to person"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="084">
         "Pay recall allows you to see the last incoming and outgoing payments you have made with the pay command."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="085">
         "The appraise skill determines the quality of items you purchase in game or pull from your inventory. The trading skill will help you barter for better deals when buying or selling to NPCs in the world."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="086">
         "A higher art skill allows you to create more complex paintings. Higher music skills allows you to play instruments better without making mistakes."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="087">
         "You can learn a number of different languages from other characters or through the NPC teachers found in the game world."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="088">
         "The @religion command allows you to set your religion to either Catholic or Protestant."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="089">
         "A higher fishing skill allows you to catch rarer fish that can be worth more at the various merchants who purchase them."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="090">
         "Depending on your rank or who you know, you can access different parts of the palace where the King and Queen reside."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="091">
         "Forte di Ricchezza is a military outpost and working class area located north of the wilderness area outside the city of Rinascita."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="092">
         "You will find a number of small settlements throughout the wilderness area outside the city walls, each one providing different stores and workshops, as well as farms that are available for purchase."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="093">
         "You can find a number of comprehensive help guides as well as the source material for the game under the help section of the website."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="094">
         "England is a Protestant nation ruled by Queen Liza Matthews."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="095">
         "In the summer of 1604, after King Heinrich's death, Prince Franz von Karlstadt inherited the rule of Protestant Germany, much to Queen Beatrix's disappointment."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="096">
         "With the Protestant Nation of Scotland being taken over by England, it is said their young Scottish King is seeking asylum in Catholic Italy."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="097">
         "Rinascita is not only the seat of power for the whole of Italy and the home of the Royal Family, but also the home of several merchants and tradesmen, producing much of Italy's commerce and fortune."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="098">
         "France is a Catholic nation ruled by King Roderic de la Puissance and his Italian wife, Queen Sonya."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="099">
         "King Joel Velazquez rules the Catholic nation of Spain alongside his Spanish wife, Queen Yasmin."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="100">
         "The Catholic nation of Italy is ruled by Empress Mirielle di Ricchezza, after the assassination of her husband King Dominic."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:show_tip">
         X[M] /* Returns a random tip */     
\$tips = this."*";     
\$tips["merry:lib:show_tip"] = nil;     
\$tips["revisions"] = nil;     
\$tips = map_values(\$tips);     
return \$tips[random(sizeof(\$tips))];
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1604973035, "ezralee", "E", 1604973304, "ezralee", "X", 1604974493, "ezralee", "E", 1604974530, "ezralee", "E", 1604975076, "ezralee", "E", 1604975134, "ezralee", "E", 1604975212, "ezralee", "E", 1604975291, "ezralee", "E", 1604975361, "ezralee", "E", 1604975645, "ezralee", "E", 1604975738, "ezralee", "E", 1604976023, "ezralee", "E", 1604976140, "ezralee", "E", 1604976238, "ezralee", "E", 1604976479, "ezralee", "E", 1604976527, "ezralee", "E", 1604976741, "ezralee", "E", 1604976807, "ezralee", "E", 1604976857, "ezralee", "E", 1604976927, "ezralee", "E", 1604978113, "ezralee", "E", 1604978166, "ezralee", "E", 1604978363, "ezralee", "E", 1604978433, "ezralee", "E", 1604978521, "ezralee", "E", 1604978612, "ezralee", "E", 1604979119, "ezralee", "E", 1604979203, "ezralee", "E", 1604979250, "ezralee", "E", 1604979346, "ezralee", "E", 1604979446, "ezralee", "E", 1604980610, "ezralee", "E", 1604980671, "ezralee", "E", 1604980750, "ezralee", "E", 1604980837, "ezralee", "E", 1604980963, "ezralee", "E", 1604981075, "ezralee", "E", 1604981151, "ezralee", "E", 1604981226, "ezralee", "E", 1604981321, "ezralee", "E", 1604981422, "ezralee", "E", 1604981511, "ezralee", "E", 1604981582, "ezralee", "E", 1604981667, "ezralee", "E", 1604981742, "ezralee", "E", 1605017374, "ezralee", "E", 1607992884, "ezralee", "E", 1613870855, "ezralee", "E", 1613871209, "ezralee", "E", 1613871363, "ezralee", "E", 1620781825, "ezralee", "E", 1620783004, "ezralee", "E", 1718398913, "annemairi", "E", 1718399011, "annemairi", "E", 1718399094, "annemairi", "E", 1720486555, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="1326528008" state="Open" user="tonyd">
           Type @compose my scroll to bring up a popup window where you can write your scroll
Type @readall to easily your scrolls or books in a popup window
Typing @help topic will display helpfiles
@toggle linebreaks gives you spaces between text in the client
You can purchase useful items in the tents in the market place
The donation box in the west commons often has useful items for those without funds
Creating your own guild just requires 50 denarii to buy the guild charter
Different Houses in the game has the right to import different things
Anyone has a chance of catching fish, even without the fishing skill or career
Finding a merchant to trade for you will give your more money when you sell fish
A merchant can help you buy better quality materials from the NPCs in game
It is faster and cheaper to learn skills and careers from other player characters
Typing @hotspots will tell you where other players are hanging out
The beggars will tell you rumours about other people if you ask about it
One aureal is the same as 24 denarii
The Bisclavret controls the import of lumber
The Doloreaux controls the import of gems and fine metals
The Avoirdupois controls the import of steel and fine fabrics
The Bisclavret is a house of wolves
The Doloreaux is a house of boars
The Avoirdupois is a house of horses
The Rinaldi is a house of foxes
Lots of information about the game can be found on the forums
Storypoints can be used to get custom items made for you in the game
Send an @assist to get in touch with staff if you have questions, complaints or ideas
With storypoints you can buy a new character that starts with rank and lands
Joining a guild can give you access NPC teachers if you can't find people in game to teach your
The pay you get from your guild can be saved up in the bank
In the auction house you will find many special items for sale
Using the @favor and @disfavor commands not only affects those you favor, but also your own chance of promotion
Make sure to balance your @favor and @disfavor as it makes your opinions more valuable
Spread out your @favor and @disfavor among many different characters to be properly heard
To get rid of stuff, toss it in the trash or @discard it
Income and skills from careers stack
Food will get stale if you don't eat it
If you can't find a Constable online, put a message in the fox-head carving outside the Gaol in Newtwon
Triskellian consists of three city parts; Docktown, Newtown and Oldtown
You can find the sweets shop in Newtown
The courier in Newtown will sell nicer things to you than the one in Docktown
There's also a bathing house in Newtown with nicer soaps and with towels
If you have an idea for a plot, send an @idea to staff outlining it
Each animal race have different attributes they are better at
If you want to smell people without them noticing, use the command scent
Use the @idle command to check how long a character has been idle
Each animal group has their own language
Clothes can be made from rolls and bolts of fabric, if you have the right tools and careers
Bars and rods of metal can be turned into weapons and jewellery if you have the career and tools to do so
If you want to pickpocket someone, make sure you stand next to them before attempting
The observation skill helps you spot pickpocketing, as well as hiding and finding items
Each House have their own language
Touching and fighting with another will leave their scent on you
Scents fade over time
If you see a crime, report it to a Constable
When you want to give testimony on a crime, use the @crime feature
If a guild leader hasn't been around for a while, the active members of the guild is given the chance to vote for a new leader
The more you play, the more learning points you get each day - though max 10
In Newtown you can buy dyes and fine fabrics
Anyone can mix dye to produce some basic colours, you need the dyer career to make the special ones.
Your income can be used to rent a room in the boarding house
Each room in the boarding house has special features
To rent a room in the boarding house, ask the concierge for a key
Armour can be useful defence, if you have the skill to use it
If you have skills from a career, you can teach yourself that skill individually to improve your rolls
Teaching yourself a skill costs more learning points than learning from another player character
Using the guild and house teachers can be expensive in learning points and costs money
What you say about people in @favor and @disfavor can end up as gossip with the beggars
The maid in the hallway outside the rooms in the inn has some juicy gossip
When you are a member of a guild or house, you can generate money or tokens for that guild to used
Only guilds and houses can bid on items in the auction houses
Everything is possible in Triskellian, a world of opportunities lie open
Seamstresses and tailors can make clothes, but only the needleworker can embroider, add buttons and make various accessories.
Some plants can be poisonous
You can pick flowers from the plants and bushes you find in the game
The apple tree down by the docks has delicious apples you can harvest
There are fruit trees scattered around in Triskellian if you get hungry
There's a nice beach just outside of Triskellian, find the crack in the wall to the east of the piers
The black market is the place for the shady people to trade and obtain illegal substances
You can hide items everywhere, and others can search to find them
Somewhere in Docktown is a trader who sells the illegal grains, but only to those who seem shady enough
Each career has its benefits and disadvantages, so choose wisely
You can find an overview the careers and their skills on the Ironclaw Online Discussion forums
The Ironclaw Online forums can be found at http://forum.skotos.net/forumdisplay.php?f=92
In game information about trading and guilds can be found at http://forum.skotos.net/forumdisplay.php?f=95
A day in Triskellian only lasts 8 hours
Broadsheets for public announcements can be obtained from the couriers, you can hang them on walls where people can read them
The brewery has some nice whiskey for sale
You can find both food and drinks in the inn
You will find the fishmonger on the docks, he will buy your fish and weeds
The fishing merchant on Dock Street sells fishing equipment
i the NPCs will have quests for you
The infirmary is found on Helloise Way
Wounds will heal on their own over time, but if you get a skilled healer to bandage them it's much faster
You can get a money pouch in the bank, this is also where you check your @account
There's access to the tailor's shop from the East Commons
In the tailors shop in Docktown you can find free clothing for your character
If you want a fancy outfit, contact a tailor or seamstress in game
The Gaol is found on Market Street in Newtown
You can find a nice and cozy cafe in Newtown that serves free coffee and tea
The marketplace is found in front of the Newtown gate
The sweets shoppe is found on Ambassador Drive just behind the Bisclavret embassy
Your gardening skill determines how nice the flowers you pick look like
All the embassies can be found on Peaceful Way
There's a dark and foreboding tunnel at the east end of Peaceful Way
You can find a small unkept graveyard in Newtown
If you die, S'Allumer might find mercy and resurrect you
Your dead body must be found and placed on the alter for resurrection to take place
The Cathedral is found in Newtown, close to the town gate
It's only in the Cathedral's crypt that you can be resurrected from
If you want a baby, you need to find a partner from the same species as you
S'Allumer is the official religion in Triskellian, though there are rumours of other practices
You can find the tournament arena on Lavender Street to the east in Newtown
To enter the northern part of Newtown, step through the waterfall
There are several parks in Newtown, good places for a romantic picnic
The parks has flowers and fruit trees that can be harvested
The nobles mostly stay in Newtown as they don't want the hassle of commoners to bother them
Typing @map will give you a map of the part of Triskellian you are in
Typing @world will give you a map of Calabria with the important towns and cities listed
The Avoirdupois comes from the plains in the east and their capitol is Chalon sur Sauldre
The Doloreaux comes from the mountains in the north and their capitol is Bruges
The Bisclavret comes from the forests in the west and their capitol is Harrowgate
The Avoirdupois makes some amazing fine wines
The Bisclavret knows how to make guns
There's a secret cellar under the warehouse in Docktown with free beer
You can practice your archery skills in the archery range on Helloise way
If you have the right tools and skills, you can pick locks you find in the game
The clerk in Home Delights can sell you things to decorate your room with
You can find the Home Delights on Helloise Way
Most NPC vendors in the game will give you a price list if you ask for it
Next to the Turret Tavern you will find a painters studio
If you're an arist you can buy basic equipment at the painters studio
The bartender in Turret Tavern on Helloise way sells nice juices and beers
You can find a secret room in one of the taverns in Docktown
There's a fairground on Helloise Way where you can test your skills in various games
You need the right password to open some doors in Docktown
There's a secret Lutarian grove in Triskellian
From Dock Street you will find an alley that leads to a training square
Duels are illegal by law, but as long as you do them honourably and in the right location, nobody's going to bother
Constables are obligated to file all crimes you press charge for, even if they know they're wrong
If a crime doesn't have enough testimonies and evidence, the guilty can't be punished
The Sailor's Guild have their headquarters on the corner of Dock Street and Market Street
The Trade House Tower is found on the corner of Market Street and Dockstreet
You can buy a guild charter in the Trade House Tower
The clerk in the Trade House Tower will sell you information about people's rank
From the top of the lighthouse on Dockstreet you have a magnificent view of the sea
The wood shop on Market Street will sell you basic lumber
If you need lacquer for your furniture, ask the wheeler at the wood shop
There's a small chapel in the west commons
The locksmith found in the west commons will sell you padlocks
You can write messages on packages and gift boxes
The courier in Dock Town sells newspapers
There's a guy on Market Circle who hands out random items the first time he meets a person
Important game information can be found at: http://forum.skotos.net/showthread.php?t=78072
A Guide to Life in Calabria can be found at: http://forum.skotos.net/showthread.php?t=52274
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
