<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="tonyd">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="cardback">
         "The back of the card is decorated with a fearsome dragon, painted in red, blue, green, and purple."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="cardfront">
         "The front of each card is decorated with an image indicating the meaning."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j1">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a barefooted man in ragged clothes carrying a stick upon his back."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j10">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of an old man standing upon a mountain peak, with a staff in one hand and a lantern containing a six-pointed star in the other."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j11">
         "The front of this card is decorated with an image of an eight-spoked wheel attended by a person donning an Egyptian headdress."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j12">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a woman leaning over a lion, clasping the beast's jaws."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j13">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a man hanging from a tree branch upside-down by one ankle."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j14">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a skeleton clad in full armor mounted upon a white horse. The skeleton carries a black and white flag in its left hand."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j15">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a person pouring liquid from one chalice into another."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j16">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of the Devil, with harpy feet, ram horns, bat wings, and a reversed pentagram upon his forehead. In his left hand he holds a torch."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j17">
         "The front of this card is decorated with an image of two nude figures fleeing from the open door of a burning building."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j18">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a naked woman kneeling by some water, with one foot in the water and one on land. A large star hangs in the sky above her head, surrounded by seven smaller stars."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j19">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a night scene featuring a wolf and a dog howling at the moon overhead. Flanking the animals on either side is a pair of large pillars."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j2">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a man standing behind a table upon which various game pieces and divination devices are scattered."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j20">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of an infant mounted upon a white horse. An anthropomorphized sun occupies much of the background, which is otherwise dotted with sunflowers."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j21">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of an angel blowing on a trumpet from which a white flag bearing a red cross hangs. The angel is surrounded by a group of humans."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j22">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a naked woman hovering above the Earth with a staff in each hand. A wreath surrounds the figure, and images of a human face, a lion, an ox, and an eagle are stationed in the four corners."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j3">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a woman clad in pale blue robes with a Papal tiara upon her head."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j4">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a woman seated upon a throne. She wears a crown of stars and holds a scepter in her raised right hand."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j5">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a bearded man seated upon a throne adorned with rams. He holds an Ankh scepter in his right hand and a globe in his left."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j6">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a man clad in a triple crown and red robe seated upon a throne between two pillars."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j7">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a couple receiving a blessing from a cleric."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j8">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a figure seated in a chariot pulled by two black and white sphinxes."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="description:j9">
         "The front of this card is decorated with a portrait of a seated man holding a golden scale in his left hand."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j1">"Fool card"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j10">
         "Hermit card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j11">
         "Wheel of Fortune card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j12">
         "Strength card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j13">
         "Hanged Man card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j14">
         "Death card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j15">
         "Temperance card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j16">
         "Devil card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j17">
         "Tower card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j18">"Star card"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j19">"Moon card"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j2">
         "Magician card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j20">"Sun card"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j21">
         "Judgment card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j22">
         "World card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j3">
         "High Priestess card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j4">
         "Empress card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j5">
         "Emperor card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j6">
         "Hierophant card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j7">
         "Lovers card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j8">
         "Chariot card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name:j9">
         "Justice card"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="names">
         ([ 1:"ace", 11:"Page", 12:"Knight", 13:"Queen", 14:"King" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="order">
         (\{ "J", "C", "P", "S", "W" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1218421734, "tonyd", "E", 1219359121, "rorschakovacs", "E", 1286496735, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1588808924, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809346, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809410, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809489, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809571, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809640, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809921, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588809937, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810059, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810073, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810132, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810225, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810328, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810403, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810455, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810520, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810535, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810600, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810735, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810822, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588810875, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811031, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811142, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811236, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811326, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811406, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811485, "sendnoodlez", "E", 1588811524, "sendnoodlez", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="suits">
         ([ "C":"Cups", "J":"Major Arcana", "P":"Pentacles", "S":"Swords", "W":"Wands" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="suits_prefix">" of "</Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
