<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details/>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="quest:introduction">
         (\{ (\{ "social", "skim", "", "actor", "assessingly", "", "3" \}), (\{ "social", "smile", "at", "actor", "warmly", "You are new here, aren't you?", "3" \}), (\{ "social", "ask", "", "actor", "helpfully", "Do you need help with anything?", "2" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:limit">0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:name">"Newbie"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:participant:reward"/>
      <Core:Property property="quest:requirements">
         ([  ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:reward">
         (\{ \<Ironclaw:Props:Newbie:pamphlet\>, 1 \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:01">
         ([ "action":"gosee", "finish_msg_success":(\{ (\{ "social", "wave", "at", "actor", "cheerfully", "Welcome to Triskellian!", "1" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Communication in Ironclaw is easy! There are hundreds of verb and adverb combinations at your fingertips that you can use to express your character's thoughts and feelings. \\"huff angrily\\" \\"laugh amusedly\\" \\"smile affectionately\\" are just a few examples of this. You can also target people and objects in the room you are in (ie. tap my foot on floor rhythmically) as well as DETAILS of people and objects (ie. shake Bob's hand excitedly). Visit URL for a full list of verbs and adverbs available to you.]", "5" \}) \}), "instructions":(\{ (\{ "social", "suggest", "to", "actor", "easily", "You should head over to the Welcome Center in Newtown and talk to Melanee. Just tell her you are new and she will teach you all you  need to know!", "1" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Use directional commands to navigate the game world (north, northeast, east, southeast, south, southwest, west, northwest, up, and down). You can also use shorthand versions of these commands for simplicity (n, ne, e, se, s, sw, w, nw, u, d).]", "5" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: The @map command will show an overview of Triskellian along with street names. Use the map and directional commands to find the corner of Market Street and Peaceful Way. Then go \\"east\\" and \\"north\\" to find the Welcome Center.]", "5" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: The @new and @chat commands also exist as tools to communicate with other players in the game world. To send a message on one of these chatlines, use the syntax: @chat \\"Hi! I could use some help.\\" You can also reach out to staff directly using the @assist command. @assist \\"Hi! I could use some help.\\"]", "5" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: One last thing! If you get stuck or can't remember how to complete your objective, use the @quest command to track your status and review objective instructions.  Happy gaming!]", "3" \}) \}), "next_step_success":"02", "param":(\{ "[Ironclaw:NPC:BrochureVendor]#45010" \}), "short_instructions":"Head over to the Welcome Center and find Melanee. Go to the corner of Market Street and Peaceful Way in Newtown and then go east and north. Then type: wave to melanee 'Hi, I am new. Can you help me?'", "triggers":(\{ "new", "newbie", "help", "maid", "concierge" \}) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:02">
         ([ "action":"gosee", "finish_msg_success":(\{ (\{ "social", "beam", "at", "actor", "excitedly", "Nice to meet you!", "1" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Ironclaw Online is considered a PG-13 game so keep this in mind when interacting with others.]", "3" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: If at any point you need to communicate out-of-character, please only use the @ooc, @chat, and @new commands to do so.]", "1" \}) \}), "instructions":(\{ (\{ "social", "chat", "to", "actor", "conversationally", "So... first things first! What is your name?", "1" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Verbs and adverbs can also be used in combination with evokes, which are spoken words denoted by quotation marks (introduce myself to melanee \\"My name is YOURNAME.\\"). Give it a try by introducing yourself to Melanee!]", "3" \}) \}), "next_step_success":"03", "param":(\{ "[Ironclaw:NPC:BrochureVendor]#45010" \}), "short_instructions":"Introduce yourself to Melanee. Type: introduce myself to melanee \\"My name is YOURNAME\\"", "triggers":(\{ "name" \}) ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:03">
         ([ "action":"command", "finish_msg_success":(\{ (\{ "social", "beam", "at", "actor", "", "I can provide you with reading material on various employment opportunities. Snoftil here handles the food and Murphy the clothes donations.", "3" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Look will give you a short summary of rooms, objects, and people and it is invisible to those in the room. Examine will give you a more detailed description but others will notice this and it could be interpreted as rude if you are caught \\"staring\\" at someone. You can also \\"look\\" and \\"examine\\" details of objects and people (\\"examine Bob's hair\\").]", "5" \}) \}), "instructions":(\{ (\{ "social", "gesture", "to", "here", "lightly", "The Welcome Center exists to help new arrivals like you acclimate to Triskellian. Why don't you take a few moments to have a look around.", "3" \}), (\{ "social", "smile", "", "", "warmly", "", "1" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Use the \\"look\\" and \\"examine\\" commands to assess your environment. Type: examine here]", "2" \}) \}), "next_step_success":"04", "param":(\{ "examine", "nil", "nil", "Ironclaw:World:NewTown:South:Buildings:WelcomeCenter:Main" \}), "short_instructions":"Use the \\"examine\\" command to examine the room. Type: examine here" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:04">
         ([ "action":"command", "finish_msg_success":(\{ (\{ "social", "grin", "at", "actor", "toothily", "Thank ye! Enjoy!", "2" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: Merchant characters play an important role in Triskellian as they can obtain better quality goods from merchants for discounted prices. This is especially important for crafter characters as the quality of their wares is based on the types of materials that they use.]", "4" \}) \}), "instructions":(\{ (\{ "social", "consider", "", "actor", "thoughtfully", "If you like, I can tell you a little about Triskellian. Grab a bite of food, browse the clothes and whenever you are ready to hear more, just have a seat!", "3" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: There are many NPCs (non-player characters) in Ironclaw Online, most of which are merchants who sell goods. To get a list of goods a merchant sells, use the syntax: ask NPC. Then to purchase an item on the list, type: ask NPC for ITEM. If you want to ask for a quantity of an item, put a number in front of the item name (ie. ask NPC for 10 ITEM). Try this out by asking Snoftil for a slice of scrapple (ask snoftil for scrapple). You can also use the @money command to check the amount of coin your character has available.]", "5" \}) \}), "next_step_success":"05", "param":(\{ "ask", "for", "[Ironclaw:NPC:HomelessFoodServer]#141272" \}), "short_instructions":"Take a look at Snoftil's inventory and then buy something. Remember the @money command is useful when checking the amount of money your character has at his or her disposal." ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:05">
         ([ "action":"command", "finish_msg_success":(\{ (\{ "social", "chatter", "", "", "nonstop", "Blah blah history stuff. This will go on for awhile.", "3" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "This will mark the end of the quest. Melanee will give the PC a pamplet that contains all the information the player has learned so far with some additional helpful commands related to communication, movement, and interaction.", "1" \}) \}), "instructions":(\{ (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: You can consume food and drinks using verbs such as eat, drink, nibble, sip, gobble, and guzzle. Smell and taste will also give you more information about consumables.]", "4" \}), (\{ "freemote", "actor", "[OOC: You can interact with many objects and details within the room (and your inventory). Sitting on an object or detail will move you within PROXIMITY of the object or detail. Sometimes there will be multiple of the same object and you will need to specify which one you wish to interact with (ie. sit on 3rd chair). To interact with an object in your inventory, you can use the MY keyword (ie. read my 4th scroll). You can take items from containers using the syntax: take ITEM from CONTAINER. Take a seat anywhere to listen to Melanee's spiel about Triskellian (sit on first chair, sit on floor, etc).]", "4" \}) \}), "param":(\{ "sit" \}), "short_instructions":"Have a seat using the \\"sit\\" verb" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:step:init">"01"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:steps">
         (\{ "01", "02", "03", "04", "05" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="quest:triggers">
         (\{ "help" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052085, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1305767332, "jominey", "R", 1305772801, "jominey", "R", 1305773594, "jominey", "R", 1305773701, "jominey", "R", 1306112864, "tonyd", "E", 1537046296, "jominey", "E", 1537048096, "jominey", "E", 1537051558, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:sync:idpsource">
         "ironclaw"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:sync:igdipro">
         "propose"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:sync:proposing-revision">
         1305773701
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
