<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="4"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="-"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="9"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="january"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="review"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="vol"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] ***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the Italian Consulate and Salvatore Costello personally.***\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Chapel Burned to Rubble (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Roderick and Orla Wounded by Arrows (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Vandalism at the Consulates (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1,000 Bounty on “Peace” Members (p. 3)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - January 9 - vol 4
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] Chapel Burned to Rubble!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 29, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At roughly 10 late on the 29th of December, bright orange lights were observed on the east side of Rinascita. The chapel on Strada di Guerra was discovered ablaze, and witnesses tried to pour buckets of water in vain to put out the fire. Unfortunately the fire grew and grew until the chapel was consumed entirely. Minutes later, the burning building caved into itself, smouldering into a pile of burning rubble. A search party entered the remains of the building, but did not find any survivors, corpses or other clues.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;While those assembled fought the blaze, a tall cloaked man appeared on the ramparts of the city walls and taunted Chief Constable Matteo. The cloaked figure reiterated that there had been warnings, and that his associates were always watching. He seemed to refer to posts on the public forums about Protestants returning to where they came from, and vandalism on the Consulates suggesting they’re not welcome in Rinascita.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] Lord Roderick and Orla Wounded by Arrows\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 22, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Roderick and Orla were each separately shot and wounded by an unknown assailant. Lord Roderick was attacked in the coffee house, and Orla was at the post office. A suspect was identified and confronted by Lord Nicolas, and a battle ensued. Both parties were injured, and the suspect was detained. While in custody, the suspect was treated for internal bleeding and infection, and died of these injuries while in custody. The suspect was later identified as Achmed, according to the Constabulary.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Vandalism at the Consulates\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 22, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Gus\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Recently it was discovered that every nation’s consulate was defaced in red paint. The vandalism was done in sticky blood red paint drips and oozes everywhere, spelling out the words "Peace is a lie! Go or die!" in crude, blocky lettering. The culprit to this acts is yet to be discovered, but is suspected to be affiliated with the “Peace” organization. The Constabulary has offered a bounty for the capture of these associates.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1,000 Bounty on “Peace” Members\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 30, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Chief Constable Matteo announced a 1,000 florin bounty, for each member of the “Peace” organization that is apprehended alive, or 500 florins if they’re brought in dead. The Chief specified one member by name, Decimus. Another man in a disguise cloak, notably wearing yellow accessory garments, is also wanted dead or alive.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] Gloria Sanchez Seeks Redemption for Her Crimes\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 4, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Isabelle Lopez\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;After the events that happened on the night of November 19th, Gloria Sanchez now desires to pay her debt of redemption for attacking the German Consulate member Arlo Haar.  Miss Sanchez is to write a letter to the Church and seek guidance in learning to control her anger. She has already made an apology to Mr. Haar and the German Consulate. Mr. Haar accepted her apology in hopes this will show Rinascita there can be forgiveness, and that we all can truly learn to live together in one place. Mr. Haar further extended his gratitude to Miss Sanchez by offering her a position when he and his sister open up their own business. Mr. Haar hope this will help Miss Sanchez get back on her feet and help aid with her anger with Germans. Miss Sanchez was filled with joy and hope as she accepted Mr. Haar’s offer. Gloria Sanchez’s release date has not been specified yet.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline’s Winter Skating Party\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Over a dozen brave souls attended Lady Emmaline’s “Winter Skating Party”, and many even strapped on bladed boots and ice-skated about on the rink just north of Piazza Vecchia.  The round skating rink was crafted from hay bales and boards surrounding a patch of smooth ice painstakingly created by pouring buckets of water over the surface of the pavement with time to allow each layer to freeze in the frigid cold temperatures.  Dorian and Maximillian provided festive music on their harps; the merchants sold brownies, black forest cake, banana bread and offered cinnamon schnapps, hot toddies, and mulled wine to drink.  Lady Agatha was on hand to treat the injured, and Chief Constable Matteo present to keep the peace.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] Although the Ambassadors for each of the Consulates were contacted for news about promotions, events and other announcements, none of them responded to the inquiry.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] Brother and Sister Hairstylist Duo Settle into Rinascita\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Isabelle Lopez\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The charming twins, Arlo and Ava Haar, have journeyed far from home to start a new life here in Rinascita. Originally from Germany, they came to Rinascita after a tragic fire accidently burned down their shop and home. Both Arlo and Ava are hoping to make names for themselves here among the citizens. When not stuffing his face with sweet pastries, Arlo is a talented stylist who is always seeking to perfect his skills. His tender sweetheart sister, Ava, enjoys getting to know her customers. She draws inspiration from her conversations with customers so that their hairstyle reflects their personality. They currently work at Smith and Dunst Barbering with Paul and Maurice. The barbering brother and scissoring sister plan to open a new shop on the northeastern part of Rinascita. They wish to continue styling and build on to make more of a spa and personal care business.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Rumors may be true, false, or somewhere in between. Though we try to vet rumors for legitimacy, what is listed on this page should not be taken for fact. If you want to submit a rumor, get in touch with Salvatore Costello.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sodomite Encounters\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There have been some whispered rumors of unusual noises coming from the female side of the bath house. Sources speak of two womanly shaped figures going into the bath house together at late hours. The sounds of pleasurable moans can be heard coming from the female bath area. Perhaps the church should start filling the baths with Holy Water. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heathen Ritualistic Activity\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;One night during the week of Christmas, there was a report of Heathen Worshiping happening within the city walls of Rinascita. Someone told the Review that three unidentified shadowy figures partook in demonic rituals that consisted of praying to false gods, risque dancing, and unconfirmed removing of clothing in public. Sources hint at they believe these are members of the Peace association.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Rumors
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring writers, salespeople and informants. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Curl Me Crazy is a guild Lacey created when she first came to the city with not a drop of coin to her name. She is so pleased and grateful to those who assisted her on my journey. Lacey is not a master stylist and it brings me great joy to offer my services to those who needed. Furthermore, Lacey is always seeking a protege or members to join the guild and be educated in the art that is beauty. Please contact Lacey through our courier should you wish to speak.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita City Guard is looking for applicants to serve our city and our gracious King. The City Guard pays its members well and there is room for growth within our organization. Those wishing to apply for the City Guard should contact Chief Constable Matteo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Need a personalised scroll box, or a fancy non-grey gift box? Or perhaps a book or journal to enter your sweet nothings or darkest thoughts? Maena Boutin, the city’s embinder can do just that for you!
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Salvatore"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         5
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1578570118
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] ***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the Italian Consulate and Salvatore Costello personally.***\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Chapel Burned to Rubble (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Roderick and Orla Wounded by Arrows (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Vandalism at the Consulates (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1,000 Bounty on “Peace” Members (p. 3)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - January 9 - vol 4
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] Chapel Burned to Rubble!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 29, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At roughly 10 late on the 29th of December, bright orange lights were observed on the east side of Rinascita. The chapel on Strada di Guerra was discovered ablaze, and witnesses tried to pour buckets of water in vain to put out the fire. Unfortunately the fire grew and grew until the chapel was consumed entirely. Minutes later, the burning building caved into itself, smouldering into a pile of burning rubble. A search party entered the remains of the building, but did not find any survivors, corpses or other clues.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;While those assembled fought the blaze, a tall cloaked man appeared on the ramparts of the city walls and taunted Chief Constable Matteo. The cloaked figure reiterated that there had been warnings, and that his associates were always watching. He seemed to refer to posts on the public forums about Protestants returning to where they came from, and vandalism on the Consulates suggesting they’re not welcome in Rinascita.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] Lord Roderick and Orla Wounded by Arrows\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 22, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Roderick and Orla were each separately shot and wounded by an unknown assailant. Lord Roderick was attacked in the coffee house, and Orla was at the post office. A suspect was identified and confronted by Lord Nicolas, and a battle ensued. Both parties were injured, and the suspect was detained. While in custody, the suspect was treated for internal bleeding and infection, and died of these injuries while in custody. The suspect was later identified as Achmed, according to the Constabulary.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Vandalism at the Consulates\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 22, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Gus\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Recently it was discovered that every nation’s consulate was defaced in red paint. The vandalism was done in sticky blood red paint drips and oozes everywhere, spelling out the words "Peace is a lie! Go or die!" in crude, blocky lettering. The culprit to this acts is yet to be discovered, but is suspected to be affiliated with the “Peace” organization. The Constabulary has offered a bounty for the capture of these associates.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1,000 Bounty on “Peace” Members\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 30, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Chief Constable Matteo announced a 1,000 florin bounty, for each member of the “Peace” organization that is apprehended alive, or 500 florins if they’re brought in dead. The Chief specified one member by name, Decimus. Another man in a disguise cloak, notably wearing yellow accessory garments, is also wanted dead or alive.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] Gloria Sanchez Seeks Redemption for Her Crimes\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 4, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Isabelle Lopez\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;After the events that happened on the night of November 19th, Gloria Sanchez now desires to pay her debt of redemption for attacking the German Consulate member Arlo Haar.  Miss Sanchez is to write a letter to the Church and seek guidance in learning to control her anger. She has already made an apology to Mr. Haar and the German Consulate. Mr. Haar accepted her apology in hopes this will show Rinascita there can be forgiveness, and that we all can truly learn to live together in one place. Mr. Haar further extended his gratitude to Miss Sanchez by offering her a position when he and his sister open up their own business. Mr. Haar hope this will help Miss Sanchez get back on her feet and help aid with her anger with Germans. Miss Sanchez was filled with joy and hope as she accepted Mr. Haar’s offer. Gloria Sanchez’s release date has not been specified yet.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline’s Winter Skating Party\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Over a dozen brave souls attended Lady Emmaline’s “Winter Skating Party”, and many even strapped on bladed boots and ice-skated about on the rink just north of Piazza Vecchia.  The round skating rink was crafted from hay bales and boards surrounding a patch of smooth ice painstakingly created by pouring buckets of water over the surface of the pavement with time to allow each layer to freeze in the frigid cold temperatures.  Dorian and Maximillian provided festive music on their harps; the merchants sold brownies, black forest cake, banana bread and offered cinnamon schnapps, hot toddies, and mulled wine to drink.  Lady Agatha was on hand to treat the injured, and Chief Constable Matteo present to keep the peace.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] Although the Ambassadors for each of the Consulates were contacted for news about promotions, events and other announcements, none of them responded to the inquiry.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] Brother and Sister Hairstylist Duo Settle into Rinascita\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;January 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Isabelle Lopez\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The charming twins, Arlo and Ava Haar, have journeyed far from home to start a new life here in Rinascita. Originally from Germany, they came to Rinascita after a tragic fire accidently burned down their shop and home. Both Arlo and Ava are hoping to make names for themselves here among the citizens. When not stuffing his face with sweet pastries, Arlo is a talented stylist who is always seeking to perfect his skills. His tender sweetheart sister, Ava, enjoys getting to know her customers. She draws inspiration from her conversations with customers so that their hairstyle reflects their personality. They currently work at Smith and Dunst Barbering with Paul and Maurice. The barbering brother and scissoring sister plan to open a new shop on the northeastern part of Rinascita. They wish to continue styling and build on to make more of a spa and personal care business.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Rumors may be true, false, or somewhere in between. Though we try to vet rumors for legitimacy, what is listed on this page should not be taken for fact. If you want to submit a rumor, get in touch with Salvatore Costello.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sodomite Encounters\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There have been some whispered rumors of unusual noises coming from the female side of the bath house. Sources speak of two womanly shaped figures going into the bath house together at late hours. The sounds of pleasurable moans can be heard coming from the female bath area. Perhaps the church should start filling the baths with Holy Water. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heathen Ritualistic Activity\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;One night during the week of Christmas, there was a report of Heathen Worshiping happening within the city walls of Rinascita. Someone told the Review that three unidentified shadowy figures partook in demonic rituals that consisted of praying to false gods, risque dancing, and unconfirmed removing of clothing in public. Sources hint at they believe these are members of the Peace association.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Rumors
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring writers, salespeople and informants. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Curl Me Crazy is a guild Lacey created when she first came to the city with not a drop of coin to her name. She is so pleased and grateful to those who assisted her on my journey. Lacey is not a master stylist and it brings me great joy to offer my services to those who needed. Furthermore, Lacey is always seeking a protege or members to join the guild and be educated in the art that is beauty. Please contact Lacey through our courier should you wish to speak.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita City Guard is looking for applicants to serve our city and our gracious King. The City Guard pays its members well and there is room for growth within our organization. Those wishing to apply for the City Guard should contact Chief Constable Matteo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Need a personalised scroll box, or a fancy non-grey gift box? Or perhaps a book or journal to enter your sweet nothings or darkest thoughts? Maena Boutin, the city’s embinder can do just that for you!
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1578570128
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">4</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
