<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="tunk_bodin">
  <Help:Node title="finances">
    <Log:Description>
       COMMAND USAGE:<br/>ask [merchant NPC]<br/>ask [merchant] for [item]<br/>pay [amount] to [player character]<br/>@money<br/><br/>Buying and selling are an integral part of IronClaw Online.<br/>
Many NPCs have items for sale. To check if an NPC can sell anything, you use the ask command. For example, if you wanted to know if the bartender sells anything, you would type:<br/>
ask bartender<br/>
If the NPC has something for sale, you'll see a list of what they can sell, along with how much that item costs. Some items are available for free.<br/>
Once you've decided on the item you want to buy, ask the NPC for the item. For example:<br/>
ask bartender for beer<br/>
Assuming you have enough money, you will get a message asking if you want to buy that item, to which you can answer @yes or @no. If you choose to buy it, the system will automatically make a haggling dice roll, to see how much of a discount your character manages to get, and then give you the item.<br/><br/>
To buy items from other players, just talk to them normally. You can pay them for the item using the PAY command. For example, if you wanted to pay 15 denarii to "John" you would type:<br/>
pay 15 to john<br/>
You can check how much money your character has with the @money command.<br/><br/>
If you want to post money to someone via the courier, you can get promissary notes from the bank clerk. You fill out the note saying how much you want to pay them, and sign it. Then whoever is holding the note can take it to the bank and collect the money. If you don't have enough money in the bank, the clerk will pay them as much as he can, and update the note to show how much is remaining.<br/>
As these commands transfer money directly, you don't see the coins themselves. If you want some coins for roleplaying reasons, you will need to visit the bank, and buy a money pouch from the clerk. You will be able to use the money pouch to withdraw coins. After a while the coins will vanish (and their value will be added back to your bank account) - if another character has the coins when they vanish, the value will be added to that other character's bank account. This allows you to roleplay handing coins over when paying if you prefer.<br/><br/>
Trade and money are key points of interest in Ironclaw Online depending what path you wish your character to take. Earning money is available in many ways including selling caught fish to NPCs. The team who made Ironclaw Online also wished to allow pure role-players an opportunity to enjoy some of the benefits that money offers without having to make it a personal goal to achieve the highest bank account balance. In order to facilitate this process, each career has a set amount of income that it recieves each day that character logs in as long as they did not earn any money from outside means. Essentially, you can survive on this small pittance but never get very far in the financial portion of the game world. This is to allow for small purchases to help with role-playing purposes and not meant as a means to get ahead in the world. Therefore, the starting salaries are quite small and if you truly wish to earn money then you can produce a higher income on your own.<br/>
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="account"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="bank"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="banking"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="deposit"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="finance"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="finances"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="income"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="money"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="set"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="withdraw"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1107875080, "dionar", "X", 1107875122, "dionar", "X", 1136677205, "rhenn", "E", 1137703549, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1187548251, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1187548997, "tunk_bodin", "X", 1187549004, "tunk_bodin", "R", 1309488366, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1379225979, "tonyd", "E", 1379230078, "tonyd", "E", 1379230269, "tonyd", "E", 1509727568, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
