<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="db:adverb">
         (\{ (\{ "grandly" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "conspiratorially" \}), (\{ "happily" \}), (\{ "cheekily" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "widely" \}), (\{ "again" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "widely" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "loudly" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:apos">
         (\{ (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pv" \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pp" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:evoke">
         (\{ (\{ "Hear ye, hear ye! All are commanded to celebrate the wedding of his Most High Lordship, Don Fidelio di Rinaldi, and his bride to be, Lady Amalsand Jakoba!" \}), (\{ "This wedding is going to be a blast!" \}), (\{ "Just reminding you all, not that you need it, the Don's wedding is happening on Jeudi, the first day of Thunder. [OOC: Saturday the 1st of July, 8pm Skotos time]" \}), (\{ "Did you know that there is free food from the wedding until the rest of the week. The Don wishes everyone to celebrate his wedding." \}), (\{ "I hear that the Jakoba family has ties to necromancers... but you didn't hear that from me" \}), (\{ "Y'know, all Rinaldi employees get free grog because of Don Fidelio's wedding to Lady Amalsand." \}), (\{ "I hear the Avoirdupois have stolen a chunk of land, rich in vinyards from the Doloreaux.... no, don't hit me... I'm just... horsing around..." \}), (\{ "The Don's wedding is happening on Jeudi. My cousin Bertram has got an invitation! [OOC: Saturday the 1st of July, 8pm Skotos time]" \}), (\{ "I hear that Vivienne and her consort, Boreas, will be attending the Don's wedding. But that might just be a rumor. [OOC: Saturday the 1st of July, at 8pm Skotos time]" \}), (\{ "The Don rules Triskellian, so his wedding is like a city-wide party! And free food and drinks for a week! Weeeee!" \}), (\{ "I hear a rumor that Lady Amalsand Jakoba used to date someone named Doctor Getheaht. Creepy name!" \}), (\{ "Do do.. I'm bored. Anyone not yet heard about the Don getting married? Yeah, I thought not..." \}), (\{ "I can't believe my shift isn't over yet." \}), (\{ "Everyone should celebrate, the ruler of our grand city is getting married on Jeudi!" \}), (\{ "Hear ye, the Don will be travelling through Docktown in his carriage right before the wedding, to allow the citizens to glimpse the wedding procession. Those with invites will follow to the Cathedrale de Temoine." \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj">
         (\{ nil, nil, (\{ (\{ "(here)" \}) \}), (\{ (\{ "my:head" \}) \}), nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, (\{ (\{ "my:fingernails" \}) \}), nil, (\{ (\{ "(here)" \}) \}), nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep">
         (\{ nil, nil, (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, (\{ nil \}), nil, (\{ nil \}), nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:verb">
         (\{ (\{ "announce" \}), (\{ "consider" \}), (\{ "tell" \}), (\{ "tilt" \}), (\{ "whisper" \}), (\{ "nod" \}), (\{ "grin" \}), (\{ "state" \}), (\{ "gossip" \}), (\{ "grin" \}), (\{ "gossip" \}), (\{ "examine" \}), (\{ "yawn" \}), (\{ "cheer" \}), (\{ "exclaim" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1309488042, "rorschakovacs", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
