<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="propriety"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="a"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="discussion"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="on"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] We at the French consulate are looking forward to starting a small series on manners and etiquette. We hope that by making this available to everyone, we can aid all among us to act cordially and with proper decorum in both public and any upcoming functions. This particular issue mainly consists of greetings and rank. We also hope you enjoy the little blurbs about upcoming events and accolades of citizens within the city. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Manners, etiquette, and proper decorum are duties that all of us should be doing on a daily basis. While small slip-ups are expected and often forgiven, it is typically found that having knowledge will help prevent these and any potentially bigger issues. Those who are content and happy with their place in life using proper manners can aid others in both their continued rise among the social ranks and prevent them from any downfalls.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By showing we are aware of ourselves and the social happenings going on around us, we can prove ourselves to those above us and reflect well on any who have taken us under their wings and reputation. We must also remember that our behavior is always an example to our peers and those who might be below and looking to us for guidance.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Hopefully this little guide will be of use to you or at the very least an interesting read. There are, of course, always different perspectives on greetings and manners depending not only on where the person came from, but also how they were raised. We have tried to keep these to generally accepted expectations. Should you find anything you wish to contest or that might need to be corrected, then please feel free to reach out so we can make adjustments in future papers.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We also encourage you to write to Thalia Solandis with any future subject matters you might like to see covered in this. It is our hope to cover a wide variety of issues and touch on things that one might come up against not only in day to day life, but also in rare or unique social situations. Please enjoy this paper, and feel free to reach out if you would like to further discuss any of the subjects placed within it.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] A Discussion on Propriety
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] Titles and Their Importance\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Most hierarchical countries are composed of a very similar ranking system. I shall list below the generally accepted hierarchy from the those of highest standing to those of more common place. Following this, we will discuss the differences between these ranks in a more in-depth manner. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;His Majesty\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Her Majesty\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Royal Highness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke/Duchess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Marquis/Marchioness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Margrave/Margravine\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Landgrave\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Count/Countess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Viscount/Viscountess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Baron/Baroness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Baronet/Baronetess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Knight/Dame\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Armigerous Gentry\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gentry\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thane\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Burgher\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Yeoman\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Freeman\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Typically, at the lower rungs of society are those of 'common' rank, which is considered anyone without title, thus, below the rank of gentry. Typically, thanes and below do not hold land freely, but often rent it from other parties. There are rare instances where enough is saved to allow purchase of a farm even without rank. Often those of this rank consist of tradesmen and crafters. In good times, these people fared well by the standards of the day. He and his family usually had enough to eat, and though work was hard, there was time, now and again, for him to take a holiday and enjoy life in the manner he most enjoyed: singing, dancing and drinking.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Nobles are often the elite of the countryside. This includes the ranks of gentry to baron. Often those of this rank hold land outright in their country of loyalty. The nobility often fill offices that transfer power, including, but not limited to, titles such as justices of peace, royal advisors, or lower members of households such as handmaidens or valets.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Among the nobility is the position of knight, which is no longer a military title. This rank can often be earned by those who earn it through service to the Crown. This is not a hereditary title and must be earned. Below knights are those holding the title of 'esquire,' either with or without the right to bear arms.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Viscounts and above are often considered 'peers' to royalty, which is to say they are not the same rank to those of the royal family, but of a similar enough status to have many of the same privileges. They are entitled to elaborate forms of address and shows of deference from all of their social inferiors. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Most members of the peerage inherit extensive lands and generous incomes, and though there are some commoners in town and country who have more money than many of the nobility, the richest people tend to be those of the peerage. The higher the rank, the higher is the status of the holder. Status, however, does not intrinsically imply power. Power can also be achieved through one's office, one's income, or perhaps most importantly, the favor of one's monarch and those closest to them, for all power flows from them.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Titles and Their Importance
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] One should always be mindful of one's company. Often in parties, public settings, or small events, there will be a multitude of people around. While some of those people might be of a lower or equal rank to you, there is just as often the chance that someone of a higher rank might be around as well. If you leave yourself unaware to this fact, it could later prove disastrous for your reputation. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You often need to adjust yourself to the room you are in. If one is in a room with those of lower social standing or perhaps a room of peers and equals, it will allow one to be a little more relaxed in demeanor. However, if you are not in fact the highest ranking, then you should make sure your behavior is reflective and respectful to the highest ranking member in company. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;If there is a high or higher ranking member of society with whom you are only acquaintances or associated with, then you should strive to use all proper social duties and niceties. Your behavior will be something for those in the room that are of lower standing to reflect off of. It is also a benefit to yourself to show those of higher rank that you are capable of good manners and form. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Should you find yourself in a smaller or more intimate setting with those of higher rank that you have a distinct knowledge are in fact your friends, then you might allow yourself a more relaxed demeanor. Always be aware of what your higher-ranked friend is comfortable with. It is in both friends' best interest to make sure you are each pleased with the level of comfort and familiarity between you. If someone chances upon you or enters the space and either one or both of you are not on proper, friendly terms, then you should immediately return to proper behavior.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;If someone sees you being more casual with those of higher rank, this might make them feel comfortable enough to also attempt this same level of casualness. This could make things awkward for your friend of higher standing because now they are either forced to accept this casualness when they did not permit it, or it puts them in a position where they now need to chide and reprimand those with a false sense of confidence. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the other hand, if you are caught presenting a more relaxed demeanor with those below you it could in fact cause you issues in the future. If you are enjoying the company of those within the same social standing or above, and someone from a lower social rank appears and starts teasing or joking around with you, it could be taken as offensive to those around you. Thus, you are now in the awkward social position of being forced to reprimand your friend's behavior in public.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Please try to always be aware of those around you and the situations you find yourself in. While small and occasional slip-ups are something that are bound to happen, being aware of your surroundings are very likely to reduce any offense or embarrassment that can occur in mixed social company. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Mixed Rank
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] Failing to understand the differences between friends and acquaintances can quickly become the biggest problem for someone's growth, either personally, socially, or in business. We interact and deal with so many people daily that it is easy to forget our own awareness of the situations and people happening around us. What might be permissible or even encouraged among friends could possibly be seen as poor form among mere acquaintances. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Often, acquaintances are those you've only recently met or perhaps those you have known awhile whose social or business circles you do not frequent. You know very little of them aside from kind pleasantries and surface knowledge. A friend, on the other hand, is someone with whom you spend a good deal more time. They have a deeper knowledge of you, and you also have a deeper knowledge of them. This allows you to know if your demeanor and behaviors work well together.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once you have a deeper knowledge of each other, you can judge what behaviors are easier for them to accept or encourage. This will allow you to continue with the friendship, hopefully without awkwardness of any behaviors they might disapprove of. It also allows you to navigate closer to them personally, thus becoming associated with them and their reputation. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Friends are often encouraged or even expected to help each other in both society and life. A friend might aid you in moving things from one home to another, and they also might feel more inclined to produce proper introductions. These proper introductions could benefit you in business and with your own social status provided your friend has a reputation \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Believing certain people are your friends when they aren't can be dangerous. Often the people that you think to be your friends are really just acquaintances. Friendship means being honest with each other, sharing between each other to both grow and develop. If you cannot be honest to people and trust them to have your best interest at heart, in return then they aren't providing their end of the friendship. This doesn't mean they are bad people or out to get you, but simply they you haven't developed the relationship enough for it to be so. This should be a two-way street, and, while you shouldn't be keeping score, there needs to be a give and take so that both you and the relationship can approve. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;That isn't to say one should have a 'I know who my friends are, and I won't talk to anyone else' mentality. This can be a very dangerous thought process as it's based off of a 'nationalistic' mentality. This is a very counterproductive type of thought pattern. As a constantly growing person, you have experiences and wisdom that can be given to those outside of your circle. This allows both them and you to grow. Completely ignoring others not only hurts growing opportunities, but might cut you off from any potential and surprising friends in the future.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Friends vs. Acquaintances
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] Proper introductions are quite important. Generally speaking, it is considered improper to address someone without proper introductions, typically by a mutual friend or acquaintance. If one wishes to be most correct in their etiquette, it is best to consult both parties involved in making sure they actually wish to for introduction. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;However, this is for those in equal social standing. When a difference resides in social standing, one should ask the lady of highest rank if she wishes to have the introduction made. While being careful to make sure that your question is not too loud or obvious, one may pleasantly ask, "Lady E., may I introduce Miss L. to you?" thus allowing the introduction to be kindly declined if it is not wanted. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Should an answer be received in the affirmative, then an introduction would follow. The lady or person of lower rank is always introduced to the lady of higher rank, never the other way around. It is also considered in bad taste to repeat the names of those in reverse. Once naming the names of those who are to be introduced to each other, is all that etiquette requires; more than this would be a breach of it and, therefore, not to be indulged in.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once the introduction has been made (ex:'Mrs L.—the Duchess of B.,'), the two ladies so introduced show reverence to each other either via curtsy, dip, or a polite nod and make some little pleasant, civil speech, such as 'Very happy to make your acquaintance,' or 'I wanted so much to know you. I have heard so much of you.'\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;When it is a question of 'garden-parties,' 'five-o'clock teas,' small 'at homes,' etc., gentlemen would be introduced to ladies by the hostess, or at least the principal guests would be so introduced, for the purpose of the gentlemen escorting the ladies to tea or supper, in the event of no other gentleman being present at the moment with whom they were already acquainted. Should a lady be present at such an event without friends or acquaintances then the hostess would be able to introduce the lady without consulting her. The gentleman, knowing why he was presented to any particular lady, would immediately ask the lady’s leave to take her to tea or supper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;With regard to introducing gentlemen to each other, it is not as a rule necessary to do so. If they wish to make each other’s acquaintance, supposing some very particular reason exists why they should do so, or there is some powerful reason which would commend itself to the person making the presentation, or else to the person whose acquaintance was desired, the gentlemen may ask their host or hostess for such an introduction, without risk of their wish being refused, or their acquaintance declined ; but when no such reason exists, the gentlemen, as a rule, are content to talk to the gentlemen they already know, without seeking to extend the circle of their friends and acquaintances.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Introductions
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] The mark of polite society and a good upbringing is to do one's duty in showing all proper marks of deference and respect. The first of these duties is to use the proper form of address. Often, the use of this duty is an easy way to distinguish between those of higher rank and lower. Below we will supply common forms of address and when and where to use them. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thee/Thou: The familiar second person singular. Used with good friends, children, social inferiors and animals, with the possible exception of horses, depending of course on the pedigree of the horse. Also used to address God.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You: Formal second person singular, for mere acquaintances, strangers and social superiors. The formal second person plural is "Ye."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister: A respectful term used in a wide variety of contexts. Generally used for gentlemen, professional men, and substantial citizens. It could be used, respectfully, with either or both the first and last names. It could be used without the name appended in the familiar context of a servant addressing his master. The female form is "Miss," which in most contexts did not have the sexual meaning it does today.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Honor/Your Worship: An all purpose form of address for all men of higher status than oneself. Particularly appropriate for justices of the peace and the like. A standard form of address for a knight.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir: Another all purpose form of address for all men of higher status and a formal form of address for equals. Also a title for knights, with "Sir" followed by the first name (e.g. "Sir Thomas"). The female form is Madame in address, though the title is "Lady" as in "Lady Jane." "Lady" could also be a formal and respectful address, in the manner of Sir or Madame.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;My Lord/My Lady: The form of address for any noble or "lord of the Church" such as a bishop. NOT appropriate for a knight. Other forms include "Lord", "Lady," or "Your Lordship/Your Ladyship." As a title, it is followed not by the given name, but by the place of which the person is lord or lady - "Lord Burghley" was actually named William Cecil, but he was the Baron Burghley.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Grace: Appropriate for a male or female noble of the rank of duke or higher. Also appropriate and common for members of the direct royal line.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Excellency: Appropriate for a holder of a high office, such as the high constable.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Highness: For any member of the direct royal line. In current usage, it is for princes, princesses, and archdukes.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Majesty: Only appropriate for the Monarch.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;My Liege: Usually reserved for the Monarch, was also suitable for other "liege lords" to whom one owed a bond of fealty.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Forms of Address
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] We have delved into many subjects within this paper, and there are still many yet to cover. However, we would like to take a brief pause to acknowledge those around us, not only for their examples of etiquette, but the efforts they put into this city and into themselves. Please note that our space on this page is limited, so some deserving people likely might have been left out, but we shall continue to try to acknowledge all good deeds and efforts in the next paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Margrat - Ambassador Margrat has come a very long way since first arriving in the city. She is always willing to step off to the side to solve any potential conflicts and strives to be an uplifting force in the community. She continues to show examples of growth and learning as she navigates her new role, and we have high hopes for her success.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dame Valeria - Dame Valeria shows continuous grace and social awareness in all situations. She makes herself pleasant company for all involved and shows apt skill in flowing conversations.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dean Persephone - Dean Persephone continues to provide benefits to both France and Italy as she takes on new challenges and responsibilities at the University of Rinascita. She is always able to extract herself from any tense or potentially improper situations. We look forward to watching her continued growth.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dame Ava - Dame Ava has been a continued advocate for togetherness and problem solving. She has been diligent in her continued efforts of bringing the city together, often hosting little gatherings and promoting friendliness and polite conflict resolution. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Trevyn - As Ambassador of the German consulate, Lord Trevyn has been a continual example of propriety and social graces. He has been a huge benefit in conflict resolution throughout the city and is always polite in anything that arises in public. He always has time to linger and chat with, continually mindful of decorum. We look forward to continuing working together to promote a positive city. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Jean - Lord Jean shows an ever patient social grace. No matter the situation or happenings around him he maintains a level head and kind countenance. He remains cordial and kind to all while upholding propriety. We look forward to his continuing examples for which to strive towards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sergeant Miles - Sergeant Miles, while a recent arrival to town, shows an eagerness to aid the city. He is eager to help boost the economy within our fair city. He also has shown to maintain his composure and friendly attitude through any interaction. We look forward to seeing him succeed \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Toddia - While Ambassador Toddia is new to her role as ambassador of the English consulate she has continued to make improvements not only for herself, but for the city. She has taken a far more active role among the people. She is clearly trying hard to provide success to her new role, and we wish her all success in it.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Accolades
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read this paper. Any questions or comments can be directed to Thalia Solandis or Lady Emmaline Beaumont\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Thank You
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Lady Emmaline"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         5
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1603066429
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="misc:lastdropped">
         "1601357162 /usr/SkotOS/merry/2bfb8f3a9ac5886548b27853f3628ff3"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:em:emmaline\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] We at the French consulate are looking forward to starting a small series on manners and etiquette. We hope that by making this available to everyone, we can aid all among us to act cordially and with proper decorum in both public and any upcoming functions. This particular issue mainly consists of greetings and rank. We also hope you enjoy the little blurbs about upcoming events and accolades of citizens within the city. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Manners, etiquette, and proper decorum are duties that all of us should be doing on a daily basis. While small slip-ups are expected and often forgiven, it is typically found that having knowledge will help prevent these and any potentially bigger issues. Those who are content and happy with their place in life using proper manners can aid others in both their continued rise among the social ranks and prevent them from any downfalls.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By showing we are aware of ourselves and the social happenings going on around us, we can prove ourselves to those above us and reflect well on any who have taken us under their wings and reputation. We must also remember that our behavior is always an example to our peers and those who might be below and looking to us for guidance.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Hopefully this little guide will be of use to you or at the very least an interesting read. There are, of course, always different perspectives on greetings and manners depending not only on where the person came from, but also how they were raised. We have tried to keep these to generally accepted expectations. Should you find anything you wish to contest or that might need to be corrected, then please feel free to reach out so we can make adjustments in future papers.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We also encourage you to write to Thalia Solandis with any future subject matters you might like to see covered in this. It is our hope to cover a wide variety of issues and touch on things that one might come up against not only in day to day life, but also in rare or unique social situations. Please enjoy this paper, and feel free to reach out if you would like to further discuss any of the subjects placed within it.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] A Discussion on Propriety
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] Titles and Their Importance\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Most hierarchical countries are composed of a very similar ranking system. I shall list below the generally accepted hierarchy from the those of highest standing to those of more common place. Following this, we will discuss the differences between these ranks in a more in-depth manner. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;His Majesty\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Her Majesty\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Royal Highness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Duke/Duchess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Marquis/Marchioness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Margrave/Margravine\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Landgrave\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Count/Countess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Viscount/Viscountess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Baron/Baroness\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Baronet/Baronetess\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Knight/Dame\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Armigerous Gentry\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gentry\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thane\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Burgher\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Yeoman\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Freeman\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Typically, at the lower rungs of society are those of 'common' rank, which is considered anyone without title, thus, below the rank of gentry. Typically, thanes and below do not hold land freely, but often rent it from other parties. There are rare instances where enough is saved to allow purchase of a farm even without rank. Often those of this rank consist of tradesmen and crafters. In good times, these people fared well by the standards of the day. He and his family usually had enough to eat, and though work was hard, there was time, now and again, for him to take a holiday and enjoy life in the manner he most enjoyed: singing, dancing and drinking.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Nobles are often the elite of the countryside. This includes the ranks of gentry to baron. Often those of this rank hold land outright in their country of loyalty. The nobility often fill offices that transfer power, including, but not limited to, titles such as justices of peace, royal advisors, or lower members of households such as handmaidens or valets.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Among the nobility is the position of knight, which is no longer a military title. This rank can often be earned by those who earn it through service to the Crown. This is not a hereditary title and must be earned. Below knights are those holding the title of 'esquire,' either with or without the right to bear arms.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Viscounts and above are often considered 'peers' to royalty, which is to say they are not the same rank to those of the royal family, but of a similar enough status to have many of the same privileges. They are entitled to elaborate forms of address and shows of deference from all of their social inferiors. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Most members of the peerage inherit extensive lands and generous incomes, and though there are some commoners in town and country who have more money than many of the nobility, the richest people tend to be those of the peerage. The higher the rank, the higher is the status of the holder. Status, however, does not intrinsically imply power. Power can also be achieved through one's office, one's income, or perhaps most importantly, the favor of one's monarch and those closest to them, for all power flows from them.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Titles and Their Importance
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] One should always be mindful of one's company. Often in parties, public settings, or small events, there will be a multitude of people around. While some of those people might be of a lower or equal rank to you, there is just as often the chance that someone of a higher rank might be around as well. If you leave yourself unaware to this fact, it could later prove disastrous for your reputation. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You often need to adjust yourself to the room you are in. If one is in a room with those of lower social standing or perhaps a room of peers and equals, it will allow one to be a little more relaxed in demeanor. However, if you are not in fact the highest ranking, then you should make sure your behavior is reflective and respectful to the highest ranking member in company. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;If there is a high or higher ranking member of society with whom you are only acquaintances or associated with, then you should strive to use all proper social duties and niceties. Your behavior will be something for those in the room that are of lower standing to reflect off of. It is also a benefit to yourself to show those of higher rank that you are capable of good manners and form. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Should you find yourself in a smaller or more intimate setting with those of higher rank that you have a distinct knowledge are in fact your friends, then you might allow yourself a more relaxed demeanor. Always be aware of what your higher-ranked friend is comfortable with. It is in both friends' best interest to make sure you are each pleased with the level of comfort and familiarity between you. If someone chances upon you or enters the space and either one or both of you are not on proper, friendly terms, then you should immediately return to proper behavior.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;If someone sees you being more casual with those of higher rank, this might make them feel comfortable enough to also attempt this same level of casualness. This could make things awkward for your friend of higher standing because now they are either forced to accept this casualness when they did not permit it, or it puts them in a position where they now need to chide and reprimand those with a false sense of confidence. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the other hand, if you are caught presenting a more relaxed demeanor with those below you it could in fact cause you issues in the future. If you are enjoying the company of those within the same social standing or above, and someone from a lower social rank appears and starts teasing or joking around with you, it could be taken as offensive to those around you. Thus, you are now in the awkward social position of being forced to reprimand your friend's behavior in public.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Please try to always be aware of those around you and the situations you find yourself in. While small and occasional slip-ups are something that are bound to happen, being aware of your surroundings are very likely to reduce any offense or embarrassment that can occur in mixed social company. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Mixed Rank
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] Failing to understand the differences between friends and acquaintances can quickly become the biggest problem for someone's growth, either personally, socially, or in business. We interact and deal with so many people daily that it is easy to forget our own awareness of the situations and people happening around us. What might be permissible or even encouraged among friends could possibly be seen as poor form among mere acquaintances. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Often, acquaintances are those you've only recently met or perhaps those you have known awhile whose social or business circles you do not frequent. You know very little of them aside from kind pleasantries and surface knowledge. A friend, on the other hand, is someone with whom you spend a good deal more time. They have a deeper knowledge of you, and you also have a deeper knowledge of them. This allows you to know if your demeanor and behaviors work well together.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once you have a deeper knowledge of each other, you can judge what behaviors are easier for them to accept or encourage. This will allow you to continue with the friendship, hopefully without awkwardness of any behaviors they might disapprove of. It also allows you to navigate closer to them personally, thus becoming associated with them and their reputation. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Friends are often encouraged or even expected to help each other in both society and life. A friend might aid you in moving things from one home to another, and they also might feel more inclined to produce proper introductions. These proper introductions could benefit you in business and with your own social status provided your friend has a reputation \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Believing certain people are your friends when they aren't can be dangerous. Often the people that you think to be your friends are really just acquaintances. Friendship means being honest with each other, sharing between each other to both grow and develop. If you cannot be honest to people and trust them to have your best interest at heart, in return then they aren't providing their end of the friendship. This doesn't mean they are bad people or out to get you, but simply they you haven't developed the relationship enough for it to be so. This should be a two-way street, and, while you shouldn't be keeping score, there needs to be a give and take so that both you and the relationship can approve. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;That isn't to say one should have a 'I know who my friends are, and I won't talk to anyone else' mentality. This can be a very dangerous thought process as it's based off of a 'nationalistic' mentality. This is a very counterproductive type of thought pattern. As a constantly growing person, you have experiences and wisdom that can be given to those outside of your circle. This allows both them and you to grow. Completely ignoring others not only hurts growing opportunities, but might cut you off from any potential and surprising friends in the future.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Friends vs. Acquaintances
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] Proper introductions are quite important. Generally speaking, it is considered improper to address someone without proper introductions, typically by a mutual friend or acquaintance. If one wishes to be most correct in their etiquette, it is best to consult both parties involved in making sure they actually wish to for introduction. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;However, this is for those in equal social standing. When a difference resides in social standing, one should ask the lady of highest rank if she wishes to have the introduction made. While being careful to make sure that your question is not too loud or obvious, one may pleasantly ask, "Lady E., may I introduce Miss L. to you?" thus allowing the introduction to be kindly declined if it is not wanted. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Should an answer be received in the affirmative, then an introduction would follow. The lady or person of lower rank is always introduced to the lady of higher rank, never the other way around. It is also considered in bad taste to repeat the names of those in reverse. Once naming the names of those who are to be introduced to each other, is all that etiquette requires; more than this would be a breach of it and, therefore, not to be indulged in.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once the introduction has been made (ex:'Mrs L.—the Duchess of B.,'), the two ladies so introduced show reverence to each other either via curtsy, dip, or a polite nod and make some little pleasant, civil speech, such as 'Very happy to make your acquaintance,' or 'I wanted so much to know you. I have heard so much of you.'\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;When it is a question of 'garden-parties,' 'five-o'clock teas,' small 'at homes,' etc., gentlemen would be introduced to ladies by the hostess, or at least the principal guests would be so introduced, for the purpose of the gentlemen escorting the ladies to tea or supper, in the event of no other gentleman being present at the moment with whom they were already acquainted. Should a lady be present at such an event without friends or acquaintances then the hostess would be able to introduce the lady without consulting her. The gentleman, knowing why he was presented to any particular lady, would immediately ask the lady’s leave to take her to tea or supper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;With regard to introducing gentlemen to each other, it is not as a rule necessary to do so. If they wish to make each other’s acquaintance, supposing some very particular reason exists why they should do so, or there is some powerful reason which would commend itself to the person making the presentation, or else to the person whose acquaintance was desired, the gentlemen may ask their host or hostess for such an introduction, without risk of their wish being refused, or their acquaintance declined ; but when no such reason exists, the gentlemen, as a rule, are content to talk to the gentlemen they already know, without seeking to extend the circle of their friends and acquaintances.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Introductions
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] The mark of polite society and a good upbringing is to do one's duty in showing all proper marks of deference and respect. The first of these duties is to use the proper form of address. Often, the use of this duty is an easy way to distinguish between those of higher rank and lower. Below we will supply common forms of address and when and where to use them. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thee/Thou: The familiar second person singular. Used with good friends, children, social inferiors and animals, with the possible exception of horses, depending of course on the pedigree of the horse. Also used to address God.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You: Formal second person singular, for mere acquaintances, strangers and social superiors. The formal second person plural is "Ye."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister: A respectful term used in a wide variety of contexts. Generally used for gentlemen, professional men, and substantial citizens. It could be used, respectfully, with either or both the first and last names. It could be used without the name appended in the familiar context of a servant addressing his master. The female form is "Miss," which in most contexts did not have the sexual meaning it does today.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Honor/Your Worship: An all purpose form of address for all men of higher status than oneself. Particularly appropriate for justices of the peace and the like. A standard form of address for a knight.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir: Another all purpose form of address for all men of higher status and a formal form of address for equals. Also a title for knights, with "Sir" followed by the first name (e.g. "Sir Thomas"). The female form is Madame in address, though the title is "Lady" as in "Lady Jane." "Lady" could also be a formal and respectful address, in the manner of Sir or Madame.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;My Lord/My Lady: The form of address for any noble or "lord of the Church" such as a bishop. NOT appropriate for a knight. Other forms include "Lord", "Lady," or "Your Lordship/Your Ladyship." As a title, it is followed not by the given name, but by the place of which the person is lord or lady - "Lord Burghley" was actually named William Cecil, but he was the Baron Burghley.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Grace: Appropriate for a male or female noble of the rank of duke or higher. Also appropriate and common for members of the direct royal line.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Excellency: Appropriate for a holder of a high office, such as the high constable.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Highness: For any member of the direct royal line. In current usage, it is for princes, princesses, and archdukes.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Your Majesty: Only appropriate for the Monarch.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;My Liege: Usually reserved for the Monarch, was also suitable for other "liege lords" to whom one owed a bond of fealty.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Forms of Address
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] We have delved into many subjects within this paper, and there are still many yet to cover. However, we would like to take a brief pause to acknowledge those around us, not only for their examples of etiquette, but the efforts they put into this city and into themselves. Please note that our space on this page is limited, so some deserving people likely might have been left out, but we shall continue to try to acknowledge all good deeds and efforts in the next paper.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Margrat - Ambassador Margrat has come a very long way since first arriving in the city. She is always willing to step off to the side to solve any potential conflicts and strives to be an uplifting force in the community. She continues to show examples of growth and learning as she navigates her new role, and we have high hopes for her success.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dame Valeria - Dame Valeria shows continuous grace and social awareness in all situations. She makes herself pleasant company for all involved and shows apt skill in flowing conversations.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dean Persephone - Dean Persephone continues to provide benefits to both France and Italy as she takes on new challenges and responsibilities at the University of Rinascita. She is always able to extract herself from any tense or potentially improper situations. We look forward to watching her continued growth.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Dame Ava - Dame Ava has been a continued advocate for togetherness and problem solving. She has been diligent in her continued efforts of bringing the city together, often hosting little gatherings and promoting friendliness and polite conflict resolution. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Trevyn - As Ambassador of the German consulate, Lord Trevyn has been a continual example of propriety and social graces. He has been a huge benefit in conflict resolution throughout the city and is always polite in anything that arises in public. He always has time to linger and chat with, continually mindful of decorum. We look forward to continuing working together to promote a positive city. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lord Jean - Lord Jean shows an ever patient social grace. No matter the situation or happenings around him he maintains a level head and kind countenance. He remains cordial and kind to all while upholding propriety. We look forward to his continuing examples for which to strive towards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sergeant Miles - Sergeant Miles, while a recent arrival to town, shows an eagerness to aid the city. He is eager to help boost the economy within our fair city. He also has shown to maintain his composure and friendly attitude through any interaction. We look forward to seeing him succeed \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Toddia - While Ambassador Toddia is new to her role as ambassador of the English consulate she has continued to make improvements not only for herself, but for the city. She has taken a far more active role among the people. She is clearly trying hard to provide success to her new role, and we wish her all success in it.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Accolades
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read this paper. Any questions or comments can be directed to Thalia Solandis or Lady Emmaline Beaumont\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Thank You
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1603066435
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">2</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1600133394
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
