<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="two"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="-"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="glamorous"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="issue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="life"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="of"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] I have lived in Rinascita for seven years, which is not as long a time as others. However, in my brief years here, I have seen a lot. I've seen people rise and fall, and guilds thrive and decay. I have experienced my gloomiest and happiest times in this city. Throughout all of that, one thing has always remained absolute. Rinascita represents a city where you can become the most efficient version of yourself. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;This is why I established this paper, to showcase the best parts of my home. To show that it does not matter where you come from or what you know. Those who know me know I am an orphan who was not always the woman I am today. Rinascita enveloped me into its arms as a mother would a babe and aided me through my struggles. The people here showed me how to discover everything I did not know I needed. Even so, there is always more for me to learn, but without this city, I do not know where I would be. Therefore, my paper will eternally honor Rinascita and everyone within it.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Two - The Crown's Royal Court, III\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Three - Eminent Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Four - Guild Spotlight\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Five - The Art of Gardening\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Six - An Insight of a Newcomer\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Seven - Sovereign of Secret Scandals\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Eight - Upcoming Socials and Announcements\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Glamorous Life of Rinascita - Issue Two
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] The Crown's Royal Court, III, by Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the twenty-eighth day of the 1600th year, the Crown's Royal Court was held by the Italian monarchs, King Dominic and Queen Mirielle. Standing with the Royal Family was the Royal Entourage which consisted of Archduke Alonzo, Lord Chamberlain Jean Frederic, Mistress of Robes, Lady Emeraude, Captain of the Royal Guard, Lady Kilana, and Handmaiden to the Queen, Lacey Fraser. This animated event drew a large crowd of various residents from all classes of Rinascita. In attendance were Ambassador Emmaline and her husband Lord Nicolas, Ambassadors Toddia and Margrat, Dames Beth, Orla, and Persephone, Miss Isabelle and Misters Landon, and Poe. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Archduke and Lord Chamberlain guided denizens into the Throne room after being thoroughly checked by Chief of the Constables, Mister Samir, and Lieutenant Selene. The King began by greeting those who arrived, "Citizens, friends, visitors from near and far, it is my pleasure to welcome you to this assembly of the Royal Court! As the harvest season nears its apex and the world bursts with color and bounty, I would like to take a moment to recognize the blessings bestowed upon us as comrades and community alike! Though our city, our nations, have struggled, we nevertheless persist and thrive!" before immediately divulging his attention to the petitions at hand.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The first petition to be announced was for a gallery of arts, by Dame Couture, which both the King and Queen ardently backed as appreciators of the arts. The second petition was likewise from Dame Couture for a performing arts theater, which was too approved. Both were promised to be completed when the crown completes its other plans for the city. The third petition came from a newcomer to the city, Landon Campion. The Englishman petitioned on behalf of city guilds to hold their own space to better provide for their employees. The King announced that the petition was approved but put on pause for additional public commentary to be heard, to gather the information on what exactly best suits those of the city. The last, but not least of the petitions came from Esquire Solandis who petitioned for improved animal control standards and shelter for those animals without. The King declared his dedication to ensuring that the standards of city animals are improved. It was decided that more thought needed to be placed on this topic to discover ways to both be rid of the threat of the feral dog population and pest, as well as establishing a safe place for lost animals.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once the petitions concluded, the King went on to share some exciting announcements which can be found on pg 8. Dinner was held after in the Royal Gallery. Bottles of cabernet sauvignon and chardonnay were graciously served with plates of bruschetta spuntini. Guests socialized as they drank wine and examined the intricate art pieces on display. The event ended with warm smiles, full bellies, and joyful conversation.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] The Crown's Royal Court, III
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] Eminent Couture, by Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What is fashion? So many people think they know what fashion is, I included. However, fashion cannot be one person's depiction over another. Although this article is a critique of Court garments, it does not mean what I say is correct. Something becomes fashionable when it is popular, therefore, no one person can claim something is fashionable alone. Instead, what you deem fashionable people are what we call trendsetters. Famous or infamous people who incite others to try new things, which can easily be picked up as fashionable or left in the wind. So actually, you choose what is fashionable more than I ever could alone. So please, do not take any of my comments to heart. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;BEST \\\& WORST DRESSED:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thalia Solandis takes the win as most fashionable for the second time in a row. This time for her pearl-studded ensemble which included the colors smoky sage, champagne gold, and cream. The outfit was paired with frosted silver and pearls that also bedecked her split front gown. The entirety of the outfit was, while safe, very soft and elegant. Exceptionally suitable for Thalia's personality. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There is this preposterous idea that men aren't able to be fashionable. This is ridiculous as I know an abundance of men who are most certainly more fashionable than the majority of women in this city. However, I do not need to prove this point because Lord Nicolas Beaumont did so for me. He takes second place for a sleek, dark ensemble that held jut the right amount of color pops. It consisted of charcoal black, ebony, and deep aubergine. He was handsomely adorned in shadowy silver jewelry, that in my opinion aided in pulling the entire look together.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline Beaumont, a first to ever grace the worst dressed list if you can even consider her that. While she looked breathtaking at Court, my eyes could not be drawn away from her gown. I cannot for the life of me understand the sheath gown she wore. The garment itself appears to be three gown variations sewn into one, so perhaps the gown itself is confused about what it wishes to be. Normally, having more than one kind of design on a gown is fine, but this is only when they look well together. I would personally never encourage anyone to don this gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Margrat Maclean is known for her vibrant and loud personality, so I suppose I should not be surprised her outfit matched. Though, unlike her delightful personality, there was nothing enjoyable about her Court outfit. Paring two exceptionally loud colors like yellow hair and a bittersweet orange gown is not the way to do vibrancy. One positive I can say is I admire Margrat for taking risks with her clothing and not following traditional fashion rules. Love or hate, Margrat will likely be one of the most discussed at Court, and that ladies and gentleman are how you become a trendsetter. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Eminent Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] The Artisan's Association, by Sophie O'Shae\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Artisan's Association is a new crafter's guild specializing in carpentry for now with hopes of adding blacksmithing and stonework to the list. I, Sophie O'Shae am the guild leader. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I lived here nearly ten years ago and now I'm back to live my life's dream which is to be my own boss and work with my hands. I spent most of my time away as an indentured servant. I worked in ship yards for most of that time. I learned everything I could about woodworking and now I'm starting to learn about metalworking. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I am now happily offering my services to the people of Rinascita. I hope to make new friends and find new opportunities with you all.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Guild Spotlight - The Artisan's Association
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] The Art of Gardening, by Doctor Beth MacDubclass\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The keys to having a thriving garden are hard work and patience. With these two things and practice, anyone can be a successful gardener. I find that plants need to be tended to at least every other day or even every day. At the very least, they should get some attention when they start to look dry or overgrown. This includes watering and pruning them. If a plant begins to look dull, you can add some fertilizer. The best fertilizers come from the manure of animals such as horses. Store bought fertilizer works just as well. You could even enrich it by adding some seaweed to it. Tools that every good gardener should have are a watering can and a pair of shears. These make the work faster and easier. There are many fun things that one is able to do as a gardener. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Herbs, fruits and some flowers, like roses can be dried into teas or made into pastes for flavoring or medicinal uses. Cigars are made from tobacco and can be flavored with a variety of pastes. Flowers are often used for decoration, whether it be to adorn a piece of clothing or in a bouquet. If there is a flower you find you just love and never want to part with, you can dry it out which will preserve it if you remain careful with it. A gardener who is good with their hands can braid reeds into simple forms of jewelry. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There are also many varieties of plants found throughout the city including coriander, fennel, feverfew, lavender, tamarind, turmeric, aloe, echinacea, basil, carrot, coriander, corn, dill, fennel, lettuce, potato, rye, sage, thyme, wheat, oat, daisy, foxglove, lily, marigold, rose, tulip, orchid, fern, juniper, pothos, wormwood, bougainvillea, nasturtium, angelica and orchid bamboo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] The Art of Gardening
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] An Account of my Arrival of Rinascita, by Landon Campion\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;It was a quiet and peaceful life, living on the farm outside Caernarvon, and despite the beauty of the Welsh countryside, I was eager for a new life, an adventure. My father had passed not long before I left home and despite an upset brother and a broken heart, I was determined to seek fortune elsewhere. I sought passage on a merchant vessel sailing from Cardiff to Rinascita and payed my faire by working the decks and rigging as best a landlubber could.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finally arriving in Italy, I had not expected the kindness and generosity brought to me by those I met. On one hand there was Miss Orla who crafted my first outfit (which I learned the hard way, do not alter what she makes you or ask anyone else to alter it) here and even paid for a forging of a proper steel rapier I now proudly wear at my side. Miss Thalia graciously offered advice for societal life in Rinascita, as well as showed me around the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At first I had founded a small Mercenary guild that was sponsored by the English, and for those new to the city, seeking to start their own, I recommend seeking one of the Consulates to sponsor you. Eventually my guild would be absorbed by the Midas Guild and for those seeking a place to at least start, write Miss Charisma, Mister Levison, or myself, I don't regret my place there.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I have met many people, most a like, some I don't, but that is the reality of the world. I am grateful for my dear friends I have made and the help they have offered me. To anyone new to this city, do not hesitate to reach out to those around you, they will help you in ways you couldn't possibly imagine. Oh, and Miss Orla's cooking is the best.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] An Insight of a Newcomer
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] Sovereign of Secret Scandals, by Storla Dior\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Rumors are frequently seen as something that one should not find joyful. I happen to disagree with that. As a statue, you can imagine I don't get the chance to experience the dazzling lives you humans live. Rumors help me get that connection that I am desperately missing. They can be fun, exciting, and sometimes even a lesson that what you do in the dark will inevitably be revealed to the light.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Therefore, the issue is not in the rumor itself, but how we use those rumors. I may have a heart of stone, but you can trust I have no ill intentions. So with that said, please always remember to -never- take gossip or a rumor too seriously. Instead, collect it as your private entertainment as these may or may not be factual. To those involved in the rumor, seize this as an opportunity to laugh at yourself.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;GOSSIP:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* The French and Italians are planning an event, I hope we aren't required to give donations this time.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Speaking of donations, I hear the Scottish won the heavily sought after trees from the auction. I guess Margrat's donation party is the new way for consulates to earn funds.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* I'm told if you have a cookie, Thalia will follow you anywhere in the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* While on cookies, Mistress Emeraude was seen sharing cookies with Lord Trevyn. It's always nice when consulates unite, sharing is caring people!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* The Spanish are apparently planning to invade the city with their own musical instruments. So long as they come with Spanish men, I doubt I will mind.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Speaking of musical instruments, prepare your ears for the classical sounds of bagpipes. Soon to wake you from slumber in the wee early mornings.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Orla's been spending a lot of nights lingering around a dashing English Lad. Perhaps there is something blooming there besides their love for food.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* I hear Lord Jean Frederic has a codpiece for every outfit, just don't get caught looking!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* There are whispers of a grand feast coming this November, with half of the city suddenly claiming to be cooks I wonder who will be cooking.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* If it's Lord Trevyn, I'm told one should never trust a cook who poisons himself.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* On the topic of questionable foods, I hear Vivaldi's imports special meats. Mystery meats. I dare you to try it and see if you can tell the difference.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Did you know that Aldo is a vampire?! Pointy teeth, up all night, and I heard him bragging about blood!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Isabelle was seen flitting about town looking for things to paint. Is she ever going to start her classes? The people demand to know!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Dean Persephone is starting the lessons up for the university. Isn't it a little weird all her teachers a female? Don't they know the fairer sex is meant to be quiet. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Dame Valeria was seen drifting through the town with a certain stylist twin on her arm. One must wonder who was leading who though.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* For someone who claims to not care about rank, Orla was all smiles and teeth towards the King.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Sovereign of Secret Scandals
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements, The City of Rinascita\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Before I divulge the upcoming announcements, I would like to personally thank the Consulates who have assisted me in bringing this paper to life. The French Consulate have been long time supporters, their more than generous donation is appreciated. The English and German Consulate also aided greatly. I also thank the Scottish Consulate. Currently, all the consulates require intelligent individuals to join them. Scribe their Ambassadors to join.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French: Lady Emmaline\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;English: Miss Toddia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;German: Lord Trevyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Scottish: Miss Margrat\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Italians: Ladies Kilana or Emeraude\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Spanish: Mister Raul\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;ROYAL ANNOUNCEMENTS:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Due to favorable circumstances overseas, the Crown can import grander items than usual. Including, but not limited to rare crafting materials and items. For example, the rose gold mirror I won. All import requests should go to Lord Jean Frederic. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- The Palace is now opening its doors to those of rank in the city. Those of Gentry rank or above may utilize the palace and its public spaces within reason. Information on how these spaces should be utilized can be obtained on the boards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;GUILD ANNOUNCEMENTS:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- To all guilds seeking sponsorship, Ambassador Toddia is open to sitting and discussing terms. The English Consulate is home to some of the most generous and kind souls I know. Please write the Ambassador for more information.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- I have a new business, J'Orla Decor! More information will be announced on the boards, but I now put my seamstress mind to designing rooms and homes for city residents.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Are you seeking items on the auction but possess no skills to acquire them? Seek out the Midas Guild owned by Charisma Pulcher. Other services include selling fine items or even employment for those without a home.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Rinascita's University has been brought back to life by its newest dean, Doctor Persephone di Catania. The Dean has already begun lectures, the first being by Doctor Beth MacDubclass on a special healing topic and the other by Charisma Pulcher with a thrilling historic retelling. I will be doing a thorough chronicle of each of these events on the boards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- A new restaurant, Bon Appetit, is on the horizon and led by Bruno Smith and I. More information will be conveyed soon, but be sure to keep your eyes and ears open and your bellies empty!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Miss Sophie O'Shae, a master carpenter has returned to the city. She is a delightful young woman who is eager to assist the city. I can vouch that she is fast, reliable, patient, and has amazing communication skills. You can acquire more information about her guild on pg4.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Speaking of carpentry, I would like to shine a little light on Miss Maria and her lumber business. I recently used her lumber, and she was a joy to work with. She is quick and has an extensive list of wood; I was in awe. If you too seek lumber, Miss Maria is the way to go.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">"Orla"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         2
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1601817983
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="misc:lastdropped">
         "1601476221 Orla[heavenlyheather]"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] I have lived in Rinascita for seven years, which is not as long a time as others. However, in my brief years here, I have seen a lot. I've seen people rise and fall, and guilds thrive and decay. I have experienced my gloomiest and happiest times in this city. Throughout all of that, one thing has always remained absolute. Rinascita represents a city where you can become the most efficient version of yourself. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;This is why I established this paper, to showcase the best parts of my home. To show that it does not matter where you come from or what you know. Those who know me know I am an orphan who was not always the woman I am today. Rinascita enveloped me into its arms as a mother would a babe and aided me through my struggles. The people here showed me how to discover everything I did not know I needed. Even so, there is always more for me to learn, but without this city, I do not know where I would be. Therefore, my paper will eternally honor Rinascita and everyone within it.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Two - The Crown's Royal Court, III\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Three - Eminent Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Four - Guild Spotlight\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Five - The Art of Gardening\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Six - An Insight of a Newcomer\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Seven - Sovereign of Secret Scandals\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Eight - Upcoming Socials and Announcements\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Glamorous Life of Rinascita - Issue Two
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] The Crown's Royal Court, III, by Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the twenty-eighth day of the 1600th year, the Crown's Royal Court was held by the Italian monarchs, King Dominic and Queen Mirielle. Standing with the Royal Family was the Royal Entourage which consisted of Archduke Alonzo, Lord Chamberlain Jean Frederic, Mistress of Robes, Lady Emeraude, Captain of the Royal Guard, Lady Kilana, and Handmaiden to the Queen, Lacey Fraser. This animated event drew a large crowd of various residents from all classes of Rinascita. In attendance were Ambassador Emmaline and her husband Lord Nicolas, Ambassadors Toddia and Margrat, Dames Beth, Orla, and Persephone, Miss Isabelle and Misters Landon, and Poe. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Archduke and Lord Chamberlain guided denizens into the Throne room after being thoroughly checked by Chief of the Constables, Mister Samir, and Lieutenant Selene. The King began by greeting those who arrived, "Citizens, friends, visitors from near and far, it is my pleasure to welcome you to this assembly of the Royal Court! As the harvest season nears its apex and the world bursts with color and bounty, I would like to take a moment to recognize the blessings bestowed upon us as comrades and community alike! Though our city, our nations, have struggled, we nevertheless persist and thrive!" before immediately divulging his attention to the petitions at hand.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The first petition to be announced was for a gallery of arts, by Dame Couture, which both the King and Queen ardently backed as appreciators of the arts. The second petition was likewise from Dame Couture for a performing arts theater, which was too approved. Both were promised to be completed when the crown completes its other plans for the city. The third petition came from a newcomer to the city, Landon Campion. The Englishman petitioned on behalf of city guilds to hold their own space to better provide for their employees. The King announced that the petition was approved but put on pause for additional public commentary to be heard, to gather the information on what exactly best suits those of the city. The last, but not least of the petitions came from Esquire Solandis who petitioned for improved animal control standards and shelter for those animals without. The King declared his dedication to ensuring that the standards of city animals are improved. It was decided that more thought needed to be placed on this topic to discover ways to both be rid of the threat of the feral dog population and pest, as well as establishing a safe place for lost animals.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Once the petitions concluded, the King went on to share some exciting announcements which can be found on pg 8. Dinner was held after in the Royal Gallery. Bottles of cabernet sauvignon and chardonnay were graciously served with plates of bruschetta spuntini. Guests socialized as they drank wine and examined the intricate art pieces on display. The event ended with warm smiles, full bellies, and joyful conversation.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] The Crown's Royal Court, III
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] Eminent Couture, by Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What is fashion? So many people think they know what fashion is, I included. However, fashion cannot be one person's depiction over another. Although this article is a critique of Court garments, it does not mean what I say is correct. Something becomes fashionable when it is popular, therefore, no one person can claim something is fashionable alone. Instead, what you deem fashionable people are what we call trendsetters. Famous or infamous people who incite others to try new things, which can easily be picked up as fashionable or left in the wind. So actually, you choose what is fashionable more than I ever could alone. So please, do not take any of my comments to heart. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;BEST \\\& WORST DRESSED:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Thalia Solandis takes the win as most fashionable for the second time in a row. This time for her pearl-studded ensemble which included the colors smoky sage, champagne gold, and cream. The outfit was paired with frosted silver and pearls that also bedecked her split front gown. The entirety of the outfit was, while safe, very soft and elegant. Exceptionally suitable for Thalia's personality. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There is this preposterous idea that men aren't able to be fashionable. This is ridiculous as I know an abundance of men who are most certainly more fashionable than the majority of women in this city. However, I do not need to prove this point because Lord Nicolas Beaumont did so for me. He takes second place for a sleek, dark ensemble that held jut the right amount of color pops. It consisted of charcoal black, ebony, and deep aubergine. He was handsomely adorned in shadowy silver jewelry, that in my opinion aided in pulling the entire look together.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline Beaumont, a first to ever grace the worst dressed list if you can even consider her that. While she looked breathtaking at Court, my eyes could not be drawn away from her gown. I cannot for the life of me understand the sheath gown she wore. The garment itself appears to be three gown variations sewn into one, so perhaps the gown itself is confused about what it wishes to be. Normally, having more than one kind of design on a gown is fine, but this is only when they look well together. I would personally never encourage anyone to don this gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Margrat Maclean is known for her vibrant and loud personality, so I suppose I should not be surprised her outfit matched. Though, unlike her delightful personality, there was nothing enjoyable about her Court outfit. Paring two exceptionally loud colors like yellow hair and a bittersweet orange gown is not the way to do vibrancy. One positive I can say is I admire Margrat for taking risks with her clothing and not following traditional fashion rules. Love or hate, Margrat will likely be one of the most discussed at Court, and that ladies and gentleman are how you become a trendsetter. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] Eminent Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] The Artisan's Association, by Sophie O'Shae\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Artisan's Association is a new crafter's guild specializing in carpentry for now with hopes of adding blacksmithing and stonework to the list. I, Sophie O'Shae am the guild leader. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I lived here nearly ten years ago and now I'm back to live my life's dream which is to be my own boss and work with my hands. I spent most of my time away as an indentured servant. I worked in ship yards for most of that time. I learned everything I could about woodworking and now I'm starting to learn about metalworking. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I am now happily offering my services to the people of Rinascita. I hope to make new friends and find new opportunities with you all.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Guild Spotlight - The Artisan's Association
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] The Art of Gardening, by Doctor Beth MacDubclass\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The keys to having a thriving garden are hard work and patience. With these two things and practice, anyone can be a successful gardener. I find that plants need to be tended to at least every other day or even every day. At the very least, they should get some attention when they start to look dry or overgrown. This includes watering and pruning them. If a plant begins to look dull, you can add some fertilizer. The best fertilizers come from the manure of animals such as horses. Store bought fertilizer works just as well. You could even enrich it by adding some seaweed to it. Tools that every good gardener should have are a watering can and a pair of shears. These make the work faster and easier. There are many fun things that one is able to do as a gardener. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Herbs, fruits and some flowers, like roses can be dried into teas or made into pastes for flavoring or medicinal uses. Cigars are made from tobacco and can be flavored with a variety of pastes. Flowers are often used for decoration, whether it be to adorn a piece of clothing or in a bouquet. If there is a flower you find you just love and never want to part with, you can dry it out which will preserve it if you remain careful with it. A gardener who is good with their hands can braid reeds into simple forms of jewelry. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;There are also many varieties of plants found throughout the city including coriander, fennel, feverfew, lavender, tamarind, turmeric, aloe, echinacea, basil, carrot, coriander, corn, dill, fennel, lettuce, potato, rye, sage, thyme, wheat, oat, daisy, foxglove, lily, marigold, rose, tulip, orchid, fern, juniper, pothos, wormwood, bougainvillea, nasturtium, angelica and orchid bamboo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] The Art of Gardening
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] An Account of my Arrival of Rinascita, by Landon Campion\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;It was a quiet and peaceful life, living on the farm outside Caernarvon, and despite the beauty of the Welsh countryside, I was eager for a new life, an adventure. My father had passed not long before I left home and despite an upset brother and a broken heart, I was determined to seek fortune elsewhere. I sought passage on a merchant vessel sailing from Cardiff to Rinascita and payed my faire by working the decks and rigging as best a landlubber could.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finally arriving in Italy, I had not expected the kindness and generosity brought to me by those I met. On one hand there was Miss Orla who crafted my first outfit (which I learned the hard way, do not alter what she makes you or ask anyone else to alter it) here and even paid for a forging of a proper steel rapier I now proudly wear at my side. Miss Thalia graciously offered advice for societal life in Rinascita, as well as showed me around the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At first I had founded a small Mercenary guild that was sponsored by the English, and for those new to the city, seeking to start their own, I recommend seeking one of the Consulates to sponsor you. Eventually my guild would be absorbed by the Midas Guild and for those seeking a place to at least start, write Miss Charisma, Mister Levison, or myself, I don't regret my place there.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;I have met many people, most a like, some I don't, but that is the reality of the world. I am grateful for my dear friends I have made and the help they have offered me. To anyone new to this city, do not hesitate to reach out to those around you, they will help you in ways you couldn't possibly imagine. Oh, and Miss Orla's cooking is the best.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] An Insight of a Newcomer
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] Sovereign of Secret Scandals, by Storla Dior\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Rumors are frequently seen as something that one should not find joyful. I happen to disagree with that. As a statue, you can imagine I don't get the chance to experience the dazzling lives you humans live. Rumors help me get that connection that I am desperately missing. They can be fun, exciting, and sometimes even a lesson that what you do in the dark will inevitably be revealed to the light.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Therefore, the issue is not in the rumor itself, but how we use those rumors. I may have a heart of stone, but you can trust I have no ill intentions. So with that said, please always remember to -never- take gossip or a rumor too seriously. Instead, collect it as your private entertainment as these may or may not be factual. To those involved in the rumor, seize this as an opportunity to laugh at yourself.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;GOSSIP:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* The French and Italians are planning an event, I hope we aren't required to give donations this time.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Speaking of donations, I hear the Scottish won the heavily sought after trees from the auction. I guess Margrat's donation party is the new way for consulates to earn funds.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* I'm told if you have a cookie, Thalia will follow you anywhere in the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* While on cookies, Mistress Emeraude was seen sharing cookies with Lord Trevyn. It's always nice when consulates unite, sharing is caring people!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* The Spanish are apparently planning to invade the city with their own musical instruments. So long as they come with Spanish men, I doubt I will mind.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Speaking of musical instruments, prepare your ears for the classical sounds of bagpipes. Soon to wake you from slumber in the wee early mornings.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Orla's been spending a lot of nights lingering around a dashing English Lad. Perhaps there is something blooming there besides their love for food.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* I hear Lord Jean Frederic has a codpiece for every outfit, just don't get caught looking!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* There are whispers of a grand feast coming this November, with half of the city suddenly claiming to be cooks I wonder who will be cooking.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* If it's Lord Trevyn, I'm told one should never trust a cook who poisons himself.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* On the topic of questionable foods, I hear Vivaldi's imports special meats. Mystery meats. I dare you to try it and see if you can tell the difference.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Did you know that Aldo is a vampire?! Pointy teeth, up all night, and I heard him bragging about blood!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Isabelle was seen flitting about town looking for things to paint. Is she ever going to start her classes? The people demand to know!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Dean Persephone is starting the lessons up for the university. Isn't it a little weird all her teachers a female? Don't they know the fairer sex is meant to be quiet. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* Dame Valeria was seen drifting through the town with a certain stylist twin on her arm. One must wonder who was leading who though.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;* For someone who claims to not care about rank, Orla was all smiles and teeth towards the King.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Sovereign of Secret Scandals
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements, The City of Rinascita\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Before I divulge the upcoming announcements, I would like to personally thank the Consulates who have assisted me in bringing this paper to life. The French Consulate have been long time supporters, their more than generous donation is appreciated. The English and German Consulate also aided greatly. I also thank the Scottish Consulate. Currently, all the consulates require intelligent individuals to join them. Scribe their Ambassadors to join.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French: Lady Emmaline\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;English: Miss Toddia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;German: Lord Trevyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Scottish: Miss Margrat\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Italians: Ladies Kilana or Emeraude\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Spanish: Mister Raul\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;ROYAL ANNOUNCEMENTS:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Due to favorable circumstances overseas, the Crown can import grander items than usual. Including, but not limited to rare crafting materials and items. For example, the rose gold mirror I won. All import requests should go to Lord Jean Frederic. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- The Palace is now opening its doors to those of rank in the city. Those of Gentry rank or above may utilize the palace and its public spaces within reason. Information on how these spaces should be utilized can be obtained on the boards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;GUILD ANNOUNCEMENTS:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- To all guilds seeking sponsorship, Ambassador Toddia is open to sitting and discussing terms. The English Consulate is home to some of the most generous and kind souls I know. Please write the Ambassador for more information.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- I have a new business, J'Orla Decor! More information will be announced on the boards, but I now put my seamstress mind to designing rooms and homes for city residents.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Are you seeking items on the auction but possess no skills to acquire them? Seek out the Midas Guild owned by Charisma Pulcher. Other services include selling fine items or even employment for those without a home.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Rinascita's University has been brought back to life by its newest dean, Doctor Persephone di Catania. The Dean has already begun lectures, the first being by Doctor Beth MacDubclass on a special healing topic and the other by Charisma Pulcher with a thrilling historic retelling. I will be doing a thorough chronicle of each of these events on the boards.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- A new restaurant, Bon Appetit, is on the horizon and led by Bruno Smith and I. More information will be conveyed soon, but be sure to keep your eyes and ears open and your bellies empty!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Miss Sophie O'Shae, a master carpenter has returned to the city. She is a delightful young woman who is eager to assist the city. I can vouch that she is fast, reliable, patient, and has amazing communication skills. You can acquire more information about her guild on pg4.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Speaking of carpentry, I would like to shine a little light on Miss Maria and her lumber business. I recently used her lumber, and she was a joy to work with. She is quick and has an extensive list of wood; I was in awe. If you too seek lumber, Miss Maria is the way to go.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1601818623
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">12</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1601817508
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
