<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="alias:flower">
         "flowers"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="alias:garmflower">
         "garmflowers"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1150071501, "tonyd", "E", 1150071670, "tonyd", "E", 1150071814, "tonyd", "E", 1150071852, "tonyd", "E", 1150071895, "tonyd", "E", 1150071970, "tonyd", "E", 1150072062, "tonyd", "E", 1150073601, "sinistrelle", "E", 1150081350, "sinistrelle", "E", 1150086089, "tonyd", "E", 1150086124, "tonyd", "E", 1309488020, "rorschakovacs", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="topic:fertilizer">
         (\{ "Try adding fertilizer to your plants. I'm sure they will be much happier for it. If the plant is growing well, make sure the fertilizer is a high enough quality, or it won't help the plant as much." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="topic:flowers">
         (\{ "I don't sell flowers directly, but I do sell bushes that grow flowers. There's no joy like growing your own flowers!", "You can buy a bush and grow your own flowers. Don't forget to water, prune, and fertilize it each day, if you want it to grow to its full potential." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="topic:garmflowers">
         (\{ "Garmflowers are well known for their fertility properties. It's common for young couples to hang a posy of garmflowers above their bed, or for the young lass to wear a bracelet of them.", "Purple garmflowers are especially rare, as they are a hybrid of two other garmflowers. They must be grown in a pot from two seperate seeds, one red, one blue.", "Garmflowers are often used to attract beneficial spirits. I don't know if that works, though.", "I hear that Lutarists prize garmflowers for their gardens. But that doesn't mean us devout S'allumer followers can't also appreciate their beauty.", "Garmflowers grow either red or blue.  Those are the only flowers that bear seeds.", "Garmflowers rarely grow more than one or two at a time on a bush.", "A garmflower will usually bear a single seed in a flower, but purple garmflowers won't bear seeds at all.", "It takes some skill in gardening to plant garmflower seeds properly.", "Purple garmflowers do not bear seeds, but can last a very long time with very little care." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="topic:witchmoss">
         (\{ "Witchmoss is usually found growing amongst other moss.", "I don't keep any witchmoss in stock, but I've heard that it grows here in Triskellian.", "If you're looking for witchmoss, I'd try searching in a dark, wet place that's rarely disturbed.", "You can recognize witchmoss because it glows a faint red in the dark.", "Witchmoss is dark red in color, and feels rough.", "If you're unsure whether you've found some witchmoss, have a healer look it over. A skilled healer should recognize witchmoss on sight." \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
