<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="blurb">
         "The Holy Roman Empire controls a considerable amount of power through most of Europe. There are certain actions that the church has enough influence to enforce and are, effectively, treated as laws."
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:apostasy/abandonment of religious belief">
         ([ "description":"Apostasy as defined by the Holy Roman Catholic Church is the practice in which a person or persons abandon or renounces the religious beliefs, scripture, and practices set forth by our Heavenly Father and the His Holiness the Pope.", "value":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:blasphemy">
         ([ "description":"Blasphemy is the act or offense of speaking sacrilegiously about or against God or sacred things.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:desecration of catholic cathedrals or chapels">
         ([ "description":"Defacing, damaging, polluting, or otherwise physically mistreating in a way that the defendant knows will outrage the sensibilities of persons likely to observe or discover the defendant's action.", "value":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:heresey">
         ([ "description":"Heresy is a gross and dangerous error, voluntarily held and factiously maintained by some person or persons within the visible Church, in opposition to the chief or substantial truth or truths grounded upon and drawn from the Holy Scripture by necessary consequence.", "value":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:practicing paganism/dark arts">
         ([ "description":"Paganism is defined as any non-Christian religion. The church does not recognize any religion other than Catholicism as legal.", "value":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1202463095, "tonyd", "E", 1202463339, "tonyd", "E", 1202463359, "tonyd", "E", 1202463561, "tonyd", "E", 1202463675, "tonyd", "E", 1202463853, "tonyd", "E", 1202464948, "tonyd", "E", 1202465992, "tonyd", "E", 1202466003, "tonyd", "E", 1576683620, "jominey", "R", 1690936204, "annemairi", "E", 1690936214, "annemairi", "E", 1690936264, "annemairi", "E", 1690936339, "annemairi", "E", 1690936342, "annemairi", "E", 1690936451, "annemairi", "E", 1690936527, "annemairi", "E", 1690936979, "annemairi", "E", 1690937023, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
