<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:abduction, kidnapping, and unlawful imprisonment">
         ([ "description":"Any person who, by force, intimidation or deception, and without legal justification or excuse, seizes, takes, transports, detains or secretes another person with the intent to deprive such other person of his personal liberty or to withhold or conceal him from any person, authority or institution lawfully entitled to his charge, shall be deemed guilty of abduction.", "value":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:aiding and abetting/accessory">
         ([ "description":"Defined as someone who aids or abets (encourages, incites) another person in the commission of a crime. Accessory is defined as contributing to the commission or concealment of a crime.", "value":7 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:arson">
         ([ "description":"Any willful or malicious burning or attempting to burn, with or without intent to defraud, a dwelling house, public building, carriage or water craft, personal property of another, etc.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:assault with bodily injury and simple assault">
         ([ "description":"Assault shall be defined as any act intended to cause pain or injury to another, coupled with the apparent ability to execute the act; any act intended to result in offensive physical contact or to place another in fear of imminent offensive physical contact; pointing or displaying a dangerous weapon at someone in a threatening manner.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:attempted murder">
         ([ "description":"The failed or aborted attempt to murder another living person.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:brandishing (wielding) a weapon">
         ([ "description":"Brandishing or wielding a dangerous weapon with the intent to use the weapon to harm, intimidate, or threaten another person without justification.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:complicity">
         ([ "description":"The act of helping or encouraging another individual to commit a crime.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:debt">
         ([ "description":"refusing to pay a bill means you are in debt. This applies to any services rendered that go unpaid. If you are charged with this crime you do not have to pay your bill because your punishment will serve as payment rendered.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:disorderly conduct">
         ([ "description":"Engaging in fighting or violent behavior in any public place or in/near any lawful assembly of persons.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:engaging in lewd acts publicly">
         ([ "description":"Conduct that is indecent, obscene, or lascivious in public.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:escape, attempted escape, and aiding escape from lawful imprisonment">
         ([ "description":"Escaping or attempted escape from lawful imprisonment.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:failure to appear, failure to respond to summons and contempt of court">
         ([ "description":"Failing to appear for court appearance. Contempt of court is defined as the act of disrespect or disobedience toward the court or interference with its orderly process.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:forgery">
         ([ "description":"A crime committed when a person creates or alters a legal instrument with the intent to defraud.", "value":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:impersonation">
         ([ "description":"The fraud of impersonation is the false representation by one person that he is another or that he occupies the position of another.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:inflammatory or derogatory statements against the crown">
         ([ "description":"Inflammatory or derogatory statements intended to incite anger, animosity, or indignation toward the Crown of Italy. ", "value":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:libel">
         ([ "description":"Libel is a method of defamation expressed by print, writing, pictures, signs, effigies, or any communication embodied in physical form that is injurious to a person's reputation, exposes a person to public hatred, contempt or ridicule, or injures a person in his/her business or profession.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:making false accusations">
         ([ "description":"A claim or allegation of wrongdoing that is untrue and/or otherwise unsupported by facts. False accusations are also known as groundless accusations or unfounded accusations or false allegations or false claims.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:malicious mischief">
         ([ "description":"A person is guilty of malicious mischief when he or she “knowingly or maliciously” causes physical damage to another person's property.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:mugging, violent plundering, and theft by threat of violence">
         ([ "description":"Mugging is defined as the act of physical attack upon an isolated pedestrian on a public street at night and the taking of money and effects from his person.- Violent plundering is defined as the act of stealing, or the taking of goods by force by use of violence and intimidation. - Theft by threat of violence is the commission of theft in circumstances of violence and involves the application or the threat of force in order to commit the theft or to secure escape.", "value":5 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:murder (premeditated and unpremeditated)">
         ([ "description":"Premeditated murder is defined as the unlawful killing of a person through planning or research with the intent to cause death. - Unpremeditated murder is defined as the unlawful killing of a person with no forethought or planning.", "value":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:non-violent plundering or larceny by stealth">
         ([ "description":"Non-violent plundering is defined as the theft of material goods for the purposes of personal use and profit or gain. Larceny by stealth is defined as the surreptitious theft of material goods under cover of stealth and deception.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:perjury and subordination of perjury">
         ([ "description":"Perjury is the offense of willfully telling an untruth in a court after having taken an oath or affirmation. Subordination of perjury is the inducing of a person to commit perjury, or to procure perjured testimony.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:petty theft">
         ([ "description":"Petty theft occurs when an individual intentionally and unlawfully takes property that is valued less than 500f from another person.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:possession">
         ([ "description":"possession or consumption of any substance or item deemed illegal by the guild council. The selling/buying of any such item fulls under this crime.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:possession of stolen goods">
         ([ "description":"Possession of stolen goods is a crime in which an individual has bought, been given, or acquired stolen goods.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:receiving stolen property">
         ([ "description":"A crime that a person is guilty of when the person receives stolen property that is known to be stolen and the person has the intent to permanently deprive the owner of the property.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:reckless endangerment (with a deadly weapon)">
         ([ "description":"Recklessly engaging in conduct that creates a substantial risk of serious physical injury or death to another person- with a deadly weapon.", "value":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:reckless endangerment (without a deadly weapon)">
         ([ "description":"Recklessly engaging in conduct that creates a substantial risk of serious physical injury or death to another person.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:resisting arrest or obstruction">
         ([ "description":"An illegal act of a suspected criminal either fleeing, threatening, assaulting, or giving false indentification to a Constable during arrest. Obstruction is defined as the crime or act of willfully interfering with the process of justice and law especially by influencing, threatening, harming, or impeding a witness, potential witness, juror, or judicial or constable or by furnishing false information in or otherwise impeding an investigation or legal process.", "value":4 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:sedition">
         ([ "description":"Sedition is inciting revolt or violence against a lawful authority (the Crown) to destroy or overthrow it.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:slander">
         ([ "description":"Defamation or the act of harming the reputation of a business or person by telling one or more people something that is untrue and damaging about them.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:solicitation">
         ([ "description":"A person solicits another person to commit a high crime or misdemeanor when the person commands, entreats, or otherwise attempts to persuade the other person to commit a particular high crime or misdemeanor.", "value":6 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:tampering with bones or corpses">
         ([ "description":"A person commits tampering with a deceased human body if, believing that an official proceeding is pending, in progress, or about to be instituted and acting without legal right or authority, the person willfully destroys, mutilates, conceals, removes, or alters a human body, part of a human body, or human remains.", "value":8 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:treason, rebellion, conspiracy, and espionage">
         ([ "description":" Treason is defined by any deliberate and voluntary act against the Crown or the Crown's realm and consists of levying war against the Crown or Realm, adhering to Enemies of the Crown, giving them aid or comfort. - Rebellion is defined by any violent acts or open resistance against the Crown or its officers. - Conspiracy: 1. A person commits conspiracy with another if, with the intent to promote or facilitate the commission of a crime which is a misdemeanor or high crime, the person does either of the following: A. Agrees with another that they or one or more of them will engage in conduct constituting the crime or an attempt or solicitation to commit the crime. B. Agrees to aid another in the planning or commission of the crime or of an attempt or solicitation to commit the crime. - Espionage is the crime of spying on the Crown or its Court and/or transferring courtly information on behalf of a foreign country. Espionage may be considered treason if the information is traded with an Enemy of the Crown (this is considered aiding an enemy).", "value":10 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:trespassing">
         ([ "description":"Unlawful entry of any private or restricted property without permission.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="crimes:vandalism">
         ([ "description":"The willful destruction or damaging of property in a manner that defaces, mars, or otherwise adds a physical blemish that diminishes the property's value.", "value":3 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="new property name">
         "New Property Value"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1690934825, "annemairi", "E", 1690934835, "annemairi", "E", 1690935038, "annemairi", "E", 1690935139, "annemairi", "E", 1690935240, "annemairi", "E", 1690935605, "annemairi", "E", 1690935659, "annemairi", "E", 1690935755, "annemairi", "E", 1690935790, "annemairi", "E", 1691002173, "annemairi", "E", 1691692366, "annemairi", "E", 1691692420, "annemairi", "E", 1691692499, "annemairi", "E", 1692219857, "annemairi", "E", 1692220167, "annemairi", "E", 1692220228, "annemairi", "E", 1692220233, "annemairi", "E", 1692220792, "annemairi", "E", 1692220857, "annemairi", "E", 1692630881, "annemairi", "E", 1692630984, "annemairi", "E", 1692631083, "annemairi", "E", 1692631132, "annemairi", "E", 1692631140, "annemairi", "E", 1692631183, "annemairi", "E", 1692631204, "annemairi", "E", 1692631274, "annemairi", "E", 1706128999, "annemairi", "E", 1706129183, "annemairi", "E", 1706133909, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
