<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="1">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "date":1577124127, "description":"A few weeks ago someone stole a Chamberpot from the Hospital. The case was closed due to lack of evidence. Now a spring green rose bush in a pot has been stolen.", "name":"Hospital Theft", "openedby":"Matteo", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="10">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:su:suspect\> \}), "date":1691690781, "description":"Unauthorized use of red paint on the public walk outside of the English Consulate. The message written; \\"Peace is a lie! Go or Die!\\".", "name":"Vandalism", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="11">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:su:suspect\> \}), "date":1691693283, "description":"A person riding a jet black horse described as wearing a red mask was seen brandishing a whip at civilians while telling them that they are unwelcome. It was noted that the masked person, presumed to be a man, also left a dead turtle dove on the Piazza Fountain before leaving the area.", "name":"Brandishing (wielding) a Weapon", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="12">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gu:gus\> \}), "date":1691721360, "description":"Preventing the legal system from proveeding further by interfering with investigations; IE: neglecting to maintain contact with the constables and otherwise avoiding court summons.", "name":"Obstruction", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="13">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:gian\>, \<Chatters:AE:di:diangelo\>, \<Chatters:AE:ce:cesare\> \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:giancarlo\>, \<Chatters:AE:su:suspect\> \}), "date":1692586470, "description":"The accused were seen setting massive fires through the center of the city and were observed setting the Cathedral on fire, causing the ultimate demise of the building. In doing so, they are also accused of harming several of His Majesty's citizens.Gian Incarcerated: Aug 15th 1603. Diangelo, Giancarlo deceased Aug 15th 1603. Other suspects remain at large.", "name":"Arson, Assault with bodily injury and simple assault, complicity", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="14">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:gian\>, \<Chatters:AE:ce:cesare\>, \<Chatters:AE:di:diangelo\> \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:giancarlo\> \}), "date":1692630415, "description":"The suspects are accused of kidnapping Lady Elle Ariencieto of the Italian Consulate for the suspected purpose of healing injured men of their group. Dame Selene di Cosenza, Chief Constable of the Rinascita City Guard and Signorina Milli were injured in an attempt to rescue the Baroness, however, the suspected kidnapped the Chief Constable as well.", "name":"Abduction, Kidnapping and Unlawful Imprisonment, Assault with Bodily Injury and Simply Assault", "openedby":"Aldo", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="15">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:di:diangelo\> \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:giancarlo\> \}), "date":1692631978, "description":"The accused accosted Lieutenant Miles Kingsley outside of his home before immuring his body in a crate and sending it to the City Guard.", "name":"Assault with Bodily Injury and Simple Assault", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="16">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gi:gian\> \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:de:decimus\> \}), "date":1703129760, "description":"While incarcerated in the palace dungeon, Duke Marcellio di Giordio was violently assaulted by Gian and Decimus, receiving numerous injuries as defined in *[1.06a] as an assault committed by any person who intentionally or otherwise causes serious injury, severe maiming, disfiguring, and/or wounding to another person.", "name":"[1.06a] Assault with Bodily Injury", "openedby":"Aldo", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="2">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:de:decimus\> \}), "date":1577822713, "description":"It was the 29th of December at half past 10 in the evening when we found the fire raging brightly in the Chapel. There was nothing we could do to save the Chapel, but we prevented it from spreading. A man came out of the shadows on the wall with a hooded cloak that matched the previous description of one Mister Decimus who is apart of the \\"Peace\\" criminal group. After taunting and laughing at us he departed into the shadows.", "name":"Arson, Destruction of Property (Catholic Chapel)", "openedby":"Matteo", "status":"\<font color='green'\>Case Open\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="3">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:Backup:AE:lo:lothario0\> \}), "date":1579068588, "description":"It was the 29th of December at half past 10 in the evening when we found the fire raging brightly in the Chapel. There was nothing we could do to save the Chapel, but we prevented it from spreading. A man came out of the shadows on the wall with a hooded cloak. He is believed to be apart of the \\"Peace\\" criminal group. After taunting and laughing at us he departed into the shadows.", "name":"Arson, Destruction of Property (Catholic Chapel)", "openedby":"Leliana", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="4">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{  \}), "date":1580139723, "description":"Reported Friday January 24th, the entire backyard of the German Consulate's garden, including a few dozen plants and pots (some custom made), were stolen and hidden for several days. Many of these plants and potswere found in the Arboreatum, but some remain missing. The criminal behind this remains at large.", "name":"Theft of German Consulate", "openedby":"Matteo", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed (unresolved)\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="5">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:de:decimus\> \}), "date":1580592795, "description":"*Interference is the hindrance, obstruction, and or disturbance, resulting in the inability to complete or perform the duty of the law.*On the 22nd Day of December, the criminal known as Achmed tagged the Consulates of this city with blood. While doing so, he was caught by Viscount Nicolas of the French Consulate. The Viscount was badly injured in the fight that followed which led to the arrest of Mister Achmed. However, despite being tended by the most skilled healer in the city, Lady Agatha, the injuries given to Achmed caused grave damage. He was dying already when the Constables decided to interrogate him on his actions and attack of the Viscount.While this case is about Decimus, I felt it prudent to explain how we concluded that Decimus is indeed working with Peace. As Achmed was being interrogated, a man was standing outside in a hooded cloak that concealed his face. Considering the man that was being interrogated was a member of Peace, I believed that to be suspicious. I informed those inside which included Mister Gus and Lady Emeraude to take cover in the case the man had arrows. As I stepped outside to confront the man, he began fleeing. I caught up to him and investigated his presence, he claimed to have only been taking a stroll through the streets. I informed him how bizarre that was that he decided to walk right outside the prison in a cloak that concealed his identity. He did shed it, so I could identify his face and gave his name. I provided to him the benefit of the doubt and allowed him to go on his way.Not even an hour later, Nurse Genvieve and Miss Margrat arrived to tell us that Decimus, the man lurking outside the prison requested her to tend to Achmed's wounds and give him a private message. The message was 'The pigeon also flies.' He claims he sent the Nurse to tend to Achmed because he was dying, but if he had not been inside to speak with Achmed, how would he know he was dying? If he had genuinely cared to merely see if the man could be saved, why not inform me of that when I caught him lurking outside? If he, in fact, meant the city no harm, why would he convey coded messages to the man that nearly murdered Lord Nicolas? Decimus has been interfering with our investigations from the start. He puts on a facade of assisting people when he truly is only helping the organization known as Peace. His coded message lost us any opportunity we had to find out more about Peace. Furthermore, the cloak that he wore the night he was first encountered is of identical material and design of every other Peace member who has been seen and or spotted.", "name":"Assisting a Criminal", "openedby":"Leliana", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="6">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:po:poe\> \}), "date":1602392903, "description":"Mister Poe is believed to have stolen a coffin from the crypts within the Cathedral.", "name":"Theft", "openedby":"Samir", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="9">
         ([ "accomplices":(\{  \}), "criminals":(\{ \<Chatters:AE:gu:gus\> \}), "date":1691000853, "description":"The accused is suspected of entering the victim's personal bank vault and removing the victim's property without the permission of the victim. The victim's property was found within the accused's vault thereafter.SENTENCING: 4wks imprisonment (excluding time served start: 8/13/1603; 500f fine (PAID 9/10/1603 ~SC).", "name":"Trespassing, Non-Violent Plundering or Larceny by Stealth, Receiving Stolen Goods", "openedby":"Selene", "status":"\<font color='red'\>Case Closed\</font\>" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="number">17</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1576683593, "jominey", "R", 1690905893, "annemairi", "E", 1691000396, "annemairi", "E", 1692632685, "annemairi", "E", 1692632715, "annemairi", "E", 1692632730, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
