<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="db:adverb">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ "hastily" \}), (\{ "erratically" \}), (\{ "up-and-down" \}), (\{ "evasively" \}), (\{ "swiftly" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:apos">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pv" \}), (\{ "pv" \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ "pp" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:evoke">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:freemotes">
         (\{ "A beetle repetitiously twitches its antennae as it familiarizes itself with the new surroundings.", "A beetle raises its hard, front wings and lifts its see-through back wings before taking flight.", "A flurry of beetles glide through the area, briefly marking the sky with darkness.", "A beetle scurries along the ground, its six legs furiously pumping it toward the nearest exit.", "A black water beetle swimmingly flits to-and-fro in a fresh puddle of rain.", "A woody brown beetle with white spots digs repeatedly into a clump of earth with its fossorial legs.", "A beetle with white spots digs repeatedly into a clump of earth with its fossorial legs.", "A pair of spackle-shelled beetles battle ferociously with their antennae, whacking each other at every opportunity.", "A random shoe squishes an oversized purple beetle resulting in an audible CRUNCH.", "A green substance oozes slowly from the body of an injured beetle.", "A beetle larvae munches on a dead leaf frog, slowly consuming the corpse in entirety.", "A beetle happily shovels small portions of a bright red leaf into its mouth.", "Four dark green stag bettles fight over a nearby female, hooking each other viciously with their mandibles.", "A beetle practicedly rolls a ball of dung and deposits it into a nearby hole in the ground.", "A beetle climbs onto the back of a pale golden beetle in an attempt to mate.", "A beetle glues its eggs to the side of a near-by object.", "A trio of sienna bettles flit about in the air, flying nowhere in particular." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj">
         (\{ (\{ (\{ "(here)" \}) \}), (\{ (\{ "(here)" \}) \}), nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep">
         (\{ (\{ "through" \}), (\{ "along" \}), nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil, nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:verb">
         (\{ (\{ "scurry" \}), (\{ "skitter" \}), (\{ "scurry" \}), (\{ "dart" \}), (\{ "scuttle" \}), (\{ "scoot" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
