<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="db:adverb">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ "slowly" \}), (\{ "slimily" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:apos">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ "pp" \}), (\{ "pp" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:evoke">
         (\{ (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}), (\{ nil \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:freemotes">
         (\{ "A large number of slugs crawl into the area, seeping slime from every pore on their body.", "A slug inches along the ground, simultaneously covering everything it touches in a lovely waterproof layer of slime.", "A small group of slugs lazily munch on a nearby dirt mound.", "Two slugs laze near a small puddle of water to occasionally drink from its shallow depths.", "A slug comfortably rests on a little pile of dirt. It doesn't appear to have any intention of moving.", "An overgrown slug enjoyably feasts on one of the moist autumn leaves that has fallen to the ground.slug enjoyably feasts on one of the moist autumn leaves that has fallen to the ground.", "A group of slugs absorb some nearby water before proceeding to slime a pathway toward the center of the area.", "A slug slowly crawls over your foot to decorate it with natural oozes.", "The eye stalks of the slug lackadaisically shift to-and-fro.", "A slug hiddenly snacks on a discarded piece of white mushroom.", "A slug lengthily drinks from a side-lying beer container; followingly, it appears to pass out.", "The victim of a beer-filled belly, a mottled slug has drowned itself. The hiss of desiccating fluids can be heard upon the wind for just a fleeting moment." \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj">
         (\{ (\{ (\{ "(here)" \}) \}), nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:obj3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep">
         (\{ (\{ "along" \}), nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep2">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:prep3">
         (\{ nil, nil, nil \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="db:verb">
         (\{ (\{ "inch" \}), (\{ "crawl" \}), (\{ "squirm" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
