<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:World:DockTown:UrOutside)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst></Base:DrinkMessageFirst>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird></Base:DrinkMessageThird>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst></Base:DieMessageFirst>
      <Base:DieMessageThird></Base:DieMessageThird>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details/>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:rand-default">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:rand-snow-gentle">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:rand-snow-storm">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:sam-default">
         X[S] \{
A \{small \|ragged \|half-starved \|\|\}\{child\|boy\|girl\|urchin\|kitten\|\{mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\} kit\|\{wolf\|bear\} cub\|puppy\|foal\} \{runs\|hurries\|scurries\} down the \{road\|street\} \{crying out\|yelling\}, "\{A spider! \|\|\}\{I saw a spider! \|\|\}A spider!\{ It might make us all sick!\| Beware!\| They're all over the place!\| I accidentally touched it!\|\|\|\}"
\|
A \{man\|child\|cat\|mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\|wolf\|bear\|dog\|horse\} absently scratches, then looks around in alarm as \{a group of citizens\|the other people in the street\|some constables\|some house guards\} \{drag him away, struggling\|\{drag\|send\} him off to the quarantine\|lead him to quarantine\|point him in the direction of the quarantine\|suggest that he \{sees a healer\}\{gets checked by a healer\|visits a healer to make sure he isn't infected\}\}.
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "...I hear that this plague is a curse... from \{that evil forest god!\|Lutara.\|some nature spirit.\|the spider gods.\|an angry priest\{ess\|\}.\|heretics\{ that brought their wicked ways to the city\| that worship Lutara, bringing her \{baleful \|unwelcome \|\|\|\} influence \{upon\|to\} us\|\|\{.\|!\}\}\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{...so they've started a cult there, worshipping Lutara, in the hope that She'll cure their sickness.\|A cure will never be found while people at the quarantine keep calling on Lutara. That only strengthens the curse!\|It's all a plot, I tell you!\|...the \{priests\|nobles\|spiders\}... no, I'd better not say anything...\|When the Doloreaux Archbishop gets here, he'll sort things out.\{ The Rinaldi Archbishop can't handle it all\{ by himself\|\}!\|\}\|...but \{Yarwoodle\|Woodle\} says \{that it's a curse\{ because of all the heretics\| from Lutara\| from a Lutaran priestess\}.\|that snakegrass might not have anything to do with the cure.\|YEEK! He's a crazy one, that woodle.\}\|There's some rat going around saying that Sir Matteo keeps spiders in his pants. I think SOMEONE is going to be charged with disrespect to nobility.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{Did you know that there's a trader who only sells things to the infected?\|I hear an evil witch visits the quarantine\{, there to steal the souls of those infected!\|, collecting more sickness with her magic, to spread through the city.\|, giving cursed gifts to people who visit the sick.\| just to laugh at our misery.\|.\}\|The quarantine area is really fun. There were story telling competitions, darts, beer drinking. And it's really not very easy to catch the itch yourself!\|I think I'll visit the quarantine, and keep those poor souls company.\|Did you know that the slaving warehouse is now decked out with cushions, beds, and privacy screens? It's become quite a comfortable leisure house for those that caught the itch, or want to spend time with the itchy.\|The \{priests\|Rinaldi\} are looking for the one who keeps spreading the sickness.\{ It's not natural, but intentionally spread!\| I keep asking the constables if they've caught the man who's spreading it, but Sheriff Joshua keeps telling me there IS no man. Sounds like a conspiracy!\| It's true, I overheard Sir Matteo saying that someone is leaving infected, dead spiders at inns and taverns where people will get sick!\| It's probably a plot by... you know who... all fancy in her palace, spreading disease amongst us commoners!\|\|\|\}\|It's all a plot you see. The Doloreaux, Avoirdupois and Bisclavret are ready to divide Triskellian and its wealth evenly\{, once the city is too sick to defend itself\|\}.\|...so they spread the disease, then claim it's Lutarists, so everyone comes back to them, and they can keep making profit...\|It seems healers and gardeners are at each other's throats over the glory of who gets the cure done\{? \|  \|\}.\|The snake grass? After it was announced on the message boards where it could be found, all the scum of docktown tried to get as much as possible for selling, or just to store in case they needed it themselves.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{...yeah, I couldn't stop scratching. So they made me go to the quarantine, but I kept telling them that I'd fallen into poison ivy!\|...my \{aunt\|mother\|sister\} caught it... yeah, but she saw \{that gypsy rabbit woman\|Madam Rue\}, and got cured.\|\{Doctors are\|Jahren is\|Lia is\|Dylan is\|Temperance is\|Ryan is\|Ada is\} working hard, a cure will be available soon.\|I found an unusual plant, and sold it for ten aureals! I'm so rich now, that I've quit my job, paid my lord for permission, and I'm going travelling!\|I hear that Mistress Meepers asked Mistress Luna if they could use the Maison for the quarantine, and got told no. Apparently it would cut into profits.\|Xena was cursed, so I hear, by Greeves and his ring.\|They say the itch isn't deadly, but Abel died.\|Do you know what \{they\|Doctor Jahren\|the doctor\|Faile\|that slaver\|Sheriff Joshua\|the constables\} did to that fox? Cut him into pieces, and looked under his skin!\|Clover lePlow fought a giant spider that \{was stalking the streets at night, preying on the innocent!\|crawled out of the sewers\{, looking for a meal... a meal of rabbitflesh!\|\|\}.\|attacked Gemma.\|really wasn't nearly as big as he claims it was.\|was in the city laying eggs, spawning the smaller infectious spiders.\|was just minding its own business. Really, not every spider is sick!\}\|The library has been busy, \{with so many people searching for a cure.\|I don't think Dylan ever leaves it.\}\|... and then \{Ada\|Lia\} got sick. It's terrible, I'm sure she's our best chance to find a cure!\|The disease isn't only spread by spiders. Anyone handling skinks too much can also catch it.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{Yes! I overheard \{him\|her\} saying they were going to burn down the warehouse.\|It's true, they're saying there is no cure other than death!\|...and the priests think that the cure is a punishment on heretics, and they should be left to suffer...\|Did you know that burning the skin will cure the infection? Of course, they die, but the church can bring them back.\}"
\|
A \{small\|tiny\|\|\|\} spider \{quickly\|rapidly\} scuttles across the \{ground\|cobbles\}, and into a crack \{in a wall\|between two stones\}.
\|
A \{man\|child\|cat\|mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\|wolf\|bear\|dog\|horse\} begins to \{frantically \|\|\}stamp on the ground\{.\|, "I think I got it!"\|, "A spider!"\|, "Quick! kill that spider!"\|, "Oh dear, I missed it!"\}
\|
A \{long shadow is cast by\|voice is heard from\|comment is made by\} \{a sorrowful\|an upset\|a \} \{clergyman\|priest\|priestess\|acolyte\} who \{declares\|states\|comments\}, "\{S'allumer has forsaken us. A plague and an infestation.\|These spiders must be a punishment from S'allumer.\|What could we poor sinners have done to bring this plague upon us?\|Could the plague be a punishment for the heresy within our populace?\|The plague must be due to people turning from S'allumer.\|So many are ill. They must have \{more \|\|\}faith in \{S'allumer\|the Light\|the Holy Light\}.\}"
\|
A dark, eight-legged shape scurries into the shadow of an alley.
\|
A \{woman\|washerwoman\|maid\|servant\} across the way suddenly squeals in terror as a \{large \|small \|tiny \|huge \|\|\}spider lands on her shoulder.
\|
A \{man\|guard\|servant\|slave\} close to you \{suddenly \|quickly \|\}turns and \{swipes\|pulls\|tears\} at an errant spiderweb.
\|
High up in the eves of the buildings, an industrious \{little \|\}\{arachnid\|spider\} \{sleeps\|works carefully on its web\}.
\|
A half-dressed man wearing a religious symbol staggers through the street, followed by a small gathering of people. He lashes his bare back repeatedly while babbling incoherently.
\|
\{A seething mass of maggots covers the corpse of a large spider.\|A skink runs past, the legs from a dead spider hanging from its mouth.\}
\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:sam-snow-gentle">
         X[S] \{A thin layer of snow delicately clings to the ground, marking the area with the first signs of winter.\|Small scatters of snowflakes lazily twirl down from the sky to nestle in the hair of loitering bystanders.\|A gentle flurry of snow drifts through the area to sparsely decorate the surroundings in a small spattering of white wonder.\|Small snow tufts fall from the winter clouds to gently splat upon nearby surfaces.\|A chilly winter breeze blows through accompanied by a slow-falling stream of pure white snow from the heavens.\|A soft shower of snow falls from the sky to lightly blanket the ground.\|Quiet thuds can be heard all around as small clods of snow connect with the ground. The delicate white blanket continues to grow beneath the wintry sky.\|A collection of fragile snowflakes flutter down from the heavens before merging seamlessly into the thin blanket of snow upon the ground.\|A soft, icy breeze ruffles up the snow covering the nearby buildings, sending it swirling about in a whimsical dance.\|Snow continues to build upon the ground; the blanket growing increasingly thicker.\|A litter of snowflakes delicately drop from the sky to tranquilly collide in a splash of white with the nearby rooftops.\|Delicate streams of snow swirl here-and-there, weightlessly dancing in the loving embrace of the winter wind.\|The falling snowflakes fall against your clothing to subtly deliver a bit of moisture and coldness.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:sys:emit:sam-snow-storm">
         X[S] \{Howling winds blow through the area, furiously shaking the rooftops and nearby objects as they pass.\|Endless scores of snowflakes cascade rapidly down from the sky to abruptly collide with surrounding objects.\|A crazy flurry of snow crashes down from the heavens to cover the area in a thick cloak of stark white.\|Large flakes of snow continuously pour from the winter clouds, hindering eyesight almost completely.\|A turbulent winter breeze blasts through the area, accompanied by an abusive flow of substantial snow from the heavens.\|A massive shower of snow gushes from the sky to crash into the high-growing piles of white upon the ground.\|Audible thuds and thops can be heard everywhere as large clusters of snow tumble gracelessly onto the ground. The ever-growing white blanket continues to increase in mass beneath the wintry sky.\|A collection of giant snowflakes swirl down from the roiling clouds above before merging clumsily into the enormous blanket of snow consuming the ground.\|A harsh, freezing breeze kicks up the snow covering the nearby buildings, sending it surging forth into the air.\|Heavy piles of snow continue to build upon the ground. You can hardly recognize any of the objects once familiar to you.\|A litter of sizable snowflakes spew from the sky to roughly collide in a splatter of white with the snowy rooftops.\|Unruly streams of snow bustle about the area, heavily smacking against nearby objects and people.\|The falling snowflakes thunk incessantly against your body to cover your clothing in a noticeable layer of white.\|Torrents of snow rain down from the sky to abuse your body and remind you of the less-than-enjoyable conditions outside.\|The winter storm kicks it up a notch, belting down thick patches of snow joined by bitterly icy winds.\|The spatterings of snow that have collected upon your clothes begin to seep through to the skin, chilling you to the bone.\|The stormy winter clouds discharge a thick and heavy burst of snow which promptly devours the ground and nearby objects in its cold embrace.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1107209474, "zwoc", "E", 1120552173, "tonyd", "E", 1120552278, "tonyd", "E", 1305527697, "catobelpas", "E", 1307222927, "tunk_bodin", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:channels">
         (\{ "snow-gentle", "snow-storm" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:clist">
         (\{ "default", "snow-gentle", "snow-storm" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:population"/>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:rand-default">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:rand-snow-gentle">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:rand-snow-storm">
         0
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:sam-default">
         X[S] \{
A \{small \|ragged \|half-starved \|\|\}\{child\|boy\|girl\|urchin\|kitten\|\{mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\} kit\|\{wolf\|bear\} cub\|puppy\|foal\} \{runs\|hurries\|scurries\} down the \{road\|street\} \{crying out\|yelling\}, "\{A spider! \|\|\}\{I saw a spider! \|\|\}A spider!\{ It might make us all sick!\| Beware!\| They're all over the place!\| I accidentally touched it!\|\|\|\}"
\|
A \{man\|child\|cat\|mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\|wolf\|bear\|dog\|horse\} absently scratches, then looks around in alarm as \{a group of citizens\|the other people in the street\|some constables\|some house guards\} \{drag him away, struggling\|\{drag\|send\} him off to the quarantine\|lead him to quarantine\|point him in the direction of the quarantine\|suggest that he \{sees a healer\}\{gets checked by a healer\|visits a healer to make sure he isn't infected\}\}.
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "...I hear that this plague is a curse... from \{that evil forest god!\|Lutara.\|some nature spirit.\|the spider gods.\|an angry priest\{ess\|\}.\|heretics\{ that brought their wicked ways to the city\| that worship Lutara, bringing her \{baleful \|unwelcome \|\|\|\} influence \{upon\|to\} us\|\|\{.\|!\}\}\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{...so they've started a cult there, worshipping Lutara, in the hope that She'll cure their sickness.\|A cure will never be found while people at the quarantine keep calling on Lutara. That only strengthens the curse!\|It's all a plot, I tell you!\|...the \{priests\|nobles\|spiders\}... no, I'd better not say anything...\|When the Doloreaux Archbishop gets here, he'll sort things out.\{ The Rinaldi Archbishop can't handle it all\{ by himself\|\}!\|\}\|...but \{Yarwoodle\|Woodle\} says \{that it's a curse\{ because of all the heretics\| from Lutara\| from a Lutaran priestess\}.\|that snakegrass might not have anything to do with the cure.\|YEEK! He's a crazy one, that woodle.\}\|There's some rat going around saying that Sir Matteo keeps spiders in his pants. I think SOMEONE is going to be charged with disrespect to nobility.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{Did you know that there's a trader who only sells things to the infected?\|I hear an evil witch visits the quarantine\{, there to steal the souls of those infected!\|, collecting more sickness with her magic, to spread through the city.\|, giving cursed gifts to people who visit the sick.\| just to laugh at our misery.\|.\}\|The quarantine area is really fun. There were story telling competitions, darts, beer drinking. And it's really not very easy to catch the itch yourself!\|I think I'll visit the quarantine, and keep those poor souls company.\|Did you know that the slaving warehouse is now decked out with cushions, beds, and privacy screens? It's become quite a comfortable leisure house for those that caught the itch, or want to spend time with the itchy.\|The \{priests\|Rinaldi\} are looking for the one who keeps spreading the sickness.\{ It's not natural, but intentionally spread!\| I keep asking the constables if they've caught the man who's spreading it, but Sheriff Joshua keeps telling me there IS no man. Sounds like a conspiracy!\| It's true, I overheard Sir Matteo saying that someone is leaving infected, dead spiders at inns and taverns where people will get sick!\| It's probably a plot by... you know who... all fancy in her palace, spreading disease amongst us commoners!\|\|\|\}\|It's all a plot you see. The Doloreaux, Avoirdupois and Bisclavret are ready to divide Triskellian and its wealth evenly\{, once the city is too sick to defend itself\|\}.\|...so they spread the disease, then claim it's Lutarists, so everyone comes back to them, and they can keep making profit...\|It seems healers and gardeners are at each other's throats over the glory of who gets the cure done\{? \|  \|\}.\|The snake grass? After it was announced on the message boards where it could be found, all the scum of docktown tried to get as much as possible for selling, or just to store in case they needed it themselves.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{...yeah, I couldn't stop scratching. So they made me go to the quarantine, but I kept telling them that I'd fallen into poison ivy!\|...my \{aunt\|mother\|sister\} caught it... yeah, but she saw \{that gypsy rabbit woman\|Madam Rue\}, and got cured.\|\{Doctors are\|Jahren is\|Lia is\|Dylan is\|Temperance is\|Ryan is\|Ada is\} working hard, a cure will be available soon.\|I found an unusual plant, and sold it for ten aureals! I'm so rich now, that I've quit my job, paid my lord for permission, and I'm going travelling!\|I hear that Mistress Meepers asked Mistress Luna if they could use the Maison for the quarantine, and got told no. Apparently it would cut into profits.\|Xena was cursed, so I hear, by Greeves and his ring.\|They say the itch isn't deadly, but Abel died.\|Do you know what \{they\|Doctor Jahren\|the doctor\|Faile\|that slaver\|Sheriff Joshua\|the constables\} did to that fox? Cut him into pieces, and looked under his skin!\|Clover lePlow fought a giant spider that \{was stalking the streets at night, preying on the innocent!\|crawled out of the sewers\{, looking for a meal... a meal of rabbitflesh!\|\|\}.\|attacked Gemma.\|really wasn't nearly as big as he claims it was.\|was in the city laying eggs, spawning the smaller infectious spiders.\|was just minding its own business. Really, not every spider is sick!\}\|The library has been busy, \{with so many people searching for a cure.\|I don't think Dylan ever leaves it.\}\|... and then \{Ada\|Lia\} got sick. It's terrible, I'm sure she's our best chance to find a cure!\|The disease isn't only spread by spiders. Anyone handling skinks too much can also catch it.\}"
\|
You overhear two \{men\|women\|guards\|constables\|merchants\|traders\|craftsmen\|washerwomen\|maids\|servants\|slaves\} gossiping, "\{Yes! I overheard \{him\|her\} saying they were going to burn down the warehouse.\|It's true, they're saying there is no cure other than death!\|...and the priests think that the cure is a punishment on heretics, and they should be left to suffer...\|Did you know that burning the skin will cure the infection? Of course, they die, but the church can bring them back.\}"
\|
A \{small\|tiny\|\|\|\} spider \{quickly\|rapidly\} scuttles across the \{ground\|cobbles\}, and into a crack \{in a wall\|between two stones\}.
\|
A \{man\|child\|cat\|mouse\|rat\|squirrel\|fox\|weasel\|mink\|wolf\|bear\|dog\|horse\} begins to \{frantically \|\|\}stamp on the ground\{.\|, "I think I got it!"\|, "A spider!"\|, "Quick! kill that spider!"\|, "Oh dear, I missed it!"\}
\|
A \{long shadow is cast by\|voice is heard from\|comment is made by\} \{a sorrowful\|an upset\|a \} \{clergyman\|priest\|priestess\|acolyte\} who \{declares\|states\|comments\}, "\{S'allumer has forsaken us. A plague and an infestation.\|These spiders must be a punishment from S'allumer.\|What could we poor sinners have done to bring this plague upon us?\|Could the plague be a punishment for the heresy within our populace?\|The plague must be due to people turning from S'allumer.\|So many are ill. They must have \{more \|\|\}faith in \{S'allumer\|the Light\|the Holy Light\}.\}"
\|
A dark, eight-legged shape scurries into the shadow of an alley.
\|
A \{woman\|washerwoman\|maid\|servant\} across the way suddenly squeals in terror as a \{large \|small \|tiny \|huge \|\|\}spider lands on her shoulder.
\|
A \{man\|guard\|servant\|slave\} close to you \{suddenly \|quickly \|\}turns and \{swipes\|pulls\|tears\} at an errant spiderweb.
\|
High up in the eves of the buildings, an industrious \{little \|\}\{arachnid\|spider\} \{sleeps\|works carefully on its web\}.
\|
A half-dressed man wearing a religious symbol staggers through the street, followed by a small gathering of people. He lashes his bare back repeatedly while babbling incoherently.
\|
\{A seething mass of maggots covers the corpse of a large spider.\|A skink runs past, the legs from a dead spider hanging from its mouth.\}
\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:sam-snow-gentle">
         X[S] \{A thin layer of snow delicately clings to the ground, marking the area with the first signs of winter.\|Small scatters of snowflakes lazily twirl down from the sky to nestle in the hair of loitering bystanders.\|A gentle flurry of snow drifts through the area to sparsely decorate the surroundings in a small spattering of white wonder.\|Small snow tufts fall from the winter clouds to gently splat upon nearby surfaces.\|A chilly winter breeze blows through accompanied by a slow-falling stream of pure white snow from the heavens.\|A soft shower of snow falls from the sky to lightly blanket the ground.\|Quiet thuds can be heard all around as small clods of snow connect with the ground. The delicate white blanket continues to grow beneath the wintry sky.\|A collection of fragile snowflakes flutter down from the heavens before merging seamlessly into the thin blanket of snow upon the ground.\|A soft, icy breeze ruffles up the snow covering the nearby buildings, sending it swirling about in a whimsical dance.\|Snow continues to build upon the ground; the blanket growing increasingly thicker.\|A litter of snowflakes delicately drop from the sky to tranquilly collide in a splash of white with the nearby rooftops.\|Delicate streams of snow swirl here-and-there, weightlessly dancing in the loving embrace of the winter wind.\|The falling snowflakes fall against your clothing to subtly deliver a bit of moisture and coldness.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:sam-snow-storm">
         X[S] \{Howling winds blow through the area, furiously shaking the rooftops and nearby objects as they pass.\|Endless scores of snowflakes cascade rapidly down from the sky to abruptly collide with surrounding objects.\|A crazy flurry of snow crashes down from the heavens to cover the area in a thick cloak of stark white.\|Large flakes of snow continuously pour from the winter clouds, hindering eyesight almost completely.\|A turbulent winter breeze blasts through the area, accompanied by an abusive flow of substantial snow from the heavens.\|A massive shower of snow gushes from the sky to crash into the high-growing piles of white upon the ground.\|Audible thuds and thops can be heard everywhere as large clusters of snow tumble gracelessly onto the ground. The ever-growing white blanket continues to increase in mass beneath the wintry sky.\|A collection of giant snowflakes swirl down from the roiling clouds above before merging clumsily into the enormous blanket of snow consuming the ground.\|A harsh, freezing breeze kicks up the snow covering the nearby buildings, sending it surging forth into the air.\|Heavy piles of snow continue to build upon the ground. You can hardly recognize any of the objects once familiar to you.\|A litter of sizable snowflakes spew from the sky to roughly collide in a splatter of white with the snowy rooftops.\|Unruly streams of snow bustle about the area, heavily smacking against nearby objects and people.\|The falling snowflakes thunk incessantly against your body to cover your clothing in a noticeable layer of white.\|Torrents of snow rain down from the sky to abuse your body and remind you of the less-than-enjoyable conditions outside.\|The winter storm kicks it up a notch, belting down thick patches of snow joined by bitterly icy winds.\|The spatterings of snow that have collected upon your clothes begin to seep through to the skin, chilling you to the bone.\|The stormy winter clouds discharge a thick and heavy burst of snow which promptly devours the ground and nearby objects in its cold embrace.\}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="volition">0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
