<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:college chat">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\> ~College Chat~ \<br\>" \}), (\{ "h2", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\>This board  will be used by everyone within the guild. Post comments, questions and answers here. Question of the Weeks and meeting recaps will also be posted here.\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "Samedi, the twenty-first day of Harvest. The current year is 890 Apres le Miracle.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>QUESTION OF THE WEEK:\<br\>\\r\\nHow do you properly inspect an injured patient? No shorter than two sentences with details. Remember to write your name with your answer.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Answers:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>First ask what happened and what symtpons the patient is experiencining.  Then completely expose the wound as to be able to assess the injury in it's entirety.  Then complete a visual examination to determine the kind and serverity of the injury. Further examination may be required at this point but if it is not then treatment may begin.                                                                                                          ---Hush Sweetling---\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "---------\<br\>I have been taught to ask first what occurred.  While patient is speaking,inspect the wound. Visually you tell by the color of the blood if an artery or vain has been severed. If blood is dark artery,if it is lighter in color then a vain. Check depth of wound while attempting to staunch the bleeding. Pressing a rolled up bandage or rolled cloth against the wound pressing strongly can help to control the bleeding till more can be done if the wound is flowing or squirting blood.  Stitch right away if it is blooding a lot.  If the wound is barely flowing..then clean...press a piece of clean bandage or cloth against it for a few moment till wound clots and quits bleeding.  Then, in both cases to finish up, apply some anti-infection cream or ointment and then a clean bandage.  - Mrs Winox de Coire\<br\>\\r\\n---------\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "It is Samedi, the twenty-fifth day of Harvest.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>QUESTIONS OF THE WEEK:\<br\>\\r\\nWhat is your favorite color? Why? No less than two sentences.\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>I really don't have a favorite color as such, but I guess if I did it would have be purple.  I do not really know the reason why.  I just like the different shades that can be created from it and it is just pleasing to the eyes. Miss Winox de Coire\<br\>\\r\\n---------\<br\>\\r\\nMy favorite colour is purple as well.  One because it is the colour of my eyes and two t'is the colour of the Rinaldi. I really don't discreminate the other colour mostly as I too like many colours.\\r\\nHush Sweetling\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\> ~The College of Medicine~ \<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "Welcome, and allow me to congratulate you on your membership with the esteemed College of Medicine.  With the generous sponsorship of the Rinaldi House, we are the first and only University devoted to the advancement of medicine and Healing.  May your career and your pursuit of knowledge be ever-fruitful and enjoyable while you study with us.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nBest Regards,\<br\>\\r\\nDoctor Temperance Zeiss\<br\>\\r\\n Dean of the College of Medicine" \}), (\{ "h3", "-Navigation-" \}), (\{ "page", "Roster", "roster" \}), (\{ "page", "College Chat", "college chat" \}), (\{ "page", "Tool Guide", "how to use your stuff" \}), (\{ "page", "College Structure", "guild structure" \}), (\{ "page", "Treatments", "treatments" \}), (\{ "page", "Supplies", "supplies" \}), (\{ "h3", "-Teacher Information-" \}), (\{ "text", "The College of Medicine teacher can be found in the Infirmary, along with Nurse Melissa.  The teacher offers complimentary instruction to College of Medicine students in the following areas: \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n--Scholar\<br\>\\r\\n--Healer\<br\>\\r\\n--Gardener\<br\>\\r\\n--Tailor\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWhat else would you like to learn?  We may be able to have our teacher broaden his areas of expertise.  Please send all requests to Doctor Temperance.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\>~The College of Medicine~\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "As of Flower 16th 888, the College of Medicine has served as home for various Healers and academics pursuing the joint advancement of medicine and scholarship.  The Rinaldi-sponsored College welcomes both novice and experienced Healers, and offers many paths for continued study and training.  Persons of all Houses, nationalities, and species are welcome to join the College of Medicine.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Roster", "roster" \}), (\{ "page", "College Chat", "college chat" \}), (\{ "page", "Guild Structure\<br\>", "guild structure" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>\\r\\nThe additional resources included in this area are reserved for College of Medicine students, professors, and administrators.  We do encourage you to join us and you will be provided access to these resources.  Anyone seeking any further information about the College may contact Doctor Temperance.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guild structure">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\> ~The College Structure~\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This page will explain the structure of the College, give suggestions on what you can do to earn a promotion within the College and who holds what position within the College." \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>Intern- temporary position with an emphasis on on-the-job training rather than merely employment. Unlimited position.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Current Interns Include:\<br\>\\r\\nGodefroi\<br\>\\r\\nCallista\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Apprentice Nurse- training a new generation of skilled crafts practitioners. Unlimited position.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Current Ap. Nurses Include: \<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>Senior Nurse- those who have completed apprenticeship and are working to move on. Unlimited position. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Current Sn. Nurses Include:\<br\>\\r\\nWinox\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Lead Nurse or Doctor- Second-in-charge in case of Dean absence. The Dean may choose up to -two- people to hold this position.  \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Current Lead Doctor or Nurse Include:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Dean- person with significant authority over a specific academic unit. Limited position: 1. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Current Dean:\<br\>\\r\\nDoctor Temperance" \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\>~How to Earn a Promotion~\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "Discuss your position or department objectives with the Dean or second-in-command. Try to find out exactly what you need to do. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Step up to the plate. Prove you can do it. Get into the mindset of the position you want.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Determine if you're eligible to move up. If you are, determine who you need to contact in order to be considered for a promotion. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>State your intentions. It's best to discuss promotions with the Dean or second-in-command, -not- your peers. Help us understand that you want to pay your dues and do your best in your current position.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "h3", "Please keep in mind that these are guidelines to help you *earn* a promotion, NOT guarantees. We will evaluate each student and their skills to determine if promotions are in order. If there are questions, write the Dean." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:how to use your stuff">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\> Jars and bandages and slings and scalpels, oh my! \<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This page is going to act as a reference page. It will teach you how to use your tools and when to use them. (OOC: OOC commands will be here too in case you guys forget. They're indicated like this: /insert command/)" \}), (\{ "text", "Scalpel-- a small, light, usually straight knife used in surgical and anatomical operations and dissections. This tool is commonly used for blood letting, in which the blood may be captured in a vial providing by Nurse Melissa for a fee. To bloodlet, you must /cut the patient's body part with your scalpel/. to get the blood in a vial, you must /collect person's blood in your vial/. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Jar-- a broad-mouthed container, usually cylindrical and of glass or earthenware. Jars contain a variety of things such as numbing ointment, burn ointment. You must /rub your ointment on person's body part/. Some jars contain a special pain killer that is extremely rare. I've never encountered one, so I don't know how to use it. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Bandages-- a strip of cloth or other material used to bind up a wound, sore, sprain, etc. You /apply your bandage to person's injury/. Remember to keep it decently tight and firm to apply slight pressure. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Stretcher-- a kind of litter, often of canvas stretched on a frame, for carrying the sick, wounded, or dead. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Crutches-- a staff or support to assist a lame or infirm person in walking, now usually with a crosspiece at one end to fit under the armpit. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\> Splint-- a thin piece of wood or other rigid material used to immobilize a fractured or dislocated bone, or to maintain any part of the body in a fixed position. You /apply your splint to person's body part/. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Sling--  a bandage used to suspend or support an injured part of the body, commonly a bandage suspended from the neck to support an injured arm or hand. Patients /wear/ these.\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "I will be adding more as we progress and get new tools." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:infirmary">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<b\>\<line\>\<center\>Supporters\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<line\>Rinaldi\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<line\>Lord Marcus and Lady Tamara\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Sir Matteo- tea kettle Tray  and sassafrass cabinet for silent auction\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Fips- 1000\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Mistress Meepers- an alizarin red gossamer parasol, a silver and onyx girdle belt, a small round mirror and a sage green watered silk purse-It contains a sage green watered silk bliaut, a pair of thigh-high gold sheer stockings, a pair of gold samite slippers, a gold samite girdle, a pearly white damask undercorset and a pair of pearly white soft velvet garters.\\r\\n\<line\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<line\>Bisclavret\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<line\> Oak Lumber\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Baron Murdoch\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Dame Charlot\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<line\>Doloreaux\<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<line\>Sir Erwin\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> \<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>\<line\> Avoirdupois \<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<line\>Gentleman Mathias-support\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<line\>Church \<br\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<line\> Bishop Basanti\<br\>\\r\\n\<BR\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<B\>\<line\> Donations \</B\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Peanut-  Table and Chair\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\>Rem -streamers- barrel of juice\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Bruno- wootz steel sword and scabbard\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<b\> \<line\> \<center\> Funds \<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Valentin- 100 Denarii\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Rem -190 \<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Decado- 1 aureal\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Kione-5 denarii\<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Fips- 1000 Denarii \<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Bruno- 500 denarii \<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Babur- 608 denarii \<br\>\\r\\n\<line\> Althea- 98 denarii \<br\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:medical examinations">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 4 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "All findings from medical examinations will be recorded here\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCity of Triskellian\<br\>\\r\\nExamination within the underground crypt\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPronounced By: Po Liang\<br\>\\r\\nCase Reported: Samedi, the seventh day of Harvest Time:Morning\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nDeceased found by Mister Valentin at the west end of the Docks\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nName of Decedent: Unknown\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nDate of Death: Month, day, year\<br\>\\r\\nHarvest, Samedi 889\<br\>\\r\\nMarital  Status:  Birthplace :  Date of Birth:  Age:\<br\>\\r\\nUnknown           Unknown       Uknown          Unnown\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPrimary Occupation:\<br\>\\r\\nUnknown\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPlace of Death:\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWest end of the Docks, near the fruit trees\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIDENTIFICATION:\<br\>\\r\\nVISUAL BY: Po Liang\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nNOTIFICATION:\<br\>\\r\\nNone at this moment\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nBROUGHT IN BY:\<br\>\\r\\nName: Mister Valentin\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nEvidence taken : X Yes No\<br\>\\r\\nTracks Yes X No\<br\>\\r\\nClothing X Yes No\<br\>\\r\\nProperty X Yes No\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPHYSICAL DESCRIPTION:\<br\>\\r\\nFACE I.D. VIEWABLE: X Yes No\<br\>\\r\\nBODY CONDITION: Good\<br\>\\r\\nAge N/A Species Grizzly Bear\<br\>\\r\\nHt Enormous Hair Red Eyes Grey\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nScars: None noted\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTattoo/Deformity: None noted\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nINVESTIGATOR'S REPORT\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nSYNOPSIS:\<br\>\\r\\nThe decedent is a Enormous Grizzly bear who suffered bruises (4) to the back, chest, face and left cheek. Cut (1) to the chest (probable cause of death.) He was transported from\\r\\nthe scene (west docks) to the Cathederal by Mister Valentin\<br\>\\r\\nDeath was pronounced by myself Mister Po. Only possible evidence was a sewing needle found in his hand at the time he was found.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nINVESTIGATION:\<br\>\\r\\nMister Valentin came to me in the commons and told me about the bear, we headed directly to the west docks to find his corpse on the boardwalk.\<br\>\\r\\nI observed the victim on the ground. He was clad in a pair of pants and a tunic.\\r\\nExamination revealed bruises to the back, chest, face and left cheek. and a cut to the chest.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nInvestigation is ongoing.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nEVIDENCE/PROPERTY:\<br\>\\r\\nOne tailoring pin.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIDENTIFICATION AND NOTIFICATION:\<br\>\\r\\nThe victim has yet to be identified.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPo Liang\<br\>\\r\\nInvestigator\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nSamedi,889 Apres le Miracle\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:roster">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h3", "College of Medicine Roster" \}), (\{ "members_list", "la" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Tokens" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "Fiurne" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies ahlan">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>Mister Ahlan; The study of bones and their injuries\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>~ Progress as of the 18th Day of Yule, 889 ~\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>My study focuses on the healing and treatment of bone injuries. These bone injuries are primarily breaks and partial fractures, of the kind often occurring from very rough sparring, combat, and at times in the punishment of slaves. The objective of this study is to improve the methods and knowledge of healers in Triskellian and potentially elsewhere in the practice of their trade.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>In particular, I am seeking answers to several particular questions:\\r\\n\<br\>- How long do different bone injuries take to heal?\\r\\n\<br\>- What are the best practices in healing bone injuries to different locations?\\r\\n\<br\>- What complications and dangers are important for healers to be aware of?\\r\\n\<br\>- Are there important variations on bone injuries that we should be aware of?\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Methods are:\\r\\n\<br\>- Interviews of bone injury patients and others with practical knowledge of bone injuries\\r\\n\<br\>- Interviews of healers who have treated bone injuries\\r\\n\<br\>- Ongoing study of current injuries\\r\\n\<br\>- Research into previous writings on the subject of bone injuries and treatment\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>So far, I have begun my studies into previous writings and have found some simple information that will be of use. Additionally, I have conducted several interviews of healers, patients, and others with knowledge of broken bones, and personally treated one patient and examined another directly. I also have my own personal experience treating injuries both in Triskellian and my home town to draw on.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>- Ahlan Rainsong, Healer\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies crina">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Miss Crina; The study of Bandages and healing" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies doctor grace">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nurse Grace Stone; The study of Religion and healing " \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies fiurne">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>Fiurne on Infections Prevention:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFrom what I have learned so far is that washing a wound with hot water and soap can help, but adding lavender oil to the wound can greatly reduce infections the area should be cleansed twice a day at least also.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf an area does become infected, soaking it in hot hot water can help pull infection out. If it is greater infected then bleeding area is suggested, or removal if possible be.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFiurne Ryash\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies jacqueline">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<p\>\<b\>Miss Jacqueline\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>The Four Humors\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThere are four humours which affect and must remain in a state of eucrasia, or balance, within every single body for said body to function in a normal state. Imbalance, dyscrasia, in the humours can lead to a myriad of ailments and unpleasant temperaments.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe first humour is the sanguine, which, as the name suggests, is comprised of the blood and is sweet to the taste. This is produced by the liver, veins, and nostrils, and has the qualities of being hot and wet. In respect to colour, this humour is red. A sanguine individual is prone to corpulence and a flushed complexion. However, a sanguine person possesses many positive personality traits, as they are generally optimistic, generous, and happy, although irresponsible.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe second humour is the choleric. The yellow bile, that is gall and urine, is produced in the bladder, the area around the liver, and the ears. Yellow bile comes in seven different colours, the basic yellow, pale-yellow, red, leek-green, yolk-yellow, verdigris, and woad, all of which are bitter. The choleric humour is the other hot humour, but it is considered dry. Ginger hair is common amongst choleric individuals, as is a thin bodily shape. Choleric people are often violent, temperamental, but ambitious.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe third humour is the phelgmatic, the phlegm produced in the stomach, loin muscles, and mouth. Phlegm is white in colour. This is the first of the cold humours, and it, like the sanguine, is also wet. Although normally tasteless, phlegm is often sweet, but can also be salty and sharp. Corpulence is again common amongst the phlegmatic people, as is a pallid complexion. These individuals also tend to be slow-moving and prone to cowardice.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe final humour is the melancholic. The black bile is produced in the area below the liver, spleen, and eyes, and it bears a distinctly sharp flavour. The proper colour of black bile should match that of olive oil. Black bile comes in four types: blood sediment, overheated yellow bile, tarry, and a fourth much like blood. The marrow of the adrenal glands, feces, and blood clots may all be associated with this humour. The melancholic humour is cold and dry. Individuals of the melancholic type are, as the choleric, thin, also with a yellowish, sickly complexion. These individuals are usually introspective and sentimental, although gluttonous.\\r\\n\<p\>\<i\>Achieving Eucrasia\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\nEucrasia by means of a sanguine imbalance can be achieved by two means, the first being to remove excess blood with leeches, and the second, to eat cold and dry foods. A common example of a sanguine  malady would be a fever.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThere are numerous locations, as depicted, from which blood can be removed from the patient:\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<img src=\\"http://www.nlm.nih.gov/exhibition/horse/images/400_pixels/blo_gersdorffx400.jpg\\"\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is best to remove blood from the main artery or vein between the area of concern and the heart." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "text", "\<p\>\<b\>Miss Jacqueline\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Oils\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThis is work is not intended to supersede Mister Suavis' work, but rather to compliment it. I have studied the oils available in the herb shop. At a later point I will post a concise sheet of common ailments and which oils can be used to treat them." \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies kaiya">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>\<size=2\>\<COLOR=DarkRed\>Study of Muscle Movement and Injuries \& The Care of Skin.\</b\>\</size\>\</COLOR\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<size=1\>Miss Kaiya Takinaga\</i\>\</size\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies suavis">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<B\>Mister Suavis; The study of herbs and plants in herbs in healing\</B\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Bay Leaf - Bay leaves and berries have been used for their astringent, carminative, diaphoretic, digestive, diuretic, emetic and stomachic properties. Bay Oil, or Oil of Bays (Oleum Lauri) is used in liniments for bruising and sprains.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Allspice Berry - Allspice is used as a paste to soothe and relieve toothache, and as a mouthwash to freshen the breath.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Cumin Seed - Chewing roasted cumin seeds can also heal soars in the mouth and reduce excess saliva. Cumin boiled in water to make a tea cures problems in the urinary tract, cleans the bladder and kidneys. It also reduces pain in the body and acts as a natural sleep aid for those who have difficulty falling asleep.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Basil - Basil is used to treat stomach cramps, vomiting, fevers, colds, flu, headaches, whooping cough, and menstrual pains. It is also used to reduce stomach acid, making it a valuable part of any treatment for ulcers, and a valuable addition to any recipe using tomatoes for those with sensitive stomachs. Externally, it can be used for insect bites, to draw out the poisons.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Sumac Berries - An infusion of sumac berries is diuretic (cleanses the urinary tract), enduces vomiting, emmenagogue, purgative and reduces fever.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Sesame Seed - Sesame seeds have antibacterial properties. They also have calming properties that are beneficial in treating PMS, anxiety, and depression. They have anti-inflammatory properties as well useful for migraines andalso insomnia.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Saffron - Saffron is used as a preventative for heart disease, as it prevents the build-up of cholesterol. It is also used to soothe the membranes of the stomach and colon. It is not to be taken in large doses.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Paprika - Very effective added to liniments for all sorts of arthritis and muscle aches. Internally it benefits the heart and circulation when taken alone or added to other remedies. It is also used to stimulate the action of other herbs. It is also used to normalize blood pressure. It will stop bleeding both externally and internally, making it excellent for use with ulcers. It is used in antibiotic combinations, for menstrual cramps, and as a part of treatment for depression.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Nutmeg Seed - A small amount of nutmeg, about the size of a pea, can be taken once daily over a long period (6 months to a year) to relieve chronic nervous problems, as well as heart problems stemming from poor circulation. Added to milk, and baked fruits and desserts, it aids in digestion, and relieves nausea. Large doses can be poisonous, and may cause miscarriage for pregnant women.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Mustard Seed - When ground into a powder can be added to a bath to ease sprains and bruising. Made into a paste it can be applied directly to bruises and sprains (caution: If left on to long it will cause blisters.). The paste can also be rubbed on the chest and back to help with a deep rattling cough.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Lemongrass - Lemongrass is used to calm the nerves, as an anti-inflammatory, digestive aid, astringent, antiseptic, insect repellant, room disinfectant, and pest control.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<LI\>Ginger Root - Ginger is an excellent herb to use for strengthening and healing the respiratory system, as well as for fighting off colds and flu. It removes congestion, soothes sore throats, and relieves headaches and body aches. Combined with other herbs, it enhances their effectiveness. It is also very effective in combatting motion sickness. Recommended during pregnancy for treating morning sickness and digestive problems, as well as safe to use during pregnancy for colds and sore throats.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Fenugreek Seed - Fenugreek is used to soften and expel mucous. It has antiseptic properties and will kill infections in the lungs. Used with lemon and honey, it will help reduce a fever and will soothe and nourish the body during illness.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<LI\>Fennel Seed - Fennel helps to take away the appetite. It is often used as a sedative for small children. It improves digestion, and is very helpful with coughs.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Dill Seed - Dill is used to treat colic, gas, and indigestion.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Cubeb Seed - Has a sharp, clearing aroma, and is antisceptic. This is a useful addition to pre- and post-sport massage blends.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Coriander Seed - Coriander is analgesic, energizing, and aids digestion. Some common uses are for arthritis, indigestion, and flatulence.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Clove Buds - Clove oil will stop a toothache when it is applied directly to the cavity. It is very warm and stimulating to the system, and is very useful with people who have cold extremities. Cloves will promote sweating with fevers, colds, and flu. It is often used in remedies for whooping cough. Cloves are also safe and effective for relieving vomiting during pregnancy.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Cinnamon Bark - Cinnamon is analgesic, an aphrodisiac, energizing, aids digestion, and is an antiseptic. It also destroys or expells intestinal worms. Common uses include arthritis, colds, coughs, influenza, nausea, flatulence, insect repellant, loss of appetite, and a room disinfectant.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Licorice - Licorice Root is a great source of the female hormone estrogen. It is used for coughs and chest ailments. It is an important herb to use when recovering from an illness, as it supplies needed energy to the system. Used as a remedy for stomach and heart problems, indigestion, and most respiratory ailments. When ground into a paste and applied to the skin it has a numbing effect.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Cassia - Aromatic, similar to Cinnamon, but differing in both strength and quality. Cassia is a tonic, carminative and stimulant. It is used to effectively treat nausea and flatulence. It is also used alone, or in combination with other herbs, to treat diarrhea.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Anise - In a spiced cake prevents indigestion. Added to cold water on a hot day makes a refreshing potion. It averts the Evil Eye, and the oil is poisonus to pigeons. Anise seeds have been known for medicine in coughs. The oil mixed with spirits has beneficial action for spasmodic cough and chest pains and is good as an antiseptic mixed with mint and wintergreen for flavor.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Chive - Chives have traditionally been considered a digestive and used to improve the appetite. The plant has also been used as a folk remedy against asthma, colds, coughs, ulcers, high blood pressure, poor circulation, tumors, and leprosy.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Thyme - As a medicinal plant, thyme has traditionally been considered an anthelmintic, antispasmodic, carminative, emmenagogue, expectorant, rubefactient, sedative, stimulant, and tonic. The plant has been used as a folk medicine against asthma, arteriosclerosis, colic, bronchitis, coughs, diarrhea, and rheumatism. Thyme has been used to promote perspiration. Thymol is a powerful antiseptic, considered to be quite toxic. The plant and essential oil can cause contact dermatitis and may affect lipid metabolism. Thymus species have been used as a folk remedy against cancer.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<LI\>Mint - Peppermint is the mint of choice for medicinal purposes. It's many uses include the following: The menthol in peppermint soothes the lining of the digestive tract an stimulates the production of bile, which is an essential digestive fluid. A hot cup of herbal tea is an excellent way to settle your stomach after a big meal. There is a very good reason that peppermint is the flavoring of choice for toothpaste. Peppermint is an excellent breath freshener. When using peppermint tea as a breath freshener, increase the effectiveness by adding a pinch of anise, caraway or cinnamon. Peppermint is reputed to have the calming, sedative effect. Menthol vapors are famous for relieving nasal, sinus and chest congestion. Remember those minty-smelling ointments your mother rubbed on your chest when you were a child with a cold? You can also get relief with a steaming cup of peppermint tea. For a more effective cold remedy, combine peppermint with elder flower and yarrow. For a hacking cough, drink 3 to four cups of cool peppermint tea throughout the day, taking a sip every 15 to 30 minutes. To make peppermint tea, use 1 to 2 teaspoons of dried peppermint leaves per cup of boiling water. Steep for 10 minutes.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nsigned, Suavis." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:studies zanthia">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<b\>Study #1\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<u\>Emergency Medical Intervention\</i\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Written by Zanthia Blackthorn\</i\>\<br\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThough it is well documented, I would like to write a specific study purely on the uses and dangers of emergency medical intervention on a patient in need. Specifically, a patient should only be put through such measures if they are in desperate need of it. I recall one situation on the field where a panther had been shot through the leg and the doctor in charge of his case removed his leg. Suffice to say, it was entirely unnecessary and resulted in the death of the patient.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTo that end, I offer, in this study, a few methods to avoid drastic actions that do not rely on the Churches power of Resurrection, which as we know, is not foolproof. It is my hope that whomever decides to read this will take my thoughts and opinions into consideration when performing high maintenance procedures.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>Cleanliness\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nThough it is known that such things cannot sometimes be helped, it is important that one at least attempts, unless impossible to do so, to move the patient to a secure and clean environment. The clinic that is being built would be a great example of a suitable environment. It is my firm belief, though I could be mistaken, that a great many deaths that are suffered during difficult procedures are because of this. On the field, we had stretchers to be able to move people quickly and easily so we could work on them. Perhaps it is time we secured some for the City.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>Equipment\</u\>\\r\\nIt is also well known that this can also be a problem. We are not of an age where things are readily available, but keeping them in good, working condition is a must. Again I take an example from the field of war. Once, I saw a nurse working with, or I should say, trying to work with an old scalpel. It was so blunt that it, after we got a new one delivered to her, could not even cut butter. If one is going to attempt something dangerous and in difficult circumstances, it is advisable to at least try to keep your own equipment in good working order.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWith those two warnings, I will go into some of the procedures I have learned in the last three or four years.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>Cauterization\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nIts use is simple. Large wounds are often left bloody and open after the initial incident. This procedure burns the wounds closed and allows the skin and hair to grow over. Often, this will leave scars in the affected area. This is normally done by those that have either no, or little medical training and in my opinion, causes more damage than harm, since the job can be done more effectively by needle and thread. Should one decide to perform this, be sure that you have the necessary pain relief to keep them settled, for often, they will struggle and cry out in pain. If necessary, put them into a state of unconsciousness beforehand.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<u\>Gangrene\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\nThis specific ailment affects those of the sea. The causes are, as thus, unknown at this point, however, the effects are obvious. It often causes the skin to turn black and quite vile and at this point, the only cure I know of that will aid a person is the removal of the effected area. This seems to only target the lower limbs, like the feet. Should one need to treat, prepare for a lot of blood and some quick decisions. Cauterization after the affected limb has been removed is a must and aftercare must be given to make sure that the patient does not have any relapses.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThough I only listed two procedures, it is my hope to continue this study further, as new ailments are discovered.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:supplies">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "h3", "College of Medicine Supplies" \}), (\{ "text", "All College of Medicine members shall receive the following upon induction:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n-- 1 healers bag (OOC: Ask Nurse Melissa, located in the Infirmary).\<br\>\\r\\n-- 1 sharp-edged STEEL scalpel which can be obtained by a blacksmith.\<br\>\\r\\n-- 1 College of Medicine ring. Dean Temperance will supply one for you. \<br\>\\r\\n-- 10 bandages. May be bought from Nurse Melissa for 1 denar per bandage, or made by an elder healer.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nAll College of Medicine members shall have access to the following supplies that are being held in the Infirmary, within the crate and trunk. Upon lending these supplies to patients, please make a note of who you are lending them to, why and make sure they return the supplies given to them.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n-- Arm slings (left and right)\<br\>\\r\\n-- Arm splints (left and right)\<br\>\\r\\n-- Leg splints (left and right)\<br\>\\r\\n-- Tail splints\<br\>\\r\\n-- Two stretchers\<br\>\\r\\n-- Healing ointments\<br\>\\r\\n-- Burn ointment\<br\>\\r\\n-- Flasks of Holy Water\<br\>\\r\\n-- Canes\<br\>\\r\\n-- Crutches\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPlease note that it is important for the College to increase its inventory of Healing supplies.  Any additional supplies that you are able to obtain should be listed here. Note that I will check inventory every few days. Splints can be obtained by contacting a carpenter. Oils via gardener and slings via seamstress or elder healer. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:treatments">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h1\>Common Treatments\</h1\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<u\>Treating Bruises\</h2\>\</u\>\\r\\nIn every treatment, you should begin by assessing the severity of an injury. I suggest determining whether a bruise is minor, major, or severe.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf the bruise is minor, some massage of the area around the bruise may promote bloodflow through the area and release some of the discoloration of the bruise. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf the bruise is major, some massage of the area around the bruise may promote bloodflow through the area and release some of the discoloration of the bruise. Further cold compresses of towels with cold water may help alleviate the pain and tension caused by the bruise.  If pain is unbearable during movement, immobilization may be necessary. \<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<u\>Treating Burns\</u\>\</h2\>\\r\\nIf a patient has a bad burn, emerise area with water as cold as you can find. Pick off any dead, burnt, or blacked skin to prevent infection. Mix water with herbs, and other ointments as needed for burns, and apply to the burn generously. Burns should not be wrapped immediately instead allowed to 'air' with constant application of water, and ointments. (For the most severe burns, do not treat with water or ointment as it might actually prevent the skin and flesh from healing properly or may cause scarring.) After a period of minutes to hours depending on severity, soak a bandage in water, and apply normally. Check the burnt area every six hours for a period of a day, apply clean dressings. \<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<u\>Treating Cuts\</u\>\</h2\>\\r\\nIn every treatment, you should begin by assessing the severity of an injury.  I suggest determining whether a cut is minor, major, or severe; and to determine whether the cut is a clean slice, a puncture, a bite, or a jagged cut.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf the wound is minor, clean the wound thoroughly. Cut any hair that may be around the wound for better access. Apply gentle, yet firm pressure on the wound to stop bleeding, then apply a bandage.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf the wound is major, instantly apply pressure to the wounded area with a clean cloth or towel.  Clean the wound thoroughly with water and soap if available.  Pick out any forgeign fragments from the wound and continue to clean.  After bleeding has subsided cut hair surrounding the wound for better access. If the wound will not stop bleeding, stitches or sutures may be applied with a needle and thread.  If this is not possible and the bleeding will not stop, cauterize the wound with a piece of highly heated metal. Get another clean bandage if one is already used and apply this bandage to the wound. \<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<u\>Making a Tourniquet\</u\>\</h2\>\\r\\nIf a tourniquet is needed, first look for a belt, or strip of cloth that is firm and will not break. Wrap the limb several times with this tighter each time to successfully cut off blood flow. Always place a tourniquet between the wound and a major joint (hip, shoulder, knee, or elbow depending where the wound is). Always make sure the tourniquet is closer to the heart than the wound is. A stick, cane, or other long slender rod-like material can be used. Place this stick near the location where you would wrap. Wrap the stick with the bandage, affixing it to the area of the body that needs the tourniquet. Grasp the stick with both hands and turn to create a tighter tourniquet. This will stop blood flow to a wound while you treat it. As the patient, or another to hold the stick in place while you treat the wound. \<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<u\>Cauterizing a Cut\</u\>\</h2\>\\r\\nIf a cauterizing is needed, first transport the patient close to a source of fire. Heat a piece of metal (blades, or anything that you can hold) until glowing red. Douse the wound with water and then immediately apply the red-hot metal. Hold in place for the count of five seconds and douse the metal and the wound with a great amout of water with removing the metal. Repeat if needed. Afterward treat the cauterized area with water, herbs, and other ointments needed for burns. Apply a bandage as needed.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "More treatments will be added. Feel free to write Doctor Temperance with suggestions or treatments you found effective." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1222214845, "barbra18", "E", 1222214874, "barbra18", "E", 1222217275, "barbra18", "E", 1222218578, "barbra18", "E", 1222218604, "barbra18", "E", 1222218617, "barbra18", "E", 1222220590, "barbra18", "E", 1222220611, "barbra18", "E", 1222220630, "barbra18", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
