<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Hi. I'm Ditto. I see your snooping but I'll be nice and not smite you. Instead I'll be nice and give you a hint. Go to plots in my guild and you can see a preview of the next plot." \}), (\{ "image", "http://i878.photobucket.com/albums/ab349/nannersbunny/ditto.jpg" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plots">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 4 \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Return to fight the cannibals.  The back story for this plot is from the previous plot.  The swamp people who are normally peaceful came to town and started blowing up parts of town to get citizen's attention.  They needed our help to rebuild their homes and they blame us. Well a large group went to the swamp and tried to rebuild but swamp conditions made it near impossible and then the cherry on top was the attacks of the cannibals.  They are enemies of the swamp people and are breaking a treaty.  The treaty states as long as no house is erected then the cannibals can hunt the swamp people so thus the cannibals won't let you rebuild.  The idea to go back is two fold. First to dress up as gods and try to trick the cannibals into thinking we are their gods.  If that fails the plan is to overwhelm and extinguish them.  My advice is to bring anything odd thing that could be useful because the cannibals know the swamp and will use it against you.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Finished plot. This week is dedicated to the shady careers.  This would include thieves, pickpockets, thugs, sabeautors, assassin, spy.  These people will get a +1 influence with the gang.  There is a new gang in town and will stay in one area of town.  They are well known to you as you set their homes on fire. Say hello to the dockstreet gang. They used to be the swamp dwellers till you blew their homes up.  Now they come to town to get some revenge.  \\r\\n\\r\\nA new aspect I am going to try out is: You get influence by your deeds.  If you are a fighter and you beat a mob you get +1 influence. Be warned this is very hard and not for the faint of heart.  IF you are a negotiator you can try to sway their mind set and get +1 influence. But again it won't be easy.  If you are a trader you could try setting up trade with the swamps and get a +1 influence.  \\r\\n\\r\\nWhat will this influence do you ask?  With +3 influence you will be a ambassador to to swamp and can set up trade and other affairs with the swamp dwellers. " \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Finished plot on Rinaldi week on May 11.  The final house series.  All rin members get a -2 to the targets.  This plot will be a little different.  Everyone is going to die...you have to die to be involved as everyone will be doing this plot in the afterlife.  So good news is you can't die on the plot..oh wait..Yes you can. There is a very slight possibility of permadeath.  IF you die as a ghost you really die.  I'll tell you before hand if what your rolling can result in permadeath.   My hint for you is to get one person you really really trust who isn't going on the plot and have them bring the bodies to the crypt.  Yup I'm being evil, you have to die and you have to be put on the altar or you have to wait two weeks instead of three days to be brought back to life.  That brings up a fun part of the plot.  You have three days to complete the task in the afterlife or you come back to life and the plot is failed and you'll have to die all over again to try to succeed. You will be ghosts so you can't bring anything with you also so no risk of losing anything. " \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
