<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:costs">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Please note that all prices shown are assuming you want IRON as the metal made. If you wish a different metal, please write to me with your order and I will write back with an estimate of the price before I begin to work." \}), (\{ "text", "\<table border=\\"1\\"\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Object\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Cost\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Description\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Chainmail Outfits\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>24 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Comes with a hood, shirt, pants, gauntlets and boots. Trimming and coloring available\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Chestplate\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>12 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>It is forged in a suitable shape to cover the torso, and allows arms to be let out freely. Chestplates are typically lighter than breastplates.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Breastplate\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>12 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>The front is curved to protect from spear blows to the chest.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Shields (Buckler, Kite, Heater, Tower)\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>10 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\> Buckler: A small, round disk-shaped shield, very light and maneuverable to block fast quick blows.\\r\\n\\r\\nHeater: The heater shield is a form of shield characterized by its distinctive shape. Smaller than the kite-shield, it is more manageable and can be used either mounted or on foot. It is flat-topped and tapers down into a pointed tip.\\r\\n\\r\\nKite: (Description Unavailable Currently)\\r\\n\\r\\nTower: This shield is roughly the size of a fully-grown man. It is curved slightly so that it can be held close to ones body and provide a great deal of protection. Its crippling weight makes it rather ineffective to maneuver with. Spears and other polearms are often favored to be used with this shield.\\r\\n\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Greaves\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>8 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>It wraps the front sides of the lower legs for protection.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Bracers\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>6 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>They are plates wrapped around the wrists, usually worn by archers or fencers for protection.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Schynbalds\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>4 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>These are metal plates strapped over chausses, each schynbald is a single piece of metal that covers the front and outside of the shin. They do not enclose the lower leg: hence, they are not true greaves.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Besagews\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>2 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>They are circular defenses used to protect the under arms, the armpits particularly, as part of a harness of plate armor.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Culet\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>8 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>A piece of plate armor consisting of small, horizontal lames that protect the small of the back or the buttocks.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Ailettes\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>4 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Ailettes are attached to the shoulders by means of silk or leather cord. They are usually flat and rectangular in shape.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Rondel\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>2 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>This is a circular piece of metal used for protection, as a harness of plate armor, or attached to a helmet, breastplate, couter, or on a gauntlet.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Sabatons\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>8 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>These are rivetted plates that are worn upon the feet and protect them from damage while allowing movement and flexibility.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Codpiece\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>2 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>It is a flap or pouch that attaches to the front of the crotch of men's pants to provide covering for the genitals. It was held closed by string ties, buttons, or other methods.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Small Bars\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Free with your materials\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Small metal bars used for crafting by jewelers.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Couters\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>2 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>They are a component in a piece of plate armor, they are used in defense of the elbows. They are forged into an articulate joint.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Poleyns\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>4 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Developed with an articulated construction, these are plates designed for protecting the knees. They can be attached to cuisses or greaves, as desired.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Spike\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>1 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>An iron spike, suitable to be added to armor.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Helmet\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>8 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Generic: It is a form of protective gear worn on the head to protect it from injuries, a variation of the hat. Kettle Hat: It is a type of helmet made from metal in the shape of a hat. The only common element is a wide brim that afforded extra protection for the wearer. It was worn by troops of all types, but most commonly by infantry. The wide brim gave good protection against blows from above, such as from cavalry sabres, and were very useful in siege warfare as the wide brim would protect the wearer from projectiles shot or dropped from above. Cervelliere:  round, close-fitting skull cap; this helmet was frequently worn beneath a great helm (heaume). Capeline:  It is also known as a lobster pot. The lobster-tailed pot had ear flaps, a visor that included a sliding nasal bar to protect the trooper from sword thrusts and an articulated \\"tail\\" protecting the back of the head that was said to resemble a lobster. Spangenhelm: The name is of Northern origin. Spangen refers to the metal straps that form the framework for the helmet and could be translated as clips, and -helm simply means helmet. The strips connect three to six plates (normally steel or bronze). The frame takes a conical design that curves with the shape of the head and culminates in a point. The front of the helmet includes a nose protector (a nasal) and cheek flaps made from leather.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Spaulders\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>6 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>A part of plate armor, they are armored plates forged to protect the upper arms and shoulders. As these do not cover the arm holes when worn with a cuirass, the gaps may be defended by besagews or simply left bare, exposing the mail beneath.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Cuirass\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>12 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>a piece of armour, formed of a single or multiple pieces of metal or other rigid material, which covers the front of the wearer's person. In a suit of armour this important piece was generally connected to a back piece and cuirass could refer to the complete torso-protecting armour.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Gauntlets\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>8 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>They protect the backs of hands and the wrists, and are made of many smaller plates that allow flexibility of the fingers.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Pauldrons\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>6 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Larger than spaulders, these are a component of plate armor made to cover the shoulders, armpits, and sometimes parts of the back and chest. Typically, pauldrons tend to consist of a single dome-shaped piece to cover the shoulder with multiple lames attached to defend the arm.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Gorget\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>6 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>A cover for the neck, shoulders, clavicles, and sternum, the top attaches directly to the base of a helmet while the bottom fastens to a breastplate or cuirass.\\r\\n\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\</table\> " \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "page", "List of Armors and Costs", "costs" \}), (\{ "page", "List of Weapons and Costs", "weapons" \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:weapons">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Please note that all prices listed are assuming you want the weapon to be made of IRON. If you would like it to be made from another material, state such and the prices shall be scaled to the cost of the metal." \}), (\{ "text", "\<table border=\\"1\\"\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Object\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Cost\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Description\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Dagger\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>10 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Not Available\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Sword\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>10 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Not Available\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Arming Sword\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>10 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>The classic double-edged knightly blade. Known as a diamond-section blade, the arming blade has a ridge in the middle, along the length of the blade.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\\r\\n\<td\>Short Sword\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>10 denarii\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>An older style of arming blade, featuring an indent along the middle of the blade. This design allows for reinforced edges with the indent reducing the overall weight.\</td\>\\r\\n\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\</table\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
