<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "\<center\>Administration\</center\>" \}), (\{ "h3", "Members And Guild Rings" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<table\>\<tr\>\<td\>" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\</td\>\<td\>" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\</td\>\</tr\>\</table\>" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Tokens" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<hr\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Guest Main Page", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Guild Patrons", "patrons" \}), (\{ "page", "Rules and Guidelines for Masters and Bonded Workers", "rules" \}), (\{ "page", "Workers for Rental", "slaves" \}), (\{ "page", "Trading and Inventory", "trading" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "\<center\>The Society for the Humane Distribution of Bonded Labour\</center\>" \}), (\{ "h3", "Our Goals" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Society Hopes to give consumers an alternative to slaves kept in a dangerous and unforgiving environment. By giving bonded labourers a modicum of control over their own fate, and their Masters a rigid set of humane rules and punishments to adhere to, we plan to bring credence to the belief that there are more to slaves than simply the work they can do and the trouble they might cause." \}), (\{ "h3", "Our Promises" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<b\>Our Promise to YOU, the Master\</b\> is that you will always have a healthy worker. We protect your right to ownership, and will never recall on a contract without legal due course. \<br\>We promise that anyone outside the Society harming your bonded labourer will be dealt with to the full extent of the law.\<br\>And we promise a cheaper contract than our competitors currently offer." \}), (\{ "h3", "Our Methods" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "We plan to maintain a happier work environment for your bonded labourer, through a variety of mechanisms, and hope that this will result in a more productive worker.\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\n - Enforcing a set of humane rules and punishments, where the bonded labourer knows exactly what misbehaviour will result in. \<br\>\\r\\n - Contributing a small amount of the rental fee to a savings plan for the bonded labourer, with the intention of buying their freedom in the future. \<br\>\\r\\n - By having the bonded labourers pay a fine from their savings plan each time they misbehave, the worker is directly responsible for the length of their bondage.\<br\>\\r\\n - By agreeing to the restrictions placed upon you, the Master, by the Society, we make owning a bonded labourer even easier, by giving you a discount on the rental cost of the worker.\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Workers for Rental", "slaves" \}), (\{ "page", "Guild Patrons", "patrons" \}), (\{ "page", "Rules and Guidelines for Masters and Bonded Workers", "rules" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:patrons">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "Patrons of the Society" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Society is looking for Patrons to support it's initial entry into the slave bidding market. Patrons can be kept anonymous or may wish their humanitarian efforts to be applauded. Noble houses will be contacted with details in the near future, Guilds will also be welcomed, as well as private donations." \}), (\{ "page", "Guest Main Page", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Workers for Rental", "slaves" \}), (\{ "page", "Rules and Guidelines for Masters and Bonded Workers", "rules" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:rules">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "\<center\>Guild Rules pertaining to the Humane and Ethical Treatment of Bonded Labourers\</center\>" \}), (\{ "h3", "Conditions for Masters" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Renters are responsible for all crimes committed by slaves that they have under contract\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nIf a Renter is punished for any crime that the slave commits, they may enact the same punishment upon the slave, in equal amounts. This counts for the following punishments:\<br\>\\r\\n-\\tFlogging\\r\\n\<br\>-\\tDeclawing\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nAlso, any fine suffered by a Renter for their slave’s actions will be taken from the slave’s standing ‘Freedom’ account.\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nThese punishments can only be enacted by the Renter of the slave, or in their presence. All punishments given to slaves in this manner must be reported to the slave overseer.\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nIn the cases where physical harm will be enacted on the slaves, the punishment may only be equal to what the Renter personally suffered. If the renter is not satisfied that their slave’s behavior has improved the following further punishments may be enacted at the Renter’s discretion, and additional fines listed can be taken from the slaves account.\<p\>\\r\\n\<table\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>\<b\>Action\</b\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>\<b\>Punishment\</b\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>\<b\>Fine\</b\>\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Assault of another Slave\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Binding\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>10\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Assault of Free Person\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Binding, de-clawing, shackling\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>20\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Possessing a weapon\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Binding, de-clawing, muzzling\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>10\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Theft\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Shackling, binding\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Value of Theft\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Vocal Disobedience\<br\>(includes swearing, vulgarity, disrespect, lying)\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Washing Mouth with Soap, Muzzling\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>5\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Vocal Disobedience targeting Nobility\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Washing Mouth, Muzzling\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>10\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Murder*\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Execution**, flogging, de-clawing, imprisonment\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>50\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Treason*\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Execution**, flogging\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>50\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Property Damage\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Shackling, Binding\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>value of damaged property\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n \<tr\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Kidnapping*\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>Execution**, flogging, de-clawing\</td\>\\r\\n  \<td\>50\</td\>\\r\\n \</tr\>\\r\\n\</table\>\\r\\n\<p\>Private Imprisonment and other non-violent punishments may be used for any disobedience\\r\\n\<p\>* Upon proof of the crime as acknowledged by a sergeant or higher in the constabulary, or a magistrate\\r\\n\<p\>** In cases where slave is executed due to lax discipline or monitoring on the part of the renter, the slaves full value will be paid to the Company. In cases where it can be proven that reasonable attempts were made to control the slave, the cost of the contract minus the time already served by the slave and the deposit will be refunded by the company.\\r\\n\<p\>Instances where these rules are not followed will immediately result in an investigation by the slave's enforcer. Any breach of these rules may be subject to immediate cancellation of the renter’s contract, at the Overseers decision. If a Renter feels that their contract was unfairly terminated, they can attempt to sue the company via the courts, or take the matter to a neutral constable to settle the matter outside the courts. Smaller breaches will be met with small fines, which will be put into the slave’s freedom fund. Gross breaches of contract will be charged with property damage, to the full extent of the law. \\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "h3", "Rules for Bonded Labourers" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Bonded Labourers are expected to follow all laws of the city, as well as the following series of rules.\\r\\n\<ol\>\<li\>A slave may not injure a free person\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A slave must obey all orders given to it by it’s master, except where orders will contravene the first rule\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A slave must protect it’s own life, so long as this does not conflict with the first or second rule\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>If a slave feels it is being treated in a way that is not according to the rules for Renters, they can contact their enforcer with details. This rule may contravene the second rule. If the maltreatment is by an enforcer, they may contact the ethical committee.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>If a slave is punished by anyone except their Master, or in their Master’s presence, they can contact their enforcer with details.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A slave must follow all orders of nobility, unless orders conflict with the first, second of third rule.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A slave must follow all orders of Bonded Labour Enforcers, unless orders conflict with first, second, third, or sixth rule.\</li\>\\r\\n\</ol\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "h3", "Additional Guild Rules" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Slaves must be fed the nutritional equivalent of prisoners rations every day. Food deprivation may not be used as a punishment. Failure to meet these nutritional needs will equate a breach of contract, and slave may be recalled. \<i\>\<b\>OOC : In the case where you are absent from the game, this of course will not be put into effect. We assume slaves are fed as a bluebooked action, unless explicitly stated otherwise.\</b\>\</i\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nIf a Master leaves the City for any length of time over 1 weeks without seeing to someone to take care of their slave, the slave will be seized by the company until the Master's return. This care must be official, and word must be sent to the company of any changes in care or ownership. Upon the Master's return, slave will be returned to their employ for the remainder of their contract. \<p\>\\r\\nIf a Master leaves the City for more than two months without transference of care, the contract is rendered void, and the company may reclaim the slave, and re-distribute it. If the Master later returns to the City, they may have the percentage of their renting fee returned (not including their deposit), or may resume their contract uninterrupted IF another contract has not been begun. \<i\>\<b\>OOC : This is to try and make things fun and fair for both slaves, who get bored without a Master, and Masters, who are paying good cash to have a slave.\</i\>\</b\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>A Master may not deny the slave medical treatment if they require it. If injuries or condition are life-threatening, and treatment is not sought, the Master can be charged bythe Company for willful property damage. If condition is not life threatening, the Master may order the slave to finish what work they require done, until either the work is completed, or their condition becomes life-threatening.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Enforcers are expected to protect slaves from harm, and in the cases of slaves not under contract, enforce the slaves discipline. When disciplining out of contract slaves, Enforcers must adhere to the same rules as Renters. \\r\\n\<p\>\\r\\nEnforcers wear the bronze Bonded Labour Rings.\\r\\n\<br\>Ethical Commitee wear silver Bonded Labour Rings\\r\\n\<br\>Slave Overseer wear Gold Bonded Labour Ring." \}), (\{ "page", "Guest Main Page", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Workers for Rental", "slaves" \}), (\{ "page", "Guild Patrons", "patrons" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:slaves">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h2", "Bonded Labourers for Rental" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Society does not have the contracts to any bonded workers presently." \}), (\{ "page", "Guest Main Page", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Guild Patrons", "patrons" \}), (\{ "page", "Rules and Guidelines for Masters and Bonded Workers", "rules" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
