<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:expense records">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Price List\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<b\>Teabags are now for sale\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThose that are avilable:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nallspice, anise, red apple, bay laurel, cassia, cherry, chive, cinnamon, clove, coriander, cubeb, fennel, fenugreek, ginger, lemongrass, licorice, peppermint, saffron, sumac, thyme, tobacco\<Br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>4 Denarii each\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<b\>Herbs for Sale at 2 denarii:\</b\> Anise Seed, Bay Leaf, Basil Leaf, Cassia Bark, Cinnamon Bark, Chives, Clove Buds, Coriander Seed, Cubeb Seed, Cumin Seed, Dill Seed, Fennel Seed, Fenugreek Seed, Ginger Root, Lemongrass, Licorice Root, Mint, Mustard Seed, Nutmeg Seed, Paprika, Saffron, Sesame Seed, Sumac Berry, Thyme and Vanilla.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flowers for sale\</b\> in bunches of 12, at 8 denarii: Daisies, Foxglove, Lilies, Marigolds, Orchids, Roses and Tulips.\<br\>\\r\\n\<BR\>\\r\\n\<b\>Oils for sale\</b\> at 10 denarii: Bergamot, Carrot seed, Cedarwood, Chamomile, Cinnamon, Clary sage, Clove, Eucalyptus blue gum, Eucalyptus lemon, Geranium, Ginger, Grapefruit, Lavender, Lemongrass, Patchouli, Peppermint, Rosemary, Rosewood, Spearmint, Sweet Orange and Tangerine.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCigars for sale at 16 denarii\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nQuartz Pendants for sale at 10 denarii.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nHerbal properties list for sale at 15 denarii.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFertilizer for sale at 3 denarii.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFlower Pots for sale at 4 denarii.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTea Kettles for sale at 150 denarii.\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Members List and Descriptions", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Orders and Opinions", "orders or opinions" \}), (\{ "page", "Plant Symbology", "plant symbology" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:herb use">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h1", "~ Herb Usage ~" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Allspice Berry - Allspice is used as a paste to soothe and relieve toothache, and as a mouthwash to freshen the breath." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Anise - In a spiced cake prevents indigestion. Added to cold water on a hot day makes a refreshing potion. It averts the Evil Eye, and the oil is poisonus to pigeons. Anise seeds have been known for medicine in coughs. The oil mixed with spirits has beneficial action for spasmodic cough and chest pains and is good as an antiseptic mixed with mint and wintergreen for flavor." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Basil - Basil is used to treat stomach cramps, vomiting, fevers, colds, flu, headaches, whooping cough, and menstrual pains. It is also used to reduce stomach acid, making it a valuable part of any treatment for ulcers, and a valuable addition to any recipe using tomatoes for those with sensitive stomachs. Externally, it can be used for insect bites, to draw out the poisons." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Bay Leaf - Bay leaves and berries have been used for their astringent, carminative, diaphoretic, digestive, diuretic, emetic and stomachic properties. Bay Oil, or Oil of Bays (Oleum Lauri) is used in liniments for bruising and sprains." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Cassia Bark - Aromatic, similar to Cinnamon, but differing in both strength and quality. Cassia is a tonic, carminative and stimulant. It is used to effectively treat nausea and flatulence. It is also used alone, or in combination with other herbs, to treat diarrhea." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Chive - Chives have traditionally been considered a digestive and used to improve the appetite. The plant has also been used as a folk remedy against asthma, colds, coughs, ulcers, high blood pressure, poor circulation, tumors, and leprosy" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Cinnamon Bark - Cinnamon is analgesic, an aphrodisiac, energizing, aids digestion, and is an antiseptic. It also destroys or expells intestinal worms. Common uses include arthritis, colds, coughs, influenza, nausea, flatulence, insect repellant, loss of appetite, and a room disinfectant." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Clove Buds - Clove oil will stop a toothache when it is applied directly to the cavity. It is very warm and stimulating to the system, and is very useful with people who have cold extremities. Cloves will promote sweating with fevers, colds, and flu. It is often used in remedies for whooping cough. Cloves are also safe and effective for relieving vomiting during pregnancy." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Coriander Seed - Coriander is analgesic, energizing, and aids digestion. Some common uses are for arthritis, indigestion, and flatulence." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Cubeb Seed - Has a sharp, clearing aroma, and is antisceptic. This is a useful addition to pre- and post-sport massage blends." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Cumin Seed - Chewing roasted cumin seeds can also heal soars in the mouth and reduce excess saliva. Cumin boiled in water to make a tea cures problems in the urinary tract, cleans the bladder and kidneys. It also reduces pain in the body and acts as a natural sleep aid for those who have difficulty falling asleep." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Dill Seed - Dill is used to treat colic, gas, and indigestion." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Fennel Seed - Fennel helps to take away the appetite. It is often used as a sedative for small children. It improves digestion, and is very helpful with coughs." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Fenugreek Seed - Fenugreek is used to soften and expel mucous. It has antiseptic properties and will kill infections in the lungs. Used with lemon and honey, it will help reduce a fever and will soothe and nourish the body during illness." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Ginger Root - Ginger is an excellent herb to use for strengthening and healing the respiratory system, as well as for fighting off colds and flu. It removes congestion, soothes sore throats, and relieves headaches and body aches. Combined with other herbs, it enhances their effectiveness. It is also very effective in combatting motion sickness. Recommended during pregnancy for treating morning sickness and digestive problems, as well as safe to use during pregnancy for colds and sore throats." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Lemongrass - Lemongrass is used to calm the nerves, as an anti-inflammatory, digestive aid, astringent, antiseptic, insect repellant, room disinfectant, and pest control.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Licorice - Licorice Root is a great source of the female hormone estrogen. It is used for coughs and chest ailments. It is an important herb to use when recovering from an illness, as it supplies needed energy to the system. Used as a remedy for stomach and heart problems, indigestion, and most respiratory ailments. When ground into a paste and applied to the skin it has a numbing effect." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Mint - Peppermint is the mint of choice for medicinal purposes. It's many uses include the following: The menthol in peppermint soothes the lining of the digestive tract an stimulates the production of bile, which is an essential digestive fluid. A hot cup of herbal tea is an excellent way to settle your stomach after a big meal. There is a very good reason that peppermint is the flavoring of choice for toothpaste. Peppermint is an excellent breath freshener. When using peppermint tea as a breath freshener, increase the effectiveness by adding a pinch of anise, caraway or cinnamon. Peppermint is reputed to have the calming, sedative effect. Menthol vapors are famous for relieving nasal, sinus and chest congestion. Remember those minty-smelling ointments your mother rubbed on your chest when you were a child with a cold? You can also get relief with a steaming cup of peppermint tea. For a more effective cold remedy, combine peppermint with elder flower and yarrow. For a hacking cough, drink 3 to four cups of cool peppermint tea throughout the day, taking a sip every 15 to 30 minutes. To make peppermint tea, use 1 to 2 teaspoons of dried peppermint leaves per cup of boiling water. Steep for 10 minutes." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Mustard Seed - When ground into a powder can be added to a bath to ease sprains and bruising. Made into a paste it can be applied directly to bruises and sprains (caution: If left on to long it will cause blisters.). The paste can also be rubbed on the chest and back to help with a deep rattling cough.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nutmeg Seed - A small amount of nutmeg, about the size of a pea, can be taken once daily over a long period (6 months to a year) to relieve chronic nervous problems, as well as heart problems stemming from poor circulation. Added to milk, and baked fruits and desserts, it aids in digestion, and relieves nausea. Large doses can be poisonous, and may cause miscarriage for pregnant women.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Paprika - Very effective added to liniments for all sorts of arthritis and muscle aches. Internally it benefits the heart and circulation when taken alone or added to other remedies. It is also used to stimulate the action of other herbs. It is also used to normalize blood pressure. It will stop bleeding both externally and internally, making it excellent for use with ulcers. It is used in antibiotic combinations, for menstrual cramps, and as a part of treatment for depression.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Saffron - Saffron is used as a preventative for heart disease, as it prevents the build-up of cholesterol. It is also used to soothe the membranes of the stomach and colon. It is not to be taken in large doses.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Sesame Seed - Sesame seeds have antibacterial properties. They also have calming properties that are beneficial in treating PMS, anxiety, and depression. They have anti-inflammatory properties as well useful for migraines andalso insomnia." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Sumac Berries - An infusion of sumac berries is diuretic (cleanses the urinary tract), enduces vomiting, emmenagogue, purgative and reduces fever." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Thyme - As a medicinal plant, thyme has traditionally been considered an anthelmintic, antispasmodic, carminative, emmenagogue, expectorant, rubefactient, sedative, stimulant, and tonic. The plant has been used as a folk medicine against asthma, arteriosclerosis, colic, bronchitis, coughs, diarrhea, and rheumatism. Thyme has been used to promote perspiration. Thymol is a powerful antiseptic, considered to be quite toxic. The plant and essential oil can cause contact dermatitis and may affect lipid metabolism. Thymus species have been used as a folk remedy against cancer." \}), (\{ "page", "Guest", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Members", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Orders and Opinions", "orders or opinions" \}), (\{ "page", "Plant Symbology", "plant symbology" \}), (\{ "page", "Pregnancy Herb Information", "pregnancy" \}), (\{ "page", "Price List", "price list" \}), (\{ "page", "Teaching Schedule", "teaching schedule" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:inventory">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:members">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "~ Guild Members ~" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<B\>Fips\</B\> is a short plump raccoon, with even, sleek light grey fur, and combed black hair, worn in an accent braid. Sharp bondi blue eyes are set above a pug nose and a plump mouth, complete with full lips. Stubby flat claws, on stubby hands, and stubby feet are also visible. You also note his arched eyebrows and attentive ears. He is carrying a gold Linlae ring, a cotton money pouch, five ripe tomatoes, a scroll and a yellow agrimony cluster. He is wearing a ragged straw hat, a jade leather satchel, a pair of muddy suede moccasins, a black leather long jacket, a raven brocade vest, a pearl silk shirt, a pearl and platinum bracelet, a black suede double-wrap belt, a bronze Rinaldi Trade Union ring, a coral-set yellow gold ring, a silver coiled armband, a multi-faceted blue quartz pendant, a bronze Rinaldi ring, a rich green brocade slashed sleeved doublet, a purple cloak and a pair of jade suede pants.\\r\\n\<BR\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:npc">
         (\{ (\{ 3, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "Non Player Character" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Teacher Maintenance: \</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCurrently taught: Translator, Merchant, Gardener, Woodcutter, Unarmed, Magic, Whip, Dagger, Scholar, Healer, Entertainer and Dilettante. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:orders or opinions">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "h1", "Orders and Opinions" \}), (\{ "h3", "Here is where the inhabitants of DockTown can place their orders or opinions about the guild." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Place your opinions here:" \}), (\{ "page", "Guest", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Members List and Descriptions", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Plant Symbology", "plant symbology" \}), (\{ "page", "Pregnancy Herb Information", "pregnancy" \}), (\{ "page", "Price List", "price list" \}), (\{ "page", "Teaching Schedule", "teaching schedule" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:other">
         (\{ (\{ 3, 3 \}), (\{ "h1", "~ Linlae Gardening Guild Allies ~" \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>The Hands of St. Trahern\</b\>, lead by Bruno,\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>lePlow Jewelers\</b\>, lead by Clover.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plant symbology">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h1", "~ Plant Symbology ~" \}), (\{ "h2", "An encyclopaedia of the symbology in common plants." \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>Acanthus:\</b\> The symbolic significance of acanthus is probably based on its thorns; it indicates that a difficult problem has been completely solved.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Agrimony (A rose plant):\</b\> It is an ancient medicinal and magical plant. Dug up with a nonferrous tool, the agrimony is supposed to provide one with the affection and love of women.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Angelica:\</b\> It was considered the primary remedy for the plague, having, according to legend, been brought to a monk by and angel.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Arnica:\</b\> It is thought to offer protection from lightning, witches and sorcerers.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Asphodel:\</b\> It is thought to be a death plant. The roots were thought to be the food of the deceased. The asphodel plant was also regarded as a defence against evil spirits.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Beans:\</b\> As seeds of an abundant, useful plant, beans promise good fortune and fertility. They are also thought to offer defence against evil spirits, disease and lightning.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Blue Flower:\</b\> It is regarded as a general symbol of romantic longing for the infinite.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Borage:\</b\> Believed to dispel gloomy thoughts. It is a symbol of excellent qualities that lie hidden behind humbleness.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Camomile:\</b\> It is used as an effective medicinal plant (especially for gynaecological ailments). It is regarded as a symbol of modesty, coupled with strength.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Carnation:\</b\> It is found to represent betrothals, probably as a love and fertility symbol.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Celandine:\</b\> A multipurpose medicinal plant. The celandine has the symbolic meaning of “enabling one to see,” of healing spiritual blindness, of being a bringer of light. Folk belief also saw the plant as a symbol of contentment, since the plant supposedly granted to anyone who carried it the power to settle disagreements.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Clover:\</b\> A symbol of vitality. It is a sacred magical plant. Four leaf clover is thought to bring good luck; on the other hand, clovers having more than four leaves are usually thought to bring misfortune, and only the five-leaf clover is occasionally thought to be a reference to a happy marriage.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Crocus:\</b\> Crocus wreaths are supposed to protect one from drunkenness. It is a symbol of light and majesty: the clothes of gods and kings were thus frequently coloured saffron yellow. It is therefore the symbol of Gold and thus the highest virtue, love.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Daisy:\</b\> It symbolises eternal life and salvation, yet also, like the Marguerite, tears and drops of blood.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Ground Ivy:\</b\> It is a common medicinal plant. A wreath made of ground ivy supposedly gives one the ability to recognise witches.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Hyssop:\</b\> Since the plants grow in rocky grounds, it is regarded as a symbol of humility. It is also commonly used as medicine.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Ivy:\</b\> Like most evergreen plants, ivy is a symbol of immortality. The unchanging green colour and climbing, yet “huggling” character of this plant also makes it a symbol of friendship and fidelity, which is why, for example, it is presented to a bride and groom at a wedding. Because of its need to lean on something, ivy is sometimes regarded as a feminine symbol as well.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Laurel:\</b\> Like all evergreen plants, the laurel is a symbol of immortality. During antiquity, it was thought to be physically and morally purifying; it was attributed with the ability to give poetic inspiration and the power to tell the future; it was also thought to ward off lightning. With respect to its significance for immortality thereby it attained; in this respect, it was also used (usually as a laurel wreath) as an award for particular achievements in science and art (especially literature).\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Lily:\</b\> The white lily is an old and very common light symbol; aside from this, it is also regarded as a symbol of purity, innocence and virginity. The lily is also a very old regal symbol and plays an important role of varying significance in heraldry.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Lily of the Valley:\</b\> A medicinal plant used for numerous ailments. Symbolises the “salvation of the world”.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Lotus:\</b\> Since it closes its flower in the evening, draws back into the water, and does not re-surface and open up again until sunrise, it is an old light symbol; as a white, blue or red flower rising from slimy waters, the lotus flower is a symbol of purity’s overcoming of impurity.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Mandrake (Mandragon or Mandragora):\</b\>  Night shade plant that, according to popular belief, grew underneath the gallows from the sperm of hanged men (the root was therefore frequently called “little gallows man”). It has uses as a medicinal agent and as a charm, also as an aphrodisiac and a narcotic before operations. It was thus regarded as a magical, efficacious symbol of love and fertility due to its effects as an aphrodisiac and narcotic. The mandrake is attributed with the power to bring happiness, fertility and wealth.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Marguerite:\</b\> Or “meadow daisy”. (Latin margarita means “pearl”), the plant was compared with the Pearl and thus also with tears, yet also with spilled drops of blood. It frequently refers to the deaths and sufferings.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Marigold:\</b\> It is also called “sun bride”; it is an ancient medicinal plant. It is a symbol of ancient salvation.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Mimosa:\</b\> The leaves of the Noli me tangere (touch-me-not) variety fold together at the slightest tough; the mimosa is thus a symbol of sensitivity and bashfulness. It is also a symbol of light and of the certainty of salvation.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Mistletoe:\</b\> Is often thought of as a defence against disease, lightning and sorcery, as a bringer of good luck and, since it is an evergreen, as an immortality symbol.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Mugwort:\</b\> Various types of mugwort were thought of as bridal flowers.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Mullein:\</b\> It is a medicinal plant; supposedly protects one from fear and harm.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Narcissus:\</b\> It is symbolically associated with sleep. It was planted on graves as a sign of the kinship between death and sleep. Sometimes it is thought of as a symbol of spring and fertility.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Orchid:\</b\> They are considered as an aphrodisiac and a fertility symbol; sometimes used for love-spells and were supposed to protect one from sickness and the evil eye, to give one good luck in gambling, and to make one rich.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Pansy:\</b\> Widely varying symbolic meanings were ascribed to the pansy; it is regarded as a symbol of the coyness of young girls, the fidelity of lovers, as well as the envy, a trait that was attributed especially to stepmothers.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Periwinkle:\</b\> Like all evergreen plants, it is a symbol of eternal life and fidelity; it is also regarded as a defence against witches and sorcerers.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Poppy:\</b\> It is a symbol of the earth, yet also of sleep and forgetfulness.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Rose:\</b\> It is a symbol of love and affection, of fertility and also of reverence toward the dead. The red rose is a symbol of divine love generally.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Rue:\</b\> It is a symbolic and magical plant that is supposed to protect a bride from black magic; it is also called a “death herb” because people lay wreaths of wound rue onto the chest or neck of corpses.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Sempervivum:\</b\> Popular beliefs thought that it offered protection against lightning and storms (“thunder plant”). As an extremely long-lived plant, it was also a symbol for eternal life (compare the Latin name), especially in nativity scenes.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Sesame:\</b\> Seeds are thought to be a food that extended one’s life and strengthened one’s mind.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Sunflower:\</b\> The sunflower is a symbol of the sun and nobility in various cultures.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Thistle:\</b\> It is a symbol for sufferings and thus a symbol of salvation. The prickles, which repel enemies, can also be a symbol of protection. The thistle is also regarded as a symbol of long life, possibly because it keeps its shape even after it has been cut and dried.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Wormwood:\</b\> A type of mugwort. Used for searching and medicinal purposes. Its bitter taste made it a symbol of pain and of bitterness.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Guest", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Members List and Descriptions", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Orders and Opinions", "orders or opinions" \}), (\{ "page", "Pregnancy Herb Information", "pregnancy" \}), (\{ "page", "Price List", "price list" \}), (\{ "page", "Teaching Schedule", "teaching schedule" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:pregnancy">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h1", "~ Pregnancy ~" \}), (\{ "h2", "What not to take during pregnancy:" \}), (\{ "paragraph", " Many people have turned to holistic approaches to health care, which include the use of herbs, as an alternative to traditional medicine. There\<br\> are some herbs, however, that shouldn’t be used during pregnancy because of what they do to reproductive organs or because of naturally-occurring\<br\> substances found in them.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCulinary herbs (basil, oregano, etc.) usually are safe in the small amounts used in cooking, but not in larger doses used for teas. Anthraquinone\<br\> laxatives stimulate muscle, including the uterus, possibly causing miscarriage. Uterine stimulants should be avoided for the same reason.\<br\> Alkaloids, bitter principles or essential oils should be avoided because they affect functions in the mom-to-be’s body as well as in the fetus.\<br\> Abortifacients also might cause miscarriage. Emmenagogues promote and regulate menstruation, which should be avoided during pregnancy.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIf you have questions about an herb or what is a safe amount, avoid the herb or ask an herbal practitioner or homeopathic healer.\<br\> " \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Anthraquinone Laxative:    \\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Aloe\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Buckthorn\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cascara Sagrada\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Docks\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Meadow Saffron\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Senna *\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Uterine Stimulant:    \\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * American Mandrake\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Black Cohosh\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Blue Cohosh\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Bloodroot\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Calamus\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cascara Sagrada\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cayenne\\r\\n\\r\\n\\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Fennel\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Feverfew\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Flax Seed\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Goldenseal\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Lady's Mantle\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Licorice\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Make Fern\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Mayapple\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Mistletoe\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Passion Flower\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Pennyroyal\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Periwinkle\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Poke Root\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Rhubarb\\r\\n\\r\\n\\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Sage\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Senna\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Tansy\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thuja\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thyme\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Wild Cherry\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Wormwood *\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Alkaloids/Bitter Priciples:    \\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Barberry\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Bloodroot\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Celandine\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cinchona\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Ephedra\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Goldenseal\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Wild Cherry *\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Essential Oils:  \\r\\n\\r\\n    * Calamus\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cayenne\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Fennel\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Juniper\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Lavender\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Marjoram\\r\\n\\r\\n\\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Oregano\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Passion Flower\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Rosemary\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Sage\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thuja\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thyme\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Yarrow *\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Emmenogogue:    \\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cascara Sagrada\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Cotton-Root Bark\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Lady's Mantle\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Licorice\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Mayapple\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thyme\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Wormwood\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Yarrow\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Mistletoe\\r\\n\\r\\n\\t\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Passion Flower\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Pennyroyal\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Periwinkle\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Poke Root\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Rhubarb\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Senna\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Tansy\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Thuja\\r\\n    *\\r\\n\\r\\n    * Rue *\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "page", "Guest", "guest" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Members List and Descriptions", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Orders and Opinions", "orders or opinions" \}), (\{ "page", "Plant Symbology", "plant symbology" \}), (\{ "page", "Price List", "price list" \}), (\{ "page", "Teaching Schedule", "teaching schedule" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:price list">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "Linlae Gardening Guild - Price List" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Teabags are now for sale:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<b\>Those that are avilable:\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>2 denarii:\</b\> Basil, Bay laurel, Chive, Peppermint, Thyme and Tobacco.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>4 denarii:\</b\> Clove, Saffron and Lavender(not currently available).\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>6 denarii:\</b\> Allspice, Red apple, Cassia, Cherry, Cinnamon, Sumac and Blueberry(not currently available).\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Those that aren't available until further notice.\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>8 denarii:\</b\> Anise, Coriander, Cubeb, Fennel and Fenugreek.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>10 denarii:\</b\> Ginger, Lemongrass and Licorice.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Herbs for Sale at 2 denarii:\</b\> Anise Seed, Bay Leaf, Basil Leaf, Cassia Bark, Cinnamon Bark, Chives, Clove Buds, Coriander Seed, Cubeb Seed, Cumin Seed, Dill Seed, Fennel Seed, Fenugreek Seed, Ginger Root, Lemongrass, Licorice Root, Mint, Mustard Seed, Nutmeg Seed, Paprika, Saffron, Sesame Seed, Sumac Berry, Thyme and Vanilla.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flowers for sale, in bunches of 12, at 8 denarii:\</b\> Daisies, Foxglove, Lilies, Marigolds, Orchids, Roses and Tulips.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Oils for sale at 10 denarii:\</b\> Bergamot, Carrot seed, Cedarwood, Chamomile, Cinnamon, Clary sage, Clove, Eucalyptus blue gum, Eucalyptus lemon, Geranium, Ginger, Grapefruit, Lavender, Lemongrass, Patchouli, Peppermint, Rosemary, Rosewood, Spearmint, Sweet Orange and Tangerine.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Cigars for sale at 1 aureal (24 denarii).\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Quartz Pendants for sale at 10 denarii.\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Herbal properties list for sale at 15 denarii.\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Fertilizer for sale at 3 denarii.\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flower Pots for sale at 4 denarii.\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Tea Kettles for sale at 150 denarii.\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Plant Symbology", "plant symbology" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:price list 2">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:teaching schedule">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:to do list:">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
