<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Tokens" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Rings" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h1", "\<center\>Lyceum Medicinae\</center\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<img src=\\"http://drblayney.com/images/onesnake.jpg\\"\>\</center\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:humors">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "The Four Humors" \}), (\{ "text", "There are four humors which affect and must remain in a state of eucrasia, or balance, within every single body for said body to function in a normal state. Imbalance, dyscrasia, in the humors can lead to a myriad of ailments and unpleasant temperaments.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe first humor is the sanguine, which, as the name suggests, is comprised of the blood and is sweet to the taste. This is produced by the liver, veins, and nostrils, and has the qualities of being hot and wet. In respect to color, this humor is red. A sanguine individual is prone to corpulence and a flushed complexion. However, a sanguine person possesses many positive personality traits, as they are generally optimistic, generous, and happy, although irresponsible.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe second humor is the choleric. The yellow bile, that is gall and urine, is produced in the bladder, the area around the liver, and the ears. Yellow bile comes in seven different colors, the basic yellow, pale-yellow, red, leek-green, yolk-yellow, verdigris, and woad, all of which are bitter. The choleric humor is the other hot humor, but it is considered dry. Ginger hair is common amongst choleric individuals, as is a thin bodily shape. Choleric people are often violent, temperamental, but ambitious.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe third humor is the phelgmatic, the phlegm produced in the stomach, loin muscles, and mouth. Phlegm is white in color. This is the first of the cold humors, and it, like the sanguine, is also wet. Although normally tasteless, phlegm is often sweet, but can also be salty and sharp. Corpulence is again common amongst the phlegmatic people, as is a pallid complexion. These individuals also tend to be slow-moving and prone to cowardice.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe final humor is the melancholic. The black bile is produced in the area below the liver, spleen, and eyes, and it bears a distinctly sharp flavor. The proper color of black bile should match that of olive oil. Black bile comes in four types: blood sediment, overheated yellow bile, tarry, and a fourth much like blood. The marrow of the adrenal glands, feces, and blood clots may all be associated with this humor. The melancholic humor is cold and dry. Individuals of the melancholic type are, as the choleric, thin, also with a yellowish, sickly complexion. These individuals are usually introspective and sentimental, although gluttonous.\\r\\n\<p\>\<i\>Achieving Eucrasia\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\nEucrasia by means of a sanguine imbalance can be achieved by two means, the first being to remove excess blood with leeches, and the second, to eat cold and dry foods. A common example of a sanguine  malady would be a fever.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThere are numerous locations, as depicted, from which blood can be removed from the patient:\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<img src=\\"http://www.nlm.nih.gov/exhibition/horse/images/400_pixels/blo_gersdorffx400.jpg\\"\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is best to remove blood from the main artery or vein between the area of concern and the heart.\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Notices" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1244152205, "rastalabor", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
