<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin_desc">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin_lessons">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:admin_students">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h1\>Schola Veneficus' Students\</h1\>\\r\\nWe are currently accepting a maximum of \<b\>six\</b\> students into each school of Magic. Below will list who under which school.\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Elementalism\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>List students here\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>White\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>List students here\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Green and Purple\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>List students here\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Thaumaturgy\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>List students here\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Alchemy\</h2\>\\r\\n\<i\>Jahren\</i\> \<b\>Paid\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Lianaar\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_combine">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Alchemy Combinations\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Zombie Cure\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Combination:\</b\> Basil + Holy Water \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Effect:\</b\> Cures the consumer of the zombie curse. Reacts differently dependant on the victim. \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> This solution does decompose as nature intended, so the sooner it can be administered the better. This combination does not completely heal those affected. To complete the process, you must be blessed by one of the priests of S'allumer. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Pregnancy Potion\</b\>\</u\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Combination (Minimum):\</b\> Witchmoss + Purple Garmflower + Golden Skink \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Combination (Maximum):\</b\> Witchmoss + Purple Garmflower + Golden Skink + Rosewood Staff + Lizardskin Pouch + Five Candles + Butterfly Wing + Feather Quill \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Effect:\</b\> Causes the user to become pregnant (Regardless of gender). \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> Though the minimum can be combined and administered, it is thought more practical to add the additional ingredients. According to my old Master, he thinks that the additional, plus a small ritual makes the potion more potent and less likely to fail. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_equip">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Alchemic Equipment\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>Rosewood Staff:\</b\> Sometimes used in specific rituals.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Lizardskin Pouch:\</b\> Sometimes used in rituals to keep several ingedients together.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Candles:\</b\> Normally used in rituals that require summoning the elements.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_flowers">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Flower Components\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>Purple Garmflower:\</b\> A very specific flower that is said to aid in fertility.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_herbs">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Herb Components\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>Basil:\</b\> A clensing herb that can be used to take away negative effects.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Witchmoss:\</b\> A thick herb that helps other components meld together.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_history">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_metal">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Metal Components\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:alchemy_misc">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>Miscellanious Components\</h2\>\\r\\n\<b\>Holy Water:\</b\> Holy water is used by the priesthood of S'allumer, and less noticeably Lutara in performing clensing rituals.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Golden Skink:\</b\> Though the entire corpse isn't necessary, the liver holds alchemic powers for fertility.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Butterfly Wing:\</b\> A rather peculiar ingredient not easily found that is said to improve chances of fertility.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Feather Quill:\</b\> The tips of a quill (A good quality quill, mind you) are said to aid in fertility.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "h1", "Schola Veneficus" \}), (\{ "text", "\<b\>Announcements:\</b\>" \}), (\{ "h2", "Magic" \}), (\{ "page", "Schools", "magic_schools" \}), (\{ "page", "Grimories", "magic_grimories" \}), (\{ "page", "Spells", "magic_spells" \}), (\{ "page", "History", "magic_history" \}), (\{ "h2", "Alchemy" \}), (\{ "page", "Herbs", "alchemy_herbs" \}), (\{ "page", "Flowers", "alchemy_flowers" \}), (\{ "page", "Metals", "alchemy_metal" \}), (\{ "page", "Miscellanious", "alchemy_misc" \}), (\{ "page", "Equipment", "alchemy_equip" \}), (\{ "page", "Known Combinations", "alchemy_combine" \}), (\{ "page", "History", "alchemy_history" \}), (\{ "h2", "Administrative" \}), (\{ "page", "Students", "admin_students" \}), (\{ "page", "Lessons", "admin_lessons" \}), (\{ "page", "School Description", "admin_desc" \}), (\{ "h2", "Other" \}), (\{ "page", "Member List (OOC)", "members" \}), (\{ "page", "Trading Market", "trading" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:magic_grimories
">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:magic_history">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:magic_schools">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<h2\>\<b\>Elementalism\</h2\>\<b\>\<br\>\\r\\nAll matter can be said to be made up of four primary constituents, or \\"elements\\", if you will. These elements are known as Air, Earth, Fire, and Water. More complex things are made up of more elements. For example, a tree is made up of the Earth that it grows from, the Water that sustains it, and even the Fire of the light of the sun that gives it life. We know that trees contain Fire, for we can release the Fire within by burning the wood. It is by true insight into the mysteries of the forces that bind this world that one may, by use of the True Names of Things, call forth the Elements of the world and manipulate them as easily as a artist would paint on a canvas, molding the universe by sheer thought and understanding. \<br\>\\r\\n--From the Primer of Elementalism, found in the Dunwasser Academy Library\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<b\>White\</h2\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nAnd it was to come to pass that the Witnesses of Helloise, so moved were they by Her piety and Her grace, would study her teachings and her example. It was discovered that if one is pure in thought and action one might un-do the harm done of others and thus set things right where once they were wrong.\<br\>\\r\\nIt is not enough for one to just hear the words and to repeat them, but to know their meaning in their heart of hearts, to ken thier true import within their very souls. In this way, one may know the will of the Creator....\<br\>\\r\\n--From To Know The True Names of Creation, The Discipline that is Known as \\"White Magick\\", Anonymous \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<b\>Green and Purple\</h2\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nDear sir: I write this letter to you to express my appreciation for the gratuity you have sent me. I salute your good taste and I applaud the skill of the jeweler who set these pieces. I will hold such a gift dear to my heart.\<br\>\\r\\nIn answer to your questions: the rumors you have heard are based upon fact. There was and is indeed a Green and Purple College. No, they do not have a fixed meeting hall or other centralized location. Rather, they are a collective of individuals with a common objective: the understanding of the true nature of the soul. Yes, it is true that the Green and Purple College has codified the secret words and gestures that can tug at the invisible threads that bind one's soul to this world. No, I do not know why they have chosen the colors of green and purple as their livery. And finally, if you would arrange suitable accomodations, I would be able to find someone more knowledgeable than myself in these matters to make your acquaintance.\<br\>\\r\\n-- Letter that arrived posthumously to Sidwell de Bisclavret, Source Unknown \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h2\>\<b\>Thaumaturgy\</h2\>\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\\"I, Kyndranigar, write these words. Know that you hold in your hands what is to my knowledge the only complete discourse on the theory and practice of Thaumaturgy, the magic of magic, the study of the forces of the highest learning that one can attain. I have striven my best to record in the limited medium of pen and paper my own personal experiences, my knowledge, and my understanding of a dozen abstractions, a hundred unspoken words, and a thousand nuances and gestures that would allow one to see the true nature of things, and how one, though living, might conquer the universe. \<br\>\\r\\n~ The First Words to Thaumaturgy, by Kyndranigar, the First Person to Name the Magic as Such\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:magic_spells">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:members">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1187765777, "barbra18", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
