<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:colors - symbology">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Colors - Symbology ~\</h1\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<UL\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Gray\</b\> ~ Elegance, humility, respect, reverence, stability, subtlety, wisdom, old age, anachronism, boredom, decay, decrepitude, dullness, dust, entanglement, pollution, urban sprawl, strong emotions, balance, neutrality, mourning, formality.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>White\</b\> ~ Light, Reverence, purity, snow, peace, innocence, cleanliness, simplicity, security, humility, sterility, winter, coldness, criticism, surrender, cowardice, fearfulness, unimaginative, air, fire, hope, the Sword, the Fish, bland, empty and unfriendly (interior), celebration.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Black\</b\> ~ Absence, modernity, power, sophistication, formality, elegance, wealth, mystery, style, evil, fear, anonymity, anger, sadness, remorse, mourning, unhappiness, sex, seriousness, conventionality, rebellion, anarchism, unity, sorrow, life, slimming quality (fashion).\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Red\</b\> ~ Passion, strength, energy, fire, love, sex, excitement, speed, heat, arrogance, ambition, leadership, masculinity, power, danger, gaudiness, blood, war, anger, revolution, radicalism, socialism, communism, aggression, summer, autumn, stop, respect, the Sword, martyrs, the Holy Spirit.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Blue\</b\> ~ Seas, men, skies, peace, unity, harmony, tranquility, calmness, coolness, confidence, conservatism, water, ice, loyalty, dependability, cleanliness, technology, winter, depression, coldness, idealism, obscenity, tackiness, air, wisdom, royalty, nobility, the Spider (light blue), the Fish (pale blue) and the Bow (dark blue), strength, steadfastness, light, friendliness, peace, truthfulness, love, sadness, aloofness. ~ In many diverse cultures blue is significant in religious beliefs, believed to keep the bad spirits away.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Green\</b\> ~ Great intelligence, life, nature, bad spirits, spring, fertility, youth, environment, wealth, good luck, vigor, generosity, go, grass, aggression, inexperience, envy, misfortune, coldness, jealousy, illness, greed, life eternal, air, earth, sincerity, hope, the Natheireun (bright green), renewal, natural abundance, growth, health, balance, harmony, stability, calming, creative intelligence, the ordinary.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Yellow\</b\> ~ Sunlight, joy, happiness, earth, optimism, intelligence, idealism, wealth (gold), summer, hope, air, liberalism, cowardice, illness (quarantine), hazards, dishonesty, avarice, weakness, greed, femininity, gladness, sociability, summer, friendship, the Chalice, the Destrier, the Coffer (golden yellow), deceit, God (gold).\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Purple\</b\> ~ Envy, Sensuality, bisexuality, spirituality, creativity, wealth, royalty, nobility, ceremony, mystery, wisdom, enlightenment, arrogance, flamboyance, gaudiness, mourning, profanity, exaggeration, confusion, pride, the Serpent (violet), riches, romanticism (light purple), delicacy (light purple), penance.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Orange\</b\> ~ Happiness energy, balance, heat, fire, enthusiasm, flamboyance, playfulness, aggression, arrogance, gaudiness, over-emotion, warning, danger, autumn, desire, the Scythe.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Brown\</b\> ~ Calm, boldness, depth, natural organisms, nature, richness, rusticism, stability, tradition, anachronism, fascism, boorishness, dirt, dullness, filth, heaviness, poverty, roughness, earth, the Comhach, the Serpent (reddish brown), down-to-earth. ~ Brown can stimulate the appetite, wholesomeness, steadfastness, simplicity, friendliness, and dependability.\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<li\>\<b\>Pink\</b\> ~ Spring, gratitude, appreciation, admiration, sympathy, femininity, health, love, marriage, joy.\\r\\n\</UL\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>~ The Mystery Guild ~\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe purpose of this guild is to discover the secrets to some of Calabria's most well known mysteries as well as provide information in the form of books to the populace. \\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Trading", "trading" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:gems - symbology">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Gems - Symbology ~\</h2\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>A\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Agate\</b\> is said to foster love, create an appreciation of nature, and provide abundance and sooth emotions.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Black Agate\</b\> is believed to relieve stress, give protection and increase courage.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Blue Lace Agate\</b\> is believed to create hope, harmony, optimism, positive thinking, smooth energy flow, joy, truth and promptness and makes us more easygoing. Blue lace agate is especially valued for its said ability to calm the mind in a manner, which causes us to expand our perspective from our hearts.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Old Crazy Lace Agate\</b\> is believed to enable one to laugh and see the “games” of the world.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Golden Lace Agate\</b\> is said to help lift depression, increase friendliness and happiness.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Moss Agate\</b\> has long been thought to be helpful to farmers. Worn when planting, it ensures a good crop. It is often called the “gardener’s stone.” It is associated with prosperity, success, abundance, congeniality, compatibility, healing, rain, restoration, and fertility of plants, protection of the earth, creativity, confidence and strength. This stone is helpful when starting new friendships or when seeking a compatible lover. Moss agate also helps us communicate directly with animals and plants.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Tree Agate\</b\> is said to assist with introspection and relieve tension. It also believed to bring plentiful crops.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Amazonite\</b\> is thought to bestow truth, integrity and honor to its wearer, enhance love, and soothe tense, aggravated emotions and situations.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Baltic Amber\</b\> is said to bring romantic love, purification, wisdom, energy and balance. It is also believed to enhance patience, and remembrance of past lives and ancient knowledge.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Amethyst\</b\> is associated with increased nobility and spiritual awareness.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Ametrine\</b\> is said to aid in meditation, relieve tension, disperse negativity and help to eliminate prejudice.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Apatite\</b\> is said to enhance intellect, focus, learning, clarity of concentration, and ideas. It is also said to foster unconditional love.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Aquamarine\</b\> is said to promote safe travel on water, release anxiety, fear and restlessness. It is said to create a peaceful stillness like the flow of a forest stream.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>C\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Carnelian\</b\> is believed to remind us to be “in the moment.” It is said to be a stone of protection particularly from anger, jealousy and fear. It is also believed to assist one in finding the right mate. This stone calms fears about death and rebirth, bringing serenity and acceptance of the great cycle of life.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Cat’s Eye Quartz (Hawks Eye)\</b\> is believed to foster serenity, peace, perspective, discernment, abundance, prosperity, healing riches and love of nature.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Citrine\</b\> is said to be especially useful in stimulating one’s mental capacities, enhancing creativity and intuition and strengthening self confidence. It is also said to give emotional control while making one more alert. It can be very helpful in assisting, acquiring and maintaining wealth.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Coral\</b\> is said to provide protection and guard against violence, accidents and theft, calm emotions and restore harmony. Believed to help with fever, colds, asthma and digestive problems.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>F\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Rainbow Fluorite\</b\> was often used in carvings. Since fluorite cleaves when struck, forming distinct four-sided pyramids, it has long been associated with psychic energy.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>G\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Garnet\</b\> is considered to be the stone of devotion both to others and to one’s self. It is said to inspire romantic love, passion, sensuality, sexuality, intimacy, positive thoughts, and inspiration, past life recall, career success, social popularity and self-confidence.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Rhodolite Garnet\</b\> is said to facilitate meditation, enhance intuition and inspire love.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>H\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Howlite\</b\> is believed to allow one to express emotions calmly, allowing oneself to say what is necessary in a manner that is non-offensive to the listener.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>I\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Iolite\</b\> is known as a stone of power. It is believed to enhance leadership ability, power, inner strength, and self-confidence and executive ability. Many people wear iolite to bed believing that it increases dreams and the ability to remember dreams. It is also used as an aid to intuition.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>J\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Jade\</b\> not only brings prosperity but also allows you to hold onto your money rather than have it slip through your fingers. All jade is believed to produce longevity, fertility, serenity, wisdom, balance, moderation, perspective and stability.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Autumn Jasper\</b\> is believed to protect oneself from negative energy. It is thought to be very strengthening.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Brecciated Jasper\</b\> is believed to enhance organization abilities, relaxation and a sense of wholeness. It is said to encourage attunement and communication with animals and may help with animal allergies. It is said to bring happiness, create a good outlook on life and ease stress.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Dalmatian Jasper\</b\> is thought to increase patience, remove disillusionment and increase loyalty to one’s partner, making it beneficial for long term relationships.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Fancy Jasper\</b\> is believed to be a stone of gentleness and relaxation. It may enhance one’s ability to relax by bringing tranquility, comfort and wholeness. It is sometimes called the nurturing stone for its nurturing and protective energies. Think of them as helping us to cease overanalyzing everything and to increase our enjoyment of life.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Leopardskin Jasper\</b\> is said to assist and protect during physical and spiritual travel. It is also believed to make it easier for one to take responsibility properly.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Ocean Jasper\</b\> is thought to promote balance of physical, intellectual, and emotional bodies.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Red Jasper\</b\> is believed to facilitate the remembering of dreams, aid in the assistance in rescue from danger and to help balance out unfair situations.\\r\\n\</UL\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>L\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Labradorite\</b\> is said to help provide clarity and insight into your destiny. It is also said to be especially helpful for dream recall and finding ways to use dreams in daily life. It is also valued as a connection on the path to love.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Lapis Lazuli\</b\> has been valued through the ages as a link to the all-knowing sources of knowledge and for invoking wisdom. It has traditionally been a stone for royalty.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>M\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Malachite:\</b\> As the color “green” has long been seen as the color of life, malachite has been seen as the restorer of life. This is interpreted as assisting the body in its natural healing process. It is said that by using this stone, one can counteract self-destructive romantic tendencies and help encourage true, pure love.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Moonstone\</b\> has been honored as the sacred stone of the moon goddess and as an aid to the traveler by opening us up to the experiences of people and new places. It is also said to create joy and peace in our homes. It is believed to help calm responses, avoid overreaction and enhance femininity, intuition and psychic abilities.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Mother-of-Pearl\</b\> has been known as a “stone of sincerity,” brining truth to situations and loyalty to a “cause”. It has signifies faith, charity and innocence. It is believed to enhance personal integrity and help to provide focus to ones attention. It has been used to inhibit boisterous behavior and to provide a reflection of the self such that one may see the manner in which one appears to others.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>O\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Mahogany Obsidian\</b\> is called the “mirror Stone” because it reflects one’s personal shortcomings, allowing these shortcomings to come to one’s consciousness to be dealt with, then let go of. It is believed to stimulate growth of physical, emotional, intellectual and spiritual centers to provide strength in times of need. It is also said to help promote a forgiving attitude and release of grievances.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Snowflake Obsidian:\</b\> Those who appreciate the powers of obsidian often carry a piece with them. Whether in the raw or formed state, obsidian helps with the integration of mental balance between the right and left hemispheres of the brain. It also assists in physical balance and with physical safety. Specifically, snowflake obsidian is believed to be a stone of purity helping one to recognize unnecessary patterns in one’s life.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Black Onyx\</b\> has been believed to repel negativity and deflect the negativity of others, keeping one safe from harm. It aids in grounding so that the person is not so flighty and can think and at in a more rational manner which will help stimulate the power of wise decision making. It is also believed to help overcome feeling of loneliness and alienation and to add comfort in unfamiliar surroundings.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Fire Opal\</b\> is a stone of inspiration, which enhances imagination and creativity. It helps one release inhibitions and enhances memory.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>P\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Pearls\</b\> promote sincerity, truth and loyalty. Enhances personal integrity,soothes, calms, yet focuses attention.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Peridot\</b\> is said to help one find happiness within one’s self and to overcome anger and jealousy.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Pietersite\</b\> has attributes that include physical protections, especially for the eyes. It also focuses the inner eye, enabling the wearer to explore himself or herself emotionally and to help one see beyond the immediate to beauty in the “All”. Spiritually and psychically, pietersite helps in working with angels, experiencing visions, and precognition, relating to feminine or goddess energy.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Q\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Quartz Crystal\</b\> has been recognized for harmony and has been used as a “stone of power”, being able to bring the energy of the stars into the soul. It stimulates brain function, aids clarity of mind, dispels negativity in one’s environment and is a very powerful healer.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Rose Quartz\</b\> is believed to restore youthful qualities, particularly of the skin and self-esteem. Those who wear it experience the joy of each new day and each new experience. They are able to appreciate the innate beauty of people and objects. Everything symbolic regarding rose quartz always returns to love and beauty.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Smoky Quartz\</b\> is said to alleviate stress and transform fear, anger and other negative emotions into positive energies, thus having a comforting and calming effect. It is also said to provide clarity of thought, improve intuition, enhance survival instincts and stimulate higher awareness in meditative states.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>R\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Rhodonite\</b\> is believed to stabilize one’s thinking into what is true for oneself. It helps in making fine distinctions in people. Rather than black-and-white judgments like “good” or “bad”, the wearer sees others as brothers and sisters, with all their complexities, worthy of love. It brings love around you and helps you remain centered when you are in the love state. When carried or worn, it allows you to see the love in all of life’s experiences, even in the simplest of daily chores.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>S\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Sodalite\</b\> assisted ancient truth seekers. Its presence helps call out the inner truths in ourselves from those around us, and helps one let go of control and be in a peaceful state. Sodalite clears the mind for deeper and wiser thinking by aiding the shift from emotional to rational thinking.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Sunstone\</b\> evokes learning, stretching and evolving qualities in order to meet our greatest potential.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>T\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Tigereye\</b\> is dramatized with movement as the chatoyant effect of the contrasting golden and brown bands.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Red Tigereye\</b\> is an excellent stone for public speaking and presentations. The qualities of this stone enhance the confidence in oneself and the subject being presented. It allows the clarity of thought to be projected with profound sensitivity to the needs of the audience.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Tiger Iron\</b\> is believed that the metaphysical power it has is more immediate and obvious than that of any other stone.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Tourmaline\</b\> Those of us who seek to know our inner truths value tourmaline. The quest is without fear; the direction is obvious. But the natural inertia we often feel is overcome by a new-born peace. Keep tourmaline available for those times you need it the most to get motivated.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Turquoise\</b\> is said to absorb negative energies, enhance intuition, and give the wearer vibrancy. This is a stone of vision, integration and clarity.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>U\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Unakite\</b\> is said to bring unconditional love of humanity, connection and reunion. It can help with healing of abandonment and separation issues.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Z\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Zoisite:\</b\> Many artists, who see their art as an extension of their individual spiritual natures, value zoisite. When you need a creativity boost, use zoisite as a touchstone.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Auroral Mysteries ~\</h1\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Auroral Mysteries\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<font color = \\"darkgreen\\"\>As I, Demeter, the owner of this guild, it is my duty to bring forth opportunities to the commoners and nobles alike within the city Triskellian to travel into both known and unknown lands to aid with mapping, scouting, researching, etcetera.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nAs most of you should know, I have recently organized a trip into the swamp terrains to the west or Triskellian. The aims of this trip are as listed above, prioritizing especially on research into plant materials, that which can be used for their medicinal qualities. Further information regarding the expedition can be found within this folder.\</font\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Your own inquiries:\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<i\>Here.\</i\>\\r\\n" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:materials - complete list">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Materials - Complete List ~\</h1\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>A\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Aba\</b\> ~ Garment of camel or goat hair; camel or goat-hair fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Aerophane\</b\> ~ Thin crinkled semi-transparent fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Alepine\</b\> ~ Mixed wool and silk or mohair and cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Alpaca\</b\> ~ Fine wool made from alpaca hair.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Angora\</b\> ~ Silk-like fabric made from wool of angora goats.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Ardass\</b\> ~ Fine silk.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Armure\</b\> ~ Twilled woollen or silk fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Arrasene\</b\> ~ Embroidery fabric of wool and silk.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Atlas\</b\> ~ Rich satin fabric.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>B\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Baft\</b\> ~ Cheap coarse cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bagging\</b\> ~ Coarse fabric for making bags or sacks.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Baize\</b\> ~ Coarse napped cotton or wool fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Balbriggan\</b\> ~ Knitted cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Baldachin\</b\> ~ Rich embroidered silk and gold fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Balzarine\</b\> ~ Light cotton dress material.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Barathea\</b\> ~ Pebbly silk or worsted fabric with broken rib weave.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Barege\</b\> ~ Gauzy fabric of silk, cotton, wool, or worsted.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Barracan\</b\> ~ Fine silk cloth.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Barras\</b\> ~ Coarse linen fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Barrateen\</b\> ~ Some kind of fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Batiste\</b\> ~ Fine soft sheer fabric of plain weave.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bayadere\</b\> ~ Fabric with horizontal stripes in strongly contrasting colours.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Beaupers\</b\> ~ Linen fabric used for flags.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bengaline\</b\> ~ Crosswise ribbed fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bombazine\</b\> ~ Twilled silk and worsted fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Borato\</b\> ~ Thin fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bouclé\</b\> ~ Fabric of uneven looped yarn.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Brilliantine\</b\> ~ Light lustrous cotton and worsted fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Broadcloth\</b\> ~ Dense twilled wool or worsted fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Brocade\</b\> ~ Rich silk fabric with raised patterns.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Buckram\</b\> ~ Stiff-finished cotton or linen used for linings of garments.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bump\</b\> ~ Coarse cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Bunting\</b\> ~ Light loosely woven fabric used for flags.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Burdet\</b\> ~ Cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Burlap\</b\> ~ Coarse plain-woven jute or hemp fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Burnet\</b\> ~ Dark brown; dark woollen cloth.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Burrel\</b\> ~ Coarse russet cloth.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>C\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>calamanco \\tsatin twilled woollen fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>calico \\tplain white cotton.\\r\\n\<LI\>camaca \\tfine silk fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>cambresine \\tfine linen fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>cambric \\tfine thin white cotton or linen fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>camlet \\tstrong waterproof silk or wool fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>caneva \\tfancy woollen fabric made to resemble canvas.\\r\\n\<LI\>canque \\tChinese cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>cashmere \\tsoft twilled fabric made of fine goat's wool.\\r\\n\<LI\>cashmerette \\tsoft imitation of cashmere.\\r\\n\<LI\>cassimere \\tclosely woven twilled cloth of fine wool.\\r\\n\<LI\>cendal \\tsilk fabric resembling taffeta.\\r\\n\<LI\>challis \\tsoft lightweight silk, wool or cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>chambray \\tlightweight fabric with coloured warp and white filling.\\r\\n\<LI\>chamois \\tcotton fabric made in imitation of chamois leather.\\r\\n\<LI\>charmante \\tsilk fabric with a crepe back.\\r\\n\<LI\>charmeuse \\tsoft and satiny silk fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>chenille \\tvelvety silk, wool or cotton fabric with protruding pile.\\r\\n\<LI\>cheviot \\tcoarse heavy plain or twilled wool or worsted.\\r\\n\<LI\>chiffon \\tsheer silk fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>chino \\tstrong twilled cotton cloth.\\r\\n\<LI\>chintz \\tglazed printed cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>cire \\tfabric with a glazed finish.\\r\\n\<LI\>cloque \\tfabric with an embossed design.\\r\\n\<LI\>coburg \\tthin single-twilled worsted fabric with cotton or silk.\\r\\n\<LI\>cordovan \\tsoft goatskin leather.\\r\\n\<LI\>corduroy \\tdurable cotton piled fabric with vertical ribs.\\r\\n\<LI\>crash \\tcoarse drapery and towelling fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>crepe \\tlight crinkled fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>crepon \\theavy crepe fabric with lengthwise crinkles.\\r\\n\<LI\>cretonne \\theavy cotton or linen cloth.\\r\\n\<LI\>crin \\thorsehair fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>crinoline \\tstiff flax or cotton fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>cubica \\tfine unglazed fabric resembling shalloon.\\r\\n\<LI\>cypress \\tsilk or cotton gauze fabric, usually black.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>D\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>damask \\tfine lustrous fabric with flat patterns and a satin weave\\r\\n\<LI\>delaine \\tlight fabric of wool or mixed wool and cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>denim \\tfirm and durable twilled cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>dimity \\tsheer and stout white cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>domett \\tplain cotton-wool blend\\r\\n\<LI\>dornick \\tstout linen\\r\\n\<LI\>dowlas \\tcoarse linen\\r\\n\<LI\>drabbet \\tcoarse linen\\r\\n\<LI\>drap-de-Berry \\told woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>dreadnought \\theavy woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>drill \\tdurable twilled cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>droguet \\tribbed woollen dress fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>drugget \\tcoarse durable wool fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>ducape \\tplain-woven stout silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>duck \\tdurable closely woven cotton fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>duffel \\tfabric of thick, low-quality woolen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>dungaree \\theavy coarse durable twilled cotton, usually coloured\\r\\n\<LI\>dupion \\tcoarse silk\\r\\n\<LI\>duroy \\tcoarse woollen\\r\\n\<LI\>duvetyn \\tsmooth lustrous velvety fabric\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>E\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>ecarlate \\tfine woollen cloth, usually dyed scarlet\\r\\n\<LI\>éolienne \\tfine silk and wool\\r\\n\<LI\>etamine \\tlight open-mesh cotton or worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>eyelet \\tsmall hole in fabric to allow passage of a cord; cotton fabric with small holes\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>F\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>faille \\tshiny closely woven silk, cotton or rayon fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>farandine \\tsilk and wool cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>filoselle \\tcoarse floss silk\\r\\n\<LI\>flannel \\tlight woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>foulard \\tsoft lightweight plain-woven or twilled silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>foulé \\tlight woollen fulled cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>frieze \\trough heavy woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>fuji \\tplain spun silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>fustian \\tcoarse twilled cotton\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>G\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>gabardine \\tclosely woven cotton or wool twill\\r\\n\<LI\>galatea \\tstriped cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>gambroon \\ttwilled worsted and cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>gazar \\tsilk organza fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>genappe \\tsmooth worsted yarn\\r\\n\<LI\>georgette \\tthin silk\\r\\n\<LI\>gingham \\tstriped cotton cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>grenadine \\tthin silk\\r\\n\<LI\>grogram \\tcoarse loosely woven silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>grosgrain \\theavy close-woven corded silk\\r\\n\<LI\>gulix \\tkind of fine linen\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>H\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>harn \\tcoarse linen\\r\\n\<LI\>herringbone \\ttwilled fabric woven in rows of parallel sloping lines\\r\\n\<LI\>hodden \\tcoarse undyed woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>holland \\tcoarse plain-woven cotton or linen\\r\\n\<LI\>hopsack \\trough-surfaced loose fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>houndstooth \\tfabric with an irregular checked pattern\\r\\n\<LI\>huckaback \\tabsorbent cotton or linen used for towels\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>J\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>jaconet \\tstout cotton cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>jacquard \\tintricately-woven variegated fabric; loom for making jacquard\\r\\n\<LI\>jaspe \\tcotton or rayon cloth with shaded effect\\r\\n\<LI\>jean \\tdurable twilled cotton material\\r\\n\<LI\>jersey \\tplain weft-knitted fabric of wool, cotton, nylon or silk\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>K\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>kalamkari \\tfabric coloured by repeated dyeing\\r\\n\<LI\>kelt \\tcoarse fabric made of black and white wool\\r\\n\<LI\>kente \\thand-woven African silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>kersey \\tcoarse woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>kerseymere \\ttwilled fine wool\\r\\n\<LI\>khaddar \\thomespun cotton cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>kincob \\tembroidered silk with gold and silver threads\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>L\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>lamé \\tfabric in which metallic threads are interwoven\\r\\n\<LI\>lasting \\tsturdy cotton or worsted cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>lawn \\tfine sheer plain-woven cotton or linen\\r\\n\<LI\>leno \\topen-woven fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>linsey \\tcoarse linen and wool blend\\r\\n\<LI\>linsey-woolsey \\tthin coarse fabric of wool and linen\\r\\n\<LI\>lockram \\tcoarse linen\\r\\n\<LI\>loden \\theavy waterproof woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>lustring \\tglossy silk\\r\\n\<LI\>lutestring \\tplain glossy silk\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>M\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>mackinaw \\theavy napped and felted wool cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>mackintosh \\tlightweight rubberized waterproof cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>madapollam \\tfine cotton cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>madras \\tfine plain-woven cotton or silk\\r\\n\<LI\>marabout \\tthin downy silk\\r\\n\<LI\>marcella \\tcotton or linen in twill weave\\r\\n\<LI\>marocain \\tribbed crepe fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>marquisette \\tsheer meshed cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>matelassé \\thaving a quilted ornamentation; fabric with raised pattern as if quilted\\r\\n\<LI\>melton \\tstrong and smooth heavy woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>merino \\tsoft wool of the merino sheep; any soft merino-like wool or wool and cotton cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>messaline \\tsoft lightweight silk with a satin weave\\r\\n\<LI\>mockado \\tinferior quality woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>mogadore \\tribbed silk used in making neckties\\r\\n\<LI\>mohair \\tfabric made from silky hair of angora goats\\r\\n\<LI\>moire \\twatered silk\\r\\n\<LI\>moleskin \\theavy durable cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>moreen \\tstout corded wool or cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>mousseline \\tfine sheer fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>mull \\tsoft fine sheer cotton or silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>muslin \\tplain-woven fine cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>musterdevillers \\tarchaic mixed grey woollen cloth\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>N\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>nainsook \\tfine cotton fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>nankeen \\tbuff-coloured; durable buff-coloured cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>needlecord \\tthinly ribbed cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>ninon \\tsilk voile or other thin fabric\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>O\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>organdie \\tfine translucent cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>organza \\ttransparent thin silk or nylon\\r\\n\<LI\>orleans \\tinterwoven cotton and worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>osnaburg \\tcoarse linen or cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>ottoman \\theavy clothing fabric with crosswise ribs\\r\\n\<LI\>oxford \\tsoft durable plain-woven cotton\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>P\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>paduasoy \\tcorded silk\\r\\n\<LI\>paisley \\tsoft wool fabric with ornamental pattern\\r\\n\<LI\>panne \\theavy lustrous silk or rayon with waxy feel\\r\\n\<LI\>paramatta \\tworsted and cotton blend\\r\\n\<LI\>pashmina \\tfine goat's wool fabric used for making shawls\\r\\n\<LI\>pekin \\tfine soft silk\\r\\n\<LI\>pellicule \\tthin diaphanous fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>percale \\tclosely woven lightweight cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>percaline \\tglossy lightweight cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>perse \\tdark blue or bluish-grey; cloth of such a colour\\r\\n\<LI\>piqué \\tstiff durable corded fabric of cotton, rayon or silk\\r\\n\<LI\>platilla \\tfine white linen\\r\\n\<LI\>plissé \\tfabric with puckered finish\\r\\n\<LI\>pongee \\tthin soft fabric woven from raw silk\\r\\n\<LI\>poodle \\tcoarsely looped or nubby fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>poplin \\tcorded woven silk and worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>prunella \\tstrong and heavy silk or wool\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>R\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>rabanna \\traffia fabric of Madagascar\\r\\n\<LI\>ramie \\tstrong lustrous fabric resembling linen or silk\\r\\n\<LI\>raploch \\tcoarse undyed woollen cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>raschel \\tlight loosely kitted cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>ratiné \\trough bulky plain-woven fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>rep \\tplain-woven fabric with crosswise ribs\\r\\n\<LI\>reticella \\told Venetian lace-like fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>romal \\thandkerchief or headcloth; silk or cotton fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>rumchunder \\tfine silk\\r\\n\<LI\>russel \\tribbed cotton and wool\\r\\n\<LI\>russet \\tcoarse homespun cloth\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>S\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>sagathy \\tlight blend of silk and cotton or wool\\r\\n\<LI\>samite \\trich and heavy silk, sometimes interwoven with gold or silver\\r\\n\<LI\>sarsenet \\tfine and soft silk; soft or gentle\\r\\n\<LI\>satara \\tribbed lustred wool\\r\\n\<LI\>sateen \\tglossy cotton or wool\\r\\n\<LI\>satin \\tclosely woven silk with lustrous face\\r\\n\<LI\>satinet \\tthin silk satin or imitation thereof\\r\\n\<LI\>saxony \\tfine soft woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>say \\tdelicate woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>scarlet \\tfine cloth\\r\\n\<LI\>scrim \\tdurable plain-woven cotton fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>seersucker \\tlight puckered cotton or linen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>sempiternum \\tdurable wool\\r\\n\<LI\>sendal \\tthin silk or linen\\r\\n\<LI\>serge \\tstrong twilled worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>shalloon \\tlight twilled wool or worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>shantung \\tplain rough silk or cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>sharkskin \\tsmooth durable wool or worsted fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>shetland \\tlightweight loosely twisted wool fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>shoddy \\twoollen fabric made from rags\\r\\n\<LI\>sicilienne \\tribbed silk\\r\\n\<LI\>silesia \\tthin twilled cotton or linen\\r\\n\<LI\>silkaline \\tsoft light cotton fabric resembling silk\\r\\n\<LI\>sindon \\tfine linen\\r\\n\<LI\>stammel \\tcoarse woollen fabric, usually dyed red; bright red colour\\r\\n\<LI\>stockinette \\tsoft elastic cotton fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>surah \\tsoft twilled silk or rayon\\r\\n\<LI\>swansdown \\theavy napped cotton flannel\\r\\n\<LI\>swanskin \\tsoft napped fabric resembling flannel\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>T\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>tabaret \\tstriped watered silk and satin fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tabby \\tplain-woven silk taffeta fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tabinet \\tsilk and wool watered fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>taffeta \\tthin glossy silk\\r\\n\<LI\>tamin \\tthin glazed worsted\\r\\n\<LI\>tamis \\tthin wool\\r\\n\<LI\>tarlatan \\tthin sheer stiff cotton\\r\\n\<LI\>terry \\tpiled fabric consisting of uncut loops\\r\\n\<LI\>ticking \\tstrong linen or cotton fabric used for mattress and pillow cases\\r\\n\<LI\>tiffany \\ttransparent silk-like gauzy fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tiretaine \\twool cloth mixed with cotton or linen\\r\\n\<LI\>toile \\tplain or simple twilled fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tricolette \\tsilk or rayon knitted fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tricot \\tplain knitted silk or woollen fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tricotine \\tdouble-twilled worsted fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tulle \\tsheer and delicate thin silk\\r\\n\<LI\>tussah \\tbrownish silk fabric\\r\\n\<LI\>tweed \\trough twilled wool\\r\\n\<LI\>twill \\tany diagonally woven fabric\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>V\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Velour\</b\> ~ Piled velvety cotton.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Veloutine\</b\> ~ Velvety corded wool.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Velvet\</b\> ~ Soft piled fabric of silk, cotton or synthetic material.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Velvetine\</b\> ~ Cotton with silk pile.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Vicuna\</b\> ~ Fabric made from wool of the vicuna, a small ruminant.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Voile\</b\> ~ Soft fine sheer fabric.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>W\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Wadmal\</b\> ~ Thick coarse wool.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Whipcord\</b\> ~ Fabric with bold twill used for making dresses.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Wigan\</b\> ~ Stiff plain-woven cotton.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Wincey\</b\> ~ Plain or twilled cotton.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Woolsey\</b\> ~ Cotton and wool blend.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Worcester\</b\> ~ Fine wool.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Worsted\</b\> ~ Fine closely-woven wool.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>Z\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Zanella\</b\> ~ Mixed twilled umbrella fabric.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Zephyr\</b\> ~ Lightweight wool or worsted fabric; the west wind.\\r\\n\<LI\>\<b\>Zibeline\</b\> ~ Soft piled wool.\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:non player character">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Teacher Information ~\</h1\>\\r\\n\</center\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<b\>Ruth teaches:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nMagic, Merchant, Scholar, Entertainer, Healer, Translator, Unarmed, Scout and Gardener.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</center\>" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "page", "Private Records", "private records" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plants - herbs">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Plants - Herbs ~\</h1\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\</center\>\<center\>\\r\\n\<h2\>~ Template ~\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Herb\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Botanical Name:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Popular Names:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Habitat:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flora:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>General medical properties:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Specific properties:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Applications and use:\</b\> " \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Agrimony\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Botanical Name:\</b\> Agrimonia eupatoria.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Popular Names:\</b\> Church steeples, sticklewort.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Habitat:\</b\> Hedge banks, copses and field borders.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flora:\</b\> Perennial, with small yellow flowers Thunder-Green.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>General medical properties:\</b\> Astringent, tonic, diuretic and expectorant.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Specific properties:\</b\> This herb has a beneficial effect on the liver, kidneys and bladder. It promotes the flow of urine, prevents diarrhoea, can be used as an expectorant for persistent coughs and as a herbal gargle for sore throats. It should be used with caution for constipation, and can be applied externally on wounds or skin complaints such as acne. A poultice made from the herb will treat insect bites and stings. Agrimony is said to have the ability to draw out splinters from the flesh.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Applications and use:\</b\> Infuse the herb by pouring approximately 1/32 of a gallon (1/4 pint) of boiling water onto 1/2 teaspoon of dried agrimony. Leave for 15 minutes and then take 3 times daily.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Angelica\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Botanical Name:\</b\> \<i\>Angelica archangelica.\</i\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Popular Names:\</b\> Holy Ghost, archangel, masterwort.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Habitat:\</b\> River banks, damp fields and meadows.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Flora:\</b\> Biennial or perennial, with greenish-white flowers Flower-Green.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>General medical properties:\</b\> Appetizer, carminative, expectorant, stimulant, stomachic, tonic and diuretic.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Specific properties:\</b\> Angelica will stimulate the appetite after long illnesses and is also recommended in cases of anorexia nervosa. It is used for treating anaemia, migraine, vertigo and general dizziness for whatever cause. The candied roots can be eaten to ward off infection and warm the stomach. As an expectorant the herb helps coughs, influenza, colds, sore throats and bronchitis. It helps to calm fevers, and eases flatulence and indigestion. Angelica can also be used to cure cystitis and as a urinary antiseptic. Good results have been achieved with this herb for treating muscular cramps, stimulating kidney action, and preventing nervous headaches and rheumatic pain. Angelica tea is good for improving bad eyesight and relieving deafness. Externally the plant can also be used for chilblains.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Applications and use:\</b\> Infuse 1 teaspoon of crushed seeds in 1/2 a cup of boiling water. Take 1 cup before each meal." \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plants - swamp">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Plants - Swamp ~\</h1\>\\r\\n\</center\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Bulrush\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Brief:\</b\> Normally light green, the plant stands 2 meters tall, with a vestigial of leaves at the base. Sprouting from the specialized leaves are long/oval spikelets.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Flower:\</b\> The bulrush spikelets vary in shades of brown.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> Essentially another version of the Cattail. The plants are often home to many insects, birds and amphibians. The rhizomes of the plant are pleasantly nutritious and an energy-rich source of food. It is best to suck or scrape the food from the touch fibers. The roots of the plant are often quite tasty. You may also eat the leaves of the plant in the Spring season whilst they are young and tender, can be both eaten raw or cooked. In Summer, the flower spike can be broken off and eaten, and once the flowers have matured in mid-Summer, the pollen can be collected to use in flower as a thickener.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Cattail\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Brief:\</b\> The cattail has a herb that stands up to a meter and a half, with wide, pale green leaves folded around the stem as protection. The flowers of the cattail are packed into dense, cylindrical spikes.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Flower:\</b\> Cinnamon coloured flower. It is spiky.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> Essentially another version of the Bulrush. The plants are often home to many insects, birds and amphibians. The rhizomes of the plant are pleasantly nutritious and an energy-rich source of food. It is best to suck or scrape the food from the touch fibers. The roots of the plant are often quite tasty. You may also eat the leaves of the plant in the Spring season whilst they are young and tender, can be both eaten raw or cooked. In Summer, the flower spike can be broken off and eaten, and once the flowers have matured in mid-Summer, the pollen can be collected to use in flower as a thickener. You may also use the Cattail, the disintegrating heads specifically, a tinder to start fires or you may use it to stuff clothing items and pillows. If you do not have a think material between you and the cattail stuffing it may cause a similar reactions to hives and cause itching.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Hemlock\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Brief:\</b\> A light red/green in colour, the plant itself stands roughly a foot and a half tall, the upper stems terminate into a compound of small white flowers.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Flower:\</b\> The small clusters of flowers vary in shades of white.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> It grows in wet meadows, along stream banks and other wet and marshy areas. Often mistaken for the parsnip due to the clusters of white tuberous roots. The plant can generally be mistaken for fennel, parsley or wild carrot. When the leaves or root are crushed it emits a rank, unpleasant odor.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Warning:\</b\> This plant can kill a person after a single bite, rapidly producing the symptoms of nausea, emesis (vomiting) and abdominal pain, typically within an hour of indigestion. Another symptom of this is paralysis, the lack of oxygen to the brain and heart would be a likely cause of death. Treatment for this is usually unsuccessful, though ventilation could prevent death until the effects have worn off.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Medicine:\</b\> Can be used as a sedative, might also be used to combat arthritis. However, it can't always be effective because the difference between a therapeutic and a toxic amount can be very slight. Overdoses can produce paralysis and loss of speech, followed closely by death.\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Mangrove Tree\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Brief:\</b\> \\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>Venus Anitrap\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Brief:\</b\> A young herb, forming a rosette of four to seven leaves, which arise from a relatively short subterranean stem that is actually a bulb-like rhizome. The mouth is shut.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Detailed:\</b\> A young herb, forming a rosette of four to seven leaves, which arise from a relatively short subterranean stem that is actually a bulb-like rhizome. Each leaf reaches a maximum size of 10\\", depending on the time of year; longer leaves with robust traps are generally formed after flowering. The mouth is shut.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Leaf:\</b\> A leaf blade that is divided into two regions; a flat, heart-shaped photosynthetic capable petiole, and a pair of midrib, forming a trap which is actually the true leaf. It has three trichomes.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Trichomes:\</b\> Three hair-like structures that are found on the upper surface of each of the lobes on the venus anitrap. They must be triggered in quick succession for the lobes to shut.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Fringe:\</b\> A series of stiff hair-like protrusions or cilia, which mesh together and prevent large prey items from escaping.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> The plant is capable of growing up to larger than our average species, giving it the ability to catch and consume prey, which, I assume, is ourselves. It seems to thrive much better on meat than that of other plant life, as my experiments have resulted in. They tend to grow much larger within a swampy environment, I have found that they do not grow much bigger if the surrounding area is not suitable. Once a meal has been caught it takes at least 10 days to digest, however, if the prey struggles it will tighten the outer lobes and only digest all the more faster. Having consumed it's meal the plant will again open, taking, at most, 12 hours.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Assumptions:\</b\> After speaking with Mister Jahren, we considered how this plant would capture its meal, regardless of the bold red coloring of the inner leaves, we decided that it could lie in wait amongst larger and lusher plant varieties offering it's beverages to those who have become lost within the swamp area. Once the trichomes have been triggered, the plant will snap shut, concealing what is inside and holding in the prey with it's fringe.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Plants - Main Page", "plants" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:plants - symbology">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Plants - Symbology ~\</h1\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>A\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>APPLE BLOSSOM - Preference, Better Things to Come, Good Fortune\\r\\n\<LI\>ARBUTUS - Thee Only Do I Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ARUM - Ardor\\r\\n\<LI\>ASPARAGUS FERN - Fascination\\r\\n\<LI\>ASPHODEL - My Regrets Follow You to the Grave\\r\\n\<LI\>ASTER - Symbol of Love, Daintiness, Talisman of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>AZALEA - Take Care, Temperance, Fragile, Passion\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>B\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>BABY'S BREATH - Innocence, Pure of Heart\\r\\n\<LI\>BACHELOR BUTTON - Single blessedness, Celibacy\\r\\n\<LI\>BALM - Sympathy\\r\\n\<LI\>BALSAM - Ardent Love\\r\\n\<LI\>BEGONIA - Beware, A Fanciful Nature\\r\\n\<LI\>BIRD OF PARADISE - Often given today from a woman to man as a symbol of faithfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>BITTERSWEET - Truth\\r\\n\<LI\>BLACK BRYONT/LADY'S SEAL - Be My Support\\r\\n\<LI\>BLUEBELL/BELL FLOWER - Humility, Constancy, Gratitude\\r\\n\<LI\>BROOM - Humility, Neatness\\r\\n\<LI\>BUCK BEAN - Calm repose\\r\\n\<LI\>BUTTERCUP - Childishness, Riches\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>C\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>CACTUS - Endurance, My Heart Burns with Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CALYCANTHUS/CAROLINA ALLSPICE/SWEET SHRUB - Benevolence\\r\\n\<LI\>CALLA LILY - Magnificent Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>CAMELLIA - Admiration, Perfection, Good Luck Gift for a Man, Gratitude\\r\\n\<LI\>CAMELLIA (PINK) - Longing\\r\\n\<LI\>CAMELLIA (RED) - You're a flame in my heart\\r\\n\<LI\>CAMELLIA (WHITE) - Adoration, Perfection, Loveliness\\r\\n\<LI\>CANDYTUFT - Indifference\\r\\n\<LI\>CANTERBURY BELLS/BELL FLOWER - Gratitude\\r\\n\<LI\>CARDINAL FLOWER/SCARLET LOBELIA - Distinction\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (GENERAL) - Fascination, Devoted Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (PINK) - I'll never forget you, Women's Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (RED) - My heart aches for you, Admiration\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (DEEP RED) - Alas! for my poor heart\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (PURPLE) - Capriciousness\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (SOLID COLOR) - Yes\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (STRIPED) - No, Refusal, Sorry I can't be with you, Wish I could be with you\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (WHITE) - Sweet \& Lovely, Innocence, Pure Love, Woman's Good Luck Gift\\r\\n\<LI\>CARNATION (YELLOW) - Disapointment, Rejection\\r\\n\<LI\>CATCHFLY (RED) - Youthful Love, I Fall Victim\\r\\n\<LI\>CATTAIL - Peace, Prosperity\\r\\n\<LI\>CATTLEYA - Mature charms\\r\\n\<LI\>CEDAR - I live but for thee, Think of Me\\r\\n\<LI\>CELANDINE/PILEWORT/FIGWORT - Future Joy\\r\\n\<LI\>CHAMOMILE/GOLDEN MARGUERITE/ANTHEMIS - Energy in Action\\r\\n\<LI\>CHERRY BLOSSOM (SINGLE) - Education\\r\\n\<LI\>CHICKWEED - I Cling to Thee\\r\\n\<LI\>CHICORY - Frugality\\r\\n\<LI\>CHRYSANTHEMUM (GENERAL) - Abundance \& Wealth, Cheerfulness, You're a wonderful friend\\r\\n\<LI\>CHRYSANTHEMUM (RED) - Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CHRYSANTHEMUM (WHITE) - Truth\\r\\n\<LI\>CHRYSANTHEMUM (YELLOW) - Slighted Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CINQUEFOIL - Beloved Child\\r\\n\<LI\>CLEMATIS - Artifice (ingenuity)\\r\\n\<LI\>CLOVER (FOUR-LEAF) - Be Mine\\r\\n\<LI\>CLOVER (WHITE) - Think of Me\\r\\n\<LI\>CLOVER (RED) - Industry\\r\\n\<LI\>COLCHICUM (MEADOW SAFFRON) - My Best Days Fled\\r\\n\<LI\>COLUMBINE (PURPLE) - Resolved to Win\\r\\n\<LI\>COLUMBINE (RED) - Anxious\\r\\n\<LI\>COMPASS FLOWER - Faith\\r\\n\<LI\>CONVOLVUS MINOR/BINDWEED - Uncertainty\\r\\n\<LI\>CORCHORUS - Impatience of Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>COREOPSIOS - Always Cheerful\\r\\n\<LI\>CORNFLOWER - Delicacy, Refinement\\r\\n\<LI\>CORONILLA/CROWN VETCH - Success to You\\r\\n\<LI\>COWSLIP - Rusticity, Winning Grace, Healing, Youth, Pensiveness\\r\\n\<LI\>COXCOMB - Foppery, Unfading Love\\r\\n\<LI\>CROCUS - Cheerfulness, Abuse not, Gladness\\r\\n\<LI\>CROWN IMPERIAL/FRITILLARIA - Majesty\\r\\n\<LI\>CYCLAMEN - Resignation and Good-Bye\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>D\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>DAFFODIL - Regard, Unrequited Love, Sunshine, Respect, The sun shines when I'm with you\\r\\n\<LI\>DAFFODIL (YELLOW ) - Chivalry\\r\\n\<LI\>DAHLIA - Dignity and Elegance, Forever Thine\\r\\n\<LI\>DAISY - Innocence, Loyal Love, I'll Never tell, Purity, Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>DAISY OX-EYE - Patience\\r\\n\<LI\>DAISY (RED) - Beauty Unknown to Possessor\\r\\n\<LI\>DANDELION - Faithfulness, Happiness, Love's oracle\\r\\n\<LI\>DAPHANE CNEORUM/ROSE DAPHANE - I Desire to Please\\r\\n\<LI\>DAPHANE ODORA/WINTER DAPHANE - I Would Not Have You Otherwise\\r\\n\<LI\>DRACAENA/DRAGON'S BLOOD/DRAGON LILY - Inner Power\\r\\n\<LI\>DEAD LEAVES - Sadness\\r\\n\<LI\>DELPHINIUM - Big-Hearted, Fun\\r\\n\<LI\>DILL - Lust\\r\\n\<LI\>DIOSMA - Your Simple Elegance Charms Me\\r\\n\<LI\>DOG ROSE - Pleasure and Pain\\r\\n\<LI\>DOGWOOD (FLOWERING) - Am I Indifferent to You?\\r\\n\<LI\>DRAGON ROOT/GREEN DRAGON (Arum draconium) - Ardor\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>E\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>EDELWEISS/ALPINE CUDWEED - Daring, Courage, Noble Purity\\r\\n\<LI\>EGLANTINE/SWEET-BRIAR/ROSA EGLANTARIA - Poetry, I Wound to Heal\\r\\n\<LI\>ELDER FLOWER - Zeal\\r\\n\<LI\>ENDINE - Frugality\\r\\n\<LI\>EPIGAEA, REPENS/MAYFLOWER/TRAILING ARBUTUS - Budding\\r\\n\<LI\>EUPATORIUM/HARDY AGERATUM - Delay\\r\\n\<LI\>EREMURUS - Endurance\\r\\n\<LI\>EUPHORBIA - Persistence\\r\\n\<LI\>EVERLASTING - Never Ceasing Memory\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>F\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>FERN - Magic, Fascination, Confidence, Shelter\\r\\n\<LI\>FERN (MAIDENHAIR) - Secret bond of love, Discretion\\r\\n\<LI\>FERN (ROYAL) - Reverie\\r\\n\<LI\>FILBERT - Reconciliation\\r\\n\<LI\>FIR - Time\\r\\n\<LI\>FLAX - Domestic Symbol\\r\\n\<LI\>FLORA'S BELL - Without Pretension\\r\\n\<LI\>FLOWERING REED - Confide in Heaven\\r\\n\<LI\>FORGET ME NOT - True Love, Memories\\r\\n\<LI\>FORSYTHIA - Anticipation\\r\\n\<LI\>FOXGLOVE/FAIRY THIMBLES/DEAD MEN'S BELLS - Stateliness, Youth\\r\\n\<LI\>FOXTAIL GRASS - Sporting\\r\\n\<LI\>FRAXINELLA/CULTIVATED DITTANY/GAS PLANT - Fire\\r\\n\<LI\>FREESIA - Innocence, Trust\\r\\n\<LI\>FUCHSIA (SCARLET) - Confiding Love, Taste\\r\\n\<LI\>FURZE - Love for All Occasions\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>G\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>GARDENIA - You're lovely, Secret love, Purity, Refinement\\r\\n\<LI\>GARLIC - Courage, Strength, Get well, Ward Off Evil \& Illness\\r\\n\<LI\>GENETIAN (FRINGED) - Intrinsic Worth, I Look to Heaven, Autumn\\r\\n\<LI\>GENTIAN (CLOSED) - Sweet Be Thy Dreams\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM - True Friend, Stupidity, Folly\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (APPLE) - Present Preference\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (IVY) - Your Hand for Next Dance\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (LEMON) - Unexpected Meeting\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (NUTMEG) - I Expect a Meeting\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (OAK-LEAVED) - True Friendship, Lady, Deign to Smile\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (PENCILED) - Ingenuity\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (ROSE) - Preference\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (SCARLET) - Consolation, Melancholy\\r\\n\<LI\>GERANIUM (SILVER-LEAF) - Recall\\r\\n\<LI\>GERBERA - Innocence\\r\\n\<LI\>GLADIOLI - Generosity, I'm sincere, Flower of the gladiators\\r\\n\<LI\>GLOBE AMARANTH - Unfading Love\\r\\n\<LI\>GLOXINIA - Love at first sight\\r\\n\<LI\>GINGER - Strength\\r\\n\<LI\>GOLDEN-ROD - Be cautious, Encouragement\\r\\n\<LI\>GOOSEBERRY - Anticipation\\r\\n\<LI\>GOOSEFOOT - Goodness\\r\\n\<LI\>GORSE - Endearing Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>GRASS - Submission\\r\\n\<LI\>GRASS/CITRONELLA/CAMEL GRASS/LEMON GRASS/GINGER/GRASS - Homosexual Love\\r\\n\<LI\>GUELDER ROSE/SNOWBALL - Winter\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>H\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>HAREBELL/CAMPANULA - Humility, Grief\\r\\n\<LI\>HEART'S EASR/PURPLE/JOHNNY JUMP UP - You Occupy My Thoughts\\r\\n\<LI\>HEPATICA (Anemone nobilis) - Confidence\\r\\n\<LI\>HEATHER (LAVENDER) - Admiration, Solitude\\r\\n\<LI\>HEATHER (WHITE) - Protection, Wishes will come true\\r\\n\<LI\>HELIOTROPE - Devotion\\r\\n\<LI\>HENBANE - For Males to Attract Love from Females\\r\\n\<LI\>HIBISCUS - Consumed by Love, Delicate Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>HOLLY - Defense, Domestic Happiness, Am I forgotten\\r\\n\<LI\>HOLLYHOCK - Fruitfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>HOLLYHOCK (WHITE) - Female Ambition\\r\\n\<LI\>HONESTY/LUNARIA/DOLLAR PLANT/MONEY PLANT - Sincerity\\r\\n\<LI\>HONEYFLOWER - Sweet, Secret love, Generous Affection, Sweetness of Disposition\\r\\n\<LI\>HONEYSUCKLE - The Bond of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>HONEYSUCKLE (CORAL) - I Love You\\r\\n\<LI\>HOUSTONIA/BLUET/QUAKER LADIES - Content\\r\\n\<LI\>HOYA/WAX PLANT - Sculpture\\r\\n\<LI\>HUCKLEBERRY - Faith, Simple Pleasures\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (GENERAL) - Games \& Sports, Rashness\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (BLUE) - Consistency\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (PURPLE) - Sorry, Please forgive me, Sorrow\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (RED OR PINK) - Playful Joy\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (WHITE) - Unobtrusive Loveliness, I'll pray for you\\r\\n\<LI\>HYACINTH (YELLOW) - Jealousy\\r\\n\<LI\>HYDRANGEA - Thank you for understanding, frigidity, heartlessness\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>I\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>IPOMACA - I Attach Myself to You\\r\\n\<LI\>IRIS - Faith, Wisdom, Promise in Love, Hope, Wisdom \& Valor\\r\\n\<LI\>IRIS (YELLOW) - Passion\\r\\n\<LI\>IVY - Wedded Love, Fidelity, Friendship, Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>IVY (SPRIG OF WHITE TENDRILS)- Anxious to please, Affection\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>J\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>JAPONICA - Sincerity, Symbol of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>JASMINE (YELLOW) - Modesty, Grace, Elegance\\r\\n\<LI\>JASMINE (WHITE) - Amiability\\r\\n\<LI\>JERUSALEM OAK - Your Love is Reciprocated\\r\\n\<LI\>JONQUIL - Love Me, Affection Returned, Desire, Sympathy\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>K\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>KENNEDIA - Intellectual Beauty\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>L\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>LADY'S SLIPPER - Win me, Capricious Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>LANTANA - Rigor\\r\\n\<LI\>LARKSPUR - Levity, An Open Heart, Lightness\\r\\n\<LI\>LAURISTINUS - Cheerful in Adversity\\r\\n\<LI\>LAVENDER - Love, Devotion\\r\\n\<LI\>LEMON BLOSSOM - Fidelity in Love; I Promise to be True\\r\\n\<LI\>LILAC (GENERAL) - Beauty, Pride\\r\\n\<LI\>LILAC (PURPLE) - First emotions of love\\r\\n\<LI\>LILAC (WHITE) - Youthful Innocence\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (GENERAL) - Majesty \& Honor, Purity of Heart\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (ORANGE) - Hatred, Dislike\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (WHITE) - Virginity, Purity, Majesty, It's Heavenly to be with You, Youth\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (YELLOW) - I'm Walking On Air, False, Gay, Gratitude\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (CALLA) - Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (DAY) - Coquetry\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (EUCHARIS) - Maiden Charms\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY (TIGER) - Wealth, Pride, Prosperity\\r\\n\<LI\>LILY OF THE VALLEY - Sweetness, Happiness, Humility\\r\\n\<LI\>LIVERWORT - Confidence\\r\\n\<LI\>LOVE IN A MIST - You Puzzle Me\\r\\n\<LI\>LOVE-LIES-BLEEDING/AMARANTHUS - Hopeless, Not Heartless, Desertion\\r\\n\<LI\>LOTUS - Estranged love, Forgetful of the Past\\r\\n\<LI\>LUCERNE - Life\\r\\n\<LI\>LUNGWORT - Thou Art My Life\\r\\n\<LI\>LUPINE - Imagination\\r\\n\<LI\>LYCHNIS/CAMPION/MALTESE CROSS - Religious Enthusiasm\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>M\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>MAGNOLIA - Nobility, Perseverance, Nobility\\r\\n\<LI\>MAGNOLIA (CHINESE) - Love of Nature\\r\\n\<LI\>MALLOW - Delicate Beauty, Sweetness\\r\\n\<LI\>MARIGOLD (COMMON) - Pretty Love, Sacred,Affection, Caress, Sorrow\\r\\n\<LI\>MARJORAM - Joy, Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>MARVEL OF PERU/FOUR O' CLOCK - Timidity\\r\\n\<LI\>MEADOW SAFFRON - My Best Days Are Gone\\r\\n\<LI\>MIGNONETTE - Your qualities Surpass your Charms, Health\\r\\n\<LI\>MEZEREON - Desire to Please\\r\\n\<LI\>MILK VETCH - Your presence softens my pain\\r\\n\<LI\>MIMOSA - Secret Love\\r\\n\<LI\>MINT - Virtue\\r\\n\<LI\>MISTLETOE - Kiss me, Affection, Difficulties\\r\\n\<LI\>MONKSHOOD - Beware, Danger is near\\r\\n\<LI\>MOUSE-EAR CHICKWEED - Simplicity\\r\\n\<LI\>MORNING GLORY - Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>MOSS - Maternal Love, Charity\\r\\n\<LI\>MOTHERWORT - Secret Love\\r\\n\<LI\>MOONWORT/HONESTY - Forgetfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>MUGWORT/WORMWOOD - Tranquility, Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>MULLEIN - Good Nature\\r\\n\<LI\>MYRTLE - Love, Joy\\r\\n\<LI\>MYRTLE (WAX) - Discipline, Instruction\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>N\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>NARCISSUS - Formality, Stay As Sweet As You Are\\r\\n\<LI\>NASTURTIUM - Conquest, Victory In Battle, Resignation\\r\\n\<LI\>NUTS - Stupidity\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>O\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>OAK LEAVES - Bravery\\r\\n\<LI\>OLEANDER - Caution\\r\\n\<LI\>OLIVE BRANCH - Peace\\r\\n\<LI\>ORANGE BLOSSOM - Innocence, Eternal Love, Marriage, Fruitfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>ORANGE, MOCK - Deceit\\r\\n\<LI\>ORCHID - Love, Beauty, Refinement, Thoughtfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>ORCHID (CATTLEYA) - Mature Charm\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>P\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>PALM LEAVES - Victory \& Success\\r\\n\<LI\>PANSY - Merriment, Thoughts (You Occupy My Thoughts)\\r\\n\<LI\>PARSLEY - Useful Knowledge\\r\\n\<LI\>PASSION FLOWER - Faith, Religious Fervor\\r\\n\<LI\>PASQUE FLOWER - Unpretentious, You Have No Claims\\r\\n\<LI\>PEAR - Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>PEACH BLOSSOM - I am your Captive\\r\\n\<LI\>PEONY - Shame, Happy Marriage, Compassion, Bashfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>PEPPERMINT - Cordiality\\r\\n\<LI\>PERIWINKLE/VINCA/MYRTLE - Early Recollections, Pleasures of Memories, Sweet Memories\\r\\n\<LI\>PETUNIA - Your Presence Soothes Me\\r\\n\<LI\>PHEASANT'S EYE - Sorrowful Memories\\r\\n\<LI\>PHLOX - Our souls are united, Unanimity\\r\\n\<LI\>PIMPERNEL/POOR MAN'S WEATHER GLASS - Change\\r\\n\<LI\>PINE - Hope, Pity\\r\\n\<LI\>PINK- Pure Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>PINK (MOUNTAIN) - You Are Aspiring\\r\\n\<LI\>POPPY (GENERAL) - Eternal Sleep, Oblivion, Imagination\\r\\n\<LI\>POPPY (RED) - Pleasure\\r\\n\<LI\>POPPY (WHITE) - Consolation\\r\\n\<LI\>POPPY (YELLOW) - Wealth, Success\\r\\n\<LI\>POMEGRANATE FLOWER - Elegance\\r\\n\<LI\>PRIMROSE - I Can't Live Without You, Woman\\r\\n\<LI\>PRIMROSE (EVENING) - Inconstancy\\r\\n\<LI\>PRIMROSE (RED) - Unpatronized Merit\\r\\n\<LI\>PRINCE'S FEATHER - Unfading Love\\r\\n\<LI\>PUSSY WILLOW - Motherhood\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Q\</h2\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>QUAKING GRASS - Agitation\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>R\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>RAGGED-ROBIN - Wit\\r\\n\<LI\>RANUNCULUS - I am Dazzled by your Charms\\r\\n\<LI\>REEDS - Music\\r\\n\<LI\>RHUBARB - Advice\\r\\n\<LI\>RHODODENDRON - Danger, Beware, I am Dangerous\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (BRIDAL) - Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (BURGANDY) - Unconscious Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (CORAL) - Desire\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (DAMASK) - Freshness\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (DARK CRIMSON) - Mourning\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (DOG) - Pleasure \& Pain\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (HIBISCUS) - Delicate, Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (LEAF) - You may Hope\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (LAVENDER) - Enchantment\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (ORANGE) - Fascination\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (PINK) - Perfect Happiness, Secret Love, Grace \& Sweetness, Indecision\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (DARK PINK) - Thankfulness\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (PALE PINK) - Grace, Joy\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (PEACH) - Immortality, Modesty\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (RED) - Love, I love you, Respect, Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (DEEP RED) - Bashful, Shame\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (TEA) - I'll Remember - Always\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (THORNLESS) - Love at first sight, Early Attachment\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (WHITE) - Innocence, Purity, Humility, I am Worthy of You, Secrecy, Silence\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (WHITE \& RED TOGETHER) - Unity\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (WHITE-DRIED) - Death is Preferable to Loss of Virtue\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (YELLOW) - Joy, Jealousy, Friendship (one yellow rose with 11 red ones means love \& passion)\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSEBUD - Beauty \& Youth, A Heart Innocent of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSEBUD (RED) - Pure \& Lovely\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSEBUD (WHITE) - Girlhood, Heart Ignorant of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSEBUD (MOSS) - Confessions of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSES (Bouquet of full bloom) - Gratitude\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSES (Single full bloom) - I truly love you, Simplicity\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSES (GARLAND or CROWN OF) - Beware of Virtue, Reward of Merit, Symbol of Superior Merit\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE (MUSK CLUSTER) - Charming\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSE-OF-SHARON - Consumed by Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ROSEMARY - Remembrance\\r\\n\<LI\>RUSH/HORSE-TAIL - Docility\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>S\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>SAGE - Wisdom, Great Respect, Speedwell Female Fidelity\\r\\n\<LI\>SATIN-FLOWER - Sincerity\\r\\n\<LI\>SENSITIVE PLANT - Timidity\\r\\n\<LI\>SHAMROCK - Lightheartedness\\r\\n\<LI\>SLOE - Difficulty, Austerity\\r\\n\<LI\>SMILAX - Loveliness\\r\\n\<LI\>SNAPDRAGON - Gracious Lady, Strength\\r\\n\<LI\>SNOWBALL - Thoughts of Heaven\\r\\n\<LI\>SNOWDROP - Hope, Consolation\\r\\n\<LI\>SPEARMINT - Warm Sentiment\\r\\n\<LI\>SPIDER FLOWER - Elope with me\\r\\n\<LI\>SOLIDAGO - Success\\r\\n\<LI\>STARWORT - Welcome to a Stranger\\r\\n\<LI\>STEPHANOTIS - Marital Happiness, Desire to Travel\\r\\n\<LI\>STOCK- Bonds of Affection, Promptness, You'll Always Be Beautiful to Me\\r\\n\<LI\>STRAW FLOWER - Agreement\\r\\n\<LI\>STRAW (BROKEN) - Broken agreement\\r\\n\<LI\>SYTINGIA/MOCK ORANGE/LILAC - Memory\\r\\n\<LI\>SUNFLOWER (TALL) - False riches, Pride\\r\\n\<LI\>SUNFLOWER (DWARF) - Adoration\\r\\n\<LI\>SWEETPEA - Good-by, Departure, Blissful Pleasure, Thank You for a Lovely Time\\r\\n\<LI\>SWEET-SULTAN - Felicity, Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>SWEET-WILLIAM - Grant me one smile, Gallantry\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>T\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>TEASEL (Dipscaus) - Misanthropy\\r\\n\<LI\>THORNAPPLE - I dreamed of thee\\r\\n\<LI\>THRIFT - Sympathy\\r\\n\<LI\>TRAVELER'S JOY - Rest, Safety\\r\\n\<LI\>TRUMPET FLOWER/ANGEL'S TRUMPET/DATURA - Separation\\r\\n\<LI\>TULIP (GENERAL) - Perfect Lover, Fame\\r\\n\<LI\>TULIP (RED) -Believe me, Declaration of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>TULIP (VARIEGATED) - Beautiful eyes\\r\\n\<LI\>TULIP (YELLOW) - There's Sunshine In Your Smile\\r\\n\<LI\>TURNIP - Charity\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>V\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>VALERIAN - Accommodating Disposition\\r\\n\<LI\>VENUS FLYTRAP - Caught at Last\\r\\n\<LI\>VENUS' LOOKING GLASS - Flattery\\r\\n\<LI\>VERBENA - Pray for me, Sensibility\\r\\n\<LI\>VERONICA SPEEDWELL - Fidelity\\r\\n\<LI\>VERVAIN - Enchantment\\r\\n\<LI\>VINE - Intoxicating\\r\\n\<LI\>VIOLET - Modesty, Virtue, Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>VIOLET (BLUE) - Watchfulness, Faithfulness, Love\\r\\n\<LI\>VIOLET (WHITE) - Let's Take A Chance On Happiness\\r\\n\<LI\>VIRGIN'S BOWER/CLEMATIS - Filial Love (Filial: referring to a son or daughter) \\r\\n\<LI\>VISCARIA - Will You Dance With Me?\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>W\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>WALL FLOWER/GILLY FLOWER - Faithful in Adversity, Fidelity, Lasting Beauty\\r\\n\<LI\>WINDFLOWER - Sincerity, Symbol of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>WINTERGREENS - Harmony\\r\\n\<LI\>WISTERIA - Welcome\\r\\n\<LI\>WITCH HAZEL - A spell\\r\\n\<LI\>WOLFBANE/ACONITE/TURK'S CAP/FRIAR'S CAP/BEAR'S FOOT - Misanthropy, Chivalry, Knight\\r\\n\<LI\>WOODBINE - Fraternal Love\\r\\n\<LI\>WORMWOOD/ARTEMISIA - Absence, Do not be discouraged\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Y\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>YARROW - Cure for heartache\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Z\</h3\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<UL\>\\r\\n\<LI\>ZEPHYR FLOWER- Sincerity, Symbol of Love\\r\\n\<LI\>ZINNIA (MAGENTA) - Lasting Affection\\r\\n\<LI\>ZINNIA (MIXED) - Thinking (or in memory) of an Absent Friend\\r\\n\<LI\>ZINNIA (SCARLET) - Constancy\\r\\n\<LI\>ZINNIA (WHITE) - Goodness\\r\\n\<LI\>ZINNIA (YELLOW) - Daily Remembrance\\r\\n\</UL\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Trading Records ~\</h1\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Guild Inventory\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Guild Trading Deals\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Bidding Market\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</center\>" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "text", "\<hr\>" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:zombies">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\\r\\n\<h1\>~ Zombies ~\</h1\>\\r\\n\</center\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<h3\>The Chapel Corruption. Written by Dio Goldengate. \</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Artifacts:\</h3\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Set 1 - found beneath the statues of DockTown Chapel:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n- Two bags of Herbs - mixed and unidentified. \<br\>\\r\\n- Two mandragoras - apparently weakened. \<br\>\\r\\n- Two scarab shells. \<br\>\\r\\n- Two tuatara skins. \<br\>\\r\\n- Two rune stones - created delay spells. \<br\>\\r\\n- Two blood stained chests - these held the above contents. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Set 2 -  trap found beneath a tile within the Chapel:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n- A cursed silver platter - affects on sight.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Set 3 - found under the stairs behind a moving panel:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n- Female Corpse - decayed badger. \<br\>\\r\\n- Female Corpse - decayed fox. \<br\>\\r\\n- Icon - unidentified and disappeared after 'Cleansing' by Priest.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Personal Notes:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nAll the following is to be viewed with skepticism, merely as form of my professional logic by which the corruption can be explained.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is my belief that the first set was used to initiate the corruption, though it was not the main catalyst, to my attention it is likely that the rune stones were placed alongside the Mandragora and the other items, to form the trigger, energy source and catalyst to a spell, or more likely, two spells.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThese will have allowed the Necromancer to somehow place set three and perhaps set two into the chapel, though my personal suspicion is that the second set was placed at the same time as the first.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSet three appears to have been the main spell focus, using the icon to create a magic ward and bind the souls of the corpses to the chapel, as Ghosts matching their species were reported in the chapel, this is likely what allowed for the corruption of the chapel.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nHaving corrupted the chapel it created a space by which the Necromancer was able to summon his Legions of zombies forth from, it is my belief that the Necromancer was able to use the warded zone to amplify whatever means they are using to transport the zombies, therefore explaining the increasing power of the zombies as the ward remained and the drop is power after the ward was removed and the chapel cleansed.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is certain due to the continuation of attacks that the necromancer is undoubtably at large, and my professional suspicion is that the necromancer has a second staging ground, either newly made, or less developed and intended secondary to the chapel, by which the necromancer allowing himself to send forth more zombies into the docks.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is likely due to reports that the location of this 'lair' ofs sorts is likely underground, due to the zombies being said to simply 'Rise' from the ground, the mist which appeared in places which covered the ground, and the reports of boots being heard 'marching' under the ground.\\r\\nIt is also probable that the location is within the docks, and close to the commons, as this is where the majority of the zombies were encountered, and due to the fact there has only been a limited number of zombies that have entered Newtown.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Noteworthy reasoning:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n- The Necromancer has yet to try and make a attempt at stopping our supplys of holy water gathered from the cathedral which is used to cleanse people of the zombie infection. \<br\>\\r\\n- The Necromancer has not made any clear targeting of nobles within the city, apparently aiming for the majority of people, rather than key individuals.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Effects of the attacks:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n- Decline in trade to the port. \<br\>\\r\\nReports of Zombie attacks in the port is scaring off some of the ships, this suggests the Necromancer may be doing this for trade reasons, and may influencial or have influence in either a nearby port, or caravaning. \<br\>\\r\\n- Increased zeal in the population. \<br\>\\r\\nDue to the fact the holy water supply has not been attacked it must be taken into account that the Necromancer may be ironically a religeous fanatic, the fact the water is considered a holy liquid of S'Allumer and that it is key in the cleansing of the disease must not be overlooked. It inspires many peoples believe in the divine.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nOther than that we must look at the nature of where the items where placed and what they actually are.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>- The bag of herbs Herbs:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThe fact that the Necromancer used a bag of mixed herbs suggests to me that they have a relatively decent knowledge of herbs and fauna, as such would be needed to identify the right herbs, and that they were fresh enough to not rot before being used to provide catalyst for the spell.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>- The Scarab Shell and Mandragora \<br\>\\r\\nThese can suggest two things, either:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>A.\</b\> The Necromancer is an accomplished scout, and is familiar with locals of both species, or \<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>B.\</b\> The Necromancer has a good established connection for acquiring rare goods, such as exotic beetles, and deadly supernatural fauna.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>- The Statues:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThe statues in the chapel actually move with relative ease, and the pits were well formed, appearing more as compartments than quickly shoveled stow-aways, this suggests that the person is likely a achieved stone-mason, or had ties to someone on the construction team.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>- The Floor tile:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThe floor tile containing the 'Trap-Platter' was not damaged by the activities of the necromancer, this suggests either it was put in before the stone was laid, the necromancer had the ties to a stonemason to have it lifted after it was laid, or has the ability to lift the tile without damaging it.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>- The secret panel:\</b\> \<br\>\\r\\nThe fact that there was a secret room, apparently unexplained by the clergy, suggests that the necromancer was in some form related to the design and construction of the stair-case, unless placed there on request by the church it is likely it means the necromancer is tied to a higher-up of the building team, or was a member of the construction team.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nEnd of report.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Guest", "guest" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E", 1203044190, "rastalabor", "R", 1286473121, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473126, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473136, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473178, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473191, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473206, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473225, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473239, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473262, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473314, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1286473330, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1288796760, "morwenlorelie", "R", 1290029918, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029923, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029932, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029937, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029949, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029961, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029972, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029980, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029991, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290029999, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290030009, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290030025, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290030041, "morwenlorelie", "E", 1290030071, "morwenlorelie", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
