<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:belgarion's announcements">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Let the words of Guardian Belgarion be written upon here and let those who wish to see his words view them in their full extent..." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "17th Day of Hunter. \<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nI just wish to announce, and to place something on this blank sheet, that even though I ran from my future in my past, I do not plan to run once again. \\r\\nI ran before not because of the work but because I did not wish to be held responsible for so many people. I did not wish to make decisions which would affect other's lives so profoundly.\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nPlus, at the tender age of 18, such thoughts as leading a village can scare you very easily. I announce that as of today, I will receive my birthright and do my utmost to honour it." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Ninth Day of Night\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nMy childhood scholar has recently made the journey from Traven and is available to teach. He can be found near the New Town gate and currently is only able to teach his art: teaching. He claims that he has other subjects he can teach however he cannot do it alone. He has agreed to teach a wider range of subjects if more people make themselves available to teach subjects. If you wish to assist with the teaching and have skill, please notify me by scroll." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "21st Yule\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nGreetings. I am making a post upon this board to introduce the new Captain of the Guard. Captain Milli is a close personal friend and I know her to be hard-working and yet still has time to enjoy the finer things in life. I hope you all find her as delightful as I do." \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:entertainment">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "h1", "Ristonam Line Entertainment" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>Greetings, actors, musicians, and artists alike!  Have you a talent you wish to showcase?  Look no further than this page.  The Ristonam Entertainers are always happy to accept new budding talent.\</center\>" \}), (\{ "h3", "What Do We Offer?" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Wondering what the benefits of joining our guild are?  Should you choose to pursue a position with the entertainers, here are some of the things that might become of it:\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>- You will have the opportunity to take classes with a fine instructor and learn much about the field of entertainment you are interested in\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>- Helpful guild leaders and fellow members are always around to answer any pressing questions or to relieve any confusion\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>- You will be able to experience the thrill of the stage firsthand, performing with us at various venues" \}), (\{ "h3", "What Do We Look For?" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Still interested in a position within the Ristonam Entertainers?  In choosing new recruits, we are not incredibly picky.  However, there are some requirements that must be met.\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Ristonam Entertainers must be willing to learn.  They must be honest and kind to fellow guild members.  They must possess a talent in what they do, and must not be afraid to showcase their talent.  They must be faithful to the guild and take pride in what they do.  These are the qualities of a true Entertainer." \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>I look forward to seeing many new musicians, actors, artists and the like.  Please, contact me via scroll if you are interested in joining us.  We would love to have you!\</center\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<b\>--Sadie Squittio, Head of Entertainment" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guard's announcement board">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "h1", "Guard announcement board" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Greetings from the Guards of the Ristonam Line\\r\\n\\r\\nAs Captain of the Ristonam Guards, I Milli Welcome you to read through our pages to learn what is expected of a guard in our service and what we have to offer you as a recruit or patron of our services.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nWhat we offer: Premium skills and a secure position within our regiment. This is not merely a job, it is something to be honoured.\\r\\n\\r\\nWhat we expect from our Guards: We expect our guards to be honorable, presentable, dutiful and polite.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nThank you for coming to the Ristonam Line.\\r\\n\\r\\nFor those interested in joining our guard, please send a missive with your name, age and training background to myself, Captain Milli of the Ristonam line" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Ristonam Line is a family that lead a small village called Traven. Each generation of the family born does their duty in minding the people of that village and ensuring it is kept secure and safe. \<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nAlthough the Ristonam's are naught but the chiefs of a village, they are a proud and well spoken line, holding a bearing far beyond what is expected of them. \<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nThe current leader of Traven is a fox named Gistabre Ristonam who has led the village well throughout his years. His wife, Estelia remains by his side and his son, Belgarion Ristonam has been missing for several years.\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nIt is he who is next in line to inherit the village of his fathers, yet when he was informed of his future at the age of 18, he vanished that very night. However, Belgarion has finally been found residing in the city of Triskellian, after leading a life which still remains untraceable.\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nNow that he has been found, the mantle of his family will be passed onto him and he shall take up his rightful duties... we hope." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:members of the ristonam line">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the family tree">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "h1", "The Family Tree of the Ristonam's (And accompanying history)" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<B\>\<U\>Overview\</U\>\</B\>\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nThe Ristonam line is not one of antiquity but is still known as a very proud line, always brought up with exceptional social skills and mannerisms, despite the almost backwardness of their isolated village. The origins of the village continue back to an encampment of foxes within a clearing. This gathering was for the main purpose of trading and ever since, Traven has been an industrious village...\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\n\<B\>\<U\>Traven Ristonam\</B\>\</U\>\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nThe founder of Traven as it is today. Not much is known about his family as Traven never mentioned them or his origins, which is fairly strange due to the fact Traven was a member of the village Elders. However we do know he was born in the year of 663 Apres le Miracle and was known as a humble scout.\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nIt appeared he once happened upon an encampment of foxes in the middle of a large clearing and decided to remain there. Slowly, his influence grew until he became an Elder and as he continued his stay, the foxes noted his uncanny abilities at organising and how much he tended to care for his fellow foxes. Eventually, he was elevated as their leader. \<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nThis was just the start of something much bigger. In the year of 683 he began construction of Traven, a village of foxes and the clearing was a hive of activity until 684 when construction was finally completed and the village of Traven was truly founded.\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nDuring this time, Traven had married to a vixen named Olyrin and shortly after Traven was founded, she bore him a son whom he named Glothen. Traven then allowed the village a minor freedom, allowing it to grow under it's own community's attention. This, in turn, meant he could focus upon raising his son to the unmistakable manner which all Ristonam's bear.\<Br\>\\r\\n\<Br\>\\r\\nSadly, as most founders eventually do, Traven passed away in the year of 702 from old age. He was buried in a crypt specially built by the citizens of Traven. There was much mourning when Traven passed away and even more so when his wife also passed away in the year of 703, leaving her only a year to teach her son the ways of the Guardian." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the teacher of the ristonam line">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
