<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:allies & allied factions">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Allies \& Allied Factions\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Company occasionally seeks to ally with an individual, company, guild or faction in order to achieve any number of political, social, economic or other goals. The company must maintain prudence when making these decisions, and assure that we are not making mutually exclusive alliances. Also important is making sure that members of large faction alliances do not conflict with one another. Given the nature of alliances and politics in the city, we will seek to limit the investment we have in such relationships, and the number of alliances in which we take part. Additionally, we will seek to specifically define the nature of all alliances, identify extended members of alliances and regularly update our information and our relations with the alliance, as well as individual members.\\r\\n\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Donatella Tonozzi, Squire to Lord Langston\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nFounded: The eight day of Yule, the eight hundred ninety-first Apres le Miracle.\<br\>\\r\\nStatus: Ongoing\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>The following individuals and organizations are allied by association:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\>Lord Twyrch Langston\<br\>\\r\\n\>\>\> The Bisclavret Embassy\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance Details:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe purpose of this alliance is primarily trade and mutual protection. We will generally provide the Squire and her House will goods at a discounted price - Associated allies will have secondary preferential rights to trade. We will also seek to personally support the Squire and provide her with favors that are within our power. In return we receive assistance from other members of the alliance most important of which being political backing stemming from the association with the Bisclavret, and favors. This also may include possible access to goods \& services.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance History:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>8 Yule: Alliance Begins - Captain Rhys negotiates for a general alliance.[Success]\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>8 Yule: With the assistance of Donatella, the Bisclavret Embassy lends its name behind Captain Rhys \& the Company in regards to unfound charges levelled by Captain Brenner of the Avoirdupois Embassy relating to steel purchased from the Easterners.[Success]\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>*11 Yule: The Company sells three(3) rods of steel (superb quality) to Donatella for five hundred(500) denarii.[Satisfied]\</li\>\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Valentin Forza \& the Forza Family\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nFounded: The twenty-eighth day of Yule, the eight hundred ninety-first Apres le Miracle.\<br\>\\r\\nStatus: Ongoing\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance Details:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nTrade alliance and functional resource sharing.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance History:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>28 Yule: Alliance Begins\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>The Triskellian Assembly of Mercenary Companies\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nFounded: The first day of Strawberry, the eight hundred ninety-first Apres le Miracle.\<br\>\\r\\nStatus: Ongoing\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance Details:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThis alliance includes all members of the Mercenary Assembly including; Clan Rhashak \& CV. The alliance purpose is legtimacy of authority, business conduct and forum, and personnel resource sharing.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance History:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>1 Strawberry: Alliance Begins\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Zephyr Slavery Company\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nFounded: The twenty-eighth day of Strawberry, the eight hundred ninety-first Apres le Miracle.\<br\>\\r\\nStatus: Ended, dishonorably by Slavers.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance Details:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nPolitical and social protection alliance.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Alliance History:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\\r\\n\<li\>28 Strawberry: Alliance Begins\\r\\n\<li\>18 Thunder: Alliance is terminated by Captain Rhys, via letter to miss Faile Neidell (cc: Adm. Flynn), due to unethical \& immoral conduct, dishonorable conduct/conduct not befitting of an ally, and attacking an ally. Ryan chief administrator of the Slavers and representative of the Slavers to the Company inappropriately and without cause attacked the physical character of Veritas Rhys in public, and sought to damage his reputation and business.\\r\\n\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:auction receipts">
         (\{ (\{ 3, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Auction Receipts\</h3\>\\r\\nA record of all items won at auction. Do not remove records, even after items leave company possession. Below is a key of how to record our auction purchases.\<br\>\\r\\n\<p style=\\"font-size:12pt\\"\>\<b\>Quantity:\</b\> The amount of items delivered per shipment - not total.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Price:\</b\> The amount the company paid at auction per shipment.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Item:\</b\> The description of the item as it is listed on the auction block.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Notes:\</b\> A description \& any other notes about the item. It does not have to directly correspond with the notes shown on the auction block.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Shipments:\</b\> The amount of shipments set to be purchased.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Acq. Date:\</b\> The date [IC] that the purchase was finalized.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Trader:\</b\> The name of trader which negotiated the deal.\<br\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<table border=\\"3\\" bordercolor=\\"4E6487\\" style=\\"background-color:6283DD\\" width=\\"745\\" cellpadding=\\"1\\" cellspacing=\\"3\\"\>\\r\\n\<tr\>\<th width=\\"25\\"\>Qty.\</th\>\<th width=\\"75\\"\>Price\</th\>\<th width=\\"75\\"\>Item\</th\>\\r\\n\<th width=\\"200\\"\>Notes\</th\>\<th\>Shipments\</th\>\<th\>Acq. Date\</th\>\<th\>Trader\</th\>\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<tr\>\<td\>1\</td\>\<td\>151 denarii\</td\>\<td\>Gold Messaline Ropa\</td\>\<td\>Made by the famous Rinaldi seamstress, Boticella. Floor-length open coat.\</td\>\<td\>1\</td\>\<td\>Dimache, 29 Grass 891\</td\>\<td\>Veritas Rhys\</td\>\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<tr\>\<td\>4\</td\>\<td\>301 denarii\</td\>\<td\>Decanter\</td\>\<td\>Rinaldi imported glass wine decanters.\</td\>\<td\>2/30\</td\>\<td\>Jeudi, 6 Flower 891\</td\>\<td\>Veritas Rhys\</td\>\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<tr\>\<td\>1\</td\>\<td\>301 denarii\</td\>\<td\>Greenheart Lumber\</td\>\<td\>Bisclavret import of Greenheart Lumber.\</td\>\<td\>1\</td\>\<td\>Mardi, 14 Flower 891\</td\>\<td\>Veritas Rhys\</td\>\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<tr\>\<td\>60\</td\>\<td\>151 denarii\</td\>\<td\>Cartouches\</td\>\\r\\n\<td\>Firearm ammunition by the Rinaldi\</td\>\<td\>3/10\</td\>\<td\>Jeudi, 24 Flower 891\</td\>\<td\>Veritas Rhys\</td\>\</tr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</table\>\</center\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<br\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>In Stock Specialty Material\</h3\>\\r\\n\<b\>Greenheart Lumber: [Unsurpassed Quality (12)]\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nQuantity: 1 full rod\<br\>\\r\\nPurchased Price: 301 denarii\<br\> \\r\\nBase price: 33d/cord\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: \<i\>none\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Steel: [Good quality (6)]\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nQuantity: 20 full rods\<br\>\\r\\nPurchased Price: 400 denarii\<br\> \\r\\nBase price: 42d/length\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: \<i\>none\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p style=\\"font-size:smaller\\"\>\<i\>The base price is the amount of money that should be sent to the guild for use of the material. Craftsmen are free to charge whatever price they desire, but this amount must be sent directly to Captain Rhys unless otherwise cleared with an authorized Company trader.\<br\>\\r\\nIf prices are too high for you to sell these materials or aren't proving profitable for the craftsmen discuss it with Veritas.\<br\>\\r\\nTo get access to special materials or to order something that you don't see write the captain or a Company trader.\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:blacklist">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Blacklist\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nAs a mercenary company it is not in our nature to blacklist an entity for actions which others types of Guilds, Companies, Organizations, or Houses would. There are two basic types of blacklisting, Services Blacklisting \& Import Blacklisting. Services blacklisting obviously refers to an individual or group being unable to contract our mercenary services, while Import blacklisting refers to the inability to purchase or request goods be imported. An entity can be placed on either or both lists. In most cases Blacklisting will be temporary, conditional of certain requirements being met before the entity can be removed from The List. Entities which are permenantly blacklisted will be marked with an asterisk.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Black listed entities will be informed of the blacklisting, as well as why they have been black listed, what is being restricted and what may be done in order to become eligible for services and/or imports again, in a timely manner from the decision being passed.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>Gaining a spot on the blacklist will \<i\>usually\</i\> be because of a combination of several negative factors that another organization or individual has stacked against it. There are certain factors, however, which will instantly gain a person or organization a spot on our blacklist. Those include:\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<ul\>\<li\>Impugning the Honor, Honesty or Integrity of The Company.\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Malicious or Menacing Business Practices\</li\>\\r\\n\</b\>\</ul\>\\r\\nNegative factors which will weigh against an individual or group and which will eventually result in blacklisting include:\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<ul\>\<li\>Failure to Pay Incurred Debts\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Breach of Contract\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Non-Contractual Use of Resources\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dishonest or Misleading Negotiations\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Unethical or Misleading Business Practices\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Failure to Settle Contract\</li\>\\r\\n\</b\>\</ul\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>Submit suggestions for additional black listable offenses to the Captain.\</i\>\\r\\n\<hr\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Services Blacklist\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Embassy of and House Doloreaux \& allied and associated organizations: This includes, but is not limited to named below.\<br\>\\r\\nDame Fern, Sir Erwin, Sir Burcet, Baronet Eberhard, Lady Anja, Count Vidar, Gretchen Thorne, Aimi Karachii, Senora Delgado, Khalon, Inalla, Abel, Yoshi, Sir Althalus, Turvel, Althea, Roofus Black, Leif, Bastien, Gronus Goodfellow, Jaslene, Snowlilly, Roxanne;\<br\>\\r\\nand, The Triskellian University, the Dividing Line.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\> " \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Import Blacklist\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Embassy of and House Doloreaux \& allied and associated organizations: This includes, but is not limited to named below.\<br\>\\r\\nDame Fern, Sir Erwin, Sir Burcet, Baronet Eberhard, Lady Anja, Count Vidar, Gretchen Thorne, Aimi Karachii, Senora Delgado, Khalon, Inalla, Abel, Yoshi, Sir Althalus, Turvel, Althea, Roofus Black, Leif, Bastien, Gronus Goodfellow, Jaslene, Snowlilly, Roxanne;\<br\>\\r\\nand, The Triskellian University, the Dividing Line.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\> " \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Permanent Stipulations\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nGroups and individuals on this list have some modifier attached to how we do business with them. The stipulation can be anything that allows us to continue doing business with the entity based on a condition. The actual condition depends upon what triggered the need for it, which should also be recorded in detail so as to allow it to be taken into account during negotiations. The stipulations are not hard and fast in all situations but there should be a \<b\>very\</b\> good reason for overlooking them in any given situation. Also, while the stipulations are considered permanent, should the entity show a clear sign of changed behavior, they can be removed from this list.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<b\>Embassy for the House of Avoirdupois:\</b\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\nUnder Dame Theressa the Avoirdupois Embassy employeed Captain Rhys' services as a guard, with the promise of 14d daily pay. Over the course of more than 5 weeks of employment [Start date 21 Nov. - End date 1 Jan = 42 days x 14d daily = 588d due - 84d accumulated = \<b\>502d b.i.\</b\>], in which the Embassy had sought to use Captain Rhys in non-contractually agreed upon ways, the Embassy had only paid the sum of 88d (2 denarii daily) leaving an outstanding balance of 502 denarii. After consulting with Dame Theressa, who refused to pay the balance and did not return requests to be seated with mediators Marguan, Gnaeus \& Grimclaw of the Eastern Mercenary Company, Captain Rhys was absolved of contractual bound. As the Dame was unable to be contacted, Mister Marguan set about contracting Captain Rhys' services. Payment for services was partially offered in the form of steel rods. Sir Bayard and Captain Brenner then thought to assault the honor of Captain Rhys, by lying and stating he was in some way (with no explanation as to how, and which was never expounded upon) duty bound to the House of Avoirdupois, and assuming to issues a false statement of dishonorable discharge when, in reality, Captain Rhys was not then, nor ever in any way duty bound to the embassy. Without any proof or reason, accused by Captain Brenner of piracy and theft for being in possession of steel, despite the presence of a receipt. Lord Edmond issued punish to Captain Brenner and a written and public apology to Captain Rhys. When Captain Rhys requested to clear the situation regarding the undue tarnish on his name, Lord Edmond demanded that Captain Rhys supply mercenaries to set about clearing the Avoirdupois' waters of pirates in exchange for public clarification on the matter of Captain Rhys' honor. The attempt at blackmail was fully rejected by Captain Rhys due to the unethical nature of the request.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Conclusion:\</b\>\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\nAny future contracts must be paid in full, with a signed and authorized contract prior to the start of any operations. Any future imports must be paid in full prior to delievery of goods. Members are strongly encouraged to ask other members of their experiences with this House.\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\> " \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Satisfaction Requirements\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<b\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\> " \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:blacksmith contracts">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 4 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Open Orders\</h3\>\\r\\nThis page used to keep track of who ordered what, what orders have been filled, what orders need to be paid and so forth.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Filled Orders: Pending Payment\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:blacksmith price list">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Items Available\</h3\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nBlacksmith - Horseshoe; Horseshoes; Fire brush; Fire poker; Fire tongs; Fire guard; Fire shovel; \<Branding iron\> \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTools - Tool Handle; Nail; Sewing Needle; Tailoring Pin; Chisel; \<Push hoe; Pitchfork; Spade; Jeweler Polisher; Transplanting Trowel; Garden rake; Hedge shear; Cultivator; Wheelbarrow\> \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nToys/Misc. - Pea Whistle; \<Flower; Rose\> \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nHome Goods - Scissors; Spoon; Sconce; Goblet; Spitoon; Chamber Pot; Comb; Hairbrush; Plate; Bowl; \<Flask; Serving tray; Ash tray; Frying pan; Stock pot; Chalice; Candelabra; Basin; Pitcher; Alter candelabra; Floor candelabra; Tea Kettle; Metal Locker\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nProfessional Supplies - Button; Bead; Hairpin; Hat pin; Buckle; Scalpel\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<Armor - Breastplate\>\\r\\n\\r\\nWeapons - Blade; Hilt; Haft\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<BLACKSMITH\\r\\nLevel 1: Tool Handle; Nail;\\r\\nLevel 2: Button; Sewing Needle; Tailoring Pin; Horseshoe;\\r\\nLevel 3: Bead; Hairpin; Hat Pin;\\r\\nLevel 4: Buckle; Fork; Horseshoes; Scissors; Spoon;\\r\\nLevel 5: Fire Brush; Fire Poker; Sconce; Fire Tongs;\\r\\nLevel 6: Chisel; Goblet; Comb; Spitoons, Pea Whistle\\r\\nLevel 7: Fire Guard; Fire Shovel; Hairbrush; Chamber Pots\\r\\nLevel 8: Blade; Hilt; Plate; Scalpel; Bowl;\\r\\nLevel 9: Flask; Push Hoe; Pitchforks\\r\\nLevel 10: Breastplate; Serving Tray; Ash Tray;\\r\\nLevel 11: Metal Locker; Spade;\\r\\nLevel 12: Jeweler Polisher; Die (singular of dice); Frying Pan;\\r\\nLevel 13: Branding Iron; Stock Pot;\\r\\nLevel 14: Chalice; Transplanting Trowel;\\r\\nLevel 15: Flower; Candelabra;\\r\\nLevel 16: Push Hoe; Basin; Pitcher; Alter Candelabra;\\r\\nLevel 17: Floor Candelabra;\\r\\nLevel 18: Garden Rake; Hedge Shears;\\r\\nLevel 19: Cultivator;\\r\\nLevel 20: Wheelbarrow;\\r\\nLevel 21: Tea Kettles\\r\\nLevel 23: Flower: rose;\\r\\nARMORSMITH\\r\\nLevel 1: Rondel;\\r\\nLevel 2: Bracers; Lumber: shield; Bracers;\\r\\nLevel 3: Ailettes; Schynbalds;\\r\\nLevel 4: Chainmail; Breastplate; Shield;\\r\\nLevel 6: Doll: smith; Figurine: smith; Greaves; Shield: buckler;\\r\\nLevel 7: Besagews;\\r\\nLevel 8: Chestplate; Culet; Shield: kite;\\r\\nLevel 10: Cutting: small bar; Sabatons; Shield: heater\\r\\nLevel 11: Couters; Poleyns;\\r\\nLevel 12: Helmet;\\r\\nLevel 13: Spaulders; Helmet: kettle hat;\\r\\nLevel 14: Gauntlets; Helmet: cervelliere;\\r\\nLevel 15: Pauldrons; Helmet: capeline;\\r\\nLevel 16: Gorget; Helmet: spangenhelm;\\r\\nLevel 17: Helmet: bascinet;\\r\\nLevel 18: Helmet: sallet, barbute, burgonet; Cuisses;\\r\\nLevel 19: Tassets;\\r\\nLevel 20: Bevor;\\r\\nLevel 21: Fauld;\\r\\nLevel 22: Vambraces; Rerebraces;\\r\\nLevel 23: Bases;\\r\\nLevel 24: Helmet: heaume.\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<p\>\<i\>\<b\>\<font size=\\"3\\" face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Prices are subject to change to meeting market value of \\r\\nmetals requested. Specialty metals are available upon request; contact Lialessa Ralune or Captain Veritas Rhys in regards to access to any metals you would like used that are not sold by the local blacksmith.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nAll members of the Sentinels will receive an in house discount for any items requested. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPlease contact Lialessa Ralune for further information.\</font\>\</b\>\</i\>\</p\>\\r\\n\<hr\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:carpentry contracts">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<u\>Open Orders\</u\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThis page used to keep track of who ordered what, what orders have been filled, what orders need to be paid and so forth.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Doctor Hush\</i\>\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe Doctor is placing an order for a several items to gift to Caliste who was recently promoted to serfdom. She has requested the use of a specific exotic wood that is currently being imported in.\<br\>\\r\\n-Painters Kit\<br\>\\r\\n-Easel\<br\>\\r\\n-Paint Brush\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCurrently awaiting word from Veritas on the status of the wood requested, along with the base price to fill order.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Order Commission:\</b\> 15th of Flower\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<u\>Filled Orders: Pending Payment\</u\>\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<u\>Completed Orders - Paid\</u\>\</h3\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Handmaiden Nan of Avoirdupois\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\n-2 Hickory Folding Screens (15 denarii)\<br\>\\r\\n-1 Hickory Stool. (5 denarii)\<br\>\\r\\n-1 Large Hickory Crate (3 denarii)\\r\\n\<br\>stain in black lacquered (provided by customer)\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Order Commission:\</b\> 22nd of Flower\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Order Paid:\</b\> Payment of 50 denarii made 23rd of Flower\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Order Filled:\</b\> 23 of Flower\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<font size=2\> Prices listed in orders above, with the exception of payments made, are per item.\</font\>\</i\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:carpentry price list">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Items Available\</h3\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<table x:str border=\\"0\\" cellpadding=\\"0\\" cellspacing=\\"0\\" width=\\"686\\" style=\\"border-collapse:\\r\\n collapse;width:516pt\\"\>\\r\\n  \<colgroup\>\\r\\n    \<col width=\\"170\\" style=\\"width: 128pt\\"\>\<col width=\\"184\\" style=\\"width: 138pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<col width=\\"174\\" style=\\"width: 131pt\\"\>\<col width=\\"158\\" style=\\"width: 119pt\\"\>\\r\\n  \</colgroup\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" width=\\"170\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; width: 128pt; font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Furniture\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td width=\\"184\\" style=\\"width: 138pt; font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Weapons/Tools\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td width=\\"174\\" style=\\"width: 131pt; font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Toys\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td width=\\"158\\" style=\\"width: 119pt; font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Building/Art Supplies\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Bookshelves\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Club\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Dice\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Boards\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cabinets\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Dagger Sheath\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cup and Ball\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Dress Form\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Chairs\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Fishing Rod\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Figurines\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Easel\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Chamber Pot\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hafts\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hoop and Stick\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Mannequin\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Chests\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hilts\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Spinning Top\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Mortar\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Coat Stand\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Shields\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Painters Kit\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cot\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Staff\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Painters Palette\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cradle\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Sword Blades\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Paneling\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Crib\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Tool Handles\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Home Goods/Accessories\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td x:str=\\"Mortar \\" style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Patten\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Dressers\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Truncheons\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Backscratcher\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Pegs\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Folding Screen\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Bangle\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Pestles\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Foot Stool\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Basin\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Shutters\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Rack\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Beads\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Stool\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Storage Units\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Bowl\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Sudare\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Bucket\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Buttons\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"font-weight: 700; text-decoration: underline; text-underline-style: single; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-style: normal; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Medical Supplies\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Tables\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cigar Box\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Cane\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Arm Splint\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Trunks\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Crates\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Combs\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Crutches\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Flat Box\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hair Brush\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Leg Splint\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Inkwells\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hair Sticks\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Tail Splint\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Jewelry Box\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Hand Fan\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Larger Barrels\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Mop\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Lumber Box\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Pitcher\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Plates\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Spoons\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \&nbsp;\</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n  \<tr height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height:12.75pt\\"\>\\r\\n    \<td height=\\"17\\" style=\\"height: 12.75pt; color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\>\\r\\n    \<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Tea Caddy\</font\>\</td\>\\r\\n    \<td style=\\"color: windowtext; font-size: 10.0pt; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-family: Arial; text-align: general; vertical-align: bottom; white-space: nowrap; border: medium none; padding-left: 1px; padding-right: 1px; padding-top: 1px\\"\> \</td\>\\r\\n  \</tr\>\\r\\n\</table\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<p\>\<i\>\<b\>\<font size=\\"3\\" face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>Prices are subject to change to meeting market value of \\r\\nwoods requested. Also when requesting higher or lower quality items please keep \\r\\nin mind that a +/- 5% price difference will be reflected in the cost of the \\r\\nitems off the basic price.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nAll members of the Sentinels will receive an in house discount for any items \\r\\nrequested. \<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nPlease contact Irene Stafline for further information.\</font\>\</b\>\</i\>\</p\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:chain of command">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<a target='_blank' title='ImageShack - Image And Video Hosting' href='http://img263.imageshack.us/i/chainofcommand.png/'\>\<img src='http://img263.imageshack.us/img263/3328/chainofcommand.png' border='0'/\>\</a\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:company inventory">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>In Stock/Stock\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<b\>ARMOR:\</B\>\<br\>\\r\\nBarbute, Steel (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\nChestplate, Steel (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>WEAPONS:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nSword, Mahogany (2/2)\<br\>\\r\\nSword, Hickory (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\nArming sword, Iron (0/1)\<br\>\\r\\nShortsword, Iron (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\nRapier, Iron (3/7)\<br\>\\r\\nSnaphaunce Pistol, various (6/6)\<br\>\\r\\nSnaphaunce Musket, steel (4 pending)\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>MISC:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nPolishing machine, metal (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\nEucalyptus tree (1/1)\<br\>\\r\\nTobacco plant, vanilla (1 pending)\<br\>\\r\\nTobacco plant, cherry (1 pending)\<br\>\\r\\nTobacco plant, chocolate (1 pending)\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:company positions">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Company Commander - Captain\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Company Commander is in charge of the administrative company functions in the city. The Captain also serves as the commander of military exercises when he is present. He also has final say on all company contracts and can approve or decline sanctions for individual contracts. Ranks and positions which are not held by an individual are the default responsibility of the Captain's to execute, in addition to all other responsibilities of this command.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently held by Taraji Hanan\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Platoon Commander - 1st \& 2nd Lieutenant\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe 2nd Lieutenant commands one platoon, or half a company of soldiers. This position, as with all officer ranks, requires at least one combat engagement. The platoon commander is directly responsible for the training of troops.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently defaulted to the First Lieutenant's Command\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Company Administrator - 2nd Lieutenant\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThis lieutenant acts as Deputy to the Company Commander and second in command. The Company Administrator is responsible for preparing their monthly report prior to the primary (first) meeting of the month. The Company Administrator is responsible for supervising the training of troops. In full battle line, the 1st Lieutenant serves as the Commander of 1st Platoon.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently held by no one\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Company Quartermaster - 3rd Lieutenant\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Quartermaster is specifically responsible for acquisitions, distribution and upkeep of all equipment obtained by the company. The Quartermaster is responsible for preparing a monthly report prior to the primary (first) meeting of the month outlining acquisitions, inventory and receipts. Though a non-combat position, as with all officer ranks, it requires the individual to be a combat veteran of at least one engagement. The Company Quartermaster is generally a 3rd Lieutenant, but may occasionally be a 2nd Lieutenant. Regardless of ranks, this position is subordinate to combat commanders.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently defaulted to Taraji's Command.\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Company Operations Administrator - 3rd Lieutenant\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Operations officer is responsible for organizing the individual contracting agents, advising them on their negotiations, making sure contracts are not mutually exclusive and that there are enough personnel to fill contracts that are being negotiated. The operations officer is responsible for preparing a monthly report prior to the primary (first) meeting of the month outlining contract activity and bringing forth contracts for a final vote and official approval. As with all officer ranks, the individual is required to be a combat veteran. This position is subordinate to combat commanders.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently defaulted to Taraji's Command.\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Section Supervisor - Sergeant\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Section Supervisor is in charge of overseeing daily operations of their soldiers and keeping their Platoon Commander informed of the activities of their section. They are also instrumental in assisting their Platoon Commander in training.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is held by Jace Bishop.\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Line Supervisor - Corporal\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Line Supervisor is in charge of the overseeing of basic tasks and keeping their Section Supervisor informed of the activities of their line.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This rank is currently held by Gnaeus.\<br\>\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Soldier/Guardsman\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nBasic line infantryman. Often considered to be the most crucial element of the Company. Their basic function changes depending on the contract or in what capacity they are acting, but they remain the heart and soul of any operation.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"times new roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Division Administrator\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nAdministrative officers of the non-military sections of the company (i.e. Company blacksmith, carpenter, weaponsmith, etc.). The division administrator is directly responsibile for keeping their division profitable for the company. They prepair reports for the Company Commander due prior to the first weekend of the month. The division administrators hold no military rank, and are a completely separate command structure.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>The rank of Carpentery Division Administrator is currently held by Irene Stafline\<br\>The rank of Blacksmith Division Administrator is currently held by Lialessa Ralune\</i\>\</b\>\</center\> \<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Specialists\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nIn addition to line soldiers, The Company employs a series of specialists whom are outside the regular military command structure. These specialists take their directions from the appropriate division administrator, or to whomever they are assigned on a case by case basis. Specialists include craftmen and any other profession which is not classified by another rank.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>Communications Specialist - Inolia Grey\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Acquisitions Agent\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThis position may be held concurrently with any other position. Acquisition agents are given the authority to place orders on behalf of the Company, and charge those orders directly to the Company's kitty. Transactions are reported to the Company Quartermaster, not through the individual's regular chain of command. The names of acquisition agents can be found on the Company's public guest board.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This position is currently held by Timurus \& Lurana.\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Contracting Agent\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThis position may be held concurrently with any other position. Contracting agents are given the authority to negotiate contracts on behalf of the Company. All contracts require general review and consensus and adequate volunteers to fill, as well as final approval by the Captain. Contracting agents seek out and negotiate the terms of the contracts brought to the attention of the company. Transactions are reported to the Company Operations Administrator, not through the individual's regular chain of command. The names of contracting agents can be found on the Company's public guest board.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>This position is currently held by Sardis.\</i\>\</b\>\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:company uniforms">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Uniforms\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nAll company employees are issued the same basic uniform. Variations distinguish certain members from one another. Employees are encouraged to remain in uniform at all times, however, not required. You are required to be in uniform whenever executing official Company business. The basic uniform consists of:\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Males\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<ul\>\<li\>ebony broadcloth cravat\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>steel blue suede gauntlets\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>ebony leather infantry boots\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>steel blue cotton shirt\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>slate grey cotton vest\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>slate grey wool jacket\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>ebony cotton breeches\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>ebony suede satchel\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>linen waist sash\</li\>\</ul\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Females\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nFemales of all positions are allowed to wear the following uniform(86). This uniform is stand alone and should not be combined with any other uniform.:\\r\\n\<center\>\<ul\>\<li\>ebony leather pants\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>slate grey leather knee-high boots\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>ebony suede satchel\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>slate grey cotton moneypouch\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>steel blue wool bellcloak\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>bright white cotton blouse\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>black leather double wrap belt\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>steel blue leather underbust corset\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>linen waist sash\</li\>\</ul\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<b\>Indicators:\</b\>\\r\\nThe color of sash and trims allowed to be worn indicate the given member's rank and function in the company. They are as follows:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Military\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nGold - Captain; Silver - Lieutenant; Steel Blue - Sergeant; Scarlet - Corporal/Soldiers\<br\> \\r\\n\<b\>Non-Military\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nVibrant Green - Traders; Ash Grey - Specialists; Bronze - Craftmen\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n*Undergarments are acceptable with all uniforms, but are not considered part of the uniform.\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:contract forms">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nThe Company utilizes a variety of standardized forms, terms and language in order that we might quickly build contracts which can be customized to meet the requirements of our employers. All soldiers are strongly encouraged to familiarize themselves with the forms and the language used in them, as well as reading over any contracts to which they are assigned, so that they are aware what is and is not expected of them when executing their duties and when the should report violation of the contractual agreement to their superiors.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nContracting Agents receive detailed training in this area, as do any military personnel with operations responsibility. If you are unclear on any contract or need clarification of language or terms you are encouraged to find those individuals.\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\> " \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:contracts">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 2 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Open Contracts\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>Contracting Entity: House Bisclavret Trade Embassy\</i\>\</b\>\</Center\>\\r\\nPurpose: Importation of small arms for Company \& personal use\<br\>\\r\\nContract Start Date: 18 day of Grass 891\<br\>\\r\\nContract End Date: Open\<br\>\\r\\nServing Personnel: Cpt. Veritas; Lt. Grimclaw; Cpl. Gnaeus\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: 4 snaphaunce pistols (160d ea.), 3 snaphaunce muskets (168d ea.)  - Taxes Paid. Contract prevent resale of firearms.\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>---Nothing Follows---\</i\>\</b\>\</Center\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>Contracting Entity: House d'Avoirdupois Trade Embassy\</i\>\</b\>\</Center\>\\r\\nPurpose: Elimination of Pirates in Avoirdupois waters\<br\>\\r\\nContract Start Date: 9th day of Thunder 891\<br\>\\r\\nContract End Date: Open, no estimates\<br\>\\r\\nServing Personnel: Cpt. Veritas; Lt. Grimclaw; (Others to be listed)\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: \<br\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<b\>\<i\>---Nothing Follows---\</i\>\</b\>\</Center\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Contract History\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<b\>Security Contract of Rinaldi House Personnel During Pirate Negotiations.\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nPersonnel: Cpt. Veritas; Lt. Grimclaw; Taraji; Kildarien\<br\>\\r\\nRun Time: 22nd day of Grass, 891 - 22nd day of Grass, 891\<br\>\\r\\nSatisfaction Status: Served Satisfactorily \& Paid\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: In addition to full payment of 200 denarii, Cpt. Rhys was awarded a favor token by Lord Marcus for professional service.\</i\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Doctor Hush Sweetling\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nPurpose: Protection of injured person (Minni) during her stay in the infirmary\<br\>\\r\\nRun Time: 28th day of Grass 891 - 4th day of Flower 891\<br\>\\r\\nServing Personnel: Taraji Hanan\<br\>\\r\\nSatisfaction Status: Served Satisfactorily \& Paid\<br\>\\r\\nNotes: \<br\>\</i\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>House Bisclavret: Contract For Small Arms\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<i\>The following is a formal contract between the Embassy of the noble House Bisclavret located within Triskellion and one, Mr. Veritas Rhys, Captain of the Sentinels Guild based within Triskellion.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIn accordance with agreement of both parties, the Embassy shall be paid a small percentage fee per firearm brought into the city by Mr. Rhys for personal usage.\<br\>\<br\> \\r\\n\\r\\nThese fees do not reflect on any normal taxes or fees that are to be paid by the Sentinels at which time they decide to procure a profit for these imported goods. Should such occur any normal fees or taxes shall be applied to the firearm in question to be paid in full to the Embassy.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nThe following are the requested percentage per firearm to be paid to the Embassy.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n*12% per pistols\<br\>\\r\\n*15% per musket\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nAny firearms personally brought in for the use of the Embassy shall be exempt from such fees previously mentioned.\<br\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nSignature: Countess Gaelawai, Lady Aedina Izmae Ealdarach de Bisclavret\<br\>\\r\\nSignature: Captain Veritas Rhys, Sentinels Mercenary Free Company\<br\>\\r\\nWitness:   Esquire Aysun Deloruix, Steward of House Bisclavret\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</center\>\\r\\n[At the bottom right of the contract, the seal of House Bisclavret has been stamped into the paper using dark crimson wax to notarize the document]\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\\r\\nIt is signed by Esquire Aysun. \</i\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Infirmary Security Contract\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<i\>\<center\>\\r\\nI, Doctor Hush Sweetling, hire one Taraji Hanan of the Sentinels to guard a patient by the name of Minni.  The short term job will consist of guarding the infirmary from all unwanted persons and focusing on the patient Minni.  The length of employeement will be one week starting 28 of Grass [March] till Flower [May] 4th of this year.  The pay rate is 10 denarri a day with a final pay of 70 denarri.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\</center\>\\r\\nSigned by both parties.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nDoctor Hush Sweetling\<br\>\\r\\nTaraji Hanan\<br\> \</i\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>House Rinaldi: Security of Rinaldi House Personnel During Pirate Negotiations\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<i\>The following is a formal contract between the noble House di Rinaldi \& the Sentinels Free Company.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIn accordance with terms set forth and agreed upon by both parties; the Sentinels will provide, for a fee, security and general military services under the command of Captain Veritas Rhys and at the direction of Lord Marcus di Rinaldi for the duration of negotiations with local pirates, including travel time prior and following said negotiations.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThe Sentinels will provide up to three soldiers for this assignment and be compensated fifty denarii for each soldier in attendance for their services should negotiations proceed without hostility, or one hundred denarii per soldier should hostilities occur. Compensation to be deposited into the Sentinel's treasury or directly to Captain Rhys.\</center\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is signed by Xena. \</i\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>The House Avoirdupois: Pirate Hunting\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<i\>\\r\\nSECTION I:  THE SENTINELS REQUEST\<br\>\\r\\nI. Payment: A maximum of twenty-five hundred (2500) denarii paid directly to the Sentinels coffers for preparation and execution expenses and to cover personnel costs, of which five hundred (500) denarii shall be paid in advance of the expedition and the remainder shall be paid, as a measure of the sucess of operations, based on the tonnage of ships captured and sunk during operations.\<br\>\\r\\na. Ship \& related supplies (900d)\<br\>\\r\\nb. Company Personnel (1200d)\<br\>\\r\\nc. Independant Personnel (400d crew)\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nII. Local Investiture: Imperium Jus Brevi Manu - While operating in the maritime claims of the Avoirdupois, Captain Veritas Rhys of the Sentinels free company will be invested with the authority to dispense low justice to the crews of any vessel deemed to be hostile. [OOC: Extends the right to pass legal judgment and see to execution of any punishment of any commoner captured in Avoirdupois waters.]\<br\>\\r\\na. This does not apply to captured nobles \& gentry, who will be detained and kept in fair health until they can be delievered to the Avoirdupois for judgment.\<br\>\\r\\nb. This investiture is only effective for the duration of operations and only while acting inside the maritime territorial claims of the Avoirdupois.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIII. Greater Investiture: Imperium Mantenerre - The Sentinels are invested by the Noble House of Avoirdupois with the authority to hold any 'special' personnel captured in their waters during the course of operations, indefinitely, upon return to the city. Captains Rhys will also maintain Imperium of Low Justice over any special personnel for the durations of their detention.\<br\>\\r\\na. Special prisoners will be defined as those who bear distinctive markings on their body, thought to be in possession of information deemed necessary to Captain Rhys (as defined by Captain Rhys), or found to be in possession of anything suspect of being of importance or which suggest expanded criminal activity beyond piracy.\<br\>\\r\\nb. If released from Captain Rhys' personal detention, the prisoners will be remanded to the custody of the Embassy of the Avoirdupois for whatever fate the House deems them worthy.\<br\>\\r\\nc. The Avoirdupois embassy will arrange for a secure facility on Avoirdupois land or a prison ship in Avoirdupois waters for special prisoners to be held, in the event the Rinaldi do not allow these prisoners to remain in his personal detention while in the city.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIV. Greater Investiture: Investment of Commission - The House of Avoirdupois will provide to Captain Rhys temporary commission as a free Naval Officer and officially recognize ships taking part under his command as vessels operating on the behalf of the Avoirdupois navy. Furthermore, Captain Rhys will personally assume the full responsibility of actions undertaken during his command. All individuals under his command shall be held blameless, by all authorities, for any actions in which they take part. Captain Rhys shall be expected to abide by and enforce the customs and traditions of Land \& Naval Warfare and shall carry the responsibility of reasonably disciplining individuals under his command who deviate from those customs.\<br\>\\r\\na. Captain Rhys' commission shall become effective on the day this contract is signed into force and shall extend one (1) month beyond the conclusion of operations, unless specifically extended by the Embassy or an authorized representative of the House of Avoirdupois.\<br\>\\r\\nb. Except in that pirates and privateers shall be deemed and treated as criminals and not prisoners of war or enemy combatants.\<br\>\\r\\nc. As a recognized officer of the Avoirdupois navy, Captain Rhys shall be subject to Avoirdupois military justice for any actions taken during the expedition that are outside both the investment of his commission and the additional investitures listed in this contract. Specifically;\<br\>\\r\\n  1. Captain Rhys shall be subject to military justice for any acts of piracy he knowingly and willingly takes part in.\<br\> \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nV. Personnel: Captain Rhys and the Sentinels are free to hire any independant individual whom they deem to be necessary or vital to the successful execution of operations, except where specific individuals have been discussed and agreed upon as not being condusive to the productive execution of this operation. Specifically, the Sentinels will seek to hire:\<br\>\\r\\nMiss Xena Al-Bahr \& certain other members of the House Rinaldi\<br\>\\r\\nCommander Khagra Rhashak and mercenaries of Clan Rhashak\<br\>\\r\\nMister Chesh Veressen and mercenaries of CV Mercenary Company\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nVI. Import Agreement: Upon completion of operations, the Avoirdupois shall arrange for the import of 5 shipments of steel. \<br\>\\r\\na. Imports may be escorted personally by Captain Rhys or via Avoirdupois merchant shipping to the Triskellian auction house.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nVII. Casualties: The Avoirdupois take no responsibility for personnel losses. Should Miss Xena Al-Bahr's ship be captured, destroyed or irrepairably damaged during operations, it is agreed that she will be provided with a new one of like make and quality.\<br\>\\r\\na. Rights to salvage shall remain with miss Xena Al-Bahr.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nVIII. Handling of Privateers: Privateers shall be logged as such and held as criminals.\<br\> \\r\\na. Privateers holding letters of marque \& reprisal from Bisclavret lords shall first be submitted to Captain Rhys for judgment regarding the legality of their investment and to ensure they are operating within the limits of their investments. After judgment these prisoners will similarly be turned over to the Avoirdupois embassy. Justice will not be taken by Captain Rhys on theses privateers deemed to be outside of their investments unless these privateers until after judgment and punishment has been handed down from the House Avoirdupois, unless they are deemed to be special circumstances\<br\>\\r\\nb. Privateers holding letters of marque from any other House or Lord shall be held as criminals and submitted to the Avoirdupois embassy for justice.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nSECTION II:  THE SENTINELS COMMIT TO\<br\>\\r\\nI. The Sentinels will commit to the capture of all hostile pirate personnel which can be reasonably subdued without excessive risk to the continued success of operations.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nII. The Sentinels will seek to extract information from any prisoner thought to be in possession of potentially valuable information. The Sentinels will share any information they obtain from prisoners with the Avoirdupois embassy, except;\<br\>\\r\\na. That which is extracted from prisoners held as 'special', except where that information will not interfere with future operations of the Sentinels.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIII. To maintain good order and the general health of all captured personnel and prepare rosters for the Avoirdupois Embassy, and to surrender all personnel not held to be 'special prisoners' to the Avoirdupois upon the return to Triskellian.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIV. To catalogue and ship all captured cargo back to Triskellian. The Avoirdupois embassy will be entitled to 75% of the total value of all captured cargo while the remainder will be allotted to the Sentinels for distribution as incentive payment to any or all participating parties. Whereas; the Sentinels will be awarded all captured vessels, the Avoirdupois maintain the right to make the first offer on all captured vessels - no reasonable offer may be refused.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nV. Should the ships under Captain Rhys' command willingly resort to piracy this contract will be null and void in full, and all members who do, in fact, commit acts of piracy following such shall be treated as pirates. In no instance shall this contract be seen as a letter of marque and reprisal.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nVI. Captain Rhys agrees to execute the agreements of this contract both in letter and the spirit of the terms.\<br\>\\r\\nIt is signed, \\"Captain Veritas Rhys\\", by Veritas.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nDear Mister Veritas Rhys,\<br\>\\r\\nI hereby formally agree to the revised contract dated 9 Thunder 891, entitled Contract outline: The House Avoirdupois: Pirate Hunting.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nFunds, to the value of five hundred denarii, for the advance payment, have been sent to your account, as per the contract quoted verbatim below.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nA maximum of twenty-five hundred (2500) denarii paid directly to the Sentinels coffers for preparation and execution expenses and to cover personnel costs, of which five hundred (500) denarii shall be paid in advance of the expedition and the remainder shall be paid, as a measure of the success of operations, based on the tonnage of ships captured and sunk during operations.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nGood luck, and may the Light bless you all in your noble endeavors to rid us of this menace,\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIt is signed, \\"Yours sincerely, on behalf of the Avoirdupois Embassy\\", by Sir Brooks.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</i\>\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Tokens" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Rings" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<center\>\<b\>The Sentinels Mercenary Trading Company\</b\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThe Sentinels Mercenary Trading Company (The Company) prides itself on providing the highest quality, most diverse mercenary services. The Company only employs mercenaries of the best spirit. Sentinels will never break from combat without being ordered. The Company is required by code to offer its services to all - prices, however, will vary significantly based on the desired services. Only those with outstanding debt are excluded until such time that debt is paid.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nWhen being employed outside of the Company, Sentinels may wear the uniform or colors of their current employer and/or fight with that employer's regulars for an additional fee. Neither The Company nor soldiers in our employ will, under any circumstances, swear an oath of loyalty to an individual, organization, House or any other entity. The Sentinels pledge temporary loyalty to their employers via contract \<b\>ONLY\</b\>. All mercenaries employed by the Sentinels have sworn sole loyalty to The Company and uphold the values and creed of the Free Companies. Mercenaries wishing to leave The Company will be provided with a summary of their service and acknowledgement of satisfaction of that oath.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe Company is completely loyal to all of our contractual agreements. The Company will always uphold the terms of contract under any and all circumstances. Should an employer breach the terms of a contract, the Company, or individual soldiers working for the Company are required to request formal absolution from the contract from the employer. If the employer refuses to release the Company from the broken contract, the Company will seek mediation from the Mercenary Assembly, requesting acknowledgement that the contract has been broken, that it is no longer legally binding, and that the Company is no longer bound to serve the contract. If an individual soldier is serving a Company sanctioned contract either the Company itself or the Mercenary Assembly may act as the mediator. In either case, there shall be a reasonable attempt to seat all parties (the employer, the employed and the mediator) for final negotiations. If the employer refuses, or does not respond, the employed and the mediator may proceed without them.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nEmployers who breach a contract remain eligible to contract the Company, usually pending stricter guidelines (such as payment in advance, etc.), unless specifically black listed. The Company is required to offer its services to the Employer immediately after settlement of a broken contract, outlining new contractual agreements. If the employer declines, does not answer or refuses the offer the business is considered to be concluded and the Company or individual may seek new contracts.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIn no instance will the Company or individuals in our employ simultaneously assume mutually exclusive contracts. Though discouraged, individual members not serving an open Company contract may assume a contract that is in conflict with the Company. All contracts must be formally dissolved or satisfied in order to be considered concluded, and new contracts signed.\<br\>\<br\> \\r\\nThe Company keeps a record of all Company sanctioned contracts which it and each individual in it are serving. These records are available upon request by parties wishing to contract our services.\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<hr\>\<br\>\\r\\nThose seeking contracts with The Sentinels should contact Veritas Rhys or an authorized contracting agent.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Contracting Agents:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nSardis\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\<b\>Blacklisted organizations need not apply:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe Embassy of and House Doloreaux\\r\\n\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "page", "\<hr\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nMain Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:indicateur">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:oath of service">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Oath of service is for your protection. It prevents you from swearing any other oaths to any entity instead allowing you to exclusively work for an employer through the use of contracts. That being said, those contracting your services should not purposefully be misled into thinking you will swear loyalty to them, nor should you ever take another oath while in the employ of the Company. The Company allows for the oath of service to be satisfied relatively easy. You will, however, lose all of the legal defense provided by the Company when doing so. To satisfy your oath contact an officer and make sure to write the Captain directly as well. Any service you have done for the company will be committed to paper and delievered to you to present to future employers." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:official documents">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<hr\>\\r\\nOn [Day], the [Date] day of [Month] in the [Year] Apres le Miracle at [0000] hours, and;\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nBy the authority of Captain Veritas Rhys, Commander, Sentinels Mercenary \& Trading Company; \\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nIn recognition of loyal and diligent execution of duties, while continually acting in the service of the Sentinels Free Company and effective immediately, [Soldiers Full Name] is hereby promoted to the rank of [New Rank]. This rank supercede all prior inferior appointments.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nThe soldier will promptly assume the duties of his or her new rank. All soldiers of lesser military rank within the company, regardless of social standing, are expected to follow the chain of command as it is affected by this promotion.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nCaptain Veritas Rhys,\<br\>\\r\\nCommanding,\<br\>\\r\\nSentinels Mercenary \& Trading Company\<br\>\\r\\nSentinels Free Company\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:ooc">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 4 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nFirearm information: The list below outlines the standard prices which firearms and explosives may be purchased for via the Sentinels, for use within the Sentinels. Most firearms require a tax to be paid, which is added on top of the cost. Firearms cannot generally be sold to individuals outside of the company, and should an individual that has possession of a company firearm leave the company, they must surrender the firearm or be subject to arrest and seizure.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nTax Exempt:\<br\>\\r\\nSmooth bore muzzle-loading iron cannon - 2880d\<br\>\\r\\nSmooth bore muzzle-loading cast bronze cannon - 4320d\<br\>\\r\\nSmooth bore muzzle-loading steel cannon - 7200d\<br\>\\r\\nGrenade (1/8ths) - 24d\<br\>\\r\\nPetard -\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n12% tax:\<br\>\\r\\nSteel pistol (any lock except snaphaunce)- 108d\<br\>\\r\\nSnaphaunce pistol mechanism - 48d\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n15% tax:\<br\>\\r\\nSteel musket (any lock except snaphaunce)- 130d\<br\>\\r\\nSteel fusil (any lock except snaphaunce)- 88d\<br\>\\r\\nSnaphaunce musket mechanism - 48d\<br\>\\r\\n\</font\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:overview">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Employee Overview\</h3\>\\r\\nThe purpose of this section is to help familiarize employees with the history and practices of the Company.\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:special trading deals">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "h3", "Special Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\nSome individuals that do business with us prefer to remain anonymous. Given that this can clearly turn into a logistics problem we use certain techniques to keep order over this sort of business. Limiting those with access to our special trading deals is one of those techniques. It's important to note that these deals are to be conducted under the most secret circumstances possible, as to not put our company at odds with any other guilds or Houses in the city.\<br\>\<br\> \\r\\nThis means that the contacts shown here are told they will be working with a third party. The Sentinels take no responsibility for bringing anything listed here into the city, we don't directly accept money for them (even to 'pass it on') and we certainly are not the ones importing it.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nGenerally payment is required in full prior to delievery - denarii only. Under no circumstances are notes or kitty transfers acceptable. The Sentinels arrange for our private dealer to make initial contact with target, they negotiate the details and if an agreement is reached the dealer either walks away with the money or sets a time and place to meet for the money. Negotiations, transfers and delivers are always done by the same individual, masked \& -NOT- in uniform. Anyone who breaks any of these rules will never be trusted on this sort of mission again, and is likely to be removed from the company.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIndividuals may be listed for anything they like, when submitting their list it should be written and left unsigned, or ended with an alias. When added to this page, the individuals name/alias should be used. The serving Captain has exclusive rights to decide what we absolutely will not trade in.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>Captain Rhys' Directive:\</b\>\<br\>\\r\\nUnder this captaincy we will not under any circumstances deal in goods, publicly or otherwise, which might put us at odds with our Rinaldi hosts, with the sole exception being gunpowder. Additionally, as long as we remain on good terms with the House Bisclavret, through our ally Squire Donatella Tonozzi, the company will not bring in any lumber without the explicit authorization and request of their embassy.\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Forza\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Forza's have exclusive rights to all steel for armor purposes. The price for common, good quality steel is currently 500 denarii.\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Controlled Substance - Breeding Potion\</h3\>\\r\\nIt is widely rumored that there is a potion which allows individuals of completely different species to create offspring together. There are several cases of individuals of different species mating and creating offspring, though there is no solid evidence that this Company possesses that surrogates were not used to create these offspring.\<br\>\\r\\nRegardless, we endeavor to discover the truth of if this is possible and, if it is, then we will continually seek to uncover the secret of creating such a potion.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nIt is important to note that the official stance of every House as well as the Church can be assumed to be against this concoction. Hence the fact that we are researching this field and, should we succeed, our distribution of the potion is of the utmost secret nature.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nSo far through the investigative work of miss Gemma we have uncovered a fairly basic list of ingredients. We have also heard vague mentioning that the process is highly dangerous, though whether that is because of the violatility of mixing the ingredients, the Churches condemnation of it, or some other reason remains unclear. The ingredients are as follows:\<br\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\<li\>Witchmoss\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Purple Garmflower\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>A gold skink\</li\>\</ul\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Irene\</h3\>\\r\\nMiss Irene Stafline requests the following varieties of nuts. Only import in quantities which would be at least semi-profitable. Order of preference is as follows:\<br\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\nWalnuts, Cashew, Pecans, Hazelnuts, Macadamias, Pine, Pistachios, Almonds,Chestnuts, Sunflower\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:teachers">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 4 \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Company Teachers\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nThe Company endeavors to have the best trained individuals in all fields which we excel. Ciprian will teach a fair amount of skills; However, everyone is encouraged to work together to supplement eachother's training. Take advantage of the knowledge your companions are able to give you. Don't waste money that could help support the company when others can train you free of charge. Everyone is requested to add the knowledge they're willing to share below.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Ciprian\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\nCiprian is our Company trainer - released from his contract prematurely by our good friends in the Eastern Mercenary Company so he could come work with us. If you have a request for something specific you'd like him to teach feel free to contact the Captain and the two of them will negotiate getting it added to what he teaches us. Skills, trades and professions that are not taught well by other employees will take priority, if it becomes necessary.\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<u\>Ciprian currently teaches\</u\>: \<i\>Gun, Offense, Precision; Blacksmith, Buccaneer, Carpenter, Dilettante, Mercenary, Merchant, Musketeer, Pirate, Scholar, Soldier, Squire.\</i\>\</b\>\<br\>\<br\>\\r\\nThe following individuals are authorized to use guild funds to train with Ciprian. Everyone else is encouraged to find these individuals if they need training in that particular area.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Grimclaw\</i\>\</b\>: Mercenary \& Soldier.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Inolia\</i\>\</b\>: Translator \& Scholar.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Iolanthe \& Jace\</i\>\</b\>: Dilettante \& Squire.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Sardis\</i\>\</b\>: Merchant.\<br\>\\r\\n\<b\>\<i\>Veritas\</i\>\</b\>: Pirate.\<br\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\</font\>" \}), (\{ "text", "\<font face=\\"Times New Roman\\"\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Veritas\</b\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<ul\>\<li\>Soldier (level 10)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Mercenary (level 10)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Pirate (level 7)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dodge (level 16)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dagger (level 6)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Sword (level 20)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Wolf (level 8)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Signing (level 1)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Eastern (level 8)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Endurance (level 2)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Gun (level 8)\</li\>\</ul\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<h3\>\<center\>\<b\>Grimclaw\</b\>\</center\>\</h3\>\\r\\n\<center\>\<ul\>\<li\>Soldier (level 12)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Mercenary (level 12)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Scholar (level 4)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Wolf (level 8)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Signing (level 1)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Defense (level 7)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Parry (level 7)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Sword (level 24)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Armor (level 7)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Dodge (level 15)\</li\>\\r\\n\<li\>Offensive (level 7)\</li\>\</ul\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\</font\>\<br\>\<br\>\<br\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Tokens" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
