<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:crafting">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 6 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Evander is currently the only craftsman within the Guild, making furniture and weaponry." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:current cases">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "npc_tokens", "" \}), (\{ "ring_listing", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Weaponry available" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Axe\\r\\nSpear\\r\\nSword\\r\\nMace\\r\\nStaff\\r\\n---\\r\\nSheathes available" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:informants listing">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Marsali\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:other services">
         (\{ (\{ 5, 1 \}), (\{ "text", "\<body background=\\"http://fc05.deviantart.com/fs8/i/2005/292/e/a/matches_box_magnifying_glass___by_w00mbat.jpg\\" text=\\"#color\\" link=\\"#color\\" vlink=\\"#color\\"\>\\r\\n\<sidebar width=\\"16%\\" link=\\"#color\\" vlink=\\"#color\\" alink=\\"#color\\"\> \<table align=\\"left\\" width=\\"16%\\" border=\\"0\\"\> \<tr\> \<td\> \\r\\n\<a href=\\"http://URL Here\\"\>Collections\</a\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<a href=\\"http://URL Here\\"\>Crafting\</a\>\\r\\n\<hr\>\\r\\n\<a href=\\"http://URL Here\\"\>Escorts\</a\>\</td\>\</tr\>\</table\>\</sidebar\>\\r\\n" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:privacy clause">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "Triskellian Detective Agency Privacy Agreement" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Those of the Triskellian Detective Agency agree to keep all client names, their business with the Agency and all provided information private. Should it be discovered that a member of the Agency shared any information with someone outside of the Agency it is agreed that such action is Breach of Contract. If a Breach of Contract has been made, it is considered equal to unpayable debt and the offender will be arrested with the request of the Agency that they be given to Slavery. " \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:sample contracts">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 1 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\\r\\n\\r\\n         We are pleased to set forth in this agreement (the \\"Agreement\\") the\\r\\nterms of the retention of Triskelian Investigations. (the \\"Consultant\\") by Evander Gray and his affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, the\\r\\n\\"Company\\").\\r\\n\\r\\n         1. The Consultant will act as the non-exclusive consultant to the\\r\\nCompany, and will, subject to the provisions hereinafter set forth:\\r\\n\\r\\n              (a)  Render investment banking and financial advisory services to\\r\\n                   the Company, including assisting in the development and\\r\\n                   structuring of a corporate financing and acquisition strategy\\r\\n                   for the Company. The Company and the Consultant will execute\\r\\n                   engagement letters or letters of intent at the appropriate\\r\\n                   time in connection with specific transactions for which the\\r\\n                   Consultant will be entitled to receive compensation; and\\r\\n\\r\\n              (b)  Any other matter as may be mutually agreed upon by the\\r\\n                   Consultant and the Company.\\r\\n\\r\\n         In connection with the Consultant's activities on the Company's behalf,\\r\\nthe Consultant will familiarize itself with the business, operations, properties\\r\\nand financial condition of the Company. Nothing contained in this Agreement\\r\\nshall require the Consultant to render a fairness opinion to the Company.\\r\\n\\r\\n         2. If the Company requests that the Consultant assist the Company in\\r\\nany debt or equity financing for the Company, or in any acquisition by, or\\r\\nrecapitalization of, the Company, in any form, including but not limited to any\\r\\nmerger, consolidation, stock or asset acquisition or divestiture, any such\\r\\nfurther action by the Consultant will be subject to a separate agreement\\r\\ncontaining provisions and terms to be mutually agreed upon but in any event\\r\\nshall be subject to the provisions of paragraph 10 below. The Consultant's\\r\\ncompensation for any such services shall be separately identified in such other\\r\\nagreement, and shall be in addition to the compensation set forth in paragraph 4\\r\\nbelow.\\r\\n\\r\\n         3. In connection with the Consultant's activities on the Company's\\r\\nbehalf, the Company will cooperate with the Consultant and will furnish the\\r\\nConsultant with all information and data concerning the Company which the\\r\\nConsultant reasonably believes appropriate to its assignment (all such\\r\\ninformation so furnished being the \\"Information\\") and will provide the \\r\\n\\r\\n\<PAGE\>\\r\\n\\r\\nTriskelian Investigations\\r\\n\\r\\nConsultant with access to the Company's officers, directors, employees,\\r\\nindependent accountants and legal counsel. The Company recognizes and confirms\\r\\nthat the Consultant (a) will use and rely primarily on the Information and on\\r\\ninformation available from generally recognized public sources in performing the\\r\\nservices contemplated by this Agreement, without having independently verified\\r\\nsame, (b) does not assume responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of the\\r\\nInformation and such other information and (c) will not make an independent\\r\\nappraisal of any of the Company's assets. The Information to be furnished by the\\r\\nCompany, when delivered, will be true and correct in all material respects and\\r\\nwill not contain any material misstatement of fact or omit to state any material\\r\\nfact necessary to make the statements contained therein not misleading. The\\r\\nCompany will promptly notify the Consultant if it learns of any material\\r\\ninaccuracy or misstatement in, or material omission from, any information\\r\\ntheretofore delivered to the Consultant. The Consultant agrees to keep\\r\\nconfidential and not disclose, without the Company's prior written consent, any\\r\\nInformation delivered to the Consultant by the Company that the Company has\\r\\nidentified in writing as not publicly available and confidential for a period of\\r\\nsix months after termination of this Agreement.\\r\\n\\r\\n         4. In addition to the fees described in paragraph 10 herein, the\\r\\nCompany agrees to reimburse the Consultant, upon request from time to time, for\\r\\nreasonable out-of-pocket expenses incurred (including, but not limited to,\\r\\ntravel and other costs, reasonable fees and disbursements of counsel, and of\\r\\nother consultants and Consultants retained by the Consultant).\\r\\n\\r\\n         5. The Company agrees to the indemnification and other agreements set\\r\\nforth in the Indemnification Agreement attached hereto, the provisions of which\\r\\nare incorporated herein by reference and shall survive the termination of this\\r\\nAgreement.\\r\\n\\r\\n         6. This Agreement shall commence on the date hereof and continue for a\\r\\nperiod of two years. Either party hereto may terminate this Agreement at any\\r\\ntime after one year from the date hereof upon three months prior written notice,\\r\\nwithout liability or continuing obligation to you (except for our\\r\\nconfidentiality obligations) or to us (except for any compensation earned, or\\r\\nexpenses incurred, by us up to the date of termination) and except as set forth\\r\\nin paragraphs 4, 5 and 10.\\r\\n\\r\\n         7. This Agreement will be governed by, and construed in accordance\\r\\nwith, the laws of Triskelian applicable to agreements made and to be\\r\\nfully performed therein. If Any portion of this contract is revealed, made known to Law enforcement or other un-related parties, it will result in forfeiture of freedoms defined by local law and under the direction of the Zeiss slave company\\r\\n\\r\\n         8. The benefits of this Agreement shall inure to the parties hereto and\\r\\ntheir respective successors and assigns, and the obligations and liabilities\\r\\nassumed in this Agreement by the parties hereto shall be binding upon their\\r\\nrespective successors and assigns.\\r\\n\\r\\n         9. For the convenience of the parties hereto, any number of\\r\\ncounterparts of this Agreement may be executed by the parties hereto. Each such\\r\\ncounterpart shall be, and shall be deemed to be, an original instrument, but all\\r\\nsuch counterparts taken together shall constitute one and the same Agreement.\\r\\nThis Agreement may not be modified or amended except in writing signed by the parties hereto.\\r\\n\\r\\n         If the foregoing correctly sets forth our Agreement, please sign the\\r\\nenclosed copy of this letter in the space provided and return it to us.\\r\\n\\r\\n                                       Very truly yours,\\r\\n\\r\\n                                      Triskelian Investigations.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n                                       By: Evander Gray\\r\\n                                          -------------------------------------\\r\\n                                          Evander Gray, Founder\\r\\n\\r\\nAGREED TO AND ACCEPTED:\\r\\n\\r\\nTriskelian Investigations, hereby accepts the terms and\\r\\nprovisions of, and agrees to be bound by the terms\\r\\nand provisions of the foregoing letter, as of this ____\\r\\n                                                    Day\\r\\nday of ____,    _____.\\r\\n        Month     Year\\r\\n\\r\\nTriskelian Investigations.\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\nBy: \\r\\n   -----------------------------------------\\r\\n   Name:\\r\\n   Title:\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:solved cases">
         (\{ (\{ 3, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Nothing has been added to this page yet." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
