<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:company policy">
         (\{ (\{ 1, 2 \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h2", "Teatime Discretionary Contractual Company" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Teatime Contractual Company is a privately-owned, unaffiliated organization which has dedicated itself to acting as third-party agents on behalf of any Greater or Lesser House, guild, or organization able to provide the appropriate funds or equivalent goods. The Company prides itself on dependability and loyalty, while at the same time maintaining enough distance from it's employers to ensure that any unpleasant entanglements are a complete nonentity. \\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "The Teatime Company is, has, and always shall be amongst the finest and most discreet, professional groups on the market. It is not a conspiracy of cut-throat merchants and thieves looking to turn a profit, nor is it a gang of illiterate criminals thinly-hid behind the facade of reputable business, nor is it even a band of bloodthirsty mercenaries after coin and violence. The Company promises discresion, honor, and above all else, class.\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Contracts are currently up for sale to respectable patrons, as are positions for hopeful members. If you wish to hire the Company's services, send a scroll addressed to Alessia with a your name and a completely-refundable processing fee of ten denarii. If you are looking for employment, simply send a scroll with a full list of your skills and qualifications.\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Background checks will be made as a matter of policy. Some restrictions may be applicable" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
