<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="page:blacklist">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<h2\>\<center\>Blacklist\</center\>\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<center\>The following individuals have been blacklisted from the services of The Dukes Century. Crewmembers are strongly encouraged to avoid all association with these troublesome individuals, including business matters.\</center\>\\r\\n" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:crew information">
         (\{ (\{ 3, 2 \}), (\{ "h2", "\<center\>Crew Information\</center\>" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<h3\>Behaviour, Duties and Etiquette\</h3\>\\r\\n\<b\>All\</b\> members of the crew are expected to perform their required duties, that their position entails. Whilst docked in port, your time is your own...however, respect the laws, customs and residents. Any lapse in proper etiquette, or failure to respect ones betters will result in a tempoary reduction in wages, for the first offense. Suspended pay for two weeks for the second, and complete and utter termination for the third offense. \<b\>I expect my crew to uphold, maintain and display the Honor of this ship, and themselves.\</b\>\\r\\n\<br\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Appearance\</h3\>\\r\\nMembers of this ship are expected to maintain a well-kept, and dignified appearance while in port. This means that hair, beards and claws must be trimmed and groomed on a regualar basis, and clothing must be neat, and acceptable. Any noticeable dirt and/or offensive aromas must be tended to immediately. (If your style of dress is apart of your culture, such as a loincloth...please let me know, so I can take it into consideration.)\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:default">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 3 \}), (\{ "h3", "Members List" \}), (\{ "members_list", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:guest">
         (\{ (\{ 2, 2 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "This is the guilds public page. The page has not yet been updated by a guild member." \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:the crew">
         (\{ (\{ 6, 1 \}), (\{ "h2", "\<center\>The Crew of the Dukes Century\</center\>" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}), (\{ "paragraph", "\<center\>\<b\>The Crew\</b\>\</center\>\\r\\n\<TABLE BORDER WIDTH=100% CELLPADDING=10 BORDER=1\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TH\>Title\</TH\>\\r\\n    \<TH\>Position\</TH\>\\r\\n    \<TH\>About\</TH\>\\r\\n    \</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Adonis D'Ellsadro\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Captain of the Dukes Century\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Adonis is a tall regal lion, with even, sleek silvery white fur, and long flowing midnight silver hair, left loose. Intense crystal blue eyes are set above a fine nose and a firm mouth, complete with sensual lips. Long sharp claws, on large hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his light eyebrows and round  ears.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Buck Eike\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>First Mate\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Buck is a towering husky malamute, with long, dense coal black fur, and long thick white hair, worn in a ponytail. He has sideburns which are silky. Bright azure eyes are set above a fine nose and a dour mouth, complete with thin lips. Long blunt claws, on strong hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his high  eyebrows and attentive  ears.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Svensgaard Ulrik\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Boatswain\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Svensgaard is a slim strapping arctic wolf, with short, sleek white fur, and long smooth white hair. He has a mustache and goatee which is short. Squinty sea-green eyes are set above a long nose and a large mouth. Long sharp claws, on strong hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his high  eyebrows, long  ears and prominent  muzzle.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Mortimer\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Dockhand\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Mort is an enormous broad-shouldered black bear, with short, smooth black fur, and medium shaggy sable hair. He has sideburns which is shaggy. Deep-set steel grey eyes are set above a blunt nose and a firm mouth, complete with thin lips. Short blunt claws, on large hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his wide  eyebrows and round  ears.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Sang Rouchambeau\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Musician\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Sang is a tall sleek fox, with wild, silky copper-colored fur, and light silver hair, worn in spikes. Gimlet emerald eyes are set above a chiseled nose and a cruel mouth, complete with sensual lips. Long tapered claws, on paint-stained hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his arched  eyebrows, pointed  ears and long silky alabaster-tipped  tail.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Anthicus Daratrazenoff\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Translator\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Anthicus is a tall rugged malamute, with long, smooth white fur, and shoulder-length silky black hair. He has a beard which is trimmed. Sharp harlequin eyes are set above a flaring nose and a full mouth, complete with sensual lips. Jagged hooked claws, on slender hands, and smooth feet are also visible. You also note his straight  eyebrows and expressive ears.\</TD\>\\r\\n\</TR\>\\r\\n\<TR\>\<TD\>\<CENTER\>Kai\</CENTER\>\</TD\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>\<CENTER\>Mercenary\</CENTER\>\\r\\n    \<TD\>Kai is a tall athletic panther, with short, sleek coal black fur, and short silky copper hair. Deep-set emerald eyes are set above a flaring nose and a cruel mouth, complete with full lips. Long sharp claws, on large hands, and large feet are also visible. You also note his arched  eyebrows, large  ears and long silky  tail.\</TD\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n\\r\\n" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="page:trading">
         (\{ (\{ 4, 3 \}), (\{ "paragraph", "Guild Trading" \}), (\{ "trading_notices", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Inventory" \}), (\{ "inventory", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Guild Trading Deals" \}), (\{ "trading_deals", "" \}), (\{ "h3", "Bidding Market" \}), (\{ "guild_bidding", "" \}), (\{ "page", "Main Page", "default" \}) \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1167789587, "tonyd", "X", 1167816846, "tonyd", "E", 1168080214, "tonyd", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
