<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="jominey">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Effects:UrEffect)"/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="effect:acquire-actor">
         X[S] A sharp pain shoots through your veins causing your heart to stop for a fleeting moment.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:cure-actor">
         X[S] A sudden warmth courses through your body as you once again become aware of your own thoughts and surroundings.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:cure-audience">
         X[S] \$(person)'s chest slowly heaves up and down indicating the return of life and breath.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:debug">0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:default_dosage">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:degrees">
         (\{ 12, "mild", 36, "moderate", 72, "severe", 146, "deadly" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:extension">
         \<Ironclaw:Effects:Poison:BloodPoisonDescriber\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:history">
         (\{ "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 19:16:13 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 19:27:11 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 19:37:36 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:15:52 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:30:37 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:32:39 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:38:44 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:50:48 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:51:09 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:51:21 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Mon Jan 10 20:51:32 2011", "StoryCoder Roo, Thu Jan 13 18:33:58 2011" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:name">
         "bloodpoison"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:random:base">3</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:severity_cap">
         149
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-chance">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-deadly">
         X[S] \{ You hear nothing but the flow of your own blood in your ears. Everything else is silent. \| No voice reaches you from the outside world. \| Where did all the colors go? They were here just a moment ago! \| Darkness claims your eyes for its very own reasons conquering your sight for its blind mistress. \| You can barely lift a finger. \| You are no longer able to keep awake. \| There is not an inch on you that is willing or capable to do any more work. \| The shapes and forms of your surroundsing lose all contrast and form, swaying and floating as the breeze guides them. \| All your muscles fall asleep and your mind is ready to join them. \| The air seems to be so thin, it can barely lift your chest with your breath. \| You are at the verge of fainting in a constant manner. \| Lead-heavy hands and feet battle your enervated muscles in a clear hope to find full contact to the horisontal ground. \| Without any difficulty your thoughts flow through your head, none of them sticking long enough around for you to make any sense of.  \| Your hear barely beats in its struggle to attempt the blood to flow through your veins. A weak bird's wings can stir a stonger storm then your heart's sorry excuse of fluttering. \| The world slowly sways and you float with your heavy body searching for a place where you can sink into sleep. \| Your lips' skin tersely dry as your staccato breath barely coats them in an insufficient breeze. Your swollen tongue void of any moisture uselessly drags over the cracked skin. \| The silent world swirls around you slowly still less and less impulse reaches you. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-mild">
         X[S] \{ A soft noise can be heard in the distance. \| The acoustics of this place are not overly impressive. \| For a moment, the content of your surroundings begins to blur. \| You feel somewhat weak. \| You begin to think on how nice it would be to lie down and sleep. \| Your mind urges you to rest, and your body seems to agree. \| Your limbs are beginning to feel like lead. \| Your head is almost featherly and your thoughts begin to freely flow, yet you can't manage to catch any of them. \| Your heart slows to a steady, rhythmic beat. \| The urge arises to moisten your drying lips. \| A strange heaviness claims your muscles only to remind you of your need for rest. \| You decide sleeping and lazing around is a good plan for the day. \| The contours of the objects around you seem to fade in and out. You find everything has taken on a certain dream-like quality. \| You are filled with a fleeting absence as your heart briefly forgets to accommodate some of its needed beats. \| A tingling sensation tickles the tips of your digits. \| You pause for a tick and your breath pauses with you. It's amazing how in sync your body is. \| The shapes around you become hazy as you faintly fade in and out of reality. \| You feel as if someone is running their fingers along the length of your back; consequently, a series of slow-creeping chills claim your spine. \| You think you see an insubstantial orb in the center of the room. It seems as though colors are gravitating toward the object, but when you attempt to focus it fades from your sight. \| Strange, you don't recall hearing crickets previous. What is that melancholy song in the distance? \| You feel as though your mouth has been stuffed with a handful of cotton balls. \| You can feel the blood faintly pulsing beneath your skin. \| You feel yourself slowly drifting to the song of your own heartbeat. \| A quiet/low ringing can be heard in the distance. \| You're so weary. Surely you can take a restful break without causing any commotion. \| Water...water...water. \| A tingling sensation radiates from your scalp all the way down to your toes. \| A coolness engulfs you like a mild onset of winter. \| Strange sounds are coming from nearby. \| Listen to your heart. One...two..three. One..two.. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-moderate">
         X[S] \{ You hear a constant buzzing. There must be a bee fluttering about somewhere. \| The acoustics in this place are quite terrible. You can hardly hear anything at all. \| As you look about, your peripheral vision loses all forms of contrast. A uniform mass of grey appears before your eyes. \| Blurry/Unclear/Dark spots suddenly mask your vision. \| You feel powerless. \| You should really consider getting some sleep. \| Your arms and feet seem to be weighed down with something. You can hardly manage yourself. \| Your head is so light and free, nothing stops the coming and passing of thoughts. \| Feeling relaxed, your heart slows in an increasing manner. \| You feel the need of moistening your dry lips. \| The world begins to grow quieter and quieter. \| You hone in on the soft lullabye your heart is playing. \| Tap, tap, tap. Tap, tap, tap. All you can hear is nearby tapping. \| A creeping numbness scales the mass of your body. \| For a fleeting moment you can see nothing but darkness. \| You should lay off the extra snacks. You're a lot heavier than you realize. \| Ooooh. You can feel the blood pulsing beneath your cold face. What an interesting sensation. \| You don't recall getting your nails painted, but look at that lovely summery blue. \| You think about the sea and all that glorious water. Ah, the beauty of unhindered thoughts. You can feel a slight hint of pain on your lips. \| A feeling of helplessness sweeps over you. \| You probably did something to deserve this, you know? \| You consider more and more the appeal of sleep. \| The wind seems to almost call out your name. Quiet sounds surround your ears, blocking all other noise. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-actor-severe">
         X[S] \{ Your ears are filled with a strong buzzing noice. \| You barely hear anything but the flood of your own blood in the ears. \| For a brief moment your vision blurs leaving but spots of uniform greyness to float before your eyes. \| Colors dull as grey claims victory over diversity coating everything in its monotom equality. \| You find it difficult to move. \| You should instantly find your bed. \| Every single muscle in your body longs for relaxation and rest. \| The thin air fills your lung leaving you thirsty of more. \| You feel blood leaving your body, all focused in your toes leaving you ligh-headed and dizzy. \| Your hands and feets are made of lead, they firmly drag you down in an attempt to touch the ground. \| Light in your head, thoughts are free to flow in and out, though less and less of them stick within. \| Your heart is slow and weak, beating in a quiet struggle to get the blood circled in your body. \| Your body demands its rest and is intent on forcing you on that. \| Your lips dry as your scattered breath occasionally coat them in a cool breeze. Your tongue void of any moisture uselessly drags over the cracked skin. \| The quit world swirls around you for a bit while little impulse reaches you. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-chance">
         1
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-deadly">
         X[S] \{ Frustratedly/Annoyedly/Startledly \$(person) rubs his ears with the vain attempt of hearing something. \| With a dull/startled/uncomprehending/confused expression on \$(person)'s face \$(person) tries to absorb the noises of \$(person)'s surroundings... in vain. \| \$(person) gains a sever squint on one of the eyes. \| The pupil of the \$(person) is expands almost entirely repressing the iris. \| The visible areas of the \$(person)'s skin take an obviously blue hued discoloration. \| Disorientedly the \$(person) tries to move \$(person)s eyes, which move in a slow motion. \| \$(person) errupts in a set of vast yawns. \| \$(person) slumps enervatedly. \| A deep pool of the \$(person)'s pupils blidnly reflect the surrounding. \| The eyeballs of the \$(person) start to dance a lively jig in \$(person)'s skull. \| \$(person) seems to be wasted as if \$(person) went without sleeping for days. \| Not even a crossbreed of coalas and sloths can appear as sleep deprived as the \$(person). \| \$(person) barely lifts \$(person)'s chest with \$(person)'s breath. \| The diffult to notice move of the chest indicates life clinging to the body of the \$(person). \| The jugular of the \$(person) shows a distant swaying as the weak heart struggles to keep the blood flowing in an obviously failing attempt. \| The \$(person)'s lips tersely dry as \$(person)'s staccato breath barely coats them in an insufficient breeze. \$(person)s swollen tongue void of any moisture uselessly drags over the cracked skin.
 \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-mild">
         X[S] \{ \$(person) flicks \$(person)s ears once. \| \$(person) seems to focus more, especially on sounds. \| \$(person) scans \$(environment) with a momentary confusion/unease/uncomprehension. \| The visible areas of the \$(person)'s skin are slightly discolored and pale. \| \$(person) barely/subtly yawns. \| The \$(person)'s eyeballs twitch once or twice. \| \$(person) appears to be somewhat sleepy. \| \$(person)'s eyes drift here-and-there as \$(person)'s attention seems to wander. \| The pace of the \$(person)s jugular slows, harmonising with the general decrease of \$(person)'s breath. \| With slow methodical movements, \$(person) attempts to bathe \$(person)'s lips in moisture. \| \$(person) slumps/leans forward. Traces of weariness line \$(person)'s face for a few short moments. \| \$(person) lazily shifts, indifferently observing the surroundings. \| \$(person)'s pupils dilate and constrict back and forth as \$(person) stares at the center of the room. \| \$(person) becomes strangely still for a few moments. \| \$(person) rubs \$(person)'s fingertips curiously. A perplexed look clouds \$(person)'s face. \| \$(person) halts mid-inhalation and stares blankly at the floor. \| \$(person)'s eyes briefly glaze over as they attempt to absorb the surroundings. \| \$(person) arches \$(person)'s back inwardly in response to an unseen stimuli. \| \$(person) leans forward to stare at the center of the room in an inquisitive manner. \$(person)'s eyes go round-and-round as they attempt to focus. \| \$(person)'s ears twitch faintly/somewhat. A sad expression gradually creeps over \$(person)'s face. \| \$(person) coughs repeatedly while searchingly skimming the area. \| \$(person) stares at \$(person)'s flesh for a short/small amount of time. \| \$(person)'s head lolls/slumps peacefully as \$(person)'s eyes partially close. \| \$(person) glances off into the distance. \| \$(person) slowly lies down and turns away from onlookers. \| \$(person) unintentionally drools. \| \$(person) mildly twitches from the head down to the toes. \| \$(person) trembles/shivers for a few moments. \| \$(person) glances to-and-fro in a suspicious fashion. \| \$(person) slowly inhales the surrounding air. A far-off look claims \$(person)'s face as \$(person) holds \$(person)'s breath. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-moderate">
         X[S] \{ \$(person) repeatedly flicks \$(person)'s ears. \| \$(person) visibly focuses on hearing things. \| \$(person) gains a cast on \$(person)s left/right eye. \| With a tentative expression \$(person) blinks in a repeated manner trying to focus \$(person)'s gaze on the surroundings. \| The visible areas of the \$(person)'s skin are somewhat discolored and faintly blue. \| The pupils of the \$(person) gradually expand. \| \$(person) moderately/somewhat yawns. \| The \$(person)'s eyeballs occasionally twitch. \| \$(person) appears to be quite sleepy. \| \$(person)'s lips grow dry and cracked as \$(person)'s constant, swooning breath contacts the sensitive skin. \| \$(person)'s eyelids droop heavily. \| \$(person)'s breath gradually slows to an unnatural, but steady, rhythm. \| \$(person) glances about in search of something. \| \$(person)'s body mostly relaxes as \$(person)'s limbs take on a limp appearance. \| \$(person) repeatedly rubs \$(person)'s eyes. \| \$(person) shifts uneasily beneath \$(person)'s weight. \| \$(person)'s face pales into a shade lighter than usual. \| \$(person)'s gaze drops to \$(person)'s fingernails. You notice they have taken on a light/pale blue tint. \| \$(person) uselessly attempts to lick \$(person)'s peeling lips. \| \$(person) withdraws more and more, becoming somewhat anti-social. \| \$(person) contemplatively/pensively frowns. \| \$(person) somehow/barely keeps \$(person)'s eyelids open. \| \$(person)'s ears stand up-right as \$(person) attempts to hone in on individual noises. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="effect:spontaneous-audience-severe">
         X[S] \{ With clear frustration \$(person) flicks \$(person)'s ears. \| \$(person) strongly focuses on hearing things. \| The eyes of the \$(person) became glassy/beady/matte/empty as \$(person) loses contact with the \$(environment) for a short while. \| Losing touch with reality \$(person) stops flicking \$(person)'s gaze left and right searching for any secure point to grasp. \| The visible areas of the \$(person)'s skin are moderately discolored playing in a blue hue. \| The pupil of the actor expands notably. \| \$(person) vastly/hugely yawns. \| The eyeballs of the \$(person) irregularly twitch and tremble. \| \$(person) appears to be sleep deprived. \| \$(person)'s breath slowed, lifting the chest just-so as a sign of life clinging within. \| \$(person) finds it hard to harmonise the individual bodyparts in their move. \| An odd daze came over the \$(person). \| The almost-trans-like daze never leaves the \$(person)'s expression. \| The \$(person)'s lips dry as \$(person)'s scattered breath occasionally coat them in a cool breeze. \$(person)s tongue void of any moisture uselessly drags over the cracked skin. \| The bloodstream of the actor moving of \$(person)'s jugular matches the \$(person)'s decaying breath. \}
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1282523727, "jominey", "E", 1282523738, "jominey", "E", 1282523808, "jominey", "E", 1282523823, "jominey", "E", 1282523984, "jominey", "E", 1282524004, "jominey", "E", 1282524215, "jominey", "E", 1282524711, "jominey", "E", 1282525212, "jominey", "E", 1282527193, "jominey", "E", 1282527791, "jominey", "E", 1282528016, "jominey", "E", 1282528195, "jominey", "E", 1282528457, "jominey", "E", 1282528607, "jominey", "E", 1282528615, "jominey", "E", 1282528817, "jominey", "E", 1282529022, "jominey", "E", 1282529055, "jominey", "E", 1282529252, "jominey", "E", 1294705721, "jominey", "E", 1294709543, "jominey", "E", 1294709912, "jominey", "E", 1294710626, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes>
      <Notes:Category cat="QA" catstate="Open">
        <Notes:Note ix="1098153724" state="Comment" user="zwoc">
           Sleepy effect. To add this effect on an object, add the Call() line below to the appropriate Merry reaction(s):
$["";/*     
  Call(${Ironclaw:Effects:Disease:SpiderItch}, "apply", $who: $actor, $severity: 5 + random(5));  
*/]
The $(severity) argument decides how strong the effect is. If you wish to make extra strong sleep effects, up the severity to e.g. 2.
        </Notes:Note>
      </Notes:Category>
    </Notes:Notes>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
