<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="1599)"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="1"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="1599"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="dec"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="december"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="review"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] --==The Rinascita Review, vol. 2, Dec 1, 1599==--\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Threat Sent to Rinascita By Feast Assassin (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Domenic’s Royal Address in Rinascita Announced (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gloria Stabs Arlo at German Consulate (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Expedition to Find Genvieve’s Father, Victims Found Dead (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Consulate Announces Glitter Ball (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Guild Advertisements (p. 7, 8)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the French, Scottish, English, Spanish, and the Italian Consulates. A major donation for this edition was made by Nix Orosedan of the Crimson Brotherhood Mercenary Company, so do business with him!***
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review (Dec 1, 1599)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] Threat Sent to Rinascita By Feast Assassin\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 23, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At the Piazza Vecchia fountain, Lady Agatha showed the assembled crowd a black box she found on the fountain, with a dead dove inside the box. The dead dove had a blood red ribbon tying a torn scroll to the bird's leg. The scroll’s message was incomplete.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Later, Lady Camellia brought a similar box she found in the post office, with a dead dove and partial scroll to the fountain. When combined, the two parts of the message read: “"When one claims to serve God, but motives are anything but... We're here, we're there, beside you watching through and through. We see you. Watch Out!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The symbol of the dove and the phrase “Watch Out!” match the engravings found on the arrows used by the assassin during the attack on Queen Mirielle and others at the Feast of Nations, hosted by King Domenic. Sir Matteo posted a notice regarding these clues and a threat to the assassin, calling them a coward.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The finished poem, eventually assembled by Sir Matteo, read:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;When one claims to serve God, but motives are anything but...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The friends become quite odd, and their ties slowly get cut.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Pride will lift noses and the finger pointing starts..\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;No matter how many roses, You're left with lonely hearts.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You try and try to start anew, but struggle is the way of life...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Just because your blood did spew, does not exempt you from this strife.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The world is not your oyster. If you never pay your due...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We're here, we're there, beside you watching through and through.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We see you.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Watch Out!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Domenic’s Royal Address in Rinascita Announced\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 25, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to the public boards, King Domenic will visit Rinascita for a Royal Address on December 5 at 9 in the evening. The address will take place in the Throne Room of the Royal Palace. Security is expected to be extensive, given the recent attacks, and guests are reminded that no bags, food, drink or weapons will be allowed. Guests are suggested to arrive at half past eight to allow time for security checks.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] Gloria Stabs Arlo at German Consulate!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 19, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the 19th of November, Gloria Sanchez wore a mask and approached the German consulate. When noise was heard outside the embassy, members went outside to discover Gloria wearing a mask. She said she needed to get into the embassy to warn someone, and upon entry she tried to run in. When she was stopped, Gloria became angry and said she wanted to leave. The German consulate members asked what she wanted, offered her food and tried to calm her. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At this time, she approached Arlo and stabbed him in the ribs with a steel dagger. Valeria disarmed her, and it is reported that Gloria was yelling about Germans. She was subdued, taken away to be treated, and taken away to a holding cell. Arlo was taken into the embassy to be treated, and is currently recovering from his wounds.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Guillen, of the Spanish Consulate, said:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“All members of the Spanish consulate are expected to conduct themselves in a civil and appropriate manner. As representatives of the Spanish people, we must constantly reflect upon our behavior to ensure that we are acting in the best interests of the consulate as a whole, which Senorita Sanchez most assuredly was not. Unprovoked acts of violence against any group of people will not be tolerated, regardless of any personal animosity that one may feel. To reiterate from my public posting, Senorita Sanchez' actions reflect the sentiments of neither the Spanish consulate nor the Spanish people.”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Trevyn, of the German Consulate, said:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The German Consulate does not condone such acts of violence against anyone, much less the members therein. However, we do not hold the actions of a single person against the Spanish Consulate. We will enedeavor to find the reasoning for the senseless acts of this person through investigation. We will also continue to welcome people who wish to visit and learn more of our glorious Country and Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Expedition to Find Genvieve’s Father, Victims Found Dead\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 26, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir Matteo led a group that include Diego, Persephone and others on an expedition to find Genvieve’s father in the outlands beyond the city gates. Genvieve reported that her family was traveling in a black carriage with gold trimming when they were accosted on the road to Rinascita by bandits. Unfortunately, when the group located Genvieve’s father and driver they were both found dead. The victims were killed by arrows and had their throats slit. According to Sir Matteo, the attack occurred 3-4 miles northwest of the city, just hours before the King’s Feast was attacked by assassins.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] French Consulate Announces Glitter Ball\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 27, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline announced an upcoming social event which will take place on December 15th: “At 9 o’clock in the evening on Sunday the 15th of December, the French will host the “Glitter Ball” to celebrate the holiday season. You are encouraged to bring one small, wrapped gift for the gift exchange portion of the event as well as one simple winter weather garment to dispense to the needy throughout the city as cold weather will be well set in by then. Please wear your most colorful, sparkling or stunning formal wear. Food and drink as well as entertainment will be provided.” The French Consulate requests that guests RSVP, and formal invitations will be sent to all of the fellow Consulates.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gus Calls Sir Matteo a Coward\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 23, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Sir Matteo, he was delivering a package to Genvieve and Persephone when he became the target of rude looks from Gus. This escalated, with Gus challenging Sir Matteo to fight and calling him a coward. Sir Matteo said he was not in proper condition to fight, and that he could not accept a challenge from Gus. When interviewed the following day, Sir Matteo said he still had time to challenge Gus. Gus did not respond to the Rinascita Review’s request for comment.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] Lady Emmaline’s Speech and Gathering\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 24, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Writ on behalf of Lady Emmaline Beaumont, Vicontesse and Ambassador of the Consulate of France; On the 24th of November in the year of Our Lord 1599, Lady Beaumont will assemble with the key members of the French Consulate at the Piazza Vecchia fountain for a series of announcements regarding current and upcoming events. The Consulate will then proceed to the gathering hall located to the west of the fountain for a general audience with those who have business to attend with the members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Despite warnings that Lady Emmaline was a potential target of the recent assassination threats, the announcement went on as scheduled. She delivered a thoughtful speech at the fountain, which covered themes of unity against the assassin’s threats, gratitude toward Sir Matteo Medici’s efforts, mourning with Spain over their death, and a blessing from God.  Following Lady Emmaline’s remarks, the French Ambassador hosted a get-together in the gathering hall which was well attended. The guests enjoyed wine, snacks and good company for a few hours before everyone parted ways.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir Matteo and Italian Consulate Announce Trial by Fire Tournament\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 30, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;As announced by Sir Matteo on the public posting boards: “There will be a special tournament hosted by the Italian Consulate and will be held December 6th through 8th in the Colosseum! All melee competitors are invited to compete for a purse of 500 Florins to the sole Champion. The event shall be held each evening starting at 8:00 in the evening and registrations end 7:55 in the evening December 6th. Being that this event is held at night the outer ring of the floor of the Colosseum will be lit with fire-pits to create a much different atmosphere than anything we've done before! Attendees are welcome to come and cheer on their favored champions and are encouraged to give a token to those this wish to see win!”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate Updates
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] Orla Volunteers to Sponsor New Guilds\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 20, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Per Orla’s announcement on the public boards: “I am currently offering to help purchase guild charters and or give each -new- guild florins to start their business. There was once a time in this city when there was a guild for every craft, when -some- consulates did not monopolize crafts. However, I understand it is not always easy to establish a guild on your own. So myself along with other seasoned guilds and even other consulates offer to aid you with this. Not only do we offer florins, but we offer our time and experience should you desire it. Connections that will help your craft and advertisement of your craft and guild. Please do contact Orla Couture should you wish to learn to be your own boss! Furthermore, if being a leader is not your preference I can provide a list of guilds that can assist you with lessons as well as be among others of your craft.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Recently Created Guilds:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Catania Healing (Persephone)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Master Stoneworks (Waylon)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Crimson Brotherhood Mercenary company offers its services to any and all individuals. No task too great nor too small, the Brotherhood will help you with it all. Should you have any questions seek Nix Orosedan, notably spotted by his crimson sword. For those looking for a job without long term agreements, the company is also hiring.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring informants, writers and salespeople. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Salvatore"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         2
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1575227101
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1575383670, "sendnoodlez", "K" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] --==The Rinascita Review, vol. 2, Dec 1, 1599==--\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Threat Sent to Rinascita By Feast Assassin (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Domenic’s Royal Address in Rinascita Announced (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gloria Stabs Arlo at German Consulate (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Expedition to Find Genvieve’s Father, Victims Found Dead (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Consulate Announces Glitter Ball (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Guild Advertisements (p. 7, 8)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the French, Scottish, English, Spanish, and the Italian Consulates. A major donation for this edition was made by Nix Orosedan of the Crimson Brotherhood Mercenary Company, so do business with him!***
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review (Dec 1, 1599)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] Threat Sent to Rinascita By Feast Assassin\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 23, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At the Piazza Vecchia fountain, Lady Agatha showed the assembled crowd a black box she found on the fountain, with a dead dove inside the box. The dead dove had a blood red ribbon tying a torn scroll to the bird's leg. The scroll’s message was incomplete.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Later, Lady Camellia brought a similar box she found in the post office, with a dead dove and partial scroll to the fountain. When combined, the two parts of the message read: “"When one claims to serve God, but motives are anything but... We're here, we're there, beside you watching through and through. We see you. Watch Out!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The symbol of the dove and the phrase “Watch Out!” match the engravings found on the arrows used by the assassin during the attack on Queen Mirielle and others at the Feast of Nations, hosted by King Domenic. Sir Matteo posted a notice regarding these clues and a threat to the assassin, calling them a coward.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The finished poem, eventually assembled by Sir Matteo, read:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;When one claims to serve God, but motives are anything but...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The friends become quite odd, and their ties slowly get cut.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Pride will lift noses and the finger pointing starts..\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;No matter how many roses, You're left with lonely hearts.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;You try and try to start anew, but struggle is the way of life...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Just because your blood did spew, does not exempt you from this strife.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The world is not your oyster. If you never pay your due...\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We're here, we're there, beside you watching through and through.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We see you.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Watch Out!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Domenic’s Royal Address in Rinascita Announced\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 25, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to the public boards, King Domenic will visit Rinascita for a Royal Address on December 5 at 9 in the evening. The address will take place in the Throne Room of the Royal Palace. Security is expected to be extensive, given the recent attacks, and guests are reminded that no bags, food, drink or weapons will be allowed. Guests are suggested to arrive at half past eight to allow time for security checks.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] Gloria Stabs Arlo at German Consulate!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 19, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;On the 19th of November, Gloria Sanchez wore a mask and approached the German consulate. When noise was heard outside the embassy, members went outside to discover Gloria wearing a mask. She said she needed to get into the embassy to warn someone, and upon entry she tried to run in. When she was stopped, Gloria became angry and said she wanted to leave. The German consulate members asked what she wanted, offered her food and tried to calm her. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At this time, she approached Arlo and stabbed him in the ribs with a steel dagger. Valeria disarmed her, and it is reported that Gloria was yelling about Germans. She was subdued, taken away to be treated, and taken away to a holding cell. Arlo was taken into the embassy to be treated, and is currently recovering from his wounds.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Guillen, of the Spanish Consulate, said:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“All members of the Spanish consulate are expected to conduct themselves in a civil and appropriate manner. As representatives of the Spanish people, we must constantly reflect upon our behavior to ensure that we are acting in the best interests of the consulate as a whole, which Senorita Sanchez most assuredly was not. Unprovoked acts of violence against any group of people will not be tolerated, regardless of any personal animosity that one may feel. To reiterate from my public posting, Senorita Sanchez' actions reflect the sentiments of neither the Spanish consulate nor the Spanish people.”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Ambassador Trevyn, of the German Consulate, said:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The German Consulate does not condone such acts of violence against anyone, much less the members therein. However, we do not hold the actions of a single person against the Spanish Consulate. We will enedeavor to find the reasoning for the senseless acts of this person through investigation. We will also continue to welcome people who wish to visit and learn more of our glorious Country and Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Expedition to Find Genvieve’s Father, Victims Found Dead\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 26, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir Matteo led a group that include Diego, Persephone and others on an expedition to find Genvieve’s father in the outlands beyond the city gates. Genvieve reported that her family was traveling in a black carriage with gold trimming when they were accosted on the road to Rinascita by bandits. Unfortunately, when the group located Genvieve’s father and driver they were both found dead. The victims were killed by arrows and had their throats slit. According to Sir Matteo, the attack occurred 3-4 miles northwest of the city, just hours before the King’s Feast was attacked by assassins.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] French Consulate Announces Glitter Ball\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 27, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline announced an upcoming social event which will take place on December 15th: “At 9 o’clock in the evening on Sunday the 15th of December, the French will host the “Glitter Ball” to celebrate the holiday season. You are encouraged to bring one small, wrapped gift for the gift exchange portion of the event as well as one simple winter weather garment to dispense to the needy throughout the city as cold weather will be well set in by then. Please wear your most colorful, sparkling or stunning formal wear. Food and drink as well as entertainment will be provided.” The French Consulate requests that guests RSVP, and formal invitations will be sent to all of the fellow Consulates.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Gus Calls Sir Matteo a Coward\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 23, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Sir Matteo, he was delivering a package to Genvieve and Persephone when he became the target of rude looks from Gus. This escalated, with Gus challenging Sir Matteo to fight and calling him a coward. Sir Matteo said he was not in proper condition to fight, and that he could not accept a challenge from Gus. When interviewed the following day, Sir Matteo said he still had time to challenge Gus. Gus did not respond to the Rinascita Review’s request for comment.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] Lady Emmaline’s Speech and Gathering\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 24, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Writ on behalf of Lady Emmaline Beaumont, Vicontesse and Ambassador of the Consulate of France; On the 24th of November in the year of Our Lord 1599, Lady Beaumont will assemble with the key members of the French Consulate at the Piazza Vecchia fountain for a series of announcements regarding current and upcoming events. The Consulate will then proceed to the gathering hall located to the west of the fountain for a general audience with those who have business to attend with the members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Despite warnings that Lady Emmaline was a potential target of the recent assassination threats, the announcement went on as scheduled. She delivered a thoughtful speech at the fountain, which covered themes of unity against the assassin’s threats, gratitude toward Sir Matteo Medici’s efforts, mourning with Spain over their death, and a blessing from God.  Following Lady Emmaline’s remarks, the French Ambassador hosted a get-together in the gathering hall which was well attended. The guests enjoyed wine, snacks and good company for a few hours before everyone parted ways.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sir Matteo and Italian Consulate Announce Trial by Fire Tournament\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 30, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;As announced by Sir Matteo on the public posting boards: “There will be a special tournament hosted by the Italian Consulate and will be held December 6th through 8th in the Colosseum! All melee competitors are invited to compete for a purse of 500 Florins to the sole Champion. The event shall be held each evening starting at 8:00 in the evening and registrations end 7:55 in the evening December 6th. Being that this event is held at night the outer ring of the floor of the Colosseum will be lit with fire-pits to create a much different atmosphere than anything we've done before! Attendees are welcome to come and cheer on their favored champions and are encouraged to give a token to those this wish to see win!”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate Updates
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] Orla Volunteers to Sponsor New Guilds\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;November 20, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Per Orla’s announcement on the public boards: “I am currently offering to help purchase guild charters and or give each -new- guild florins to start their business. There was once a time in this city when there was a guild for every craft, when -some- consulates did not monopolize crafts. However, I understand it is not always easy to establish a guild on your own. So myself along with other seasoned guilds and even other consulates offer to aid you with this. Not only do we offer florins, but we offer our time and experience should you desire it. Connections that will help your craft and advertisement of your craft and guild. Please do contact Orla Couture should you wish to learn to be your own boss! Furthermore, if being a leader is not your preference I can provide a list of guilds that can assist you with lessons as well as be among others of your craft.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Recently Created Guilds:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Catania Healing (Persephone)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Master Stoneworks (Waylon)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Crimson Brotherhood Mercenary company offers its services to any and all individuals. No task too great nor too small, the Brotherhood will help you with it all. Should you have any questions seek Nix Orosedan, notably spotted by his crimson sword. For those looking for a job without long term agreements, the company is also hiring.
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring informants, writers and salespeople. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1575227136
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">2</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
