<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="3"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="-"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="15"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="december"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="review"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="vol"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] ***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the Italian, English, French, Spanish and Scottish Consulates.***\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic’s Royal Address (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Valeria Attacked and Robbed (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The French Consulate’s Glitter Ball (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Trial By Fire Tournament Results (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Orla’s Fashion Review: Best and Worst Dressed (p. 6)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - December 15 - vol 3
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] King Dominic’s Royal Address\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo greeted the crowd and invited them to the Throne Room. Santiago of Spanish Consulate waited outside to stand guard during this event. Nobody was allowed to bring in weapons or pouches, except for Sir Matteo, who carried in a sheathed dagger, and there are rumors of weapons being smuggled in.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Queen Mirielle was the first to address the throne room, "Thank you to everyone who came out tonight. A special appreciation to those who shared well wishes and gifts, prayers and kind thoughts. You were a much needed light in a very dark time."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic spoke next, "We appreciate your appearance at this audience, citizens and visitors to our country alike. My Queen is right that these are dark and uncertain times. God has graced us all with precious lives and we are reminded just how fleeting and precious they are in times like these. Let not these murderous wretches try to tear apart the peace we have crafted. Let not these assassins destroy the hope for a brighter future. Now more than ever is the time to come together and fight against these woes and travails."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic lifted his right fist poignantly, "Together, we can prevail and together we can fight these foes!" King Dominic then relayed to an imposing throne room, "We have seen and heard your good deeds. Your brave words and comforting gestures. We see clearly how hard you work to preserve this precious peace we are trying to craft here. And we thank you. We wish to make a special recognition of a true embodiment of this fighting spirit, this dedication to forging a new future through camaraderie, peace, diligence and honorable spirit."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;For Sir Matteo’s dedication to the Crown and people, he was named Chief Constable of the City Guard. He accepted an engraved burnished steel platinum crossed spear badge from Archduke Alonzo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic addressed the crowd again, "During the course of our safety procedures and investigations, we have made a number of necessary cuts from our roster of peerage and nobility in service to the Crown. This has brought a new and unique opportunity and need to the Crown. We will be seeking applicants of good standing from those invited to this city...be they National or diplomat...to flesh out the roles within our freshly vacant Royal Household."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finally, King Dominic made one more announcement, "With the Day of Immaculate Conception fast approaching, I wish to announce the commencement of the Christmas season! Again as in years gone by...we so very graciously sponsor the annual Christmas Markets of Piazza Vecchia! Our workers are busy and soon...you will find the spirit and joy of the season awaits you! Do good work, go with God and become the shining beacon of hope for your people I know you can be. God bless you."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Important News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] Valeria Attacked and Robbed\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 8, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Chief Constable Matteo, “A heinous attack and robbery happened two nights past in an alleyway between the German Consulate and the Faire.” According to the public crime files, Valeria of the German Consulate was the victim of the robbers. There was no description of the attackers, and the victim sustained heavy bruises. The Chief Constable said the robbers took her money. Sir Matteo recommended that folks take an escort because two separate attacks occurred in the alleys near the docks. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Rinascita City Guard Constables \\\& Militia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 10, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Chief Constable Matteo’s announcement: “The Rinascita City Guard is looking for applicants to serve our city and our gracious King. It is preferred if you are skilled with defending yourself, but we are willing to provide training, armor, and weaponry to protect you while you serve. The City Guard pays its members well and there is room for growth within our organization. Those wishing to apply for the City Guard should contact Chief Constable Matteo via scroll with their times that they are available to meet, background, and why they wish to join the City Guard.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“For those already working in their own guild, serving a consulate, or have other duties preventing them from joining the Rinascita City Guard can Volunteer their services in times of emergency by joining the Rinascita Militia. The Militia is to be called upon when needed to deal with emergencies. This could be during a multitude of situations and we appreciate anyone willing to offer their assistance in these times of need. Please contact Chief Constable Matteo via scroll with your intent to join and times you could be available to meet.”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Royal Household is Hiring\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;As announced at the Royal Address, details were posted to the public forums regarding positions in the Royal Household. The male positions include Grand Chamberlain, Royal Valet and Page. The female positions include Mistress of the Robes, Lady in Waiting and Handmaiden. No limitations on nationality, skill levels were specified. All application should be sent to Archduke Alonzo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] The French Consulate’s Glitter Ball\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Arafel\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline of the French Manor greeted guests at the ball with a small speech, "Your kindness, generosity, and companionship is a true testament to the meaning of the season, and I am gladdened that we can assemble together tonight to celebrate these joys that have come to us over the last year. I invite you all to eat, drink, make merry and dance the night...and chill, away! Happy Christmas and joyous New Year to each and every single one of you whom I name as a friend!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;It was a joyous event filled with Christmas cheer and gift opening for everyone that attended. Many warm clothes, blankets, and necessities for the poor were collected at the event. There was a gift exchange for those in attendance and an excellent selection of food and beverages. Needless to say, it will be a Happy Holidays for those that attended, and for those in need!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Afterward Lady Emmaline said, "We would like to thank everyone who came to the Ball and generously donated winter wear to the needy. The outpouring of kindness and good spirit is warming to the heart and we are so pleased to...enjoy renewed kinship with our fellow diplomats and envoys."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Trial By Fire Tournament Results\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 6, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Night 1:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Leliana\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Nix def. Margrat\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Nix (semi-finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Night 2:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Titus def. Maena\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sumner def. Draz\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sumner def. Titus (semi-finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finals:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Sumner (finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir Seeks Adoption Family for Orphan\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 9, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir Marcus, recent victor in Sir Matteo’ Trial by Fire tournament, has announced that he will donate his winnings from the tournament to pay for the adoption fees for an orphan named McKennan. Preference will be given to married couples with no children but Sair is willing to meet and speak with anyone who shows interest. Applications will be accepted until December 24.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] Diego Named Spanish Ambassador\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 16, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Diego was recently named the new Ambassador for the Spanish consulate, replacing Lord Guillen. The Spanish Consulate said an event would be announced to celebrate this new appointment, and to invite the city to meet the new leader of the consulate. Diego said this celebrate would be open to everyone in the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Consulate Previews Upcoming Events\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to a source in the French consulate, there are plans to host regular poetry readings, whisperings of a gentlemen's club and rumors of an upcoming ice-skating party.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] Orla’s Fashion Review\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Fashion took the form of vibrant colors and sparkling gems crafted by many of the most talented crafters in the city. In this exclusive article, I will be discussing some of the best looks of the evening and the worst.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Best Dressed:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Genvieve de Martinique proved that she could hold her own when it comes to fashion. The young nurse caught the eye of more than one person for her dazzling jewelry and the purest of white garments. She donned an off-the-shoulder gown with matching accessories. The starlight white silk garment was heavily embroidered with silver patterns that shimmered as she turned throughout the Ball. The outfit was paired with brilliant silver jewelry crafted by a newcomer jeweler named Gus.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Of the men, Frederic de Marigny a French Nobleman stole the show in his vibrant nacreous peacock and powdered gold attire. His garments, while of the traditional polished pieces of France, were elevated to a more superior level of fashion due to his embroidered waistcoat. The garment was extravagantly embroidered with feathers and iridescent beetle wings that were woven through with shimmering silver thread. He entirely raised the bar for male clothing and adorned the outfit with burnished silver jewelry.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) The Hostess and Ambassador of the French Consulate, Lady Emmaline Beaumont was a stunning sight as well for all who attended. Her gown design had the air of classic elegance, but with an exotic mix of shadowy black and glittery silver which created a fashionable ombre piece. Sparkling beads adorned her gown in swirling embroidery of silver that wispily circled the hem forming luminous stars against the black fabric. She completed the look with diamond and silver jewelry.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;4.) Countess Kilana Corvasci, Ambassador to Italy's Consulate and wife to Count Cross Corvasci delighted all who received the honor of viewing her in her striking glossy gown. She was adorned in gold and garnet with sparkling golden beads that accentuated the bodice of the garment. The gown itself was flowy and daring as it revealed much of the skin on the arms with an elegant haltered neckline. Lavish gold and silver accessories completed the look, causing the Countess to stand out among many others.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;5.) Handmaiden Valeria d'Allessandro's gown was dazzling. She sported a unique shade of vibrant red that did exceptional things for her beautiful complexion and green eyeshade. While her gown was marvelous, her accessories were not up to par with the extravagant main piece. If not for many various colors utilized in the outfit such as crimson, black, rose gold, ruby, gold, and charcoal black, the gown would have achieved what it was supposed to and stood out. However, for someone who was brutishly assaulted, she remains one of the best looking of the injured. The beautiful pearls within her hair were striking and did tumble down her back as she walked, giving her an overall radiance to the outfit.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] Orla’s Fashion Review (continued)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Not Best Dressed:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;While Bruno Smith is admired by many, I think it is clear that it's not for his fashion. He arrived in work clothing designed in an extensive array of colors from black, brown, slate-grey, sienna, sapphire, and chalcedony blue. He did, however, do his best to attempt fashion by donning a handsome fedora feathered hat. It helped shift some of the attention from his selection of garments as he stylishly tilted the hat in greeting.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[A chalcedony blue felt fedora. The piece is finished with a glossy blue-black crow feather. A fedora is a hat that is creased lengthwise down the crown and pinched in the front on both sides.]\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister Mox can be forgiven as he only just recently arrived in the city and was invited to the Ball. He was donned in the most basic of traveling clothing without much of a color statement. I am certain that with time he will establish himself and prove that even men can interpret fashion. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister Dieter, however, is another matter entirely, he has been in the city for some time and while his garments were fashionable, they did not fit the theme. It was not Ball worthy clothing, but everyday clothing. We hope he will place more effort into his outfits when attending future themed events.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Honorable Mentions:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Elspeth: Above-average in height and thin in build, Elspeth Falconer is a young woman of alabaster complexion with a head of thigh-length satiny charcoal black hair, worn in a braided bun. She is wearing prettily applied glitter eyeshadow, a shimmering black crushed velvet capelet, a pair of shimmering black silk heeled shoes, a dainty shimmering black silk circlet, expertly applied glittering black lip-color, a pair of black sapphire and metallic gold tassel earrings, a black sapphire and metallic gold drop necklace, and an elegant black sapphire-studded shimmering blue-green damask partlet gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Emeraude: Tall in height and gracefully slender in build, Lady Emeraude di Notte is a young woman of nut-brown complexion with a head of long soft rich ebon hair, worn in swept-back curls. She is wearing a pair of chocolate silk heeled shoes, a gleaming gold velvet back cloak, a pair of champagne pearl and filigreed gold drop earrings, a chocolate silk choker, a bejeweled filigreed gold wild vine tiara, an off-the-shoulder beaded snowdrop white cashmere hanging-sleeved gown, a decorative curly maple fan, wine lip-color, and a snowdrop white pashmina sweeping train.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Kino: Average in height and sculpted in build, Kino Quin is a young man of tanned complexion with a head of shoulder-length smooth honey blonde hair, worn loose with a love lock. He is wearing a silvery-grey batiste ruffled shirt, a beaded shimmering blue-green damask sleeveless doublet, a pair of silvery-grey leather knee-high boots, a pair of white smoke sheer silk braies, a white smoke sheer silk ascot, and a silver ear cuff.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Guild News (continued)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The purpose, and duty, of Catania Healing is to serve the people with honesty, integrity, and compassion. We promise to provide the best care we can offer. Contact Persephone or more information!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Come get your books, stationary and other items from Maena Boutin, of the university. Finest wares in the city with even better prices. Folders, books, cards, scroll and card boxes, gift boxes and packages galore! Also available as a merchant if required for better quality goods!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring informants, writers and salespeople. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">
         "Salvatore"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         4
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1576634162
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:sa:salvatore\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] ***This edition of the Rinascita Review is sponsored by the Italian, English, French, Spanish and Scottish Consulates.***\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic’s Royal Address (p. 2)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Valeria Attacked and Robbed (p. 3)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The French Consulate’s Glitter Ball (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Trial By Fire Tournament Results (p. 4)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Orla’s Fashion Review: Best and Worst Dressed (p. 6)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Rinascita Review - December 15 - vol 3
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] King Dominic’s Royal Address\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Archduke Alonzo greeted the crowd and invited them to the Throne Room. Santiago of Spanish Consulate waited outside to stand guard during this event. Nobody was allowed to bring in weapons or pouches, except for Sir Matteo, who carried in a sheathed dagger, and there are rumors of weapons being smuggled in.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Queen Mirielle was the first to address the throne room, "Thank you to everyone who came out tonight. A special appreciation to those who shared well wishes and gifts, prayers and kind thoughts. You were a much needed light in a very dark time."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic spoke next, "We appreciate your appearance at this audience, citizens and visitors to our country alike. My Queen is right that these are dark and uncertain times. God has graced us all with precious lives and we are reminded just how fleeting and precious they are in times like these. Let not these murderous wretches try to tear apart the peace we have crafted. Let not these assassins destroy the hope for a brighter future. Now more than ever is the time to come together and fight against these woes and travails."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic lifted his right fist poignantly, "Together, we can prevail and together we can fight these foes!" King Dominic then relayed to an imposing throne room, "We have seen and heard your good deeds. Your brave words and comforting gestures. We see clearly how hard you work to preserve this precious peace we are trying to craft here. And we thank you. We wish to make a special recognition of a true embodiment of this fighting spirit, this dedication to forging a new future through camaraderie, peace, diligence and honorable spirit."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;For Sir Matteo’s dedication to the Crown and people, he was named Chief Constable of the City Guard. He accepted an engraved burnished steel platinum crossed spear badge from Archduke Alonzo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;King Dominic addressed the crowd again, "During the course of our safety procedures and investigations, we have made a number of necessary cuts from our roster of peerage and nobility in service to the Crown. This has brought a new and unique opportunity and need to the Crown. We will be seeking applicants of good standing from those invited to this city...be they National or diplomat...to flesh out the roles within our freshly vacant Royal Household."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finally, King Dominic made one more announcement, "With the Day of Immaculate Conception fast approaching, I wish to announce the commencement of the Christmas season! Again as in years gone by...we so very graciously sponsor the annual Christmas Markets of Piazza Vecchia! Our workers are busy and soon...you will find the spirit and joy of the season awaits you! Do good work, go with God and become the shining beacon of hope for your people I know you can be. God bless you."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] Important News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] Valeria Attacked and Robbed\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 8, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Chief Constable Matteo, “A heinous attack and robbery happened two nights past in an alleyway between the German Consulate and the Faire.” According to the public crime files, Valeria of the German Consulate was the victim of the robbers. There was no description of the attackers, and the victim sustained heavy bruises. The Chief Constable said the robbers took her money. Sir Matteo recommended that folks take an escort because two separate attacks occurred in the alleys near the docks. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Rinascita City Guard Constables \\\& Militia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 10, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to Chief Constable Matteo’s announcement: “The Rinascita City Guard is looking for applicants to serve our city and our gracious King. It is preferred if you are skilled with defending yourself, but we are willing to provide training, armor, and weaponry to protect you while you serve. The City Guard pays its members well and there is room for growth within our organization. Those wishing to apply for the City Guard should contact Chief Constable Matteo via scroll with their times that they are available to meet, background, and why they wish to join the City Guard.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt; \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;“For those already working in their own guild, serving a consulate, or have other duties preventing them from joining the Rinascita City Guard can Volunteer their services in times of emergency by joining the Rinascita Militia. The Militia is to be called upon when needed to deal with emergencies. This could be during a multitude of situations and we appreciate anyone willing to offer their assistance in these times of need. Please contact Chief Constable Matteo via scroll with your intent to join and times you could be available to meet.”\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Royal Household is Hiring\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 5, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;As announced at the Royal Address, details were posted to the public forums regarding positions in the Royal Household. The male positions include Grand Chamberlain, Royal Valet and Page. The female positions include Mistress of the Robes, Lady in Waiting and Handmaiden. No limitations on nationality, skill levels were specified. All application should be sent to Archduke Alonzo.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] City News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] The French Consulate’s Glitter Ball\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;By Arafel\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Lady Emmaline of the French Manor greeted guests at the ball with a small speech, "Your kindness, generosity, and companionship is a true testament to the meaning of the season, and I am gladdened that we can assemble together tonight to celebrate these joys that have come to us over the last year. I invite you all to eat, drink, make merry and dance the night...and chill, away! Happy Christmas and joyous New Year to each and every single one of you whom I name as a friend!"\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;It was a joyous event filled with Christmas cheer and gift opening for everyone that attended. Many warm clothes, blankets, and necessities for the poor were collected at the event. There was a gift exchange for those in attendance and an excellent selection of food and beverages. Needless to say, it will be a Happy Holidays for those that attended, and for those in need!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Afterward Lady Emmaline said, "We would like to thank everyone who came to the Ball and generously donated winter wear to the needy. The outpouring of kindness and good spirit is warming to the heart and we are so pleased to...enjoy renewed kinship with our fellow diplomats and envoys."\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Trial By Fire Tournament Results\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 6, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Night 1:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Leliana\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Nix def. Margrat\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Nix (semi-finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Night 2:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Titus def. Maena\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sumner def. Draz\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Sumner def. Titus (semi-finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Finals:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir def. Sumner (finals)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir Seeks Adoption Family for Orphan\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 9, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Samir Marcus, recent victor in Sir Matteo’ Trial by Fire tournament, has announced that he will donate his winnings from the tournament to pay for the adoption fees for an orphan named McKennan. Preference will be given to married couples with no children but Sair is willing to meet and speak with anyone who shows interest. Applications will be accepted until December 24.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] Social News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] Diego Named Spanish Ambassador\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 16, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Diego was recently named the new Ambassador for the Spanish consulate, replacing Lord Guillen. The Spanish Consulate said an event would be announced to celebrate this new appointment, and to invite the city to meet the new leader of the consulate. Diego said this celebrate would be open to everyone in the city.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;French Consulate Previews Upcoming Events\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;According to a source in the French consulate, there are plans to host regular poetry readings, whisperings of a gentlemen's club and rumors of an upcoming ice-skating party.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] Consulate News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] Orla’s Fashion Review\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Fashion took the form of vibrant colors and sparkling gems crafted by many of the most talented crafters in the city. In this exclusive article, I will be discussing some of the best looks of the evening and the worst.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Best Dressed:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Genvieve de Martinique proved that she could hold her own when it comes to fashion. The young nurse caught the eye of more than one person for her dazzling jewelry and the purest of white garments. She donned an off-the-shoulder gown with matching accessories. The starlight white silk garment was heavily embroidered with silver patterns that shimmered as she turned throughout the Ball. The outfit was paired with brilliant silver jewelry crafted by a newcomer jeweler named Gus.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Of the men, Frederic de Marigny a French Nobleman stole the show in his vibrant nacreous peacock and powdered gold attire. His garments, while of the traditional polished pieces of France, were elevated to a more superior level of fashion due to his embroidered waistcoat. The garment was extravagantly embroidered with feathers and iridescent beetle wings that were woven through with shimmering silver thread. He entirely raised the bar for male clothing and adorned the outfit with burnished silver jewelry.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) The Hostess and Ambassador of the French Consulate, Lady Emmaline Beaumont was a stunning sight as well for all who attended. Her gown design had the air of classic elegance, but with an exotic mix of shadowy black and glittery silver which created a fashionable ombre piece. Sparkling beads adorned her gown in swirling embroidery of silver that wispily circled the hem forming luminous stars against the black fabric. She completed the look with diamond and silver jewelry.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;4.) Countess Kilana Corvasci, Ambassador to Italy's Consulate and wife to Count Cross Corvasci delighted all who received the honor of viewing her in her striking glossy gown. She was adorned in gold and garnet with sparkling golden beads that accentuated the bodice of the garment. The gown itself was flowy and daring as it revealed much of the skin on the arms with an elegant haltered neckline. Lavish gold and silver accessories completed the look, causing the Countess to stand out among many others.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;5.) Handmaiden Valeria d'Allessandro's gown was dazzling. She sported a unique shade of vibrant red that did exceptional things for her beautiful complexion and green eyeshade. While her gown was marvelous, her accessories were not up to par with the extravagant main piece. If not for many various colors utilized in the outfit such as crimson, black, rose gold, ruby, gold, and charcoal black, the gown would have achieved what it was supposed to and stood out. However, for someone who was brutishly assaulted, she remains one of the best looking of the injured. The beautiful pearls within her hair were striking and did tumble down her back as she walked, giving her an overall radiance to the outfit.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] Guild News
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] Orla’s Fashion Review (continued)\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;December 15, 1599\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Not Best Dressed:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;While Bruno Smith is admired by many, I think it is clear that it's not for his fashion. He arrived in work clothing designed in an extensive array of colors from black, brown, slate-grey, sienna, sapphire, and chalcedony blue. He did, however, do his best to attempt fashion by donning a handsome fedora feathered hat. It helped shift some of the attention from his selection of garments as he stylishly tilted the hat in greeting.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[A chalcedony blue felt fedora. The piece is finished with a glossy blue-black crow feather. A fedora is a hat that is creased lengthwise down the crown and pinched in the front on both sides.]\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister Mox can be forgiven as he only just recently arrived in the city and was invited to the Ball. He was donned in the most basic of traveling clothing without much of a color statement. I am certain that with time he will establish himself and prove that even men can interpret fashion. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Mister Dieter, however, is another matter entirely, he has been in the city for some time and while his garments were fashionable, they did not fit the theme. It was not Ball worthy clothing, but everyday clothing. We hope he will place more effort into his outfits when attending future themed events.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;---\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Honorable Mentions:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Elspeth: Above-average in height and thin in build, Elspeth Falconer is a young woman of alabaster complexion with a head of thigh-length satiny charcoal black hair, worn in a braided bun. She is wearing prettily applied glitter eyeshadow, a shimmering black crushed velvet capelet, a pair of shimmering black silk heeled shoes, a dainty shimmering black silk circlet, expertly applied glittering black lip-color, a pair of black sapphire and metallic gold tassel earrings, a black sapphire and metallic gold drop necklace, and an elegant black sapphire-studded shimmering blue-green damask partlet gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Emeraude: Tall in height and gracefully slender in build, Lady Emeraude di Notte is a young woman of nut-brown complexion with a head of long soft rich ebon hair, worn in swept-back curls. She is wearing a pair of chocolate silk heeled shoes, a gleaming gold velvet back cloak, a pair of champagne pearl and filigreed gold drop earrings, a chocolate silk choker, a bejeweled filigreed gold wild vine tiara, an off-the-shoulder beaded snowdrop white cashmere hanging-sleeved gown, a decorative curly maple fan, wine lip-color, and a snowdrop white pashmina sweeping train.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Kino: Average in height and sculpted in build, Kino Quin is a young man of tanned complexion with a head of shoulder-length smooth honey blonde hair, worn loose with a love lock. He is wearing a silvery-grey batiste ruffled shirt, a beaded shimmering blue-green damask sleeveless doublet, a pair of silvery-grey leather knee-high boots, a pair of white smoke sheer silk braies, a white smoke sheer silk ascot, and a silver ear cuff.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Guild News (continued)
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Note: Advertising in the Rinascita Review may bring your business more customers and employees! Write to Salvatore Costello if you’re interested in advertising in the next edition.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;SoWeCanSew is one of the oldest guilds in the city and the longest-running clothing guild. It was originated by Lady Tara and has only grown since, as we continue to take in new clothiers and refine their skills and knowledge. We have helped produce some of the most competent seamstresses and tailors this city has ever seen. Furthermore, we have consistently maintained the cheapest prices in the city that you will find. Our customers have described us as fast, reliable, caring, and fashionable. You will never go wrong when you shop with SoWeCanSew. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The purpose, and duty, of Catania Healing is to serve the people with honesty, integrity, and compassion. We promise to provide the best care we can offer. Contact Persephone or more information!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Come get your books, stationary and other items from Maena Boutin, of the university. Finest wares in the city with even better prices. Folders, books, cards, scroll and card boxes, gift boxes and packages galore! Also available as a merchant if required for better quality goods!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Heavenly Jewelry is guild created by the people and for the people. We make jewelry, armor, and weapons and we are always open to new members.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Preston LeBeau Tailoring - I provide stylish, modern and formal wear for men; there are many options for your tailoring, so choose Preston and dress to impress!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Rinascita Review is hiring informants, writers and salespeople. If you like tracking the latest scoop or writing stories in a relatively objective way, then this line of work may be for you!\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Advertisements
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1576634188
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">2</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1576445286
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
