<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="SkotOS">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Allegory:Props:Writing:PrintingPress:UrNewspaper)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="one"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="-"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="glamorous"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="issue"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="life"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="of"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="rinascita"/>
          <Base:Adjective adjective="the"/>
        </Base:Adjectives>
        <Base:Descriptions/>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="base:initialcontents"/>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00">
         X[S] For those who do not know me, my name is Orla Couture, and I am a seamstress within the Guild So We Can Sew. I have lived within the walls of this city for nearly seven years and have experienced a lot in that short time. One of those things was my encountering of various people from all walks of life. It makes life richer when you get to see or learn about cultures and people you would not usually come across. This place is more than just a wealthy trade city; it is a place for us to come together. No matter which Consulate or Guild you are in, this city is about unity.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Therefore, I wanted to produce a paper that mentioned various topics, one that I genuinely enjoyed. Since I have not seen one like that yet, I have decided to create my own. I hope you all enjoy it because this is only the start of what I have planned. Without further ado, I invite you to experience my newspaper 'The Glamorous Life of Rinascita'.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Two - The Feast of Saint Valentine\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Four - The English's Toga Social\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Five - An Overview of Courtesy\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Six - A Taste of Culture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Seven - Crafters Spotlight\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Eight - Upcoming Socials and Announcements\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Glamorous Life of Rinascita - Issue One
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01">
         X[S] It was the time for love in the month of February which the French Consulate took full advantage of by announcing their Saint Valentine socials. It began with a memorial service for those who were attacked or harmed by Peace. In that respect, citizens were invited to donate to the church and healers for their assistance with the injured and widows. The top three benefactors that evening were Misters Samir, Ladies Kilana and Emeraude for the Italian Consulate and Lady Tara and Miss Orla for the SoWeCanSew Guild.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The following event that took place was the Saint Valentine Ball, which was held in the Grand Salon Ballroom. The location did justice for the event with its glittering crystal chandeliers and the elegant, broad windows that washed the room in beautiful moonlight. As everyone dined in lavish foods and drinks provided by the French, Archduke Alonzo and Count Frederic brought music from the Spanish Wedding that took place recently. Those in attendance enthusiastically took to the exotic sounds, as the majority moved to dance with or without a partner. Couples such as Dame Persephone and Mister Samir or Lady Emmaline and Lord Nicolas danced the entire night. Those in attendance included Archduke Alonzo, Count Frederic, Countess Emmaline, Viscountess Emeraude and Tara, Viscount Nicolas, Dame Persephone, Misses Orla, Thalia, Genvieve, and Margrat as well as Misters Samir and Pio.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page01:title">
         X[S] The French Consulate's Feast of Saint Valentine - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02">
         X[S] As seamstress to the SoWeCanSew guild, I took the time to observe the fashionable creations worn by those who attended, and these are my top favorite looks.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Dame Persephone: The shapely Dame donned shades of spring green and burgundy which looked divine on her creamy complexion. While the colors itself are a bold statement, the entirety of the outfit made her appear as if she freshly stepped out of a fairy tale. Her hair was worn up and adorned with wildflowers which matched the embroidered flowers of her gown. Whimsical tippets hung low on her arms and flowed the length of her gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[A sheer spring green silk pleated gown. Delicate lavender grey silk flowers are tactically scattered here and there. This dress features a cinching waist secured with a clasp. A scooped neckline dips enough to reveal a modest amount of cleavage before disappearing into a ruched, inlay bodice. The skirt skims over the hips in pleated folds as it extends towards the feet of the wearer and trails weightlessly over the ground. A pair of bell sleeves snugly encircle the biceps and fan out elegantly towards the wrists, leaving the shoulders bare. A cluster of muted multi-colored wildflowers gracefully adorns the bust of the gown. Elegantly enveloping the entirety of the hem, it modestly covers the decolletage of the wearer. A similar embroidery of petaled flowers traverses the hem of the skirt in an untamed array of various subdued colors and exotic shapes, completing the overall design.]\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Archduke Alonzo: The dominant Archduke arrived at the second place of my favorite looks of the evening. He donned an exotic shade of rose cisele that was dusted with specks of gold. It was stunning against the smooth olive of his skin and playing well with the golden-brown of his hair. He paired the shade with champagne and gold pieces that complimented his outfit well. The dashing waistcoat stood out among all the pieces as it was adorned with shimmering golden beads. This is the first non-royal Ball that the Archduke has attended this year, and he has set the bar high. I look forward to seeing what he comes up with next.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) Genvieve: Last, but not least we naturally have Genvieve who once again arrived in grand style as she has been known to typically do. Her porcelain complexion shined brighter against the exotic shade of iridescent black that she wore for her seductive mermaid gown. Matching shoes and circlet satisfactorily completed the outfit. Her obsidian hair was gathered upwards and adorned with miniature rose quartz gems which matched the theme of her rose gold accessories which were set with the same gem. While this outfit was not up to par as her first outfit she, however, managed to capture the attention of many onlookers. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Honorable Mentions: Countess Emmaline for representing a glittering goddess. Count Frederic for his complimentary theme colored outfit. Finally, Viscountess Tara for her extravagant diamond-adorned headpiece.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page02:title">
         X[S] The French Consulate's Feast of Saint Valentine - Continued
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03">
         X[S] The English Consulate's newest Ambassador, Arafel Bellator, started his leadership off with a unique social to end the month of love. When the Toga Party was first announced, many were uncertain if it would be something a Consulate should host. However, the anticipation of dressing up and having lighthearted fun pushed past the worries. The event took place within the English Consulate where various foods and drinks were served to guests who arrived. The Ambassador was unable to attend the social but Misses Ava and Toddia took over the hosting duties for the evening.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Throughout the night, those who attended socialized with each other before starting a game named truth or dare. The guests played several rounds with one of the dares from Lady Morven being that Miss Magrat needed to do a jig dance with Mister Dieter. Miss Margrat enthusiastically gathered Mister Dieter and began a complicated performance, daring him to keep up. As their audience created a piece of music with their hands and the surface of furniture, Mister Dieter took the lead and pulled Miss Margrat into ballroom dances. The pair continued moving and adjusting their dance for a few minutes before concluding with a round of applause.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;More rounds continued as truths were revealed and dares were completed. The attire of the evening is what took this from a simple social to and enjoyable costume party as everyone was donned in garments from ancient Rome. As always, my favorite looks will be below.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Toddia Wincott: As the hostess of this social, Miss Toddia looked divine in her silken toga of plum that was lightly embroidered with shimmering silver swirls. The shade of purple radiantly popped against her pale complexion and light brown hair. She adorned her toga with a matching circlet that contained various flowers, whimsical tippets, and silver and black accessories. The silver jewelry and purple eye shadow made completed the look and allowed her to stand out among the others.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Thalia Solandis: Miss Thalia is a newcomer to the city, but with her refreshing social skills, she has quickly become recognized by just about everyone. This evening, she showed that not only was she smart but that she has the ability to eve look breathtaking while in a toga. Her rosy complexion and strawberry blonde hair prepared a perfect canvas for the azure mist of her toga. The silk garment was eloquently trimmed in argent damask which also adorned her feet in knee-high sandals. The outfit was paired with matching argent waist cord and lavish azure mist sword cape that elegantly draped over her shoulders.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) Lady Morven: As one of the few nobles to attend the social, Lady Morven showed she knew how to have fun. She donned an extravagant teal toga which was embroidered with gold vines. Her bluish-black hair was intricately woven into a bun that additionally bore a likeness of vines. The outfit was paired with gold and emerald jewelry as well as gold silk accessories.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page03:title">
         X[S] The English's Toga Social - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04">
         X[S] \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Courtesy. It should be an ever present part of our daily lives, and yet do we truly understand what it is? \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At its core, courtesy represents all that is regarded as courtly and regal, honorable and sociable. We see it in each day, as we reverence and greet our peers, lessers, and betters. A familiar nod to those below us, a deep curtsy to those higher in rank. And yet it is not only unspoken grace and respect, but a silent language, a way to converse without voice, and a way to express favor in a subtle way. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Many see courtesy as a sighing thing to fulfill, a ridiculous notion that the everyday folk of cities need not pay attention to; a glittering adornment of golden palaces and gossiping noble ladies. Yet we all show courtesy to one another, to the master carpenter who furnishes our rooms, and the skillful seamstresses who help us to look our best. We respect those who have spent their lives learning to grow, be that in the way of a peer and respected member of the court and nobility, or as a master crafter.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;In its most raw form, courtesy is naught more than respect. Respect to the crown from which they received their peerage and distinction, or respect for hours and years given to a craft. Respect which should be shown, if not in honor to the person, than at least to the power above that graced them with their talents, or honored them with position. Of course, one can grace courtesy with style and flair, and a charming smile, yet those are merely embellishments to drape the courtesy in. Sometimes the simplest and most heartfelt display can be in a pure show of deference, or in a passing reverence. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page04:title">
         X[S] An Overview of Courtesy - by Dame Valeria dAllessandr
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05">
         X[S] In this issue, I asked Miss Margrat of the Scottish Consulate to write a little about her people to give outsiders and inside on who they are. I hope to do one of these for each of my articles because it never hurts to get to know your neighbors. Those seeking to join the Scottish Consulate should write Ambassador Valentine. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;-------------------------------\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Who Are The Scottish?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Scottish are a fun-loving folk with a lot of time-honored traditions. We are very family-oriented and love our Clans and our country, but we can also be as fierce as a kicked over beehive when needed. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Do They Traditionally Wear?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Tartan plaid is extremely important in our culture. Each Scottish Clan has their own plaid pattern that can exclusively be worn by members of that Clan and is typically displayed kilts. Clan pride is immensely important to the Scottish as many frequently develop a fiercer loyalty to their Clan then they do Scotland as a whole.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Music Do They Like?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Bagpipes are incredibly important to the Scottish. They can be utilized for both fun and very serious business. They represent a longstanding tradition and we perform them when our warriors are marching or heading into battle. They can also be played for dances and ceremonies around the village.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;How Do The Scottish Have Fun?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We love dancing, especially jigs and reels. These are often very fast dances with many folks dancing together at the same time. We like organizing dances to get the whole village together. Sometimes we even have other villages join us. We can often dance the whole day and night away while children laugh and play games or listen to tales from the elders. The women chatter and gossip while baking and the men have arm-wrestling matches and toss giant logs around called cabers. Singing is also important as we do it while we work. We have hundreds of old songs that we sing while working the wool to help us keep time and make the job more fun. The songs typically have simple words and repeat oft. The significant part is they all have a steady rhythm to go along with the working.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Food Do They Like?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We have various foods that we enjoy eating. One of my preferred foods to eat that causes me to feel like I am home on the Isle of Jura, is haggis. Haggis is a sort of sausage, that can be made from lots of parts of the animal that we don't use for anything else. Scots don't normally abide waste and while some folks might think it is gross you would be missing out if you've never tried it. My grandmother had the most delicious recipe for haggis in my whole village. She would use all the usual organ meats like the liver, kidney, heart, and lungs. Though she also included a hearty portion of trip to her haggis. It made it extra nice and moist. The Haggis here in Rinascita is still good, but it just doesn't compare to my grandmother's haggis.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page05:title">
         X[S] A Taste of Culture with Margrat Maclean
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06">
         X[S] This portion of the paper is dedicated to all crafters of the city who reside in a guild either as a member or leader. Each issue I will single out one crafter of the many to bring them to the light for those who may or may not know of them. It is crucial to support guild crafters; we work hard at what we do, and it's never easy. I respect each person on this list who knows the struggle of spending hours, money, and time learning to hone your skills to be almost perfect. So be sure to look their way when you are in need.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;In this issue I want to discuss Mister Pio, he is a new carpenter to the city and is eager to learn. While his list may not be as large as others, I believe his eagerness to help the city will make up for what he lacks. Be sure to greet him to our great city and send orders to him when you can. A crafter can only get better with practice and we are a city that supports each other. Not only does he take his craft seriously, but I have also found him to be kind, funny, and easy to talk to. Keep reading to page eight so you can get to know him a little more.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;-------------------------------\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Bookbinders]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Maena\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Carpenters]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Christian\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bjorn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Pio\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Jayland\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Dyers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Orla\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tara\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Preston\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Lacey\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Hairstylists]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Thalia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Lacey\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Healers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Persephone\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Genvieve\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Trinity\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Jewelers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bruno\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Gus\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Heather\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Seamstresses/Tailors]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Orla\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tara\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Carolyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tamm\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Preston\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Valeria\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Smiths]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bruno\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Heather\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Weavers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Carolyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tamm\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Crafters Spotlight - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07">
         X[S] Welcome to the City: Thalia Solandis\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Pio Marini has only just recently arrived in the city, appearing the night of the French ball for Saint Valentine. He lost both of his parents and was raised as an orphan. He got into woodworking to help repair and aid the places he was staying in. He arrived in our city so that he could find teachers to help him in furthering his skill. He is quite fond of sour things and enjoys spending time whittling and making little things out of cords of lumber.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Upcoming Events and News: J'Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Audience with the Mistress of Robes: For those who may have business with the Crown or the Queen specifically, Viscountess Emeraude will soon be hosting Audience Hours. The first of these will take place on the Sixth Day at [Ten in the -morning-]. They will be held in the Administration Office. Should you not be able to make this time, you may scribe a Handmaiden to assist you in setting up a private meeting.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Spanish Royal Visit: This coming Sunday, the Royal Crown is hosting a celebration for the arrival of His Majesty, King Joel Velazquez of Spain and the newly coronated Queen Yasmin of Spain. This will take place at the Royal Palace and [Nine in the -evening-]. The Lord Chamberlain encourages all who plan to attend to don proper court attire.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Royal Ball: The Crown plan to host a lavish Ball to mark the closure and departure of the Spanish Royal Family. This has been marked to take place on the Fifteenth Day at [Nine in the -evening-]. Just as before, formal clothing strictly encouraged.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Crafters Emporium: The French Consulate are planning to resume their tradition of the Crafters Emporium. This is a gathering where the Consulate gives back to the crafters and charity by allowing the crafters to present their items to the city. Crafters wishing a spot should write to Countess Emmaline Beaumont for more information. It will take place on the Twenty-Ninth Day at [Nine in the -evening-]. An auction will be conducted on the same day for crafters who may own rare items.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Fruhling Feier Tanzen: The German Consulate is excited to announce their Spring Ball which will happen on the Eighteenth Day of April. It will be held in the Grand Salon at [Eight in the -evening-]. Guests are asked to dress in colors that remind them of spring. All questions may be directed to the German Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Gamble for Charity: On the Twenty-Sixth Day of April, Orla Couture will be hosting a Charity Social. Those who participate in the games will be playing for a charity of their choice. Each person will automatically be gifted a hundred florins towards their chosen charity so no go without a donation. The winner of each game will have their portion of winnings donated and receive a personal prize for their participation. This will take place in the Gamble Hall at [Eight in the -evening-]. Those wishing to join should contact Orla Couture.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="export:trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements - by J'Orla Couture and Thalia Solandis
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter">"Orla"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_object">
         \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwriter_recognition_difficulty">
         6
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="lastwritetime">
         1583118151
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="misc:lastdropped">
         "1582940123 Orla[heavenlyheather]"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:editor">
         \<Chatters:AE:or:orla\>
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00">
         X[S] For those who do not know me, my name is Orla Couture, and I am a seamstress within the Guild So We Can Sew. I have lived within the walls of this city for nearly seven years and have experienced a lot in that short time. One of those things was my encountering of various people from all walks of life. It makes life richer when you get to see or learn about cultures and people you would not usually come across. This place is more than just a wealthy trade city; it is a place for us to come together. No matter which Consulate or Guild you are in, this city is about unity.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Therefore, I wanted to produce a paper that mentioned various topics, one that I genuinely enjoyed. Since I have not seen one like that yet, I have decided to create my own. I hope you all enjoy it because this is only the start of what I have planned. Without further ado, I invite you to experience my newspaper 'The Glamorous Life of Rinascita'.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Two - The Feast of Saint Valentine\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Four - The English's Toga Social\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Five - An Overview of Courtesy\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Six - A Taste of Culture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Seven - Crafters Spotlight\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Page Eight - Upcoming Socials and Announcements\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page00:title">
         X[S] The Glamorous Life of Rinascita - Issue One
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01">
         X[S] It was the time for love in the month of February which the French Consulate took full advantage of by announcing their Saint Valentine socials. It began with a memorial service for those who were attacked or harmed by Peace. In that respect, citizens were invited to donate to the church and healers for their assistance with the injured and widows. The top three benefactors that evening were Misters Samir, Ladies Kilana and Emeraude for the Italian Consulate and Lady Tara and Miss Orla for the SoWeCanSew Guild.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The following event that took place was the Saint Valentine Ball, which was held in the Grand Salon Ballroom. The location did justice for the event with its glittering crystal chandeliers and the elegant, broad windows that washed the room in beautiful moonlight. As everyone dined in lavish foods and drinks provided by the French, Archduke Alonzo and Count Frederic brought music from the Spanish Wedding that took place recently. Those in attendance enthusiastically took to the exotic sounds, as the majority moved to dance with or without a partner. Couples such as Dame Persephone and Mister Samir or Lady Emmaline and Lord Nicolas danced the entire night. Those in attendance included Archduke Alonzo, Count Frederic, Countess Emmaline, Viscountess Emeraude and Tara, Viscount Nicolas, Dame Persephone, Misses Orla, Thalia, Genvieve, and Margrat as well as Misters Samir and Pio.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page01:title">
         X[S] The French Consulate's Feast of Saint Valentine - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02">
         X[S] As seamstress to the SoWeCanSew guild, I took the time to observe the fashionable creations worn by those who attended, and these are my top favorite looks.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Dame Persephone: The shapely Dame donned shades of spring green and burgundy which looked divine on her creamy complexion. While the colors itself are a bold statement, the entirety of the outfit made her appear as if she freshly stepped out of a fairy tale. Her hair was worn up and adorned with wildflowers which matched the embroidered flowers of her gown. Whimsical tippets hung low on her arms and flowed the length of her gown.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[A sheer spring green silk pleated gown. Delicate lavender grey silk flowers are tactically scattered here and there. This dress features a cinching waist secured with a clasp. A scooped neckline dips enough to reveal a modest amount of cleavage before disappearing into a ruched, inlay bodice. The skirt skims over the hips in pleated folds as it extends towards the feet of the wearer and trails weightlessly over the ground. A pair of bell sleeves snugly encircle the biceps and fan out elegantly towards the wrists, leaving the shoulders bare. A cluster of muted multi-colored wildflowers gracefully adorns the bust of the gown. Elegantly enveloping the entirety of the hem, it modestly covers the decolletage of the wearer. A similar embroidery of petaled flowers traverses the hem of the skirt in an untamed array of various subdued colors and exotic shapes, completing the overall design.]\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Archduke Alonzo: The dominant Archduke arrived at the second place of my favorite looks of the evening. He donned an exotic shade of rose cisele that was dusted with specks of gold. It was stunning against the smooth olive of his skin and playing well with the golden-brown of his hair. He paired the shade with champagne and gold pieces that complimented his outfit well. The dashing waistcoat stood out among all the pieces as it was adorned with shimmering golden beads. This is the first non-royal Ball that the Archduke has attended this year, and he has set the bar high. I look forward to seeing what he comes up with next.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) Genvieve: Last, but not least we naturally have Genvieve who once again arrived in grand style as she has been known to typically do. Her porcelain complexion shined brighter against the exotic shade of iridescent black that she wore for her seductive mermaid gown. Matching shoes and circlet satisfactorily completed the outfit. Her obsidian hair was gathered upwards and adorned with miniature rose quartz gems which matched the theme of her rose gold accessories which were set with the same gem. While this outfit was not up to par as her first outfit she, however, managed to capture the attention of many onlookers. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Honorable Mentions: Countess Emmaline for representing a glittering goddess. Count Frederic for his complimentary theme colored outfit. Finally, Viscountess Tara for her extravagant diamond-adorned headpiece.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page02:title">
         X[S] The French Consulate's Feast of Saint Valentine - Continued
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03">
         X[S] The English Consulate's newest Ambassador, Arafel Bellator, started his leadership off with a unique social to end the month of love. When the Toga Party was first announced, many were uncertain if it would be something a Consulate should host. However, the anticipation of dressing up and having lighthearted fun pushed past the worries. The event took place within the English Consulate where various foods and drinks were served to guests who arrived. The Ambassador was unable to attend the social but Misses Ava and Toddia took over the hosting duties for the evening.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Throughout the night, those who attended socialized with each other before starting a game named truth or dare. The guests played several rounds with one of the dares from Lady Morven being that Miss Magrat needed to do a jig dance with Mister Dieter. Miss Margrat enthusiastically gathered Mister Dieter and began a complicated performance, daring him to keep up. As their audience created a piece of music with their hands and the surface of furniture, Mister Dieter took the lead and pulled Miss Margrat into ballroom dances. The pair continued moving and adjusting their dance for a few minutes before concluding with a round of applause.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;More rounds continued as truths were revealed and dares were completed. The attire of the evening is what took this from a simple social to and enjoyable costume party as everyone was donned in garments from ancient Rome. As always, my favorite looks will be below.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;1.) Toddia Wincott: As the hostess of this social, Miss Toddia looked divine in her silken toga of plum that was lightly embroidered with shimmering silver swirls. The shade of purple radiantly popped against her pale complexion and light brown hair. She adorned her toga with a matching circlet that contained various flowers, whimsical tippets, and silver and black accessories. The silver jewelry and purple eye shadow made completed the look and allowed her to stand out among the others.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;2.) Thalia Solandis: Miss Thalia is a newcomer to the city, but with her refreshing social skills, she has quickly become recognized by just about everyone. This evening, she showed that not only was she smart but that she has the ability to eve look breathtaking while in a toga. Her rosy complexion and strawberry blonde hair prepared a perfect canvas for the azure mist of her toga. The silk garment was eloquently trimmed in argent damask which also adorned her feet in knee-high sandals. The outfit was paired with matching argent waist cord and lavish azure mist sword cape that elegantly draped over her shoulders.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;3.) Lady Morven: As one of the few nobles to attend the social, Lady Morven showed she knew how to have fun. She donned an extravagant teal toga which was embroidered with gold vines. Her bluish-black hair was intricately woven into a bun that additionally bore a likeness of vines. The outfit was paired with gold and emerald jewelry as well as gold silk accessories.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page03:title">
         X[S] The English's Toga Social - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04">
         X[S] \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Courtesy. It should be an ever present part of our daily lives, and yet do we truly understand what it is? \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;At its core, courtesy represents all that is regarded as courtly and regal, honorable and sociable. We see it in each day, as we reverence and greet our peers, lessers, and betters. A familiar nod to those below us, a deep curtsy to those higher in rank. And yet it is not only unspoken grace and respect, but a silent language, a way to converse without voice, and a way to express favor in a subtle way. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Many see courtesy as a sighing thing to fulfill, a ridiculous notion that the everyday folk of cities need not pay attention to; a glittering adornment of golden palaces and gossiping noble ladies. Yet we all show courtesy to one another, to the master carpenter who furnishes our rooms, and the skillful seamstresses who help us to look our best. We respect those who have spent their lives learning to grow, be that in the way of a peer and respected member of the court and nobility, or as a master crafter.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;In its most raw form, courtesy is naught more than respect. Respect to the crown from which they received their peerage and distinction, or respect for hours and years given to a craft. Respect which should be shown, if not in honor to the person, than at least to the power above that graced them with their talents, or honored them with position. Of course, one can grace courtesy with style and flair, and a charming smile, yet those are merely embellishments to drape the courtesy in. Sometimes the simplest and most heartfelt display can be in a pure show of deference, or in a passing reverence. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page04:title">
         X[S] An Overview of Courtesy - by Dame Valeria dAllessandr
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05">
         X[S] In this issue, I asked Miss Margrat of the Scottish Consulate to write a little about her people to give outsiders and inside on who they are. I hope to do one of these for each of my articles because it never hurts to get to know your neighbors. Those seeking to join the Scottish Consulate should write Ambassador Valentine. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;-------------------------------\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Who Are The Scottish?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;The Scottish are a fun-loving folk with a lot of time-honored traditions. We are very family-oriented and love our Clans and our country, but we can also be as fierce as a kicked over beehive when needed. \\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Do They Traditionally Wear?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Tartan plaid is extremely important in our culture. Each Scottish Clan has their own plaid pattern that can exclusively be worn by members of that Clan and is typically displayed kilts. Clan pride is immensely important to the Scottish as many frequently develop a fiercer loyalty to their Clan then they do Scotland as a whole.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Music Do They Like?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Bagpipes are incredibly important to the Scottish. They can be utilized for both fun and very serious business. They represent a longstanding tradition and we perform them when our warriors are marching or heading into battle. They can also be played for dances and ceremonies around the village.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;How Do The Scottish Have Fun?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We love dancing, especially jigs and reels. These are often very fast dances with many folks dancing together at the same time. We like organizing dances to get the whole village together. Sometimes we even have other villages join us. We can often dance the whole day and night away while children laugh and play games or listen to tales from the elders. The women chatter and gossip while baking and the men have arm-wrestling matches and toss giant logs around called cabers. Singing is also important as we do it while we work. We have hundreds of old songs that we sing while working the wool to help us keep time and make the job more fun. The songs typically have simple words and repeat oft. The significant part is they all have a steady rhythm to go along with the working.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;What Food Do They Like?\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;We have various foods that we enjoy eating. One of my preferred foods to eat that causes me to feel like I am home on the Isle of Jura, is haggis. Haggis is a sort of sausage, that can be made from lots of parts of the animal that we don't use for anything else. Scots don't normally abide waste and while some folks might think it is gross you would be missing out if you've never tried it. My grandmother had the most delicious recipe for haggis in my whole village. She would use all the usual organ meats like the liver, kidney, heart, and lungs. Though she also included a hearty portion of trip to her haggis. It made it extra nice and moist. The Haggis here in Rinascita is still good, but it just doesn't compare to my grandmother's haggis.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page05:title">
         X[S] A Taste of Culture with Margrat Maclean
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06">
         X[S] This portion of the paper is dedicated to all crafters of the city who reside in a guild either as a member or leader. Each issue I will single out one crafter of the many to bring them to the light for those who may or may not know of them. It is crucial to support guild crafters; we work hard at what we do, and it's never easy. I respect each person on this list who knows the struggle of spending hours, money, and time learning to hone your skills to be almost perfect. So be sure to look their way when you are in need.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;In this issue I want to discuss Mister Pio, he is a new carpenter to the city and is eager to learn. While his list may not be as large as others, I believe his eagerness to help the city will make up for what he lacks. Be sure to greet him to our great city and send orders to him when you can. A crafter can only get better with practice and we are a city that supports each other. Not only does he take his craft seriously, but I have also found him to be kind, funny, and easy to talk to. Keep reading to page eight so you can get to know him a little more.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;-------------------------------\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Bookbinders]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Maena\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Carpenters]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Christian\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bjorn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Pio\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Jayland\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Dyers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Orla\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tara\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Preston\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Lacey\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Hairstylists]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Thalia\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Lacey\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Healers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Persephone\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Genvieve\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Trinity\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Jewelers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bruno\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Gus\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Heather\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Seamstresses/Tailors]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Orla\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tara\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Carolyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tamm\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Preston\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Valeria\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Smiths]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Bruno\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Heather\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;[Weavers]:\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Carolyn\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Tamm\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page06:title">
         X[S] Crafters Spotlight - by J'Orla Couture
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07">
         X[S] Welcome to the City: Thalia Solandis\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Pio Marini has only just recently arrived in the city, appearing the night of the French ball for Saint Valentine. He lost both of his parents and was raised as an orphan. He got into woodworking to help repair and aid the places he was staying in. He arrived in our city so that he could find teachers to help him in furthering his skill. He is quite fond of sour things and enjoys spending time whittling and making little things out of cords of lumber.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;Upcoming Events and News: J'Orla Couture\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Audience with the Mistress of Robes: For those who may have business with the Crown or the Queen specifically, Viscountess Emeraude will soon be hosting Audience Hours. The first of these will take place on the Sixth Day at [Ten in the -morning-]. They will be held in the Administration Office. Should you not be able to make this time, you may scribe a Handmaiden to assist you in setting up a private meeting.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Spanish Royal Visit: This coming Sunday, the Royal Crown is hosting a celebration for the arrival of His Majesty, King Joel Velazquez of Spain and the newly coronated Queen Yasmin of Spain. This will take place at the Royal Palace and [Nine in the -evening-]. The Lord Chamberlain encourages all who plan to attend to don proper court attire.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Royal Ball: The Crown plan to host a lavish Ball to mark the closure and departure of the Spanish Royal Family. This has been marked to take place on the Fifteenth Day at [Nine in the -evening-]. Just as before, formal clothing strictly encouraged.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Crafters Emporium: The French Consulate are planning to resume their tradition of the Crafters Emporium. This is a gathering where the Consulate gives back to the crafters and charity by allowing the crafters to present their items to the city. Crafters wishing a spot should write to Countess Emmaline Beaumont for more information. It will take place on the Twenty-Ninth Day at [Nine in the -evening-]. An auction will be conducted on the same day for crafters who may own rare items.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Fruhling Feier Tanzen: The German Consulate is excited to announce their Spring Ball which will happen on the Eighteenth Day of April. It will be held in the Grand Salon at [Eight in the -evening-]. Guests are asked to dress in colors that remind them of spring. All questions may be directed to the German Consulate.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;- Gamble for Charity: On the Twenty-Sixth Day of April, Orla Couture will be hosting a Charity Social. Those who participate in the games will be playing for a charity of their choice. Each person will automatically be gifted a hundred florins towards their chosen charity so no go without a donation. The winner of each game will have their portion of winnings donated and receive a personal prize for their participation. This will take place in the Gamble Hall at [Eight in the -evening-]. Those wishing to join should contact Orla Couture.\\\&lt;br/\\\&gt;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:page07:title">
         X[S] Upcoming Socials and Announcements - by J'Orla Couture and Thalia Solandis
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:published">
         1583119287
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:quality">15</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trait:smells:lastchecked">
         1583111593
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
