<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="location:bruges">
         ([ "color":"green", "disable_martial_conflict":1, "disable_social_conflict":1, "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "icon":"historicalquarter.png", "position_x":63, "position_y":41.8, "ruler":"doloreaux", "ruler_name":"the Great House Doloreaux", "title":"Bruges", "tribute":\<Allegory:Guilds:germany\>, "tribute_name":"the Great House Doloreaux" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:chalon">
         ([ "color":"blue", "disable_martial_conflict":1, "disable_social_conflict":1, "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "icon":"historicalquarter.png", "position_x":80.1, "position_y":28.2, "ruler":"avoirdupois", "ruler_name":"the Great House of Avoirdupois", "title":"Chalon-Sur-Sauldre", "tokens":([ "defence":2 ]), "tribute":\<Allegory:Guilds:france\>, "tribute_name":"the Great House of Avoirdupois" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:corsair_1">
         ([ "color":"black", "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Xin Tsu", "icon":"palm-tree-export.png", "minimize":1, "position_x":26, "position_y":8, "ruler":"commoners", "ruler_name":"Jadelanders!", "title":"Jungle", "tokens":([ "defence":10000, "social":10 ]), "tribute_name":"Jadelanders" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:corsair_2">
         ([ "color":"black", "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Feronus Taslim", "icon":"palm-tree-export.png", "minimize":1, "position_x":35, "position_y":5, "ruler":"commoners", "ruler_name":"Jadelanders!", "title":"Islands", "tokens":([ "defence":10000, "social":10000 ]), "tribute_name":"Jadelanders" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:corsair_3">
         ([ "color":"black", "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Quisling Zhang", "icon":"landmark.png", "minimize":1, "position_x":40, "position_y":6.2, "ruler":"commoners", "ruler_name":"Jadelanders!", "title":"Terremoto Isola", "tokens":([ "defence":3492, "social":1000 ]), "tribute_name":"Jadelanders" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:harrowgate">
         ([ "color":"red", "disable_martial_conflict":1, "disable_social_conflict":1, "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "icon":"historicalquarter.png", "position_x":36.5, "position_y":43, "ruler":"bisclavret", "ruler_name":"the Great House Bisclavret", "title":"Harrowgate", "tribute":\<Allegory:Guilds:scotland\>, "tribute_name":"the Great House Bisclavret" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:port_lolonaise">
         ([ "color":"grey", "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Nobody (although Old Neant runs The Saltbelly, and commands a lot of influence)", "icon":"smallcity.png", "position_x":29, "position_y":9, "ruler":"commoners", "ruler_name":"Nobody (Both Bisclavret and Rinaldi claim ownership)", "title":"Port L'Olonoise", "tokens":([ "defence":10000, "social":2000 ]), "tribute_name":"Old Neant" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:salthaven">
         ([ "color":"grey", "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"A reeve, elected by the townsfolk", "icon":"landmark.png", "position_x":30.5, "position_y":6.1, "ruler":"commoners", "ruler_name":"Nobody (Both Bisclavret and Rinaldi claim ownership)", "title":"Salthaven", "tokens":([ "defence":10000, "social":2000 ]), "tribute_name":"Whoever is passing through" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:thanon">
         ([ "color":"red", "disable_martial_conflict":1, "disable_social_conflict":1, "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Angus McAlistair", "icon":"historicalquarter.png", "position_x":7.5, "position_y":49, "ruler":"bisclavret", "ruler_name":"Great House of Bisclavret", "title":"Thanon", "tokens":([ "defence":200, "social":200 ]), "tribute":\<Allegory:Guilds:scotland\>, "tribute_name":"Great House of Bisclavret" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="location:triskellian">
         ([ "color":"purple", "disable_martial_conflict":1, "disable_social_conflict":1, "governor":\<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, "governor_name":"Don Fidelio di Rinaldi", "icon":"palace-2.png", "position_x":62.2, "position_y":20, "ruler":"rinaldi", "ruler_name":"the Great House Rinaldi", "title":"Triskellian", "tribute":\<Allegory:Guilds:italy\>, "tribute_name":"the Great House of Rinaldi" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC", 1221752477, "???", "R", 1443250832, "tonyd", "E", 1443251401, "tonyd", "E", 1443252812, "tonyd", "E", 1443252860, "tonyd", "E", 1443252888, "tonyd", "E", 1443252911, "tonyd", "E", 1443252977, "tonyd", "E", 1443252994, "tonyd", "E", 1443253006, "tonyd", "E", 1443253020, "tonyd", "E", 1443253030, "tonyd", "E", 1443253041, "tonyd", "E", 1443253053, "tonyd", "E", 1443253069, "tonyd", "E", 1443253081, "tonyd", "E", 1443253092, "tonyd", "E", 1443253290, "tonyd", "E", 1443253775, "tonyd", "E", 1443253791, "tonyd", "E", 1443253803, "tonyd", "E", 1443253817, "tonyd", "E", 1443253828, "tonyd", "E", 1443253840, "tonyd", "E", 1443253910, "tonyd", "E", 1443254359, "tonyd", "E", 1443254636, "tonyd", "E", 1443254945, "tonyd", "E", 1443255335, "tonyd", "E", 1443255402, "tonyd", "E", 1443255427, "tonyd", "E", 1443255445, "tonyd", "E", 1443255461, "tonyd", "E", 1443255477, "tonyd", "E", 1443255492, "tonyd", "E", 1443255509, "tonyd", "E", 1443255513, "tonyd", "E", 1443256016, "tonyd", "E", 1443256061, "tonyd", "E", 1443256608, "tonyd", "E", 1443256692, "tonyd", "E", 1443256751, "tonyd", "E", 1443256781, "tonyd", "E", 1443256842, "tonyd", "E", 1443256866, "tonyd", "E", 1443256898, "tonyd", "E", 1443269780, "tonyd", "E", 1443270137, "tonyd", "E", 1443270194, "tonyd", "E", 1443322398, "tonyd", "E", 1443322408, "tonyd", "E", 1443322416, "tonyd", "E", 1443322428, "tonyd", "E", 1443322436, "tonyd", "E", 1443328780, "tonyd", "E", 1443328805, "tonyd", "E", 1443328852, "tonyd", "E", 1443328865, "tonyd", "E", 1443328879, "tonyd", "E", 1443329336, "tonyd", "E", 1443329370, "tonyd", "E", 1443329389, "tonyd", "E", 1443329407, "tonyd", "E", 1443329422, "tonyd", "E", 1443329752, "tonyd", "E", 1443329776, "tonyd", "E", 1443329920, "tonyd", "E", 1443330097, "tonyd", "E", 1443330378, "tonyd", "E", 1443330514, "tonyd", "E", 1443330701, "tonyd", "E", 1443330713, "tonyd", "E", 1443330797, "tonyd", "E", 1443330836, "tonyd", "E", 1443330956, "tonyd", "E", 1443330976, "tonyd", "E", 1443330990, "tonyd", "E", 1443331318, "tonyd", "E", 1443331664, "tonyd", "E", 1443331818, "tonyd", "E", 1443331839, "tonyd", "E", 1443331875, "tonyd", "E", 1443332214, "tonyd", "E", 1443332235, "tonyd", "E", 1443332246, "tonyd", "E", 1443332257, "tonyd", "E", 1443332440, "tonyd", "E", 1443332510, "tonyd", "E", 1443332523, "tonyd", "E", 1443332617, "tonyd", "E", 1443332667, "tonyd", "E", 1443332784, "tonyd", "E", 1443332807, "tonyd", "E", 1443332898, "tonyd", "E", 1443332916, "tonyd", "E", 1443333057, "tonyd", "E", 1443333426, "tonyd", "E", 1443333439, "tonyd", "E", 1443333478, "tonyd", "E", 1444445599, "tonyd", "P", 1444445608, "tonyd", "P", 1444445618, "tonyd", "P", 1444445640, "tonyd", "P", 1444445647, "tonyd", "P", 1464065165, "tonyd", "P", 1464065371, "tonyd", "P", 1464065379, "tonyd", "P", 1464065391, "tonyd", "P", 1464065399, "tonyd", "P", 1464065689, "tonyd", "P", 1464065762, "tonyd", "P", 1464065801, "tonyd", "P", 1464065874, "tonyd", "P", 1464065930, "tonyd", "P" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:bruges">
         "\<h2\>\\"Iron Tusks and Gardener's Souls\\"\</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\>History\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux made their home on the northern part of Calabria, moving quickly to claim the area between the Rother and Lyore rivers. Their arrival was not without violence --- the Doloreaux expansion was the first to buffet the Rinaldi, and later the Avoirdupois and Bisclavret. Young lords, eager to stake their claims to land, went to war whenever they thought they could win. After many victories and few losses, the Doloreaux have staked their claim . . . but they command no sea ports, and their farmland can only sustain their cirrent population.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Current Affairs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux are in a stalemate. Surrounded by rival houses, and with only enough farmland for subsistence, their holdings have no room to grow. Their leaders have chosen to expand their power through material wealth . . . which means dealing with the Guilds of Triskellian.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Friends and Foes \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux have few friends. The Avoirdupois believe that all other noble houses should be evicted from Clalabria, and the Bisclavret have their eyes keen on expansion. The Chevernaise do not negotiate with anyone. The Rinaldi\\\\\&#8217;s power has all but disappeared. A stoic lot, the Doloreaux house is resigned to campaign against everyone, biding their time. They are building their resources through the help of sympathetic Triskellians and minor houses. They hope to expand their land holdings and be strong enough to keep their new borders --- no easy feat, given the Bisclavret\\\\\&#8217;s mercenaries and Avoirdupois\\\\\&#8217; great forces.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Geography \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux lands are bounded by the southern foothills of the Rothos Mountains. Their western border with the Bisclavret is the edge of the Rother River and the southern portion past the eastern face of the Walls of Calabria. It then proceeds down the western side of northern road past the beginning of the Granvert and stopping at the Three Corner fort. Their eastern border is the length of the Lyore River and they are faced there by the Avoirdupois.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Landmarks \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>Bruges:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThis largest of all the Doloreaux cities is the focus of their financial efforts to maintain their shaky hold on their kingdom. Its battlements are a blocky affair: its squat, square towers and walls are on a raised plateau, surrounded by a moat. Its back is to the mountain face and it faces toward the Lyore River. Some say there is a network of caverns behind the battlements, which is the Doloreaux\\\\\&#8217;s real fortress.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>The Walls of Calabria:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nThese massive cliffs tower over the adjoining rivers of the Rother and Lyore. Fully half a league high, they stand in testament to the might of the Granvert River, which roars toward Triskellian. Some speculate that these could not be the creation of the river alone.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>Auriville:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nA small town far up-river, closest to the Chevernaise pass, this hamlet would be considered pastoral and serene were it not for the fresh bulwarks and defenses built around it, as the other Noble Houses se it as a prime target for acquisition.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>The Sacred Grove of Lutara:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nLocated somewhere in the Doloreaux foothills is reportedly a thick, uncut forest that the Doloreaux rangers do not permit anyone to enter. The local serfs have been known to refer to this area as the \\\\\&#8220;Harvest Haunt\\\\\&#8221; and they give it a wide berth. Since some Doloreaux are known to be ardent worshippers of an old faith, it is assumed that the Lutara Grove must be part of some religious mystery. Others whisper in hushed tones about more unsavory things.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Climate \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Doloreaux lands are deep inland and bordered by mountains, their winters are milder than most, although there is a rainy season in the spring. Doloreaux live in a land whose temperature varies widely. When it is winter in Auriville it may be a balmy day in Bruges.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Flora and Fauna \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The forests run toward the softer woods, good for building, but poor for ships or bows. Their farms tend to be terraced and grow mostly root crops. Some serfs attempt to raise drays on the scrub that grows in the hills, but they lack the skill and resources for proper destriers.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Economy \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux have willingly adopted the denar as a unit of currency. The hills yield the iron, tin, and copper necessary to make cannons, which the gentry sell to buy the other goods they need. The hills are also a reasonable source of gems stones and precious metals. It is from their mountains that they extract and ship the finest ores and gems in all Calabria. Their skill in the mines is unequalled and is surpassed only by their skill in trade.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Customs \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Most Doloreaux maintain a belief in the Old Faith, despite the efforts of Penitent missionaries. The deities worshipped vary from place to place, but the worship of Lutara invariably enjoys popularity above others. Their festivals and rites are renowned for their opulence. Conservative by nature, most Doloreaux look upon the prudish customs of S\\\\\&#8217;allumer with disdain, and upon the secular modernism of wizardry and technology with distaste. Most folk continue to use the old Doloreaux calandar.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Law \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Doloreaux law is simple and tends to conform closely to that in Triskellian. This is fairly new and as a result has been an increase in overall trade. This combined with their acceptance of the denar as their primary currency has made the Doloreaux a mercantile power.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Religion \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Although recently they have \\"Seen the light\\" of S'allumer, many whisper that the Doloreaux still maintain belief in the secretive \\\\\&#8220;Old Faith,\\\\\&#8221; often called \\\\\&#8220;Lutarism\\\\\&#8221; because of their goddess Lutara \\\\\&#8220;the Lady.\\\\\&#8221; Their religion is dominated by a sacred order of High Mystes, whose membership is exclusively female. The Hierarchs of Lutara command supernatural mysteries beyond the understanding of scholarly wizards, and they do not share their secrets with unbelievers or outsiders.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Armed Forces \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Despite an aggressive campagn to motdenize to gunpowder, most of the Doloreaux levy and cavalry are still equipped with spears, swords, and shields. Fortunately, with their highly-defensible position, the Doloreaux do not need to modernize too quickly. They have been biding their time and building their assets.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Language \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Increased commerce with Triskellian has encouraged the Doloreaux folk to learn Calabrese. The Doloreaux family dialect is still practiced, but only among the gentry.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Names \</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Men\\\\\&#8217;s given names include Burcet, Gauthier, Kalman, Mercer, and Tybault. Women\\\\\&#8217;s names include Calendre, Eglantine, Liana, Patrice, and Vivienne. Doloreaux surnames are more likely to be taken from the place they hail from (such as des Feurebouche, des Vosges, des Lyore, or des Mortemere), or from the month of their birth (such as d\\\\\&#8217;Aubepine, de Chene, de Houx, de Vigne, or de Roseau) than their family name, unless they are of noble blood --- then such surnames include Bien-etre, Cattermaux, and DeLume.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:chalon">
         "\<h2\>\\"Pure in Thought, Pure in Deed\\"\</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\>History\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The equine Avoirdupois claim that their noble line is the oldest and the proudest of all time. To back up their claim, the Avoirdupois maintain the oldest known castles and have the longest written records of anyone in Calabria. Steeped in tradition, members of this house are known for their unfailing courage, their unfaltering attention to their chivalric code, and their intolerance for everything not \\"Avoirdupois\\".\<br/\>\\r\\nThe Avoirdupois are proud and strong, fleet of hoof and of mind. They control the vast sweeping northeastern plains of Calabria. Their great vineyards and sweeping manors are responsible for most of the specialized food production on the continent. They pride themselves on having the swiftest army in the land and the most rigorously trained knights. They wish to maintain their open fields and keep their heritage intact. Despite their military stance, they are also quite concerned with the knightly virtues of loyalty and honor. None could be said to be more pious than an Avoirdupois knight on the morning of battle.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Current Affairs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois control a large demesne of plains to the east of the City of Triskellian - but the Avoirdupois claim to have a history that dates back before any of the other cultures on Calabria. They make little secret of what they see as their \\"manifest destiny\\" - the domination of all of Calabria. At first glance, such a goal might make people unlikely to do business with them, much less ally with them. However, the Avoirdupois are nothing if not chivalrous - they always keep their word and never stab anyone in the back.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Friends and Foes\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois are outspoken foes of the Bisclavret and the Doloreaux. They do not appreciate the Doloreaux control of the River Lyore and are rankled by having to buy timber from the Bisclavret. They tolerate the presence of the Constabulary of Triskellian - as long as they \\"remember their place\\".\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Geography\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois control a large estate of hills and plains to the east of Triskellian. They are bordered on the south by the Paludestris, on the east by ocean cliffs, on the west by Triskellian and the Granvert River, on the north-northwest by the Lyore River and the Doloreaux. Their fields and farms are well situated in the heart of their territory, well-protected from attack. The Sauldre river feeds the farms and supplies the Avoirdupois with a small river trade.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Landmarks:\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>Chateau d'Avoirdupois:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nLocated at the center of their largest city, Chalon su Sauldre, it is also their ruling seat and home to the House of Avoirdupois. This oldest functioning castle in Calabria sprawls out on a wide flat plateau with treacherous sides. The plateau was shaped generations ago by the deliberate designs of clever engineers. The might of the entire Avoirdupois race was necessary to build the great plateau. The castle is in a dumbbell shape with high parapets and meticulously-maintained catapults.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>The Barrows:\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nIn the center of one of the rocky hills unsuitable for farmaland is a cluster of oddly-shaped hills. If one looks around long enough, they may find the secret entrance to the tunnels below. Within the twisting corridors are interred the bones of uncountable skeletons, of various races and sizes. The people who built these barrows are unknown, and so is the reason they chose such a location. The Avoirdupois histories have yielded no clues. Some say the barrows are haunted, and that the dead walk, searching for the souls of the living. Others say it's a thief's hideout, and that villians who lurk there perpetuate the rumors to keep people away.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Climate\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The wind often howls across the mostly-treeless plains. While the Avoirdupois have an extensive irrigation system, it only works well in the summer. Winters in this land are notoriously harsh.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Flora and Fauna\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Much of the land is either farmland or wild grasslands. The few trees are clustered together in small forests that are zealously guarded by Avoirdupois rangers. Only small game and livestock are to be found outside of ranches. The richest Avoirdupois raise their own destriers.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Economy\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois are very efficient farmers, but their lack of lumber hampers them immensely. To compensate, many farmers live in sod houses or even earthern homes. Their organization is impressive - precise records are kept, and taxes are collected on time. The skilled serfs are rewarded; the poor performers are punished. The Avoirdupois also maintain their own arms, using techniques handed down for generations. It is illegal for Avoirdupois serfs to accept denarii.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Customs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Avoirdupois lifestyle is austere - as one scholar described it, \\"first toil, the the grave.\\" Avoirdupois of all ages have a great sense of pride in their land and holdings be they serf, tradesman, merchant or noble. All of the gentry regularly drill in the arts of combat and heraldry, male and female alike. Manners and etiquette are not only valued, but mandatory. To outsiders, the Avoirdupois look humorless and severe. They use the S'allumer calender to measure their days.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Law\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>All gentry are schooled in the precise laws of Avoirdupois rule, unchanged in over a hundred years. Ignorance of the law is no excuse, and the nobles have no patience with scofflaws. Low justice is meted out on the spot, and is usually a quick beating for light crimes, indentured servitude for greater offenses, and summary execution for murderers or worse.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Religion\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The \\"approved\\" religion of Avoirdupois nobles is Penitence of S'allumer. Serfs and underlings are expected to worship as their lord does, but this is not always the case. Local churches are small and modest, as the Avoirdupois prefer their worship to be as simple and pragmatic as their lifestyles, and not weighted down with grandiose icons, but as the influence of the Church grows, so do their buildings and estates.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Armed Forces\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Since all gentry, save the infirm or young children, are combat-worthy and highly-disciplined, the Avoirdupois can field land-based forces more formidable than any on Calabria. Conservative by nature, they prefer not to engage a foe unless they can win a quick, decisive victory, which explains why the Avoirdupois have yet to campaign in earnest to fulfill their \\"manifest destiny\\" as rulers of all Calabria.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Language\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The modern, pragmatic Avoirdupois speak Calabrese. The Avoirdupois have refused to translate their law books into a more common language, so as not to \\"alduterate\\" their meaning.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Names\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Examples of male given names include Astolpho, Ignace, Somer, and Warrane. For women, Albracca, Calandre, Fanette, and Joanna.\<br/\>\\r\\nAvoirdupois are most likely to pay homage to their family, and will include that in their name. Some noble surnames include Boulanger, Chausse, Criniere, Enclume, and Sabot - for example, a noble's full name might be Astolpho du Sabot l'Avoirdupois. Other Avoirdupois fancy themselves as \\"knights errant\\" and drop their surname in favor of just their family, such as Anton d'Avoirdupois.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:corsair_1">
         "\<p\>The largest island in the Corsairs, containing lush dangerous jungle.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>Very difficult to navigate, full of diseases and dangerous wildlife, with jungles in the interior and mangroves along the coasts. Fresh water is unreliable and hard to find.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:corsair_2">
         "\<p\>A small chain of islands, containing a mix of mountains, fields, sand and settlements.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:corsair_3">
         "\<p\>This semi-active volcano has created an island that creates a mix of high rocky cliffs and ledges, covered with fertile green jungles.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>The white beaches of Terremoto Isola are a spectacle to behold, and the hot springs are a luxury few ever experience.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>Terremoto Isola would host a major farming community if there was a steady water supply. The only fresh water to be found is rainwater that has gathered in pools in the rocks.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:harrowgate">
         "\<h2\>\\"From Stone \& Wood to Brick \& Steel\\"\</h2\>\\r\\n\<h3\>History\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Bisclavret were once part of the demesne of the Phelan. Over three hundred years ago, on the night of the \\"Seiscethir,\\" the Bisclavret proclaimed themselves a seperate nation. They threw off the trappings of their old ways and embraced the \\"modernism\\" of the Church of S'allumer, of kings and vassals, of commerce and technology. Today they are a formidable Noble House in their own right. \<br/\>\\r\\nTheir control over the northwestern forests of Calabria has given them the economic power to build an army second only to the Avoirdupois. The might of their mercenaries and the quality of their troops should not be doubted. They have pretensions of being a great power but are limited by endless infighting and lack of supplies. Their nobles are forever in a contest over land and status, each trying to best the other. Their shipping industry has been a priority of late and is growing.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>At one time, the Bisclavret thought they could compete with the port of Triskellian through lower taxes and dock fees. However, that resulted in Bisclavret shores becoming glutted with pirate ships, slavers' frigates, and an influx of unsavory characters onto their lands. In the past twenty years, the Bisclavret have tried to \\"reclaim\\" their shipyards, mostly by intimidating people to leave, sometimes seizing their ships and enslaving their crews.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Current Affairs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Bisclavret make the other noble houses nervous. Apparently, the Bisclavret gentry have seen the future, and they believe that sea power will play a dominant role. Their control over most of the lumber in Calabria places them in a fine position to control ship construction. To further their own power, the only ships allowed to dock at their ports are either owned outright by the Bisclavret or have purchased expensive \\"letters of marque.\\"\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Friends and Foes\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Since they closed their ports to foreigners, the Bisclavret enjoy improved (if somewhat strained) relations with the city of Triskellian. Since the Avoirdupois view all other inhabitants of Calabria as \\"squatters,\\" the Bisclavret do not get along with them. The Doloreaux are envious of the Bisclavret seaports, but neither is willing to risk a land conflict.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Geography\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Bisclavret holdings run along the southern coast, and deep into heavily-forested areas. They are bordered by the ocean on the south and west, and their territory stretches far into the dark northern forests. Somewhere in the deep northern woods is the blurry boundary between the Bisclavret and their tribal cousins the Phelan. Triskellian borders their southeastern reach. Directly to the east are the Rother and Granvert rivers and across them are the lands of the Doloreaux and Avoirdupois. While they and the Phelan may control the rocky mountains of the far north, no one has bothered to move into the inhospitable area, and prospectors have not found any significant mineral wealth.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Landmarks\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>Harrowgate\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nLong ago, a meeting hall with a watchtower was built on a high hill. The hall and tower became what is now the center of the Harrowgate Castle. It is a massive circular structure of stone quarried from the banks of Lake Coire. It is surrounded on all sides by a flat expanse of low grassy fields then beyond into the heavily patrolled forest. It is bordered on its northwest side by Lake Coire.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>The Invisible Guild\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nRumors circulate of a gang of pirates and marines who have a base of operations in one of the Bisclavret ports. Legend says they call themselves \\"The Invisible Guild\\" in mockery of the rigidly-organized and xenophobic Merchant Guilds of Triskellian. The Invisibles are purported to sell forged letters of marque and to smuggle illegal goods into Calabria.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>The Unfinished Bridge\</em\>\<br/\>\\r\\nJutting out from the west coast in the port of Thanon is a wide bridge, built centuries ago by some forgotten race or culture. A remarkable feat of engineering, it extends over one hundred paces into the water. The western end is broken, but not crumbling... and it only faces the endless sea. Was there once an island off the shore? Or was the bridge built for some mad, unknown purpose? The only clue is the cornerstone of the bridge, with the script written in a language yet to be deciphered.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Climate\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>In the depths of the forests it is quite cool and mild, though during the summer, the lands of Bisclavret are notoriously buggy. In the south the weather is often rainy and warm. In winter, the port of Tharon freezes over and becomes unusable. The forests become blanketed with a thick layer of snow.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Flora and Fauna\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Bisclavret lands are thick with forests and undergrowth. Clear-cut forest is being converted to farm-land; often gunpowder is used to blow up stumps. The fishing grounds outside Bisclavret inlets are good. The gentry also maintain livestock, in the form of domesticated saurians, as the Bisclavret and their kin are consumers of meat. While once the forests were run with monsters such as the thick-skinned, fanged \\"bethrachanna,\\" today the forests are cleared of most beasts... and are over-run with bandits.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Economy\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Wood is constantly in demand, and no one on Calabria has more wood than the Bisclavret. In return, they often trade for metals that they lack. Thus the Bisclavret need the Doloreaux metal as much as the Avoirdupois need Bisclavret wood. The Bisclavret mint their own coins, called fibulae, but these coins are only of value in Bisclavret lands, and mercenaries will prefer to be paid in denarii.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Customs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Like most noble families, the Bisclavret revere tradition and the codes of chivalry. Those of lower status are expected to bow and defer to their betters, although there has been known to be some bickering in the ranks. The have a particular problem with duels amongst the nobles as they vie for title and rank amongst themselves. Positions and titles are awarded by bloodline to the strong and loyal; disputes within and between bloodlines are settled by combat.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Law\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Unlike Triskellian, the Bisclavret tax codes are confusing. They tend to vary greatly from region to region and city to city. This is primarily due to feuds between the various officials and households. Corruption among dock officials is widespread; often wardens can be bribed and forged letters of marque can be obtained by those in the know.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Religion\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>As part of their attempt to appear more modern, many Bisclavret converted to S'allumer. Among the serfs, and even a few gentry, there are a considerable number who still practice their older religions, even though such practices are proscribed by Bisclavret law. These are as varied and rich as the Chevernaise. Churches are usually small affairs, even in Harrowgate.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Armed Forces\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Bisclavret royal family is smaller than either the Avoirdupois or Doloreaux - but they employ large numbers of fairly loyal mercenaries of both their own race and many others. The gentry are also investing in gunpowder cannons, for both ships and field carriages, although the artillerists have to be imported.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Language\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Calabrese is the default language of trade, and it is commonly spoken in Bisclavret territory. It has become something of a tradition for Bisclavret officers to learn a smattering of the Berla Feini, so that they may have a pidgin they may communicate to one another with in front of their mercenaries. Both of these languages are in addition to their already complex system of body language.\</p\>\\r\\n\<h3\>Names\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>\\"Before Riddock's Dawn, Families would claim lineage along their mothers' lines, but this practice has since been outlawed. Now that wealth is inherited solely along male lines, only the name of the father's family (or patronym) is taken. As with all modern folks, Bisclavret citizens havce two names: their first name and their family name.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\"Claiming descent from Noble Bisclavret families is a great honor. The Families include Afligeant, Buadhachan, Devlin, Ealdarach, Fagen, Raciner, and Uilleam. Cousins of one of these first families might have Mac added to their family name; for example, Logan MacFagan is not a Fagan in pure blood, but he can claim lineage to their line.\<br/\>\\r\\n\\"Families of the servants of the Bisclavret often have the prefix Gil- orKil-, meaning \\"one who serves.\\" For example, Dona Gilleam's name is derived from Gil-Ulleam ; her family probably served the Uilleam clan for generations. Mercenaries often use \\"Giolla\\" as an improvised last name, a custom dating back to the Bianfael, which simply means \\"servant.\\"\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:port_lolonaise">
         "\<p\>This town, situated on a particularly inhospitable stretch of shore and extending on rickety piers over the buffeting waves, acts as a home away from home for the most hardened and vile of characters. Pirates who are too notorious to dispose of their booty in any Calabrese port come to Port L'Olonoise to spend their ill-gotten gains.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Port is especially infamous for The Saltbelly, a tavern, bawdy-house, pawn-broker, and slave market. This reprehensible hive actually lies underneath the water. The location of the entrance is a secret that can be bought for a few denarii from any knowledgeable Port ruffian.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:salthaven">
         "\<p\>This village hangs precariously off the side of a rocky prominence. About two-dozen ramshackle wooden buildings are home to about three hundred people of almost every race.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>The people of Salthaven earn a living through fishing and, it is rumoured, smuggling.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>It is also rumoured that the Bisclavret maintain an Indicateur office here, but if so, it serves as little more than an observation post.\</p\>\\r\\n\<p\>The town's inhabitants answer to an elected reeve.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:thanon">
         "\<p\>Situated on a narrow spit of rocky land, Thanon is the western-most settlement in Calabria. It gazes out towards an unknown horizon, lashed by frequent storms and floods. Thanon is often the first view of Calabria seen by the crews of foreign vessels, and it is a grim one.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="text:triskellian">
         "\<h2\>City of Triskellian - InDepth\</h2\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>\<em\>\&quot;Honorable Guild-Master Navigator Maratuch:\<br /\>\\r\\nMy greetings and prayers unto you. I would that this were a happy writing. I have of late received the map of Triskellian which I commossioned from you a fortnight ago. As I gazed upon it I could not help but notice certain inaccuracies and omissions of detail. Your depiction of the Cathedrale of Temoin is almost heretical. By eliminating its majestic dome and replacing it with a single spire, you cheat it of its beauty. Our marvelous aqueduct system has been reduced to a mere trickle. Those reading this map would think us lax indeed, for they could only assume that we throw our offal into the streets. Our grand markets, which are equaled by none, you have reduced to a mere blank space. All who know the truth will surely realize the Great Market is only one of a dozen spread throughout the parishes. To sum up this letter, I will not levy unto you the sum of two aureals for which you originally asked. Either correct your errors or receive no payment.\&quot;\</em\>\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>5th of Hawthorn Moon, 2nd of Fidelio \<br /\>\\r\\nFaithful servant of the Light, \<br /\>\\r\\nMaster Merchant Trallius of House Belette\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Brief History\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Upon the Bay of Auvrich in the lands of Lykaemon lies the city of Triskellian. Rumors abound that buildings in the older parts of the city are far older than any modern history book. The bulk of affairs take place in the new districts, near the dockyards - where the Guilds hold sway.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>The vulpine Rinaldi were the founding family, led by their powerful and wise patriarch Don Jon. He rebuilt Triskellian around its ancient ruins and established his clan there and in the surrounding territory. Triskellian grew to be a port city and, since transport of goods overland was dangerous and expensive, it flourished. The Granvert River and the roads from the north brought the wealth of Calabria to Triskellian's markets. Here one can find Bisclavret timber, Doloreaux gems and Avoirdupois armor. The Rinaldi's influence on the other houses is great, for it is in their city where fortunes are made and lost. Here is the place to find a tradesman of the finest skill, a mage of the highest caliber and a thief of great ability.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>The Rinaldi are not without their troubles. Of late, they have become more and more consumed with infighting and have let their precious city slip away. Some say it is the recent conversion to S'allumer by the Don and his high court that led to the disappearance of one of the duchesses and her reluctance to come into the Light. But they still rule with an iron fist and an eye for the market. Should trouble ever arise, the Rinaldi are well defended by more than military might. Their city is home to many of the Houses' highest nobles and their fortunes will not be easily taken.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Current Affairs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Today, the Guild Council controls the police, the dockyards, the gates, the libraries - everything within the city save the deed itself. Their power is economic in nature. Triskellian is far too valuable as a free trading port for the Great Houses. Thus its very prosperity is its mightiest shield. What of the Rinaldi? They are far from powerless. Their might is more in the market, the Church, and their cunning than in any army.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Friends and Foes\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Triskellian is situated on the inlet of the Granvert River and the Bay of Auvrich. Being the southern-most port it never freezes over and is in an easily-defended position. Should any one army lay siege to the city, it can always be resupplied by its allies, for no one Noble House has the strength to both blockade the city and besiege it simultaneously. Hills and farmland surround it on the north, west, and east sides. A few centuries ago, a wall was built around the city. When the population expanded, new buildings were built outside the \&quot;old\&quot; wall, eventually a \&quot;new\&quot; wall was built around the entire town. These two districts are often referred to as \&quot;Old Town\&quot; and \&quot;New Town.\&quot;\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Landmarks of Triskellian\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>(These are not necessarily represented in our gameworld yet and some may never be)\<br /\>\\r\\n\<br /\>\\r\\n\<u\>Cathedrale de Temoin:\</u\> \<br /\>\\r\\nLocated on the border of Old Town, this sprawling edifice stands as a monument to the compassion of Helloise. It is the central icon and holy site for the faith of S'allumer. Its giant ivory dome dominates the northeastern skyline of Triskellian. The Cathedrale, besides being a place of reverence, is a site of great learning and contains what may be the largest library in the known world. Penitents make a pilgrimage to it each year, flooding Triskellian with customers and bedeviling the Constabulary.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>\<u\>The Old Tower: \</u\>\<br /\>\\r\\nIn the middle of Old Town, there stands an unused crumbling watchtower. Today, the tower is too short and the city too large for it to offer a view of anything but the dilapidated inner city. The Old Tower has become a favorite hangout of criminals and other unsavory elements. If you wish trouble for yourself or others, the Old Tower and its surrounding parish are where it is to be found.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>\<u\>The Aqueducts: \</u\>\<br /\>\\r\\nThe founders of Triskellian designed an intricate system of canals, sewers, tunnels, and channels for transporting water. The Constabulary puts alot of effort into keeping the Aqueducts in good condition. Often, work-gangs of arrested criminals are put to work busting clogs, mortaring stones, and doing alot of the unsavory heavy labor.\<br /\>\\r\\n \<br /\>\\r\\n\<u\>The Three Spears Inn: \</u\>\<br /\>\\r\\nAn expensive, rambling structure at the north gate to the city, the Three Spears Inn is famous for its plushly-furnished rooms, its warm bath and cold baths, and its outrageous prices.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Climate\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Triskellian is on the southern coast of Calabria, where the summers are pleasant though not extremely hot. Storms come in from the west and pass upward into the plains of the Avoirdupois. The winters are cold, although the bay does not freeze over. The ports are open throughout the year.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Flora and Fauna\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Triskellian is a town of brick, stone, and earth which has been worked on by thousands of inhabitants over hundreds of years. Most dwellings are stone, with the streets paved with cobblestone. What little greenery there is exists only in the private walled gardens of the rich Guild Masters, Merchant Captains and Nobles. The only fauna are the drays and similar livestock at the market and the vermin in the sewers and dark corners.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Economy\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Because Triskellian is a port of call, most trading and economic transactions are done in the currency of the Rinaldi. The denar, as the silver coin is called, is worth a Stevedore's work for half a day. The only other coin used is the aureal; it is gold and is worth 24 denarii. Those who are too poor to earn denarii trade in barter and are usually paid in the same manner. Barter is not restricted exclusively to the lower classes. Nobles and Guild Masters simply barter in more expensive items and services. A full third of the city's trade is still done by barter.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>The Guilds of Triskellian\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>Triskellian is an unusual city; it alone on Calabria has guilds independent of the noble houses. They have the House Rinaldi to thank for their freedom. Over the years the Rinaldi have been more and more consumed with infighting and have left more and more of the city's administration to the Guilds and Constabulary.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>Guilds in other lands and cities are generally beholden to the nobility for profit and advancement. Some hundred years ago Auvrich II, then Don of the Rinaldi, became tired of running the city and keeping up with court intrigue. The Avoirdupois were contesting the Doloreaux claims and fighting had broken out along their common border. In haste Don Auvrich II appointed a Council of the then largest Guilds in the city with the mayor of the Constabulary to oversee the city's governance. The guilds which comprise the Council are: Merchants, Ironsmiths, Navigators, Shipwrights, Millers \&amp; Weavers.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>When a young child is taken as apprentice, he can expect to serve his Master in every capacity. A cooper's apprentice, for example, can be expected to clean the shop, care for the tools and run all manner of errands. For the first several years he will learn only the rudiments of barrel making. It will only be later, when the Master is satisfied of his readiness, that the true secrets of the craft will be passed along. The Master, for his part, is bound by the Orders of the Guild to teach his craft in full and to the best of his ability.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>The time in apprenticeship varies from craft to craft and trade to trade, ranging from five to eight years. When apprentices have successfully completed their trials, they are brought into the Guild as Journeymen. Then they either leave the services of the Master to set up another shop (often many leagues away in another city), or the Journeymen stay on at the Master's as senior craftsmen.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>If he chooses to leave then he may take on apprentices of his own. He then becomes a Master in his own right. Not all Masters are created equal. Those who have distinguished themselves in the quality and perfection of their craft will have more apprentice applicants to choose from. This allows the truly talented master room to pick and choose, thus insuring that he gets only the most talented apprentices. He thereby increases his reputation further.\</p\>\\r\\n \\r\\n\<h3\>Customs\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The citizenry of Triskellian are very cosmopolitan. All manner of commoner and noble can be found wandering its streets and skulking in its shadows. People arrive from dozens of lands, bringing their own customs. Within the city, people of like culture live together in parishes. Each parish has its own distinct flavor and atmosphere. To find oneself amongst the otters is to be assured of a tasty meal, while to find oneself amongst the rats is to risk larceny, at best.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Laws\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The citizenry of Triskellian prefer to think of themselves as \&quot;free,\&quot; without the need for lords and masters. However, the charter of the city still acknowledges the Guild Council and the Mayor to be commoners, and not of noble birth - and as such, the magistrates and constables of Triskellian can only mete out \&quot;low justice,\&quot; the law of common folk. Nobles of the \&quot;blooded\&quot; royal families can only be tried by other nobles, not by \&quot;low judges.\&quot;\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>High Justice is meted out by the High Court, whose Justices are entirely of noble birth. There is one representative from each of the Great and Minor houses. They are appointed by their sovereigns for a period of not less than five years. Holding a proceeding of the court requires that there must be enough justices present to form a quorum (three-quarters of the total membership). The High Court deals with all the aspects of the law involving nobilitiy save those which are reserved for the monarchy.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>The Court of Commoners metes out low justice. These courts are presided over by the Magistrates. The Magistrates in turn report to the High Justices but are accountable only to the local officials. Magistrates hold proceedings most every day of the week and deal with all aspects of the law save those concerning the nobility. A typical session of Court might consist of hearing a murder case, simple larceny and minor trade disputes among commoners.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<p\>The commoner police, known as the Constabulary, can only hold gentry in custody, later handing them over to one of the three noble families for trial. Often issues of \&quot;legitimacy\&quot; crop up. Can an Avoirdupois criminal be tried in a Bisclavret court and expect a fair trial? The constables of Triskillion aren't always particular to whom they deliver their prisoner...but sometimes bribes or other favors play a role in the decision-making process.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Religion\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>As with customs, religion also varies from parish to parish. However, the city is the home of the Penitents of S'allumer, which is the primary religion of Calabria. The city observes all the high holy days of S'allumer, and every seventh day of the week is the day of Dimache where it is forbidden to exchange money within the city limits, by clerical and secular law. Each year pilgrims from across the land gather in the city to visit the Cathedrale de Temoin.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Armed Forces\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The Constabulary is composed of about three hundred regulars called \&quot;Captains\&quot;, and six hundred or so \&quot;Deputies\&quot;. The Guildsmen pay for their arms, armor, and wages from the excise taxes they collect. Constables are also entitled to shares of loot from arrested criminals. On the whole, the Constables are well paid, have high morale, and are seasoned combatants. They are also the best-equipped force in the known world, having all of the best arms and armor. The Constables drill for both skirmishes and for sieges, usually in plain view of noble house emissaries to \&quot;keep them guessing\&quot;. The Constabulary of Triskellian claims to remain neutral in the conflict between the Houses of Avoirdupois, Bisclavret, and Doloreaux. The constables tend to err on the side of the High Court in matter of the nobles.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Language\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The original tongue of the Rinaldi, and thus Triskellian, was Matriloquentia. Many Rinaldi nobles still speak it with a heavy accent, and some of the older Guild Masters do too, especially those who know the finer points of the law. Some Penitant ceremonies are conducted entirely in this older tongue. Today, the common language of Triskellian and the rest of the island is Calabrese. However, on the dockyards, the better merchants know a handful of languages to deal with their hodgepodge crew and their various customers.\</p\>\\r\\n\\r\\n\<h3\>Names\</h3\>\\r\\n\<p\>The original Rinaldis have Calabrese names. Some example given names for women include Agata, Bianca, Carlotta, Giulia and Volante; for men, Arnaldo, Davide, Enzo, Fidelio, Paolo, and Salvatorio. The polygot population of the city, coming from a dozen languages and cultures, has a wide variety of names.\</p\>"
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
