<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/help" owner="SkotOS">
  <Help:Node title="Quest">
    <Log:Description>
       <b>GENERAL CONCEPT: Quests</b>
<br/>Quests can be obtained by interacting with CNPC quest givers. They can range from simple, mundane jobs to time sensitive tasks with profound consequences. So read those instructions carefully! Whether or not a given CNPC is a quest giver is something to be discovered through experimentation (though they will occasionally drop hints if they are in need of some kind of help). Quest givers react to certain keywords which is unique to the type of job they have available.
<br/><br/>
<i>A burly sailor sighs, "I will never get these crates moved in time."</i>
<br/>
<i>\> You insist to a burly sailor, "Never fear, good man, for I will <b>help</b> you with those crates."</i>
<br/>
<i>A burly sailor perks at your words, "You want to <b>help</b> me move these crates, huh?"</i><br/>
<i>A burly sailor offers you a quest. Do you want to accept? <br/>
@yes/@no</i>
<br/>
<i>\> @yes</i>
<br/><br/>
Once you have accepted a quest, you can use the @quest command to check the status of the quest. You may also use this command to abandon the quest. However, note that if abandoning a quest will flag it as a fail and you will have to deal with any negative consequences that may occur as a result. When all the requirements for completing the quest, you will need to turn the quest in. Instructions for how to do this will be given by the quest giver but you may also double-check using the @quest command. In most cases, it will only require further interactions with a quest giver.
<br/><br/>
<i>\> You declare to a burly sailor, "I am <b>finished</b>!"</i>
<br/>
<i>A burly sailor smiles, "Hey great. Now I can meet the guys for some drinks. Here is a token of my thanks."</i>
<br/>
<i>A burly sailor hands you a rusty trinket.</i>
<br/>
<i>\> You cheer.</i>
<br/><br/>
<b>Note from Staff:</b><br/> While quests can be a fun form of entertainment, they are not meant to replace roleplay; they are meant to enhance it. Therefore we strongly recommend that quest hunting never be used a substitute to roleplay/plots as it will never be as rewarding as interacting with your fellow playerbase!
    </Log:Description>
    <Help:Keywords>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="@quest"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="quest"/>
      <Help:Keyword keyword="quests"/>
    </Help:Keywords>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1309488233, "rorschakovacs", "R", 1315246329, "jominey", "E", 1315246367, "jominey", "E", 1315247160, "jominey", "E", 1315247191, "jominey", "E", 1315247261, "jominey", "E", 1315247279, "jominey", "E", 1315247305, "jominey", "E", 1315247339, "jominey", "E", 1315247399, "jominey", "E", 1315247448, "jominey", "E", 1315247473, "jominey", "E", 1315247542, "jominey", "E", 1315247568, "jominey", "E", 1315247598, "jominey", "E", 1509728431, "jominey", "R", 1509841854, "jominey", "R" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:HelpNodes:UrHelpNode)"/>
  </Help:Node>
</object>
