<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="SkotOS">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1144052088, "-", "SYNC" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="trading:notes">
         (\{ "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 1 Purple eyeshadow.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 1 Purple eyeshadow has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 10 Bananas.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 1 Satara.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 1 Plum Tree.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 10 Bananas has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 5 Hot Chili Pepper.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 1 Matte Steel.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 1 Matte Steel has reached its conclusion.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 1 Plum Tree has reached its conclusion.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 5 Hot Chili Pepper has reached its conclusion.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 1 Satara has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 3 Cashmere Comforter.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 3 Cashmere Comforter has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 3 Angora Wool Bespread.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 3 Angora Wool Bespread has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 1 Barrel of Moonshine.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 1 Barrel of Moonshine has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 2 Glass Panel.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 2 Glass Panel has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 2 Eucalyptus Tree.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 2 Eucalyptus Tree has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 30 Chocolate-covered Strawberry.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 30 Chocolate-covered Strawberry has reached its conclusion.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 30 Honey-baked Almonds.", "Your guild has successfully won a trade deal for 30 Chocolate-drizzled Blueberry.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 30 Honey-baked Almonds has reached its conclusion.", "Your trading deal for the receipt of 30 Chocolate-drizzled Blueberry has reached its conclusion." \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
