<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="ezralee">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject urobject="OBJ(Ironclaw:World:UrInside)"/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="1" maxweight="1"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details>
      <Base:Detail id="default" prime="true" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames/>
          <Base:PNames/>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             wagon crowded with passengers
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="examine">
             All around you, passengers are crowded into the wagon as it slowly creaks through the wilderness heading away from the city of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="glance">
             All around you, passengers are crowded into the wagon as it slowly creaks through the wilderness heading away from the city of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             All around you, passengers are crowded into the wagon as it slowly creaks through the wilderness heading away from the city of Triskellian.
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="mapurl">
             http://i.imgur.com/66EdGAa.jpg
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="passengers" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="passenger"/>
            <Base:SName sname="person"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="people"/>
            <Base:PName pname="passengers"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             number of passengers crowded around you
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A large number of passengers are crowded into the wagon with you.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="plains" prime="false" def="false" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="plain"/>
            <Base:SName sname="surroundings"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="land"/>
            <Base:PName pname="plains"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             swath of plains swallowed by darkness
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             A swath of plains swallowed by the darkness of night.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
      <Base:Detail id="sky" prime="false" def="true" abstract="false" hidden="false" luminosity="0" targetable_in_dark="false" plural="false">
        <Base:Preposition close="false" against="false" under="false" on="false" inside="false" near="false" over="false" behind="false" before="false" beside="false"/>
        <Base:Names>
          <Base:SNames>
            <Base:SName sname="sky"/>
          </Base:SNames>
          <Base:PNames>
            <Base:PName pname="stars"/>
          </Base:PNames>
        </Base:Names>
        <Base:Adjectives/>
        <Base:Descriptions>
          <Base:Description type="brief">
             the starlit sky overhead
          </Base:Description>
          <Base:Description type="look">
             The sky overhead is lit by starlight.
          </Base:Description>
        </Base:Descriptions>
        <Base:Exit door="false" never_obvious="false" obvious_when_open="false" hidden_when_closed="false" separate="false" self-locking="false" deadbolt="false"/>
        <Base:Climbable/>
      </Base:Detail>
    </Base:Details>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="merry:lib:dream:begin">
         X[M] /* This script runs after the chatter has been teleported to their room and a dream has been chosen */

/* Immobilize chatter */
\$actor."base:immobile" = TRUE;

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("A violent pounding on your door wakes you from your slumber with a start. In the distance you hear dull chaos; screaming children, arguing, men shouting.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "acb1");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("The pounding at the door becomes louder, \\"Evacuate! You must leave the city or be left for dead!\\" You stumble from the bed and pull open the door only to be pulled out and pushed into the confused and chaotic group of people.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "c2c8");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Everything is in chaos as bodies shuffle and shift around one another in a tight knot, moving with the Constables who continue to grab others from their bedrooms as they move along.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "f157");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Before you realize exactly what is happening, the group is moving in unison, headed through the familiar streets toward the North Gate of the city.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "e94f");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("A series of men and women in macabre plague doctor masks move through the group, pulling away any hapless soul that shows signs of sickness, the wails and screams of fear and panic growing louder with each passing moment.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "ff32");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("A doctor leans in close to you and you tense in fear. His beady eyes peer at you with intense scrutiny as her pokes and prods at your flesh and squints closer at your eyes. Before long, he pushes you northward toward the gate and you breathe a sigh of relief as he turns his attention elsewhere.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "8e6c");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Cargo wagons laden with trembling bodies await outside the gate, the scared gazes of the passengers searching for any sense of solace in the chaos and confusion. You are gruffly directed toward the closest wagon and with a heave, you climb aboard to squeeze in close to the others.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "1709");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("A sinking feeling pulls at your gut as the wagon creaks into motion. With a glance backward, you see the city of Triskellian, smoke rising in wispy clouds of black in the distance. You wonder if you'll ever return to this place, the fear of the unknown gnawing at the pit of your stomach.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "e708");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("All around you, the haunted eyes of your fellow passengers seem to be doing the same and a gradual hush of silence falls over the wagon, interspersed only by the occasional, soft whimper from one of the younger passengers.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "87cc");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("The wagon creaks softly, swaying as the beasts of burden strain against their harnesses to pull the vehicle further away from the city.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "3b9f");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Time becomes an illusion with the monotonous swaying of the wagon, each bump in the road like a deja vu of motion.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "d67c");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You feel your body begin to droop, the adrenaline dissipating to leave you exhausted and dazed.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "7c45");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Your eyelids flicker shut and you somehow fall into a fitful sleep as the wagon plods onward.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "5854");

/* Have to mobilize the chatter before we can teleport them */
\$actor."base:immobile" = FALSE;

/* Spawn a unique dream room and get it set up */
\$dreamRoom = Spawn(\$\{Ironclaw:Dreams:Evacuation:room\});
Set(\$dreamRoom, "details:door:exit:closed", TRUE);
Set(\$\{Ironclaw:Dreams:Lib\}, Str(\$actor), \$dreamRoom);

/* This delay is necessary so the chatter does not witness the door closing */
\$delay(5, FALSE, "75e7");

/* Teleport chatter to room and place them on the bed */
Act(\$actor, "teleport", \$dest: \$dreamRoom);

/* Immobilize them again */
\$actor."base:immobile" = TRUE;

\$delay(5, FALSE, "7870");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You gasp with a start as the wagon creaks loudly, jostling over a particularly deep rut in the road. All around you it is dark; night has fallen over the plains.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "1a7f");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You scan the area but everywhere it is dark. Glancing upward, the night sky is crystal clear and filled with stars and for just a moment, all seems well and peaceful.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "6070");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You hear dull sounds of other wagons, distant both ahead and behind. Somewhere, a woman begins singing a soft lullaby, her voice sweet and almost cherub-like as it laces through the dark starlit night.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "7dc8");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You tilt your head, the words becoming clearer as you concentrate on the familiar tune, \\"Toora, loora, loora...toora, looralie, hush now my sweet baby, you don't need to cry.\\" With a smile, you recall the song and can't help but sway in time to the words.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "4c12");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("\\"Oft in dreams I wander...to that cot again...\\", the soft sweet voice of the woman cuts through the darkness, the melody punctuated almost perfectly by the gentle creaking and swaying of the wagons as they move ever northward through the dark and peaceful night.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "31a6");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You close your eyes, listening to the song as it fills the air with sweet notes, \\"I feel her arms hugging me...as when she held me then.\\" Memories flood your mind, sweet and nostalgic as the breeze gently caresses your cheek. ", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "c46a");

EmitTo(\$actor, "\\"And I hear her voice humming as in the days of yore...\\" Almost without thought, you feel a soft hum come to your throat, almost silent in its softness.");

\$delay(5, FALSE, "ad61");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You can faintly make out other voices, humming along in unison, \\"When she used to rock me fast asleep inside the bedroom door.\\" Before long, the night is filled with the sound of singing, more voices picking up the familiar song one after the other.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "aa7f");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("All around you is the sound of song, strangers and friends alike joining together to sing the words.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "2c4a");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("\\"Toora, loora, loora. Toora, looralie.\\"", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "4bab");

EmitTo(\$actor, "Peace falls over the land as the last wavering notes of the song drift into the darkness beyond, the stars overhead flickering as though they were dancing.");

\$delay(5, FALSE, "299e");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You exhale a soft sigh, turning your eyes to the sky overhead, memories flitting through your thoughts as you contemplate the twinkling stars up above.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "2f0a");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("\\"Everything is going to be alright...\\", you whisper to no one in particular, closing your eyes once more as sleep overcomes you.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "35e6");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("After awhile, birdsong rouses you from your slumber, the sun warm on your fur as it peeks over the horizon.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "78d3");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("The land around you is golden with the colors of autumn and in the distance, you can make out the walls of Three Corners, people coming and going through the front gate to head toward their harvest season duties.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "22d0");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("The wagon plods closer and closer, following the one ahead of it as you move toward the gates. People passing by wave and call out a welcome as they head to the fields and forests for the day.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "6efb");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("As the gates open, the wagons progress through, curious children peeking out from the group of people gathered around the side streets to see the newcomers in their large wagon caravan.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "87f8");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Moving through another gate, the wagon gradually pulls to a stop in the center of town, people parting to allow room for the road-weary travelers to disembark.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "2abe");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You grunt, your body stiff from sitting for so long and a kindly gentleman from town steps forward to help you from the wagon with a smile and a warm welcome.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "e0ed");

/* Mobilize them and send them back */
\$actor."base:immobile" = FALSE;
Act(\$actor, "teleport", \$dest: \$\{Allegory:Setting:ForteRicchezza:Squares:MainSquareSouth\});

\$delay(5, FALSE, "716f");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("You peer around the city, people moving here and there, going about their daily business without a care in the world and everything seems...all right.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "048a");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Gradually, the people from the wagons regain a sense of clarity and begin to disperse, exploring this new city and finding their bearings.", "imp"));

\$delay(5, FALSE, "efa1");

EmitTo(\$actor, TAG("Welcome to Three Corners!", "imp"));

return TRUE;
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1571105806, "jominey", "E", 1571106761, "jominey", "E", 1571106797, "jominey", "E", 1571107557, "ezralee", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="sys:emit:population"/>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
